<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:23:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Le &#171; Mal Aim&#233; &#187; d&#233;figur&#233; ? Intermarch&#233; fait marche arri&#232;re et ne proposera pas les photos par IA dans les photomatons</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2913123_le-mal-aime-defigure-intermarche-cede-finalement-a-lia-pour-surfer-sur-le-buzz</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2913123_le-mal-aime-defigure-intermarche-cede-finalement-a-lia-pour-surfer-sur-le-buzz</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s s'&#234;tre vu f&#233;liciter pour l'absence d'IA &#224; la cr&#233;ation de son spot de pub, Intermarch&#233; va utiliser l'IA.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This cute little Behringer synthesizer sounds massive and costs just $49</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/this-cute-little-behringer-synthesizer-sounds-massive-and-costs-just-49-191513007.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7cf7538-f43f-4182-aa84-60cdb675778f</guid>
      <description>Behringer is no stranger to remaking classic synthesizers and selling them at much cheaper price points. However, this latest release may just take the budget-friendly cake. The company just introduced the UB-1 Micro, previously called the Spirit, a portable analog synth inspired by the Oberheim Matrix line that costs just $49.
Despite the price tag, this thing still manages to sound extremely beefy. It features a pair of digitally controlled oscillators (DCOs) based on the Oberheim Matrix 6 analog chip. The monophonic/duophonic synth boasts two LFOs to control filters and tuning and an arpegg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best stocking stuffer ideas you can shop for $50 or less</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-best-stocking-stuffer-ideas-you-can-shop-for-50-or-less-130049822.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32df60b9-ebc7-4bd2-a9e6-0777477036d5</guid>
      <description>The big ticket tech gifts may get the lion's share of attention during the holidays, but it's surprising how much people appreciate small and thoughtful accessories and gadgets. We picked out a dozen such stocking stuffers for under $50 &#8212; perfect for a little something extra for a loved one or a welcome gift for a coworker. Just be sure to check the shipping windows to make sure these handy gizmos will arrive in time. Here are some of our favorite techie gift ideas that come in at $50 or less.
Best stocking stuffers for $50 or less


























Check out the rest of our gift ideas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Very Best Gifts for Dads of Christmas 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-very-best-gifts-for-dads-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6937095a008ae88504a14ec6</guid>
      <description>Dads are traditionally tough to shop for&#8212;let me help with these handpicked gift ideas for fathers with great taste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI toys are telling kids how to find knives, and senators are mad</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/846573/ai-toys-built-on-openais-chatgpt-inappropriate-content-senators-letter</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T14:03:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846573</guid>
      <description>Sexual fetish content. How to light a match. Where to find knives in the home. These are all conversation topics that recently-recalled children's toys - built atop AI chatbots like OpenAI's GPT-4o - are capable of bringing up to children. On Tuesday, U.S. senators Marsha Blackburn (R-Tenn.) and Richard Blumenthal (D-Conn.) sent a letter to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X &#8216;Bid Adieu&#8217; to the Twitter Brand, but Now It&#8217;s Suing to Keep It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/x-bid-adieu-to-the-twitter-brand-but-now-its-suing-to-keep-it-2000700860</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700860</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s company is suing a startup that wants to resurrect Twitter, claiming it never gave up the brand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nex Playground is a fine entry-level video game console for preschoolers, elderly individuals and anyone interested in light fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nex-playground-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zf4ZDJemhRyt3DgaLd9dRF</guid>
      <description>A motion control-only gadget that&#8217;s cheaper than the Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation 5, Xbox Series and PC yet almost manages to stand next to them uniquely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the stunning collapse of Believer Meats, the $600 million lab-grown meat startup</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462102/believer-meats-stunning-collapse-600-million-cooling-cultured-meat-industry</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462102/believer-meats-stunning-collapse-600-million-cooling-cultured-meat-industry</guid>
      <description>How Believer went from sizzle to fizzle in a matter of weeks, the latest blow to the once-promising alternative meat industry. 
Last month, Believer Meats was basking in acclaim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco says Chinese hackers are exploiting its customers with a new zero-day</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/cisco-says-chinese-hackers-are-exploiting-its-customers-with-a-new-zero-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076962</guid>
      <description>Cisco said it discovered a Chinese hacking campaign targeting its customers by exploiting a zero-day in some of the company's most popular products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars will exclusively air on YouTube starting in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/the-oscars-will-exclusively-air-on-youtube-starting-in-2029-181545531.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aadd9da4-bf4f-4282-81c6-149564519e84</guid>
      <description>The entertainment industry&#8217;s most well-known awards show is heading to streaming. The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences (AMPAS) has announced that the Academy Awards, popularly known as the Oscars, will exclusively air on YouTube starting in 2029. The new deal means the awards show is abandoning its long-time partnership with ABC (owned by frequent Oscars heavyweight, The Walt Disney Company), though the Oscars will continue to air on the network through its 100th anniversary in 2028.The Academy Awards will be joined by other Academy events and programming on the Oscars YouTube chann...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Didn&#8217;t Make My Old-Ass Smart Speaker Feel Any Less Dumb</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gemini-didnt-make-my-old-ass-smart-speaker-feel-any-less-dumb-2000700763</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700763</guid>
      <description>Gemini for Home has its perks, but I don't know that free users will feel the "next-gen" of it all compared with the old Google Assistant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans are fine with giving cash as holiday gifts, new poll finds</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462221/holiday-gifts-cash-poll-new-years-eve</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462221/holiday-gifts-cash-poll-new-years-eve</guid>
      <description>The poll found about two-thirds of Americans under 45 say cash is a &#8216;very&#8217; acceptable holiday gift.
Welcome to exhausted America 2025: Most adults are more than a little fine with&#160;doling out cash as gifts, and many plan to be asleep before midnight on New Year&#8217;s Eve, according to a new AP-NORC poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal user beware - experts warn subscriptions being abused to send fake purchase emails</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/paypal-user-beware-experts-warn-subscriptions-being-abused-to-send-fake-purchase-emails</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GAZGohYdmoNrqpo9fNae5X</guid>
      <description>A legitimate PayPal platform is being abused to bypass email protections and send phishing messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Loses the Oscars to the Home of MrBeast and &#8216;Hot Ones&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oscars-streaming-youtube-2029-2000700856</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700856</guid>
      <description>YouTube will stream the Super Bowl of the movies starting in 2029.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars will stream on YouTube in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846560/youtube-the-oscars-streaming-2029</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:30:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846560</guid>
      <description>The Oscars are headed to YouTube - in a few years. "Beginning in 2029, the Oscars will broadcast exclusively on YouTube for free globally and on YouTube TV in the U.S.," YouTube announced. YouTube's coverage will include the red carpet, behind the scenes content, and Governors Ball access. The deal runs through 2033, according to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 22 best gift ideas for the remote worker in your life</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-22-best-gift-ideas-for-the-remote-worker-in-your-life-140037336.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7354ab-106c-4b9a-ab03-3baa917ca395</guid>
      <description>For many folks, working from home is simply the new normal. If you&#8217;re looking to treat someone who spends most of their time in the home office, this holiday season is as good a time as any to make their daily routine a little more convenient. As a collection of remote workers ourselves, we at Engadget have rounded up a few gift ideas that should add a bit more delight to the WFH life.
Best gifts for remote workers












































Check out the rest of our gift ideas here. This article originally appeared on Engadget at https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is testing a link posting limit for professional accounts and pages</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/facebook-is-testing-a-link-posting-limit-for-professional-accounts-and-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076954</guid>
      <description>Meta said that the test impacts professional accounts and pages on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix vs. Paramount: What you need to know about the bidding war for Warner Bros.</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462217/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-bidding-war-explained</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T18:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462217/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-bidding-war-explained</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s what to know about the three players and what the bids mean for the entertainment industry.
Warner Bros.&#160;is telling shareholders of the company that it believes a&#160;$72 billion buyout offer from Netflix&#160;is superior, and to reject a hostile takeover bid from Paramount Skydance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Bets on Small Drones to Expand US Surveillance Reach</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/border-patrol-bets-on-small-drones-to-expand-us-surveillance-reach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6941a9ca898599d8134eb0d0</guid>
      <description>Federal records show CBP is moving from testing small drones to making them standard surveillance tools, expanding a network that can follow activity in real time and extend well beyond the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon appoints longtime AWS exec Peter DeSantis to lead new AI org</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/amazon-appoints-longtime-aws-exec-peter-desantis-to-lead-new-ai-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076946</guid>
      <description>DeSantis has spent 27 years at Amazon, including eight years as an SVP for AWS, the cloud provider that powers about one-third of the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 best last-minute Christmas gifts for 2025 that will arrive by December 24</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-12-best-last-minute-christmas-gifts-for-2025-that-will-arrive-by-december-24-140037753.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f10f3474-8a9f-4844-b943-494ef9bdc916</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re almost out of time &#8212; the holidays are just about here, and if you&#8217;re still doing your holiday shopping, you&#8217;re not alone. Between wrapping things up at work before some well-deserved time off and making sure you have everything you need to host family and friends, it can be hard to find the time to go shop for some gifts. And if you&#8217;re going to physical stores right now, you&#8217;re probably being met with half-empty shelves. But the internet remains an option, even this late in the game: you still have time to buy holiday gifts online.USPS, UPS and FedEx have laid out their holiday shipping ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximus is more important than ever in Fallout season 2</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/846429/fallout-season-2-maximus-aaron-moten-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:02:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846429</guid>
      <description>As we tuck into Fallout season 2, eager to see Amazon bring New Vegas to life, there's one person who stands out - and not just because of his power armor. Knight Maximus of the Brotherhood of Steel is the most important of Fallout's three main characters, and I'm glad the new season is finally [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla would have to rein in FSD under new Democratic bill</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846387/level-2-operational-design-domain-markey-bill</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846387</guid>
      <description>Tesla and other automakers working on Level 2 and higher driving systems would be required to restrict their vehicles to specific road types or clearly defined operational domains under a new bill introduced today by Massachusetts Senator Ed Markey (D). Operational design domains, or ODDs, are a set of conditions, either geographic or weather-related, in [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Newcastle vs Fulham for *FREE* &#8212; Stream Carabao Cup Quarter-Final 25/26</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/newcastle-vs-fulham-carabao-cup-quarter-final-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iSdXBDHrWR8RhUsajqMoHE</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on how to watch Newcastle vs Fulham for free in the Carabao Cup 2025/26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IO Interactive's 007 First Light reimagines James Bond as a young and reckless spy</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/io-interactives-007-first-light-reimagines-james-bond-as-a-young-and-reckless-spy-180000758.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57fdd544-194b-467d-8745-ffaad8cc4055</guid>
      <description>The creators of the Hitman series have honed their style of- open-ended and spectacle-driven sandboxes across several games, and now they're taking their signature immersive gameplay to the world of James Bond. With 007 First Light, developer IO Interactive is crafting an origin story for the globetrotting British spy, showing how he undertook daring missions at the start of his career to eventually become the world's most infamous agent.Before the reveal at The Game Awards of 007 First Light's newest villain, played by Lenny Kravitz, we had an early look at the latest bits of plot for James B...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV makers take screenshots of what we watch, says Texas AG</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/texas-ag-samsung-tcl-hisense-tv-screenshot-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04U7u6EkdFOeaahpXzhrsTc</guid>
      <description>The Texas attorney general is suing various TV manufacturers for allegedly monitoring what users watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette manette transforme votre smartphone en GameBoy</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/manette-de-jeu/2914269_cette-manette-transforme-votre-smartphone-en-gameboy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/manette-de-jeu/2914269_cette-manette-transforme-votre-smartphone-en-gameboy</guid>
      <description>
GameSir s&#8217;appr&#234;te &#224; lancer la Pocket 1, une manette au format vertical in&#233;dit qui promet de m&#233;tamorphoser votre smartphone en console r&#233;tro, le tout &#224; un prix particuli&#232;rement agressif.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argos launches a final pre-Christmas sale &#8212; save up to 50% on tech, appliances, toys, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/argos-launches-a-final-pre-christmas-sale-save-up-to-50-percent-on-tech-appliances-toys-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95bvFLpiznVjQ3qrqYEFNF</guid>
      <description>Argos has launched one last sale before Christmas, featuring savings of up to 50% across tech, appliances, furniture, toys, and more &#8211; I've rounded up the 11 best deals right here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CMF Watch 3 Pro &#8212;&#160;one of the best smartwatches of 2025 &#8212;&#160;just hit a new record-low price</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-17-nothing-cmf-watch-3-pro-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">007ZDCxV7WAc6LscfHWOAwD</guid>
      <description>The CMF Watch 3 Pro by Nothing is down to $78.90 at Amazon, marking a new best price ever at 20% off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires want data centers everywhere, including space</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/845453/space-data-centers-astronomers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:48:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845453</guid>
      <description>Tech billionaires have been obsessed with space for a long time. Now, as the largest AI companies race to build more data centers in a frenzied pursuit of profitability, space is looking less like a pet project and more like a commercial opportunity. In 2025 alone, six proposals for giant AI data centers needing multiple [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Gerard Butler vs. the Post-Apocalypse in the Fiery New &#8216;Greenland 2: Migration&#8217; Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/its-gerard-butler-vs-the-post-apocalypse-in-the-fiery-new-greenland-2-migration-trailer-2000700813</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700813</guid>
      <description>He and his family survived the comet&#8212;but what comes next? Find out in the sequel hitting theaters in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The age of satellite TV is ending &#8212; Sky Q is finished, and Sky Stream is the future</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-age-of-satellite-tv-is-ending-sky-q-is-finished-and-sky-stream-is-the-future</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SSF6gM2v8v7gG4nuP3WbSR</guid>
      <description>Hey satellite man, your time has come: Sky Q is now 'unplugged' from new orders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN is debuting a new data-filled Monday Night Football stream next week</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846478/espn-monday-night-football-playbook-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:35:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846478</guid>
      <description>A new Monday Night Football broadcast will offer an alternate telecast that presents the game live from the All-22 camera angle that shows the entire field, coupled with on-screen analytics and commentary. It's called MNF Playbook with Next Gen Stats, and it premieres next week. To develop the show, ESPN partnered with sports data analytics [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Votre smartphone devient une cl&#233; avec cette serrure connect&#233;e &#224; moiti&#233; prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913669_votre-smartphone-devient-une-cle-avec-cette-serrure-connectee-a-moitie-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913669_votre-smartphone-devient-une-cle-avec-cette-serrure-connectee-a-moitie-prix</guid>
      <description>
Si vous avez l'habitude d'oublier ou d'&#233;garer vos cl&#233;s, voici une serrure connect&#233;e qui devrait r&#233;soudre ce probl&#232;me puisqu'elle transforme votre smartphone en cl&#233;. D&#233;couvrez-la chez PC Componentes pour 64,99 euros au lieu de 139 euros habituellement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VID&#201;O &#8211; Voici les meilleurs produits tech de l&#8217;ann&#233;e : Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/video-podcast/2911809_video-voici-les-meilleurs-produits-tech-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/video-podcast/2911809_video-voici-les-meilleurs-produits-tech-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
D&#233;couvrez notre vid&#233;o &#233;v&#233;nement sp&#233;cialement d&#233;di&#233;e aux Frandroid Awards 2025 avec Delos. Un v&#233;ritable court-m&#233;trage pour vous informer et vous faire rire.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is exploiting US-funded research on nuclear technology</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461998/china-exploiting-us-funded-research-nuclear-tech-congressional-report</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T17:30:45</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461998/china-exploiting-us-funded-research-nuclear-tech-congressional-report</guid>
      <description>Investigators found that federal funds went to research collaborations with Chinese state-owned laboratories and universities that work directly for China&#8217;s military.
China is exploiting partnerships with U.S. researchers funded by the Department of Energy to provide the Chinese military with access to sensitive nuclear technology and other innovations with economic and national security applications, according to a congressional report published Wednesday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rad Power Bikes files for bankruptcy and is looking to sell the business</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/rad-power-bikes-files-for-bankruptcy-and-is-looking-to-sell-the-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076928</guid>
      <description>It's the latest e-bike company to seek bankruptcy protection after pandemic-era excitement for the category wore off.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
