<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:56:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ring says its leaked plan to 'zero out crime in neighborhoods' doesn't mean mass surveillance</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/home-security/ring-says-its-leaked-plan-to-zero-out-crime-in-neighborhoods-doesnt-mean-mass-surveillance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QvKNEW8Rxn3mXzqYEAbGGo</guid>
      <description>Ring cameras could be used to track a lot more than lost dogs, a leaked email suggests. But the company has hit back at claims that it means mass surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audi dote sa nouvelle RS 5 hybride d&#8217;une technologie &#233;lectrique in&#233;dite pour en faire la reine de la glisse</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/audi/2983505_audi-rs-5-la-sportive-hybride-de-639-ch-qui-se-rapproche-le-plus-dune-voiture-electrique</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/audi/2983505_audi-rs-5-la-sportive-hybride-de-639-ch-qui-se-rapproche-le-plus-dune-voiture-electrique</guid>
      <description>
Avec son moteur V6 2,9 litres bi-turbo de 639 ch coupl&#233; &#224; un moteur &#233;lectrique, la nouvelle Audi RS 5 s'attaque &#224; un exercice p&#233;rilleux : celui de l'hybridation d'un monument de l'auto sportive. Un pari techniquement s&#233;duisant, d'autant plus que la voiture se dote d'une technologie d&#233;j&#224; vue sur plusieurs mod&#232;les &#233;lectriques un tantinet sportifs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV&#8217;s The Hunt finally has a premiere date</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881386/apple-tv-the-hunt-premiere-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T12:40:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881386</guid>
      <description>The Hunt - Apple TV's new French-language drama that was previously put on indefinite hold following concerns about plagiarism - has been given a solid release date. Today, Apple announced that The Hunt, which was produced by French studio Gaumont and directed by C&#233;dric Anger, is set to premiere on March 4th. The news comes [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is bringing the Gemini-powered 'Ask' button to TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/youtube-is-bringing-the-gemini-powered-ask-button-to-tvs-173900295.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56979402-33d4-4177-9cd8-04fe96c5f50e</guid>
      <description>YouTube's "Ask" button is making its way to the living room. The Gemini-powered feature is now rolling out as an experiment on smart TVs, gaming consoles and streaming devices. 9to5Google first spotted a Google support page announcing the change.Like on mobile devices and desktop, the feature is essentially a Gemini chatbot trained on each video's content. Selecting that "Ask" button will bring up a series of canned prompts related to the content. Alternatively, you can use your microphone to ask questions about it in your own words.The "Ask about this video" feature on desktopYouTubeGoogle sa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdGuard's Windows VPN upgrade prioritizes usability for all</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/adguards-windows-vpn-upgrade-prioritizes-usability-for-all</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hDS4hyYbiiicSdcs3jfwkC</guid>
      <description>New AdGuard VPN update makes Windows app screen reader-friendly. Here's all you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avowed's first anniversary update arrives on PS5 today, but there are no major PS5 Pro enhancements to look forward to</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/avoweds-first-anniversary-update-arrives-on-ps5-today-but-there-are-no-major-ps5-pro-enhancements-to-look-forward-to</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eJ6C5bjtFW3vT5BDjEfuXA</guid>
      <description>Obsidian Entertainment has released the Anniversary Update for Avowed to celebrate the game's first birthday, along with the long-awaited PlayStation 5 edition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour &#171;&#160;sauver&#160;&#187; les Europ&#233;ens de la &#171;&#160;censure&#160;&#187; de Bruxelles, l&#8217;administration Trump d&#233;velopperait un portail VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/pour-sauver-les-europeens-de-la-censure-de-bruxelles-ladministration-trump-developperait-un-portail-vpn.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1326859</guid>
      <description>L'administration Trump, pour contrer &#171; la censure en Europe &#187;, serait en train de d&#233;velopper un portail en ligne agissant comme un VPN. L'objectif : permettre aux citoyens du Vieux continent et &#224; d'autres d'acc&#233;der aux contenus illicites ou pr&#233;judiciables proscrits par la r&#232;glementation europ&#233;enne sur le Num&#233;rique, ou d'autres lois locales. L'information n'a pas &#233;t&#233; confirm&#233;e officiellement....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google launches Gemini 3.1 Pro, retaking AI crown with 2X+ reasoning performance boost</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/google-launches-gemini-3-1-pro-retaking-ai-crown-with-2x-reasoning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4QDqJisUgJMszQWEBqu07x</guid>
      <description>Late last year, Google briefly took the crown for most powerful AI model in the world with the launch of Gemini 3 Pro &#8212; only to be surpassed within weeks by OpenAI and Anthropic releasing new models,  s is common in the fiercely competitive AI race.Now Google is back to retake the throne with an updated version of that flagship model: Gemini 3.1 Pro, positioned as a smarter baseline for tasks where a simple response is insufficient&#8212;targeting science, research, and engineering workflows that demand deep planning and synthesis.Already, evaluations by third-party firm Artificial Analysis show tha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian rolls out an Apple Watch app with vehicle controls and digital key support</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/rivian-rolls-out-an-apple-watch-app-with-vehicle-controls-and-digital-key-support-172642545.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1aa0317-4276-4c77-a09e-97b0b9453832</guid>
      <description>Rivian suggests that vehicle owners can leave their phone at home (or perhaps in a glove box) and instead control some aspects of their EV using a new Apple Watch app. With a tap of your watch, you can unlock and lock the doors, sound the alarm and vent the windows. After the digital key is set up, R1S and R1T Gen 2 owners can unlock their vehicle automatically simply by walking up to it thanks to the passive car key feature.It's possible to set the cabin temperature and a target state of charge by turning the digital crown on an Apple Watch. You also can choose four quick controls to put fron...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This high-performance creators laptop is the deal of 2026 so far &#8212; the Alienware 16 Aurora with Intel Core 7 240H and Nvidia GeForce RTX 5060 graphics is $300 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-high-performance-creators-laptop-is-the-deal-of-2026-so-far-the-alienware-16-aurora-with-intel-core-7-240h-and-nvidia-geforce-rtx-5060-graphics-is-usd300-off-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SnHPA5bG8357P3wK7Z6rGi</guid>
      <description>Powerful Alienware 16 Aurora creators laptop with RTX 5060 and 16GB DDR5 RAM gets huge $300 discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RAM crisis is completely warping my usual PC-building advice, so here's a fresh priority list for anyone looking to build or upgrade a PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/computing-components/the-ram-crisis-is-completely-warping-my-usual-pc-building-advice-so-heres-a-fresh-priority-list-for-anyone-looking-to-build-or-upgrade-a-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gzAVMxP8KgbhnKffjVkHVN</guid>
      <description>I used to recommend RAM and SSDs as a wallet-friendly PC upgrade, but the RAM crisis has left that advice dead in the water &#8212; here's what to do instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteelSeries Arctis Nova Pro Wireless : on n&#8217;a jamais vu un prix aussi bas pour ce casque gaming haut de gamme de qualit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982825_steelseries-arctis-nova-pro-wireless-on-na-jamais-vu-un-prix-aussi-bas-pour-ce-casque-gaming-haut-de-gamme-de-qualite</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982825_steelseries-arctis-nova-pro-wireless-on-na-jamais-vu-un-prix-aussi-bas-pour-ce-casque-gaming-haut-de-gamme-de-qualite</guid>
      <description>
Faker, Rain ou encore James Baldwin jouent avec le SteelSeries Arctis Nova Pro Wireless, un casque gaming multiplateforme que vous retrouvez pour 219,99 euros sur Amazon au lieu de 379,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Redmi Buds 8 Active seront-ils des concurrents s&#233;rieux aux mod&#232;les d&#8217;entr&#233;e de gamme&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2983733_les-redmi-buds-8-active-seront-ils-des-concurrents-serieux-aux-modeles-dentree-de-gamme</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2983733_les-redmi-buds-8-active-seront-ils-des-concurrents-serieux-aux-modeles-dentree-de-gamme</guid>
      <description>
Xiaomi s'appr&#234;te &#224; commercialiser les Redmi Buds 8 Active, une nouvelle paire d'&#233;couteurs sans fil positionn&#233;e sous le mod&#232;le Lite lanc&#233; en janvier 2026. Une fuite r&#233;v&#232;le l'ensemble des caract&#233;ristiques techniques, le design et le prix de ces &#233;couteurs qui adoptent un format ouvert semi-intra-auriculaire.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Toy Story 5&#8217; Trailer Reminds Us Tech Is a 4-Letter Word</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/toy-story-5-new-trailer-super-bowl-2000716852</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716852</guid>
      <description>Andrew Stanton wrote and directed the latest in Pixar's much-loved animated franchise, starring the voices of Tom Hanks, Tim Allen, Joan Cusack, and series newcomer Greta Lee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT Scans Reveal Gruesome Details of Inca Child Sacrifices</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ct-scans-reveal-gruesome-details-of-inca-child-sacrifices-2000723968</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723968</guid>
      <description>New research investigates the centuries-old remains of sacrificial victims recovered from volcanoes in Peru.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers claim breach of Adidas systems - but it says a third-party is the real victim</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-claim-breach-of-adidas-systems-but-it-says-a-third-party-is-the-real-victim</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tbF59CLLvzfmA5LxUsaGxF</guid>
      <description>Was Adidas hacked? Or was it a third-party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to dial in your coffee grinder? Baratza's new stepless Encore ESP Pro could be exactly what you need</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/struggling-to-dial-in-your-coffee-grinder-baratzas-new-stepless-encore-esp-pro-could-be-exactly-what-you-need</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bxHb7hNGjueqq3W8BQ3fTi</guid>
      <description>Dialing in your grinder just got easier, whichever brewing style you prefer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube teste un bouton Gemini pour &#171;&#160;discuter&#160;&#187; avec les vid&#233;os</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/youtube-teste-un-bouton-gemini-pour-discuter-avec-les-videos.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1326954</guid>
      <description>YouTube veut faire la causette. La plateforme teste actuellement un bouton Gemini qui permet au spectateur de poser des questions sur le contenu d'une vid&#233;o. Reste &#224; savoir s'il s'agit d'une bonne id&#233;e ou pas&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia sues Apple for allegedly letting child abuse spread in iCloud</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881433/apple-west-virginia-lawsuit-icloud-csam</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T12:02:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881433</guid>
      <description>West Virginia has filed a lawsuit against Apple, accusing the company of allowing the distribution and storage of child sexual abuse material (CSAM) in iCloud. In a lawsuit filed on Thursday, West Virginia Attorney General JB McCuskey claims that by abandoning a CSAM detection system in favor of end-to-end encryption, iCloud has become a "secure [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is shutting down Messenger&#8217;s standalone website</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/meta-is-shutting-down-messengers-standalone-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094426</guid>
      <description>The move comes a few months after Meta shut down Messenger&#8217;s stand-alone desktop apps for Windows and Mac.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Gives Its Kids (and Itself) the Grace to Find Their Own Path</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-episode-7-recap-genesis-darem-2000723708</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723708</guid>
      <description>'Ko'Zeine' puts the spotlight on the overachievers of its cadet cast, and in doing so, takes the opportunity to relieve itself from the weight of its own expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Opens a Billion-Dollar Tab With Palantir</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/department-homeland-security-ice-billion-dollar-agreement-palantir/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699712c289eae8e26970c3e6</guid>
      <description>"If you are interested in helping shape and deliver the next chapter of Palantir&#8217;s work across DHS, please reach out,&#8221; a Palantir executive wrote to employees about the massive purchasing agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orbital AI data centers could work, but they might ruin Earth in the process</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/orbital-ai-data-centers-could-work-but-they-might-ruin-earth-in-the-process-170000099.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be369cf6-5cd7-455d-98e2-649734bde3b1</guid>
      <description>At the start of the month, Elon Musk announced that two of his companies &#8212; SpaceX and xAI&#160; &#8212; were merging, and would jointly launch a constellation of 1 million satellites to operate as orbital data centers. Musk's reputation might suggest otherwise, but according to experts, such a plan isn't a complete fantasy. However, if executed at the scale suggested, some of them believe it would have devastating effects on the environment and the sustainability of low Earth Earth orbit.&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Musk and others argue that putting data centers in space is practical given how much more efficient solar panels ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego&#8217;s new Monet-inspired set is full of hidden details</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91493787/legos-new-monet-inspired-set-is-full-of-hidden-details</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91493787/legos-new-monet-inspired-set-is-full-of-hidden-details</guid>
      <description>Lego&#8217;s designers took a lesson in impressionism to create this wall-worthy set.
From afar, Lego&#8217;s new set inspired by Claude Monet&#8217;s painting Bridge over a Pond of Water Lilies looks like a slightly more vivid version of the original. Step a bit closer, though, and you&#8217;ll find that its intricate brushstrokes are composed of Lego bananas, katana swords, and carrot tops....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI&#8217;s biggest problem isn&#8217;t intelligence. It&#8217;s implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495084/ais-biggest-problem-isnt-intelligence-its-implementation</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495084/ais-biggest-problem-isnt-intelligence-its-implementation</guid>
      <description>Culture, workflows, and human habits may set the real pace of the AI economy.
Welcome to&#160;AI&#160;Decoded,&#160;Fast Company&#8217;s weekly newsletter that breaks down the most important news in the world of&#160;AI.&#160;You can sign&#160;up to receive this newsletter every week via email&#160;here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a proposed tax on California billionaires is dividing Democrats ahead of the midterms</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495290/how-proposed-tax-california-billionaires-dividing-democrats-ahead-midterms</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T16:58:41</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495290/how-proposed-tax-california-billionaires-dividing-democrats-ahead-midterms</guid>
      <description>The contentious proposal has turned Sen. Bernie Sanders and Gov. Gavin Newsom into adversaries at time when the party can least afford it.
As national Democrats search for a unifying theme ahead of the fall&#8217;s midterm elections, a California proposal to levy a hefty tax on billionaires is turning some of the party&#8217;s leading figures into adversaries just when Democrats can least afford division from within.Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders traveled to Los Angeles on Wednesday to campaign for the tax proposal, which has Silicon Valley in an uproar, with tech titans threatening to leave the state. Democ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Is Working on a Site to Help Europeans Bypass Content Bans on Hate Speech: Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-us-is-working-on-a-site-to-help-europeans-bypass-content-bans-on-hate-speech-report-2000724058</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724058</guid>
      <description>The online portal is set be hosted at Freedom.gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beat the RAM crunch with this Ryzen 7 9850X3D combo including 32GB DDR5-6400 RAM and motherboard &#8212; save $409 and get a free game too</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/beat-the-ram-crunch-with-this-ryzen-7-9850x3d-combo-including-32gb-ddr5-6400-ram-and-motherboard-save-usd409-and-get-a-free-game-too</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3kWdZafjatv5a8vT5BxaEn</guid>
      <description>Save $409 on this Ryzen 7 9850X3D processor, MSI X870 motherboard, and 32GB DDR5 combo right now, while stocks last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York drops plan to legalize robotaxis in setback for Waymo</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/881354/new-york-drops-plan-to-legalize-robotaxis-waymo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T11:53:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881354</guid>
      <description>New York Governor Kathy Hochul (D) dropped her proposal to allow robotaxi companies to launch commercially in cities other than New York City, citing a lack of support among state legislators, Bloomberg reports today. The move is a blow to Waymo and other robotaxi companies who saw New York, and especially New York City, as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York hits the brakes on robotaxi expansion plan</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/new-york-hits-the-brakes-on-robotaxi-expansion-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092214</guid>
      <description>The governor of New York pulled a robotaxi expansion proposal that was viewed as a win for Waymo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've used Squarespace for over a decade and with their custom domains you're guaranteed to stand out online</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-building/ive-used-squarespace-for-over-a-decade-and-with-their-custom-domains-youre-guaranteed-to-stand-out-online</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xN8eFrYNUznEhBMctQdjFV</guid>
      <description>Every dream needs a domain &#8211; get started and stand out online with a custom domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I found the perfect budget office chair for ergonomics - the FlexiSpot ErgoX has dynamic lumbar support that adjusts with your posture</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/i-found-the-perfect-budget-office-chair-for-ergonomics-the-flexispot-ergox-has-dynamic-lumbar-support-that-adjusts-with-your-posture</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2C3Datm4V8j88zZ2rFuHDM</guid>
      <description>FlexiSpot&#8217;s ErgoX has the key features I look for in an ergonomic chair, including dynamic lumbar support that adjusts with you during long hours at the desk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le d&#233;clin d&#8217;Ubisoft continue : l&#8217;&#233;diteur annonce 40 licenciements de plus</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2983609_le-declin-dubisoft-continue-lediteur-annonce-40-licenciements-de-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2983609_le-declin-dubisoft-continue-lediteur-annonce-40-licenciements-de-plus</guid>
      <description>
Ubisoft continue l'&#171; ajustement &#187; de ses effectifs en annon&#231;ant 40 licenciements chez Ubisoft Toronto.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God of War actor Christopher Judge seems to tease Santa Monica Studio's next project &#8212; 'You&#8217;ll be hearing about what we&#8217;re doing probably in late summer'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/god-of-war-actor-christopher-judge-seems-to-tease-santa-monica-studios-next-project-youll-be-hearing-about-what-were-doing-probably-in-late-summer</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oSmTzZMGiqJQruY8RX8fKe</guid>
      <description>God of War actor Christopher Judge has seemingly teased Santa Monica Studio's next major project, which he suggests will be revealed this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia is suing Apple alleging negligence over CSAM materials</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/west-virginia-is-suing-apple-alleging-negligence-over-csam-materials-164647648.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b402186d-4b90-43e8-9619-6fc9fab45910</guid>
      <description>The office of the Attorney General for West Virginia announced Thursday that it has filed a lawsuit against Apple alleging that the company had "knowingly" allowed its iCloud platform "to be used as a vehicle for distributing and storing child sexual abuse material." The state alleges this went on for years but drew no action from the tech giant "under the guise of user privacy."
In the lawsuit, the state repeatedly cites a text from Apple executive Eric Friedman, in which he calls iCloud "the greatest platform for distributing child porn" in a conversation with another Apple executive. These ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming deal alert: The BritBox Prime Video add-on is 25% off for your first year</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-19-britbox-prime-video-streaming-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02AUzmyGk4NifYbOoeRBJoG</guid>
      <description>Save 25% on your first year of streaming on BritBox through the Prime Video add-on subscription after a seven-day trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turtle Beach&#8217;s new PC controller with swiveling sticks is 30 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/881030/turtle-beach-stealth-pivot-controller-lego-mario-yoshi-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T11:42:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881030</guid>
      <description>Many modern gamepads have adopted a modular design in recent years, from the Victrix Pro BFG Reloaded to Hyperkin&#8217;s clamp-on X5 Alteron for the Nintendo Switch. However, few of them are quite as innovative as last year&#8217;s Turtle Beach Stealth Pivot, which is now on sale at Amazon and Best Buy for an all-time low [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg grilled in court over social media harms on teens</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/zuckerberg-grilled-in-court-over-social-media-harms-on-teens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094430</guid>
      <description>Meta's CEO was questioned over the addictive nature of its social media apps like Instagram, and other teen harms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House of the Dragon Season 3 teaser gives fiery glimpse of the Battle of the Gullet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/house-of-the-dragon-season-3-teaser</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01BhQ34lwlEMRd4NnvJSjKf</guid>
      <description>"House of the Dragon" Season 3 premieres in June. Watch the teaser trailer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Amazon Fire TV is about to get a free upgrade to make it faster and easier to use &#8212; here's what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/your-amazon-fire-tv-is-about-to-get-a-free-upgrade-to-make-it-faster-and-easier-to-use-heres-what-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zxz469PtGsnZQjsYgaLo8j</guid>
      <description>Amazon's Fire TV update is rolling out to select models in the US first, and will be available more widely and in other countries soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift the most important family member the Petlibro Automatic Pet Feeder while its on sale for under $70</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-19-petlibro-automatic-feeder-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02Q3fIwjhSB9WT6TxWu32b3</guid>
      <description>The Petlibro Automatic Pet Feeder (5 liter) is on sale at Amazon for $69.99, down from the list price of $99.99. That's a 30% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy&#8217;s Iconic Lovers&#8217; Arch Collapsed&#8212;Of All Days&#8212;On Valentine&#8217;s Day</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/italys-iconic-lovers-arch-collapsed-ironically-on-valentines-day-2000724033</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724033</guid>
      <description>The beloved attraction fell victim to a recent surge in destructive storms that have ravaged southern Italy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next iTunes may be vibe-coded</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/881256/parachord-vibe-coded-music-streaming-app</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T11:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881256</guid>
      <description>This is Lowpass by Janko Roettgers, a newsletter on the ever-evolving intersection of tech and entertainment, syndicated just for The Verge subscribers once a week. Wouldn't it be great if you could exchange music recommendations with your friends, no matter whether they use Spotify, Apple Music, or Bandcamp? What if you could follow DJs and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftBank to spend an eye-popping $33B to build huge U.S. gas power plant</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/softbank-to-spend-an-eye-popping-33b-to-build-huge-u-s-gas-power-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094431</guid>
      <description>If completed, the project would be among the largest and most expensive natural gas power plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachat de SFR : pourquoi Orange, Free et Bouygues sont lanc&#233;s dans une course contre-la-montre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2983513_rachat-de-sfr-pourquoi-orange-free-et-bouygues-sont-lances-dans-une-course-contre-la-montre</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2983513_rachat-de-sfr-pourquoi-orange-free-et-bouygues-sont-lances-dans-une-course-contre-la-montre</guid>
      <description>
Les op&#233;rateurs fran&#231;ais veulent acc&#233;l&#233;rer le projet de rachat de SFR. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour trouver un SSD externe de 2 To &#224; bon prix, direction la Fnac avec sa promotion sur le Lexar SL300</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982461_pour-trouver-un-ssd-externe-de-2-to-a-bon-prix-direction-la-fnac-avec-sa-promotion-sur-le-lexar-sl300</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982461_pour-trouver-un-ssd-externe-de-2-to-a-bon-prix-direction-la-fnac-avec-sa-promotion-sur-le-lexar-sl300</guid>
      <description>
Le Lexar SL300 est un SSD externe l&#233;ger, mais qui peut stocker jusqu'&#224; 2 To de donn&#233;es. Du c&#244;t&#233; de la Fnac, il est actuellement en promotion &#224; 159,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the 8 editor-approved laptops I'd buy this week from $199</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/these-are-the-8-editor-approved-laptops-id-buy-this-week-from-usd199</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UFoQzPJanTkzrXWPHwSxM9</guid>
      <description>I've looked through the top retailers and manufacturers and picked out the eight best laptop deals available this week, with prices starting at $199.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Sky TV price hike is on the way ahead of new HBO Max package being added &#8212; here&#8217;s what&#8217;s changing, and what to do if you&#8217;re affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/sky-tv/another-sky-tv-price-hike-is-on-the-way-ahead-of-new-hbo-max-package-being-added-heres-whats-changing-and-what-to-do-if-youre-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TtYDRahAej4t3oXc8Dkp8R</guid>
      <description>Sky TV packages are getting another price increase on April 1, just in time for the arrival of HBO Max.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo&#8217;s Adorable Wooden Amiibos Will Hook Kids on Mario Even Earlier</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nintendos-adorable-wooden-amiibos-will-hook-kids-on-mario-even-earlier-2000723999</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723999</guid>
      <description>Nintendo has a slew of new early childhood toys, plus an app that harkens back to the N64.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sues TP-Link over suspected China links and concern for security vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/texas-sues-tp-link-over-suspected-china-links-and-concern-for-security-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zGv7ernNoifohU3PeNAbuU</guid>
      <description>"Let this server as a clear warning to any Chinese entity seeking to compromise our nation's security," Texas Attorney General Paxton writes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE made a smaller version of its nugget ice maker that needs less counter space</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881365/ge-profile-opal-mini-nugget-ice-maker-pro-chewable-appliance</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T11:12:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881365</guid>
      <description>GE has announced two new versions of its popular Opal nugget ice machines with smaller footprints that take up less counter space, and more affordable price tags. Like GE's larger and pricier Opal 2.0 Ultra, the two new machines make nugget ice - frequently also referred to as chewable ice, or pellet ice - by [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frida built its brand on dirty jokes for parents. Now the internet isn&#8217;t laughing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495133/frida-built-its-brand-on-dirty-jokes-for-parents-now-the-internet-isnt-laughing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T16:11:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495133/frida-built-its-brand-on-dirty-jokes-for-parents-now-the-internet-isnt-laughing</guid>
      <description>Screenshots of the baby care company&#8217;s edgy innuendos have racked up millions of views and even sparked boycott calls.
Baby care brand Frida is facing online backlash after screenshots of sexual innuendos in its marketing materials began circulating on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elder Scrolls 6 isn't going to be like Starfield says Todd Howard, and will instead be in the studio's 'classic style'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-elder-scrolls-6-isnt-going-to-be-like-starfield-says-todd-howard-and-will-instead-be-in-the-studios-classic-style</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MZb2CWygxtm9BXsTTETgf7</guid>
      <description>Todd Howard has suggested that The Elder Scrolls 6 will be more like the studio's past games than the likes of Starfield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastodon is testing easier ways to get you started in the fediverse</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881352/mastodon-default-server-recommendations-experiment</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T11:03:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881352</guid>
      <description>New users on the decentralized social network Mastodon could soon have an easier time getting started. Mastodon is running "onboarding experiments" to test ways to improve the new user experience, starting with default server recommendations. Now when new users join Mastodon from the mobile app, they may see a button to "join" a recommended server [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Ces t&#226;ches seront automatis&#233;es par une IA&#160;&#187; : Microsoft annonce la fin de ces m&#233;tiers d&#8217;ici 18 mois</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/ces-taches-seront-automatisees-par-une-ia-microsoft-annonce-la-fin-de-ces-metiers-dici-18-mois.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1326891</guid>
      <description>Pour le patron de l'IA de Microsoft, Mustafa Suleyman, les performances de l'IA seront &#233;quivalentes &#224; celles des humains dans la plupart des t&#226;ches professionnelles d'ici 18 mois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le miracle de P&#233;kin : la m&#233;thode stricte qui a d&#233;pollu&#233; l&#8217;air chinois en seulement 10 ans</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/2983233_le-miracle-de-pekin-la-methode-stricte-qui-a-depollue-lair-chinois-en-seulement-10-ans</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/2983233_le-miracle-de-pekin-la-methode-stricte-qui-a-depollue-lair-chinois-en-seulement-10-ans</guid>
      <description>
Les centrales fossiles chinoises n&#8217;affectent pas seulement le climat, elles p&#232;sent aussi lourdement sur la qualit&#233; de l&#8217;air. Si la bataille contre le r&#233;chauffement climatique est encore loin d&#8217;&#234;tre gagn&#233;e, la Chine a en revanche d&#233;j&#224; obtenu des r&#233;sultats spectaculaires concernant la pollution atmosph&#233;rique. Voici comment.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study Confirms: Reentering SpaceX Rockets Are Peppering the Upper Atmosphere With Metal Pollution</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/study-confirms-reentering-spacex-rockets-are-peppering-the-upper-atmosphere-with-metal-pollution-2000723932</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723932</guid>
      <description>For the first time, scientists were able to directly detect upper-atmospheric pollution from space debris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;House of the Dragon&#8217; Teases an Absolutely Scorching Season 3</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/house-of-the-dragon-season-3-trailer-release-date-2000723480</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723480</guid>
      <description>HBO returns to Westeros this June with a new installment in the war-torn 'Game of Thrones' prequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hull KR vs Brisbane Broncos Free Streams: How to watch World Club Challenge 2026 online, TV Channels, Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/rugby/hull-kr-vs-brisbane-broncos-world-club-challenge-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Pi4aM3AeZmh4HUeV4hQViJ</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Hull KR vs Brisbane Broncos live streams online &#8211; including for FREE &#8211; in the 2026 World Club Challenge at MKM Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Canada vs. USA in the womens ice hockey final online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/usa-canada-womens-ice-hockey-final-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00Bb1EEERDZLBYrF6uREdsB</guid>
      <description>How to watch ice hockey for free. Live stream Canada vs. USA in the women's ice hockey final for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
