<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:36:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>US Declassifies Vintage Spy Satellite With a Wildly Lopsided Orbit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/us-declassifies-vintage-spy-satellite-with-a-wildly-lopsided-orbit-2000715963</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715963</guid>
      <description>JUMPSEAT launched from 1971 to 1987 to collect intelligence during the Cold War-era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arcee's U.S.-made, open source Trinity Large and 10T-checkpoint offer rare look at raw model intelligence</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/arcees-u-s-made-open-source-trinity-large-and-10t-checkpoint-offer-rare-look</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7KTjcOjJ7ASiuycmk85tDD</guid>
      <description>San Francisco-based AI lab Arcee made waves last year for being one of the only U.S. companies to train large language models (LLMs) from scratch and release them under open or partially open source licenses to the public&#8212;enabling developers, solo entrepreneurs, and even medium-to-large enterprises to use the powerful AI models for free and customize them at will.Now Arcee is back again this week with the release of its largest, most performant open language model to date: Trinity Large, a 400-billion parameter mixture-of-experts (MoE), available now in preview,Alongside the flagship release, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s a social network for AI agents, and it&#8217;s getting weird</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/871006/social-network-facebook-for-ai-agents-moltbook-moltbot-openclaw</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T14:11:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=871006</guid>
      <description>Yes, you read that right. "Moltbook" is a social network of sorts for AI agents, particularly ones offered by OpenClaw (a viral AI assistant project that was formerly known as Moltbot, and before that, known as Clawdbot - until a legal dispute with Anthropic). Moltbook, which is set up similarly to Reddit and was built [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $110 standing desk deal from our favorite maker fixes the biggest design flaw found on almost every other budget model</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-usd110-standing-desk-deal-from-our-favorite-maker-fixes-the-biggest-design-flaw-found-on-almost-every-other-budget-model</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4R7umMphKqs2mfYmPPCkQm</guid>
      <description>FlexiSpot&#8217;s EN1 standing desk features a sturdy one-piece 48&#215;24-inch desktop with smooth electric height adjustment, and it&#8217;s just received a $60 price cut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We finally heard from Trump Mobile&#8230; and they immediately ghosted us</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/870934/trump-mobile-executive-team-don-hendrickson</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T14:06:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870934</guid>
      <description>Where's the Trump phone? We're going to keep talking about it every week. We've reached out, as usual, to ask about the Trump phone's whereabouts. As usual, we're still waiting for a response. In the meantime, I finally got a reply from a company exec. After months - months - of emailing various official Trump [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA's cosy lighting will will give your home a glow-up to beat the winter blues, with prices from just &#163;7</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/ikeas-cosy-lighting-will-will-give-your-home-a-glow-up-to-beat-the-winter-blues-with-prices-from-just-gbp7</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cZ5EK9efbiXsT8ue8bNxZT</guid>
      <description>Add a splash of warmth to any room, without touching the thermostat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL Flip 7 vs Bose SoundLink Flex Gen 2: two audio giants, only one winner</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/jbl-flip-7-vs-bose-soundlink-flex-gen-2</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">M8UXmyNDMcB2qpqj9zEXLk</guid>
      <description>I pitted JBL against Bose in this showdown of two audio behemoths, but there was only ever going to be one champion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200 exp&#233;riences dans la Station spatiale : ce que Sophie Adenot va vraiment tester dans l&#8217;espace pendant 9 mois</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sophie-adenot-200-experiences-station-spatiale-ce-sophie-adenot-va-vraiment-tester-espace-pendant-9-mois-130264/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:57:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sophie-adenot-200-experiences-station-spatiale-ce-sophie-adenot-va-vraiment-tester-espace-pendant-9-mois-130264/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Alors que son d&#233;part approche, c'est l'occasion de faire un point sur les exp&#233;riences que m&#232;nera Sophie Adenot durant son s&#233;jour de neuf mois dans la Station spatiale internationale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber is literally in the driver&#8217;s seat when it comes to AV bets</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/uber-is-literally-in-the-drivers-seat-when-it-comes-to-av-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3088305</guid>
      <description>Self-driving truck startup&#160;Waabi&#8217;s billion-dollar fundraise&#160;isn&#8217;t&#160;just about trucks.&#160;&#160; The deal, for $750 million up front plus another $250 million from Uber tied to deployment milestones, marks a major expansion into robotaxis for the company founded by former Uber AI chief Raquel Urtasun. It also feels like another chip from Uber on the&#160;autonomous vehicle&#160;roulette table. With more [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine O&#8217;Hara, Star of &#8216;Beetlejuice&#8217; and &#8216;Home Alone,&#8217; Has Died</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/catherine-ohara-star-of-beetlejuice-and-home-alone-has-died-2000716080</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716080</guid>
      <description>The comedic legend also starred in 'Schitt's Creek,' 'Best in Show,' 'The Last of Us,' and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyson&#8217;s powerful 360 Vis Nav robot vacuum is nearly 75 percent off today</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/870256/dyson-360-vis-nav-robot-vacuum-lego-lotr-balrog-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T13:48:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870256</guid>
      <description>In case you missed it, we recently overhauled our guides to the best budget robot vacuums and the best mopping vacs, both of which feature a slate of new picks from Roborock, Narwal, Dreame, and others. Dyson&#8217;s 360 Vis Nav Robot Vacuum didn&#8217;t technically make the cut, though it was once one of our top [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Robot Hand Pops Off and Crawls. I Hate It So Much.</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-robot-hand-pops-off-and-crawls-i-hate-it-so-much-2000715991</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715991</guid>
      <description>Like a robotic spider! But somehow worse!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest DDoS attack ever has been detected - but fortunately you probably barely noticed it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/the-biggest-ddos-attack-ever-has-been-detected-but-fortunately-you-probably-barely-noticed-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GgzmLyZmN3jpLHhXCKY6fL</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare mitigated a major attack on a telco which broke all previous records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;app France Identit&#233; teste une fonction pour prouver son &#226;ge en ligne</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/lapp-france-identite-teste-une-fonction-pour-prouver-son-age-en-ligne.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323541</guid>
      <description>Prouver son &#226;ge va devenir une contrainte de plus en plus pr&#233;sente &#224; mesure que les r&#233;gulateurs &#233;largissent la liste des sites et services en ligne tenus de v&#233;rifier que leurs utilisateurs sont bien des adultes certifi&#233;s. L'application France Identit&#233; pourrait avoir une carte &#224; jouer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook is destroying his own legacy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/870717/tim-cook-melania-minneapolis-tiktok-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T13:09:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870717</guid>
      <description>What responsibility do you have to speak up about bad things happening in the world? Does that responsibility change when speaking up might affect your business? What about if you're a sports creator, or the moderator of a deeply NSFW subreddit? What about if you're just a little ol' phone website? Ultimately, everyone has to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for the Galaxy S26? I have the perfect T-Mobile deal to tempt you into picking up a Google Pixel 10 Pro XL instead</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/network-providers/waiting-for-the-galaxy-s26-i-have-the-perfect-t-mobile-deal-to-tempt-you-into-picking-up-a-google-pixel-10-pro-xl-instead</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7wEZTYwXz8irtHFm3BQ8VJ</guid>
      <description>T-Mobile's current deal on the Google Pixel 10 Pro XL gets you this superb device for free with a new unlimited line - without a trade-in needed, either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sundance doc 'Ghost in the Machine' draws a damning line between AI and eugenics</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/sundance-doc-ghost-in-the-machine-draws-a-damning-line-between-ai-and-eugenics-180613367.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11f3334f-4881-48b9-97e7-07f459eda8bd</guid>
      <description>The Sundance documentary Ghost in the Machine boldly declares that the pursuit of artificial intelligence, and Silicon Valley itself, is rooted in eugenics.&#160;Director Valerie Veatch makes the case that the rise of techno-fascism from the likes of Elon Musk and Peter Thiel is a feature, not a bug. That may sound hyperbolic, but Ghost in the Machine, which is built around interviews with philosophers, AI researchers, historians and computer scientists, leaves little room for doubt.If you've been following the meteoric rise of AI, or Silicon Valley in general, Veatch's methodical deconstruction of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next &#8216;Fast and Furious&#8217; Movie Finally Has an Official Title and Release Date</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-next-fast-and-furious-movie-finally-has-an-official-title-and-release-date-2000716061</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716061</guid>
      <description>It's called 'Fast Forever' and will be in theaters on March 17, 2028.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic brings agentic plug-ins to Cowork</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/30/anthropic-brings-agentic-plugins-to-cowork/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087918</guid>
      <description>The company says you can use plug-ins to "tell Claude how you like work done, which tools and data to pull from, how to handle critical workflows, and what slash commands to expose so your team gets more consistent outcomes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 2026&#8217;s full &#8216;snow&#8217; moon comes with a side of free chips and queso: How and when to get yours</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482836/february-1-2026-full-moon-snow-free-chips-queso-dip-qdoba-when-what-day-to-see-it-tonight</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482836/february-1-2026-full-moon-snow-free-chips-queso-dip-qdoba-when-what-day-to-see-it-tonight</guid>
      <description>A major fast-food chain has a special deal to celebrate the &#8216;big cheese,&#8217; and stargazers can grab it this weekend.
This Sunday&#8217;s full moon, or &#8220;big cheese,&#8221; as it&#8217;s sometimes called, comes with a side of queso and chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The JBL Charge 5 is my most loyal travel buddy &#8212; and now this trusty Bluetooth speaker can be yours for almost &#163;90 off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/the-jbl-charge-5-is-my-most-loyal-travel-buddy-and-now-this-trusty-bluetooth-speaker-can-be-yours-for-almost-gbp90-off</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8EfnweYXSm6eUAGucKGSxa</guid>
      <description>My fave Bluetooth speaker for taking on adventures is at its lowest price yet &#8211; so grab it for nearly half off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: The Galaxy S26 lineup and everything else we expect</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-the-galaxy-s26-lineup-and-everything-else-we-expect-130000999.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hands-on coverage of Samsung's new smartphones soon after they're announced. While we wait for an official invite, here's everything we expect Samsung will introduce at the first Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026.What is Unpacked 2026 taking place?But...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI IPO: What to know about the most anticipated stock listing in years amid rumors of a 2026 date</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484259/openai-ipo-chatgpt-maker-rumored-stock-listing-2026-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T17:48:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484259/openai-ipo-chatgpt-maker-rumored-stock-listing-2026-date</guid>
      <description>The ChatGPT maker and world&#8217;s most valuable startup could go public as soon as this year, according to a WSJ report.
It&#8217;s shaping up to be a busy year for initial public offerings from some of the most closely watched companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google's Project Genie lets you create your own 3D interactive worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/googles-project-genie-lets-you-create-your-own-3d-interactive-worlds-183646428.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f96776b3-9f86-4da3-a49e-ab792ecdecfc</guid>
      <description>This past summer, Google DeepMind debuted Genie 3. It&#8217;s what&#8217;s known as a world world, an AI system capable of generating images and reacting as the user moves through the environment the software is simulating. At the time, DeepMind positioned Genie 3 as a tool for training AI agents. Now, it&#8217;s making the model available to people outside of Google to try with Project Genie. To start, you&#8217;ll need Google&#8217;s $250 per month AI Ultra plan to check out Project Genie. You&#8217;ll also need to live in the US and be 18 years or older. At launch, Project Genie offers three different modes of interaction: Wo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos home theater gear is up to 20 percent off ahead of Super Bowl LX</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/sonos-home-theater-gear-is-up-to-20-percent-off-ahead-of-super-bowl-lx-174053619.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d95ac4b9-448d-4c43-906a-61793dfa0aef</guid>
      <description>Like many other companies during Super Bowl season, Sonos is discounting its home theater gear. Today, you can save $130 on the Beam (Gen 2) soundbar, bringing its price down to $369. You'll also find deals on the flagship Arc Ultra Soundbar, Sonos subwoofers, and more.
The Sonos Beam is the company's sub-$500 soundbar. Engadget's pick for the best midrange model, the compact speaker has impressive sound for its size. Part of that is its Dolby Atmos support. Although the soundbar lacks upward-firing speakers, it uses software tricks to compensate. Audio timing and frequency adjustments make so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save up to 81 percent on ExpressVPN two-year plans right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/save-up-to-81-percent-on-expressvpn-two-year-plans-right-now-180602273.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $88 for two years, plus four additional free months. The Basic plan is where you'll see the biggest discount: it's $68 for two years, plus the same four additional free months.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. On...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
