<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:23:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Primal&#8217; Is Back From the Dead and as Gnarly as Ever</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/primal-season-3-review-adult-swim-2000707843</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707843</guid>
      <description>The third season of Genndy Tartakovsky's Adult Swim animated series sees its titular caveman fighting one prehistoric battle after another&#8212;this time, as a zombie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest on Grok&#8217;s problem with gross AI deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/859715/x-grok-ai-deepfakes</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T14:13:32-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=859715</guid>
      <description>The launch of an AI image editing feature on xAI&#8217;s Grok has caused chaos on X after it was used to generate a flood of non-consensual sexualized deepfakes. As Hayden Field wrote, &#8220;screenshots show Grok complying with requests to put real women in lingerie and make them spread their legs, and to put small children [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiFlix Helps You Catch Up on Films That Just Entered the Public Domain</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wikiflix-helps-you-catch-up-on-films-that-just-entered-the-public-domain-2000708070</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708070</guid>
      <description>New films hit the public domain at the start of every year. WikiFlix is helping collect them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 emergency directives retired as CISA declares them redundant</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/10-emergency-directives-retired-as-cisa-declares-them-redundant</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NSxg6zvxWUPFYyLdnrMgr3</guid>
      <description>The directives served their purpose and are no longer needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp might soon be subject to stricter scrutiny under the EU's Digital Services Act</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/whatsapp-might-soon-be-subject-to-stricter-scrutiny-under-the-eus-digital-services-act-191000354.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15b9bf01-2b0f-4d95-8a80-257395bcc698</guid>
      <description>Meta's messaging app WhatsApp could soon be subject to deeper scrutiny (and punishment) under the European Commission's Digital Services Act, Reuters reports. Because the app's broadcasting feature WhatsApp Channels grew to around 51.7 million average monthly active users in the European Union in the first six months of 2025, the feature has crossed the 45-million-person barrier that lets DSA rules apply.A platform is designated as a "very large online platform" or VLOP once it has 45 million monthly users or more, according to the European Commission. Once an app or service passes that amount...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 000 &#8364; moins cher qu&#8217;une Audi : Zeekr arrive enfin en France avec le break &#233;lectrique 7GT qui fait mieux que Tesla</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/zeekr/2938071_20-000-e-moins-cher-quune-audi-zeekr-arrive-enfin-en-france-avec-le-break-electrique-7gt-qui-fait-mieux-que-tesla</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/zeekr/2938071_20-000-e-moins-cher-quune-audi-zeekr-arrive-enfin-en-france-avec-le-break-electrique-7gt-qui-fait-mieux-que-tesla</guid>
      <description>
La marque chinoise de voitures &#233;lectriques Zeekr arrive enfin en France, avec notamment ce nouveau mod&#232;le, le 7GT. Au programme : une recharge ultra-rapide, et des technologies qui font clairement penser &#224; une Tesla. Pour un prix d&#233;fiant toute concurrence.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta expands nuclear power ambitions to include Bill Gates&amp;#8217; startup</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/859751/meta-nuclear-energy-plant-agreements-ai-data-centers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T13:53:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859751</guid>
      <description>Meta has forged agreements with three nuclear power providers in an effort to secure the vast amount of electricity it needs to power AI data centers. The agreements with TerraPower (which is backed by Bill Gates), Oklo (backed by Sam Altman), and Vistra are expected to deliver 6.6 gigawatts of energy for Meta's projects by [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Thousand Blows season 2 review: the Disney+ bareknuckle boxing series is more brutal than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/a-thousand-blows-season-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rRfnBMUFE6S3Q7F9GHVLjG</guid>
      <description>A Thousand Blows season 2 returns to Disney+ and Hulu, and this time, it's an even tougher fight for survival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takedowns and arrests didn't slow down ransomware in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/takedowns-and-arrests-didnt-slow-down-ransomware-in-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ChHbWvo9EMrANS6s5fiM5a</guid>
      <description>Despite the police's best efforts, ransomware continues to rise with more actors, more victims, and more trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are migraines still not taken seriously?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470170/migraines-still-not-taken-seriously</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470170/migraines-still-not-taken-seriously</guid>
      <description>If a condition that disables one in seven adults were perceived as a &#8216;men&#8217;s disease,&#8217; it would almost certainly receive more attention.
Some words are far too mild for the violence of what they describe. Migraine is one of them. For many people, it evokes a simple headache &#8212; an inconvenience solved with an aspirin (or Tylenol) and a glass of water. For those who&#8217;ve never experienced it, migraine is almost a clich&#233;: a lame excuse to stay in bed or avoid a meeting....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Serkis Talks About the Impossible Task of &#8216;The Hunt for Gollum&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/andy-serkis-hunt-for-gollum-lord-of-the-rings-2000708167</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708167</guid>
      <description>'The Lord of the Rings' star turned director is currently prepping the next 'Lord of the Rings' film, due in December 2027.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Mirror has been renewed for another season</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/859699/netflix-black-mirror-season-8</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T13:10:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859699</guid>
      <description>In an interview with Netflix's Tudum, Black Mirror creator Charlie Brooker announced today that the sci-fi anthology series will be returning for an eighth season. "Well, luckily it does have a future, so I can confirm that Black Mirror will return, just in time for reality to catch up with it," Brooker said. "That chunk [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Ludicrously Light Headset Restored My Passion for VR</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-ludicrously-light-headset-restored-my-passion-for-vr-2000708053</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708053</guid>
      <description>Pimax's Dream Air weighs less than my iPhone 17 and somehow has a micro OLED display with an 8K resolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell Pro Max 16 Plus mobile workstation review: Backpack-friendly desktop-class power with a beautiful display</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dell-pro-max-16-plus-mobile-workstation-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NpJKcfSEHNGVU9rneLwz6V</guid>
      <description>The Dell Pro Max 16 Plus is an impressively powerful mobile workstation designed to take on any and all challenges you may throw at it in the professional workspace, all at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-two-year-plans-are-up-to-78-percent-off-right-now-180602025.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $101 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.59 for the promo period.


We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 
In our review we were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I can&#8217;t find the Trump phone at America&#8217;s largest tech show</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859023/i-cant-find-the-trump-phone-at-americans-largest-tech-show</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T13:05:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859023</guid>
      <description>Where's the Trump phone? We're going to keep talking about it every week. We've reached out, as usual, to ask about the Trump phone's whereabouts. As usual, we're still waiting for a response. In the meantime, it's nowhere to be found at CES 2026. CES isn't a big smartphone show, but there have been more [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is turning the White House into a McMansion. Here&#8217;s what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91472141/trump-is-turning-the-white-house-into-a-mcmansion-heres-what-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T18:05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91472141/trump-is-turning-the-white-house-into-a-mcmansion-heres-what-you-need-to-know</guid>
      <description>The President&#8217;s proposals including slapping another story onto the West Wing.
Less than three months ago, the world watched the Trump administration reduce the White House&#8217;s historic East Wing to a pile of rubble to begin construction on a massive new ballroom. But it looks like the dust from that demolition will have barely settled before Trump starts another project to turn the presidential residence into his own personal real estate development endeavor....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve tested the latest Switch 2 controllers, and this one is the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/791574/best-switch-2-controllers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T13:00:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=791574</guid>
      <description>If you choose to get an extra controller for your Nintendo Switch 2, you can spend a lot &#8212; and get a lot in return. Buying Nintendo&#8217;s own $89 Switch 2 Pro Controller, for instance, will net you the console&#8217;s only wireless controller with a 3.5mm headphone jack for private listening, not to mention great-feeling [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Federal Agents Using GoPros, Smart Glasses, and Phones to Record Us?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-are-federal-agents-using-gopros-smart-glasses-and-phones-to-record-us-2000707835</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707835</guid>
      <description>"What happened to the police body cameras?" one Uber driver in Minnesota asked a Border Patrol agent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I waited two years to get a PlayStation Portal, and now wish I&#8217;d bought one sooner</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/i-waited-two-years-to-get-a-playstation-portal-and-now-wish-id-bought-one-sooner</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Jch4EBTCbTpC4zhszCw2AJ</guid>
      <description>The PlayStation Portal is one of the most surprising gaming accessories I&#8217;ve owned in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES: So very big, so little sustainability tech</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/ces-so-very-big-so-little-sustainability-tech-180000648.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d60aade-77de-4a76-affd-d89b1ce8308b</guid>
      <description>Every third booth at CES showed off some new AI product or other.  If you wanted to find a robotic lawn mower, throw a rock. Humanoid robots, smart locks and super thin TVs were everywhere. But if you went looking for sustainability products, you&#8217;re going to have to hunt a bit. Last year, the Sustainability section at the Las Vegas Convention Center had 20 booths. This year, there were 38, but that&#8217;s in part due to the combination of the energy and sustainability categories. So exhibitors like South Korea&#8217;s largest electric utility company, a nuclear power company from the same country and lot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premi&#232;re fois &#224; l&#8217;int&#233;rieur de la Tesla Model 3 Standard &#224; 36 990 &#8364; : le hold-up de l&#8217;ann&#233;e est confirm&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2937703_premiere-fois-a-linterieur-de-la-tesla-model-3-standard-a-36-990-e-le-hold-up-de-lannee-est-confirme</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2937703_premiere-fois-a-linterieur-de-la-tesla-model-3-standard-a-36-990-e-le-hold-up-de-lannee-est-confirme</guid>
      <description>
On s'attendait &#224; une version "&#233;co+", d&#233;pouill&#233;e, un peu triste. La r&#233;alit&#233; ? C'est tout l'inverse. La nouvelle Tesla Model 3 Standard, affich&#233;e &#224; un prix agressif de 36 990 &#8364;, vient d'&#234;tre aper&#231;ue au salon de Bruxelles. Et franchement, &#224; part les enjoliveurs, il faut un &#339;il d'expert pour voir la diff&#233;rence avec le haut de gamme.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta signs deals with three nuclear companies for 6-plus GW of power</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/09/meta-signs-deals-with-three-nuclear-companies-for-6-plus-gw-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081433</guid>
      <description>Two smaller companies, Oklo and TerraPower, along with Vistra, a large energy company, just signed agreements with Meta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic Hubble Telescope Could Be Dead in 3 Years</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iconic-hubble-telescope-could-be-dead-in-3-years-2000708044</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708044</guid>
      <description>The silver lining is that there may be a privately funded alternative in the works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 proved the PC industry is hosed this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/ces-2026-proved-the-pc-industry-is-hosed-this-year-174500314.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db798e3a-f4ab-4554-828a-98500fcc1f8f</guid>
      <description>Dell's XPS 14 now costs over $2,000. An AMD executive predicts that PC builders will likely make piecemeal upgrades this year, instead of building entirely new systems. And new AI supercomputers from NVIDIA and AMD are gobbling up the RAM market. At CES 2026, it was hard not to notice the dire year ahead for the computing industry, one that will likely lead to higher prices and more limited availability for consumer goods across the board.Really, though, the show just confirmed what was apparent since RAM prices skyrocketed over the last few months, driven by demand from AI datacenters. As Sam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first sets with Lego&#8217;s new Smart Brick are now available for preorder</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859525/lego-smart-brick-play-system-now-available-preorder-star-wars-sets</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T12:31:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859525</guid>
      <description>It may have been one of the smallest devices announced at CES 2026, but Lego's new Smart Brick was also one of the most talked about debuts of the show. We've recognized it as the "Best in show" in our CES 2026 awards, and following the Smart Play system's launch earlier this week, the first [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Bezos says successful people find ways to make a lot fewer decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469229/jeff-bezos-successful-people-fewer-decisions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469229/jeff-bezos-successful-people-fewer-decisions</guid>
      <description>According to Bezos, two or three decisions a day should be the goal.
Run a small business and you probably feel like you make dozens of decisions every day. Whether to cut a quality corner, or miss a ship date. Whether to respond to a customer complaint, or hope the problem goes away. Whether to address an&#160;employee&#8217;s behavior, or kick that can down the road....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai jou&#233; aux LEGO avec la Smart Brick : les possibilit&#233;s sont infinies, le coup de c&#339;ur est &#233;norme</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2936269_jai-joue-aux-lego-avec-la-smart-brick-les-possibilites-sont-infinies-le-coup-de-coeur-est-enorme</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2936269_jai-joue-aux-lego-avec-la-smart-brick-les-possibilites-sont-infinies-le-coup-de-coeur-est-enorme</guid>
      <description>
J'ai jou&#233; avec la LEGO Smart Brick et les sets Star Wars compatibles. Un plaisir simple, une belle id&#233;e et un coup de c&#339;ur &#233;norme. Retour d'exp&#233;rience.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O&#249; pr&#233;commander les nouveaux LEGO Star Wars connect&#233;s au meilleur prix ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2938039_ou-precommander-les-nouveaux-lego-star-wars-connectes-au-meilleur-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2938039_ou-precommander-les-nouveaux-lego-star-wars-connectes-au-meilleur-prix</guid>
      <description>
Vous aviez pr&#233;vu de faire des &#233;conomies en ce d&#233;but 2026 ? C'est rat&#233;. Quelques jours apr&#232;s l'annonce choc du CES, LEGO vient d'ouvrir les vannes. Les trois premiers sets Star Wars Smart Play sont disponibles en pr&#233;commande d&#232;s maintenant. Et comme pr&#233;vu, la technologie, &#231;a se paie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Black Mirror&#8217; Will Bring More Dystopia to Our Dystopia With Season 8</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/black-mirror-will-bring-more-dystopia-to-our-dystopia-with-season-8-2000708106</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708106</guid>
      <description>Charlie Brooker's series will return to Netflix for another round of (inevitably) eerily timely episodes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
