<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:39:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>8 billion tokens a day forced AT&amp;T to rethink AI orchestration &#8212; and cut costs by 90%</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/8-billion-tokens-a-day-forced-at-and-t-to-rethink-ai-orchestration-and-cut</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7BND9iiQlzpkzhHFbu182m</guid>
      <description>When your average daily token usage is 8 billion a day, you have a massive scale problem. 

This was the case at AT&amp;T, and chief data officer Andy Markus and his team recognized that it simply wasn&#8217;t feasible (or economical) to push everything through large reasoning models. 

So, when building out an internal Ask AT&amp;T personal assistant, they reconstructed the orchestration layer. The result: A multi-agent stack built on LangChain where large language model &#8220;super agents&#8221; direct smaller, underlying &#8220;worker&#8221; agents performing more concise, purpose-driven work. 

This flexible orchestration lay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens Declare: Superheroes Are Out, Daddy Energy Is In</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/teens-declare-superheroes-are-out-daddy-energy-is-in-2000726710</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726710</guid>
      <description>According to a new study, kids are moving on from stoic heroes&#8212;and want more compassionate portrayals of masculinity in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung hikes price of Galaxy S26 lineup over S25, but it won't say the RAM crisis is to blame &#8212; even though it almost certainly is</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/samsung-hikes-price-of-galaxy-s26-lineup-over-s25-but-it-wont-say-the-ram-crisis-is-to-blame-even-though-it-almost-certainly-is</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rDgZmKQYsrNjK5jQwcXL7T</guid>
      <description>Samsung won't blame the RAM crisis for its S26 price hikes, but I will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman says plans for data centers in space are 'ridiculous' &#8212; is this the start of a new war of words with Elon Musk?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sam-altman-says-plans-for-data-centers-in-space-are-ridiculous-is-this-the-start-of-a-new-war-of-words-with-elon-musk</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">j8MNf5HqNtWADH7r5C7dck</guid>
      <description>Sam Altman dismisses current plans for orbital data centers, citing high launch costs, hardware fragility, and infrastructure limitations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used Teslas Are Getting More Expensive While Other EVs Get Cheaper</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/used-teslas-are-getting-more-expensive-while-other-evs-get-cheaper-2000726699</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726699</guid>
      <description>If you want a used EV, you might have to pay the Elon tax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Assassin's Creed game loses its creative director</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-next-assassins-creed-game-loses-its-creative-director-210119005.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17eb1259-d9e2-48f1-a61a-ad2f7d8a34cf</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft's shakeups continue unabated. The creative director of the next Assassin's Creed game, codenamed Hexe, has left the company. The departure of Clint Hocking, a 20-year veteran of the company over two stints, was reportedly announced in a staff meeting this week.Hocking's resume at Ubisoft included serving as creative director on Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory, Far Cry 2 and Watch Dogs: Legion. The details of why he's leaving the company haven't been reported.Ubisoft told VGC, which first reported on Hocking's exit, that development on Hexe will continue. Jean Guedson, one of three new lead...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I can't believe I'm actually excited to sit in virtual traffic in the 'most ambitious and content-rich Bus Simulator to date'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/i-cant-believe-im-actually-excited-to-sit-in-virtual-traffic-in-the-most-ambitious-and-content-rich-bus-simulator-to-date</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jcpTJ6V7PDmFKDtAxi7azk</guid>
      <description>Publisher Astragon Entertainment has announced Bus Simulator 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;There&#8217;s possibility for another partner to join the ecosystem&#8217; &#8212; as Perplexity lands on Samsung Galaxy S26 phones a Samsung head is already teasing the next AI addition</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/theres-possibility-for-another-partner-to-join-the-ecosystem-as-perplexity-lands-on-samsung-galaxy-s26-phones-a-samsung-head-is-already-teasing-the-next-ai-addition</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">x5vduHDbt8VwWPdfrdTNBC</guid>
      <description>As Samsung adds Perplexity to its S26 smartphones it's already teasing the next AI addition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Speaks Incel Now</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/everyone-speaks-incel-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6994a3670520b9cafe8c9c5c</guid>
      <description>After migrating from misogynist forums to social media feeds, terms like &#8220;looksmaxxing&#8221; and &#8220;mogged&#8221; are now impossible to avoid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 things we learned from Samsung&#8217;s big Galaxy Unpacked 2026 event &#8212; from the S26 Ultra to the Buds4 Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/9-things-we-learned-from-samsungs-big-galaxy-unpacked-2026-event-from-the-s26-ultra-to-the-buds4-pro</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QAJjXUX782iShGvmdTBADE</guid>
      <description>Samsung has wrapped up it first big Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026 &#8212; here's everything it announced in one handy place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Overdue&#8217; West Coast Mega-Earthquake May Not Be Looming After All</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-overdue-west-coast-mega-earthquake-may-not-be-looming-after-all-2000726724</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726724</guid>
      <description>Make no mistake&#8212;this doesn&#8217;t mean there is no danger. The researchers urge policymakers to treat seismic risk as a constant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian government demands safety changes from OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/canadian-government-demands-safety-changes-from-openai-204924604.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7143f0a0-5eab-4993-93a8-6fe1c88c1ff1</guid>
      <description>Canadian officials summoned leaders from OpenAI to Ottawa this week to address safety concerns about ChatGPT. The crux of the government concerns was that OpenAI did not notify authorities when it banned the account of a user who allegedly committed a mass shooting in British Columbia earlier this month.&#160;"The message that we delivered, in no uncertain terms, was that we have &#8204;an expectation that there are going to &#8288;be changes implemented, and if they're not forthcoming very quickly, the government is going to be making changes," Justice Minister Sean Fraser said of the company and its AI chatb...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Peace Corps is recruiting volunteers to sell AI to developing nations</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/884625/peace-corps-tech-promote-american-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T15:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884625</guid>
      <description>For more than six decades, the Peace Corps has represented itself as an agency focused on helping underserved communities around the globe. But a new initiative, called the "Tech Corps," threatens to unravel the agency's original mission by recruiting de facto Silicon Valley salespeople to promote the biggest names in AI - many of which [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House wants AI companies to cover rate hikes. Most have already said they would.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/the-white-house-wants-ai-companies-to-cover-rate-hikes-most-have-already-said-they-would/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096961</guid>
      <description>Many of hyperscalers have already made public commitments in to cover electricity cost increases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox consoles now support 1440p streaming</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/xbox-consoles-now-support-1440p-streaming-204115304.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2924601-b0fe-41ec-b482-be0d7169a2d8</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has announced that its rolling out support for streaming games at 1440p on Xbox consoles. Game streaming is a key benefit of paying for a Game Pass subscription, and as of 2025, now also includes games players own that aren't part of the larger Game Pass library.The higher bitrate streaming option will let subscribers with an Xbox Series X or S, Xbox One X or Xbox One play their games at a higher resolution, provided the game and their display supports it. Microsoft previously only offered 1440p streams on select Fire TVs, LG TVs, Samsung TVs, web browsers and the Xbox PC app. At lea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims tech companies will sign deals next week to pay for their own power supply</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/884191/ai-data-center-energy-state-of-the-union-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T15:37:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884191</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump tried to quell Americans' concerns about rising electricity costs during his State of the Union speech - and now we're learning that the deals he promised could land next week. Trump claimed that he's negotiated a "rate payer protection pledge" with major tech companies, which would see them build out or pay [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Messed-Up-Looking &#8216;Absolute Batman&#8217; Villains, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-most-messed-up-looking-absolute-batman-villains-ranked-2000726415</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726415</guid>
      <description>A hero is only as good as his villains&#8212;and so far DC's blockbuster new take on the Dark Knight is knocking it out of the park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US cybersecurity agency CISA reportedly in dire shape amid Trump cuts and layoffs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/us-cybersecurity-agency-cisa-reportedly-in-dire-shape-amid-trump-cuts-and-layoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096990</guid>
      <description>Under the first year of the Trump administration, the U.S. cyber agency CISA has faced cuts, layoffs, and furloughs, as bipartisan lawmakers and cybersecurity industry sources say the agency is unprepared to handle a crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalshi Bans MrBeast Video Editor and Political Candidate Over Insider Trading</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kalshi-bans-mrbeast-video-editor-and-political-candidate-over-insider-trading-2000726520</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726520</guid>
      <description>This is the first known action that the prediction market has taken against users for alleged insider trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the post-hype crypto market</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/welcome-to-the-post-hype-crypto-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3096986</guid>
      <description>Crypto is creeping back into the startup conversation, but at&#160;ETHDenver&#160;last week, the buzz was as much about Washington as it was about tokens. Policy shifts are rippling through the market as&#160;Tether&#160;and stablecoins face scrutiny,&#160;players like Stripe&#160;re-enter the&#160;conversation, and startups either find traction or flame out. The hype cycle is&#160;over, or&#160;at least taking a&#160;break.&#160;So&#160;what&#160;comes next?&#160; On [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26 phone cases: Where to get fun ones right now</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-galaxy-s26-phone-cases-where-to-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02REE2i9sWSkcipKupyhg5p</guid>
      <description>At Samsung Unpacked, the brand released the new Samsung Galaxy S26 phone. If you've already preordered your new phones, start shopping for a new case from Samsung, Burga, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The surge of video podcasts raises an awkward question for the industry: Why do we still call them &#8216;podcasts&#8217;?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91498688/why-still-called-podcasts-video-pods-new-medium</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T20:20:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91498688/why-still-called-podcasts-video-pods-new-medium</guid>
      <description>As Netflix builds out its visual-podcasting slate, some media watchers say we need new language to describe the medium. It might not be that easy.
With Netflix now streaming original podcasts and Apple announcing a &#8220;category-leading video experience&#8221; on its app this spring, the meaning of the word &#8220;podcast&#8221; has grown increasingly diffuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why This Part of Antarctica Bleeds Blood Red</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-this-part-of-antarctica-bleeds-blood-red-2000726530</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726530</guid>
      <description>Perhaps surprisingly, the answer isn't climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s how the new Samsung Galaxy S26 compares with last year&#8217;s S25</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/884281/samsung-galaxy-s26-plus-ultra-vs-s25-specs-features</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T15:09:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884281</guid>
      <description>Samsung unveiled its Galaxy S26 lineup at its recent Unpacked event in San Francisco. As expected, the new series consists of the baseline S26, which starts at $899.99, and the bigger S26 Plus, which starts at $1,099.99. At the high end, there's also the $1,299.99 S26 Ultra, which is the largest in the lineup and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung to auto-tag AI-generated photos in Galaxy S26</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-autotag-ai-generated-photos-galaxy-s26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01jUDhyQfJNdNidrfgaxrBf</guid>
      <description>When you make AI-generated images with your Galaxy S26 camera app, Samsung will apply an AI label.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet-owned robotics software company Intrinsic joins Google</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/alphabet-owned-robotics-software-company-intrinsic-joins-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096871</guid>
      <description>Nearly five years after graduating into an independent Alphabet company, Intrinsic is moving under Google's domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce qui cloche avec les Samsung Galaxy S26</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2987095_ce-qui-cloche-avec-les-samsung-galaxy-s26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2987095_ce-qui-cloche-avec-les-samsung-galaxy-s26</guid>
      <description>
Samsung vient d'annoncer les Galaxy S26, S26 Plus et S26 Ultra. Au milieu de plusieurs qualit&#233;s, certains d&#233;fauts retiennent aussi notre attention sur ces smartphones.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This hotline is letting fans congratulate the U.S. women&#8217;s hockey team after its gold medal win</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91498742/womens-hockey-gold-medal-hotline</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T19:59:34</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91498742/womens-hockey-gold-medal-hotline</guid>
      <description>The 1-833-SHE-WON1 hotline has already received hundreds of emotional messages.
A new hotline is inviting Americans to congratulate the U.S. women&#8217;s hockey team after its historic Olympic gold medal win&#8212;and it&#8217;s already flooded with messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riley Walz, the Jester of Silicon Valley, Is Joining OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-hires-riley-walz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699e08ff458686361c3c0d20</guid>
      <description>The software engineer is famous for his online stunts. Now he&#8217;s joining the company behind ChatGPT to work on new ways for humans to use AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google and Samsung just launched the AI features Apple couldn&#8217;t with Siri</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/884703/google-samsung-galaxy-s26-gemini-apple-siri</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T14:56:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884703</guid>
      <description>Google just announced that Gemini will soon be able to take care of some multi-step tasks on your phone, like ordering food or hailing a car, starting first with the Pixel 10, Pixel 10 Pro, and the just-announced Samsung Galaxy S26 phones. It all sounds a bit like features Apple announced for Siri way back [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat announces &#8216;The Snappys,&#8217; its first-ever creator awards show</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/snapchat-announces-the-snappys-its-first-ever-creator-awards-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096864</guid>
      <description>Snapchat is the latest social media platform to launch awards for creators, joining TikTok and Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked live blog: See the latest updates</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-live-blog-s26-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03IxQBaXFXkzLsx80GSuNbN</guid>
      <description>Check out the latest Samsung Galaxy phones and products released during the February Unpacked event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tecno just unveiled a ridiculously thin modular smartphone concept design</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/tecno-just-unveiled-a-ridiculously-thin-modular-smartphone-concept-design-194741776.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3f8f8ca-6771-42a1-a5f0-26e1ee8704e5</guid>
      <description>Tecno just unveiled a rather intriguing modular smartphone concept design at MWC 2026. The standout feature here is likely the size. Most modular smartphone concepts start bulky and only get bulkier once attaching accessories. Tecno's base smartphone is just 4.9mm thin, which is significantly thinner than a pencil and the iPhone Air.
Of course, the size increases with each attached module. However, snapping on the power bank module makes the thickness comparable to a standard modern smartphone. Another key feature here is how these various modular components stick together. Tecno has developed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel ditches human customer support for 'one of the first of its kind in the semiconductor industry' system made up of Copilot-powered AI agents</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/intel-ditches-human-customer-support-for-one-of-the-first-of-its-kind-in-the-semiconductor-industry-system-made-of-copilot-powered-ai-agents</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xmBtpT933EEoFPpkQo9tVE</guid>
      <description>Ask Intel is an AI-powered assistant replacing phone-based support and centralizing warranty, troubleshooting, and case management online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 things you can do with Galaxy S26 Ultras Privacy Display</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-s26-ultra-privacy-display-features-4-things-you-can-do</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05ehUZmXCd5uPvAPXWBxWwP</guid>
      <description>Samsung's new Galaxy S26 Ultra has Privacy Display, which can do a lot of things to keep your screen's secrets safe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
