<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:31:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star Giannis Antetokounmpo joins Kalshi as an investor</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/07/nba-star-giannis-antetokounmpo-joins-kalshi-as-an-investor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090799</guid>
      <description>Antetokounmpo is the first NBA player to directly invest in Kalshi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Supergirl&#8217; May Get a Last-Minute Musical Change</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/supergirl-may-get-a-last-minute-musical-change-2000719178</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719178</guid>
      <description>The techno tones of Ramin Djawadi briefly teased in 'Supergirl' are now possibly replaced with Junkie XL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ is investigating if Netflix used anticompetitive tactics as part of its merger probe</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/doj-is-investigating-if-netflix-used-anticompetitive-tactics-as-part-of-its-merger-probe-210940856.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15e98a26-8164-4c91-8c60-63e87f601512</guid>
      <description>Netflix's acquisition of Warner Bros. Discovery isn't quite a done deal yet. As first reported by The Wall Street Journal, the US Department of Justice has started its probe of Netflix's proposed purchase, but is notably interested in whether the streaming giant was involved in any anticompetitive practices. According to the civil subpoena seen by WSJ, the Justice Department is looking into any "exclusionary conduct on the part of Netflix that would reasonably appear capable of entrenching market or monopoly power."
While Netflix announced plans to acquire Warner Bros. Discovery in December at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State Department is scrubbing its X accounts of all posts from before Trump's second term</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/the-state-department-is-scrubbing-its-x-accounts-of-all-posts-from-before-trumps-second-term-205515745.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a0dc813-8e52-4f52-8bb4-d4a3485f687a</guid>
      <description>The State Department is wiping the post history of its X accounts and making it so you'll have to file a Freedom of Information Act request if you want to access any of the content it removed, according to NPR. The publication reports that the State Department is removing all posts from before President Trump's current term &#8212; a move that affects several accounts associated with the department, including those for US embassies, and posts from the Biden and Obama administrations. Posts from Trump's first term will be taken down too.&#160;Unlike how past administrations have handled the removal of soc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOG is already working on native Linux support</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/875425/gog-native-linux-support</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T15:23:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875425</guid>
      <description>GOG recently posted a job listing for a senior software engineer focused on porting its Galaxy desktop client to Linux. Now, in reply to a Reddit AMA, the GOG team has revealed that work on native Linux support is already underway. It's still too early to give an ETA, according to the Reddit thread. But [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charli XCX Is a Demonic Brat in Takashi Miike&#8217;s &#8216;Untitled Tokyo&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/charli-xcx-is-a-demonic-brat-in-takashi-miikes-untitled-tokyo-2000719231</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719231</guid>
      <description>Get ready to see Charli XCX go horror mode in the next horror project from Takeshi Miike.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
