<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:27:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta has closed three VR studios as part of its metaverse cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/meta-has-closed-three-vr-studios-as-part-of-its-metaverse-cuts-202720670.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7129ad-5b4d-4ae8-b8a4-80cc0b970d30</guid>
      <description>Several of Meta's VR studios have been affected by the company's metaverse-focused layoffs. The company has shuttered three of its VR studios, including Armature, Sanzaru and Twisted Pixel. VR fitness app Supernatural will no longer be updated with fresh content.Employees at Twisted Pixel, which released Marvel's Deadpool VR in November, and Sanzaru, known for Asgard's Wrath, posted on social media about the closures. Bloomberg reported that Armature, which brought Resident Evil 4 to Quest back in 2021 has also closed and that the popular VR fitness app Supernatural will no longer be updated w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York governor clears path for robotaxis everywhere, with one notable exception</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/13/new-york-governor-clears-path-for-robotaxis-everywhere-with-one-notable-exception/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082486</guid>
      <description>New York City will be a notable exclusion from proposed legislation to legalize commercial robotaxis across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roblox's age verification system is reportedly a trainwreck</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/robloxs-age-verification-system-is-reportedly-a-trainwreck-220320016.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3895f3-ad9b-4a47-85b4-2dd2f09073a1</guid>
      <description>Roblox's age-verification system was designed as a response to allegations it has a child predator problem. Less than a week in, how's it going? Well, Wired reported on Tuesday that, in some cases, it's classifying children as adults and adults as children. So, not so great!Last week, Roblox made age verification mandatory for anyone using the platform's chat feature. That process involves either submitting a facial age estimate via selfie or (optionally for anyone 13 or older) uploading a government ID check. After verifying, you can only chat with groups of players around your age.The move c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is an Absolute Triumph</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-review-game-of-thrones-2000705180</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705180</guid>
      <description>The casting is perfect, and so is the tone: HBO&#8217;s latest journey to George R.R. Martin&#8217;s Westeros brings a smaller-scaled but no less epic adventure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Ear Audio Is Having a Huge Moment Right Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/open-ear-audio-is-having-a-huge-moment-right-now-2000709804</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709804</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, one audio trend was more audible than the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched all of A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms &#8212; and the new HBO Max show is the triumphant underdog tale that HBO's Game of Thrones franchise needs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dzfcwzPKmRd8tfiY5D6wC</guid>
      <description>A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms is a near-medieval masterpiece that stands tall among its Game of Thrones peers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram wants you to personalize your Reels algorithm for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/instagram-wants-you-to-personalize-your-reels-algorithm-for-2026-215252736.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d16159ac-55d0-4b30-9176-6632d84df1ab</guid>
      <description>Last month, Instagram began rolling out a new set of controls that allowed users to personalize the topics recommended to them by the Reels algorithm. Now, Meta is making that feature available to all English users of the app globally, along with the ability to highlight their top topics for the coming year.&#160;The feature begins with a selection of topics Meta's AI thinks you're interested in based on your recent activity, and has controls to remove them or add new categories. There's also a separate field for identifying what you want to see less of, and a new "build your 2026 algorithm" that a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s Solix E10 Battery Backup System Can Power Your Home for Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ankers-solix-e10-battery-backup-system-can-power-your-home-for-days-2000709853</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709853</guid>
      <description>Anker gets into the whole home backup game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is either the world's fastest laptop or someone made a massive typo: Obscure Chinese vendor Mechrevo unannounced Core Ultra 300HX CPU at CES, and apparently almost no one noticed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-is-either-the-worlds-fastest-laptop-or-someone-made-a-massive-typo-obscure-chinese-vendor-mechrevo-unannounced-core-ultra-300hx-cpu-at-ces-and-almost-no-one-noticed</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QeiXri2hMmKfSUdQY4YDBm</guid>
      <description>Mechrevo quietly unveiled the Yaoshi 18 Pro at CES 2026, featuring an unannounced Intel processor and powerful Nvidia graphics, which attracted minimal attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal&#8217;s Founder Turns His Attention to AI&#8217;s Privacy Problem</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/signals-founder-turns-his-attention-to-ais-privacy-problem-2000709897</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709897</guid>
      <description>Confer, an open source chatbot, encrypts both prompts and responses so companies and advertisers can&#8217;t access user data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested several cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T16:25:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Sure, it can take away from the slick design. But using a case relieves me of the worry that the console will accumulate tons of little scratches, or worse. I&#8217;ve tested several types of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes Defiance Act for a second time to address Grok deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/senate-passes-defiance-act-for-a-second-time-to-address-grok-deepfakes-212151712.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0a6c06b-3e97-4086-bf22-8cfdc6be3dba</guid>
      <description>The Senate has passed the Disrupt Explicit Forged Images and Non-Consensual Edits (DEFIANCE ) Act with unanimous consent, according to the bill&#8217;s co-sponsor Senator Dick Durbin (D-IL). The bill lets the subjects of nonconsensual, sexually explicit deepfakes take civil action against the people who create and host them.Deepfakes are a known issue online,  but without the proper protections, easy access to AI-powered image and video generation tools has made it possible for anyone to create compromising content using another person's likeness. This has become a particular problem on X, where the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8217;28 Years Later: The Bone Temple&#8217; Is Smaller, Gorier, and More Fun Than Its Predecessor</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/28-years-later-the-bone-temple-is-smaller-gorier-and-more-fun-than-its-predecessor-2000709678</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709678</guid>
      <description>Ralph Fiennes and Jack O'Connell star in the zombie sequel directed by Nia DaCosta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marc Andreessen to Tech Founders: &#8216;Raise Prices, Raise Prices, Raise Prices&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marc-andreessen-to-tech-founders-raise-prices-raise-prices-raise-prices-2000709835</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709835</guid>
      <description>Just what the consumer wants to hear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bone Temple turns 28 Years Later into a terrifying crisis of faith</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/859756/28-years-later-the-bone-temple-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859756</guid>
      <description>Because there was such a long gap between the releases of 28 Weeks Later and 28 Years Later, it was surprising to hear that writer-director duo Alex Garland and Danny Boyle already had plans for their latest collaboration to be the first chapter of a new horror trilogy. Sony seemed keen on fast-tracking the pair's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I heard, and felt, Victrola's new 'soundbase for turntables' speaker &#8212; and this risky idea just might work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/speakers/i-heard-and-felt-victrolas-new-soundbase-for-turntables-speaker-and-this-risky-idea-just-might-work</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HyhPiEJkZUgLdQQfLzucQE</guid>
      <description>A beefy speaker you rest your turntable on top of, but vibrations aren't really a concern, based on my time with it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s why TikTok says vegans can eat bacon</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473079/heres-why-tiktok-says-vegans-can-eat-bacon</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473079/heres-why-tiktok-says-vegans-can-eat-bacon</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s part of a new trend that champions going halfway on your goals.
If you&#8217;ve already given up on your 2026 rebrand because you couldn&#8217;t stick to your six gym sessions a week and no-sweet-treats resolutions, adopting a &#8220;vegan plus bacon&#8221; mindset may be the answer to all your problems.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 Years Later: The Bone Temple review: Nia DaCosta delivers an exhilarating horror epic</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/28-years-later-bone-temple-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Pm9JZ8Vl2TxKu5G6LJGAA</guid>
      <description>Nia DaCosta delivers an exhilarating horror epic with "28 Years Later: The Bone Temple." Review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dont buy the Roadster if safety is your goal, says Elon Musk</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/elon-musk-tesla-roadster-safety-not-a-priority</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03U56yLP3gYJIw7k3IzYjRQ</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is making more wild claims about Tesla's upcoming Roadster vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes a bill that would let nonconsensual deepfake victims sue</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861531/defiance-act-senate-passage-deepfakes-grok</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:53:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861531</guid>
      <description>The Senate passed a bill that could give people who've found their likeness deepfaked into sexually-explicit images without their consent a new way to fight back. The Disrupt Explicit Forged Images and Non-Consensual Edits Act (DEFIANCE Act), would let victims sue the individuals who created the images for civil damages. The bill passed with unanimous [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best phone to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:51:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</guid>
      <description>Haven&#8217;t you heard? Phones are boring now. And that&#8217;s just fine! Most people buying a new phone just want something familiar that works better than the device they&#8217;re replacing. If that&#8217;s your MO, then you&#8217;re sure to find something reliable in my recommendations below. But even if you&#8217;re looking for something a little more extra, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing the GMKtec NucBox M5 Ultra made me realize just how flexible an entry-level mini PC can be</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gmktec-nucbox-m5-ultra-mini-pc-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ApoJjhCPLumCY6LYgjdnMM</guid>
      <description>The GMKTec M5 Ultra delivers plenty of functionality at an affordable price for those willing to source their own memory, storage and OS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple just straight up robbed Google</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474359/apple-just-straight-up-robbed-google</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474359/apple-just-straight-up-robbed-google</guid>
      <description>Apple didn&#8217;t lose the AI race to Google. It won the chance to show us what &#8216;Apple Intelligence&#8217; might actually look like.
A few weeks ago, my iPhone woke me up at 3:30am.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there an iOS 26 backlash? Not so fast.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/apple-ios-26-adoption</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03FG8gESrk4yRNj8UNP6gX8</guid>
      <description>Apple's new iPhone operating system, iOS 26, seems unpopular with users. That may be so, but don't believe everything you read.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give the Internet an Infinite Word Search and the Internet Will Draw a Dick on It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/give-the-internet-an-infinite-word-search-and-the-internet-will-draw-a-dick-on-it-2000709697</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709697</guid>
      <description>Because of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Book a Hotel on the Moon? This Startup Is Now Taking $250K Deposits</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/want-to-book-a-hotel-on-the-moon-this-startup-is-now-taking-250k-deposits-2000709632</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709632</guid>
      <description>An upcoming space tech startup is looking to build the first hotel on the lunar surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic shakes up C-suite to expand its internal incubator</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/861475/anthropic-ai-c-suite-internal-incubator-labs-team-mike-krieger</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861475</guid>
      <description>Mike Krieger, the Instagram co-founder who joined Anthropic two years ago as its chief product officer, is moving to a new focus at the AI startup: co-leading its internal incubator, dubbed the "Labs" team. The Anthropic Labs team started in mid-2024 with just two members; now, the company has decided to expand it, with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
