<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:30:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Apple and Google reportedly still offer dozens of AI &#8216;nudify&#8217; apps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/apple-and-google-reportedly-still-offer-dozens-of-ai-nudify-apps-192712446.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3483249-cac8-4770-aa8a-036a5118cd6d</guid>
      <description>A recent investigation by an online advocacy organization called the Tech Transparency Project (TTP) found that the Apple App Store and Google Play Store are rife with so-called "nudify" apps. These are AI applications that create nonconsensual and sexualized images, which is a clear violation of both companies' store policies.
All told, the investigation found 55 of this type of app in the Google Play Store and 47 in the Apple App Store. Both platforms also still offer access to xAI's Grok, which is likely the most famous nonconsensual deepfake maker in the world.
"Apple and Google are suppos...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon UK slashes the price of Blink, Ring, Fire TV, Kindle and Echo devices &#8212; here are the 12 best deals I'd buy from &#163;13.99 to upgrade my home</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/amazon-uk-slashes-the-price-of-blink-ring-fire-tv-kindle-and-echo-devices-here-are-the-12-best-deals-id-buy-from-gbp13-99-to-upgrade-my-home</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xo5fxg6rceYHuFCLBW3y2b</guid>
      <description>There's a big sale on Amazon Devices right now at Amazon UK, so I've gathered together 12 of the best deals on smart home tech and gadgets starting from &#163;13.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Alexa+ Is Now Available to Everyone. Here&#8217;s How to Turn It Off (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/alexa-plus-early-access-rollout-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6971123a9ce7149baee42b25</guid>
      <description>Alexa+ has been rolling out to everyone with a Prime membership, even if you didn't ask for it. Here's how to change it back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is AI adoption at work flatlining? This major survey thinks so - but it's definitely not the end just yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/is-ai-adoption-at-work-flatlining-this-major-survey-thinks-so-but-its-definitely-not-the-end-just-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZBWeufrAsex8efX932CDt8</guid>
      <description>The number of people using AI might be flatlining, but it looks like we'll see more uses cases develop next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos introduces Amp Multi for complicated residential installs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/sonos-introduces-amp-multi-for-complicated-residential-installs-191000421.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61b9fdd2-95a6-4818-be19-8af52e686d49</guid>
      <description>Sonos has unveiled its first new product of 2026, the Amp Multi. This amplifier is a niche option for the owners of very large or complicated spaces, and it's being billed as professional grade option for residential audio installations. The Amp Multi has eight 125W outputs and four configurable zones, and each channel can support up to three Sonos Architectural speakers. In other words, that's a lot more audio than the average home needs. Even the Sonos Amp would probably be overkill for those of you living the apartment life.The Amp Multi will be available "in the coming months," according t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Puppet Girl&#8217; of &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; on Doing a Performance Within a Performance</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-puppet-girl-of-a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-on-doing-a-performance-within-a-performance-2000713659</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713659</guid>
      <description>Tanzyn Crawford plays Tanselle, a Dornish artist, in the new 'Game of Thrones' spin-off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting Against Elon Musk&#8217;s Predictions on Polymarket Might be the New Inverse Cramer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/betting-against-elon-musks-predictions-on-polymarket-might-be-the-new-inverse-cramer-2000714552</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714552</guid>
      <description>Easy money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA home office trends for 2026: freshen up your workspace with sage green and crisp white &#8212; from just $5</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/ikea-home-office-trends-for-2026-freshen-up-your-workspace-with-sage-green-and-crisp-white-from-just-usd5</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VMVMhBdb8z5fEK358dNxnC</guid>
      <description>IKEA's latest collection of office accessories, lighting, and furniture will bring a breath of spring to your working day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's no telescope this large ever built. It's not like we have a precedent for how to do these things,' Giant Magellan Telescope engineers on why they used the Unreal Engine to build an unprecedented telescope simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/inside-giant-magellan-telescopes-unreal-engine-based-bob-simulation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hou6mqdtLb7qJPWfafxCb3</guid>
      <description>The Giant Magellan Telescope under construction in Chile will help us find exoplanets &#8212; but before that, there's a complete, operating replica built in Unreal Engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon shutters all of its physical Go and Fresh stores</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868800/amazon-go-and-fresh-stores-closed</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:55:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868800</guid>
      <description>Amazon Go and Fresh physical store locations will soon be no more, with Amazon announcing on Tuesday that it's closing up the majority of the stores and converting others into Whole Foods Market locations. Customers will still be able to order from Amazon Fresh online, but won't be able to shop at physical stores with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Feature-Packed Earbuds Are Less Than $50</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/anker-soundcore-a40-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6978fedb7a840e550e16b6df</guid>
      <description>Anker knocks almost half the cost off its already budget-friendly earbuds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cet &#233;cran PC gamer 34&#8243; MSI ultra-&#233;quip&#233; (QD-OLED, 240 Hz) ne d&#233;passe pas les 700 &#8364; pendant ces soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2956395_cet-ecran-pc-gamer-34-msi-ultra-equipe-qd-oled-240-hz-ne-depasse-pas-les-700-e-pendant-ces-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2956395_cet-ecran-pc-gamer-34-msi-ultra-equipe-qd-oled-240-hz-ne-depasse-pas-les-700-e-pendant-ces-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Pour profiter d'une exp&#233;rience de jeu bien fluide et r&#233;active, il n'y a pas de myst&#232;re : un moniteur gaming dot&#233; d'une configuration solide est indispensable. Le MSI MPG 341CQPX en est justement un, et pendant les soldes d'hiver 2026, vous le trouverez affich&#233; &#224; 699,99 euros au lieu de 999,99 euros chez Darty et Cdiscount.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The French government is ditching Zoom and Microsoft Teams for a home-grown alternative</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/the-french-government-is-ditching-zoom-and-microsoft-teams-for-a-home-grown-alternative-184747010.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcbd4ff3-d78b-43ce-93fe-c75bd8f27a1f</guid>
      <description>The French government is saying au revoir to Microsoft Teams and Zoom as it embraces a home-grown alternative. By next year, civil servants across all departments will have switched to French videoconference platform Visio, as EuroNews reports.As with Teams and Zoom, Visio has an AI-powered transcription tool. Visio runs on a French company's cloud infrastructure as well. The platform has around 40,000 users and it's been in testing for the last year. The government expects the switch to help reduce costs by as much as &#8364;1 million ($1.2 million) each year for every 100,000 users.The decision to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok settles to avoid major social media addiction lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/tiktok-settles-to-avoid-major-social-media-addiction-lawsuit-183943927.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abcc6c37-37ca-4e5e-8875-a91aaac1cd59</guid>
      <description>TikTok has reached a settlement in a closely-watched lawsuit over social media addiction, narrowly avoiding a trial that's scheduled to begin jury selection Tuesday. Terms of the deal, which was reported by The New York Times, weren't disclosed.&#160;TikTok's settlement comes about one week after Snap reached a settlement in the same case. The trial is expected to move forward in Los Angeles with Meta and YouTube as the only defendants. Mark Lanier, a lawyer for the plaintiff, said in a statement to NYT that they were "pleased" with the settlement and that it was "a good resolution." TikTok didn't ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State-Led Crackdown on Grok and xAI Has Begun</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-state-led-crackdown-on-grok-and-xai-has-begun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965700bc9e9698ec20c258f</guid>
      <description>At least 37 attorneys general for US states and territories are taking action against xAI after Grok generated a flood of nonconsensual sexual images of women and minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;An issue that has gone unaddressed for too long': Major US city takes bold decision to ban single-use printer cartridges but will others follow suit?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/an-issue-that-has-gone-unaddressed-for-too-long-major-us-city-takes-bold-decision-to-ban-single-use-printer-cartridges-but-will-others-follow-suit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7PCKjmdvbXbe9hy4uz7vNH</guid>
      <description>A proposed ban on single-use ink cartridges in Los Angeles exposes the hidden environmental and financial cost of home printing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Data Shows Robotaxis Competing on Price&#8212;and Speed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-data-shows-robotaxis-competing-on-price-and-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977aa218ad4d08d0dc3c326</guid>
      <description>Research from the ride-hail aggregator Obi finds Waymo is starting to edge up on Uber and Lyft in San Francisco. Tesla, which operates a ride-hail service with human drivers, is winning the price wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A former Netflix game studio went indie to reach more players</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/868711/spry-fox-netflix-game-studio-indie-spirit-crossing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868711</guid>
      <description>When Netflix first acquired cozy game developer Spry Fox in 2022, it made a lot of sense. The studio had been around for over a decade and had several hits with mobile games like Triple Town and Alphabear. That approachable style of puzzle game seemed like a good fit for Netflix's mobile-first strategy, and, as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philip Glass cancels Kennedy Center symphony premiere to protest Trump&#8217;s leadership</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481979/philip-glass-kennedy-center-cancellations</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481979/philip-glass-kennedy-center-cancellations</guid>
      <description>Glass was a Kennedy Center honoree in 2018.
Prize-winning composer Philip Glass has called off a scheduled world premiere at the&#160;Kennedy Center&#160;of a symphony about Abraham Lincoln, the latest in a wave of cancellations since&#160;President Donald Trump&#160;ousted the previous leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An app developer is suing Apple for Sherlocking it with Continuity Camera</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868740/apple-reincubate-lawsuit-camo-continuity-camera</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:25:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868740</guid>
      <description>Reincubate, which makes the Camo and Camo Studio apps for turning your iOS or Android phone into a webcam for your Mac or PC, is suing Apple, alleging anticompetitive conduct and patent infringement. Camo first launched in 2020, but two years after, Apple launched a similar feature called Continuity Camera, which works just with Apple [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic and OpenAI CEOs condemn ICE violence, praise Trump</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/anthropic-and-openai-ceos-condemn-ice-violence-praise-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086660</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's Dario Amodei and OpenAI's Sam Altman spoke out against ICE enforcement tactics following Minneapolis violence, with one addressing concerns publicly and the other in an internal message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Is Blocking Links To ICE List on Facebook, Instagram, and Threads</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/meta-is-blocking-links-to-ice-list-on-facebook-instagram-and-threads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6978dd298a2e73820b9b99b2</guid>
      <description>Users of Meta&#8217;s social platforms can no longer share links to ICE List, a website listing what it claims are the names of thousands of DHS employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s foldable 3-in-1 charging station has hit a new low price of $50</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/868696/anker-maggo-wireless-charging-station-foldable-3-in-1-lego-roses-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:08:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868696</guid>
      <description>Buying separate chargers for your phone, watch, and earbuds adds up quickly. Anker&#8217;s MagGo Wireless Charging Station (Foldable 3-in-1) replaces all three, and now through January 30th it&#8217;s just $49.99 ($60 off) at Amazon-owned Woot. That&#8217;s the best price we&#8217;ve seen, and cheaper than many chargers designed for just one device. The charging station delivers [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Go and Fresh stores are closing as Amazon focuses on grocery delivery and Whole Foods</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/amazon-go-and-fresh-stores-are-closing-as-amazon-focuses-on-grocery-delivery-and-whole-foods-180448412.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd490677-0c7f-4d7b-a6bc-00afe8c1157b</guid>
      <description>Amazon is rethinking its grocery business, and as part of that, it will shut down all of its remaining Amazon Go and Amazon Fresh physical stores. The company will convert some locations into Whole Foods Market stores.&#160;"While we've seen encouraging signals in our Amazon-branded physical grocery stores, we haven't yet created a truly distinctive customer experience with the right economic model needed for large-scale expansion," the company wrote in a blog post. Amazon added that it would help workers at Go and Fresh stores to find positions elsewhere within the company.For now, Amazon is focus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp&amp;#8217;s new &amp;#8216;lockdown&amp;#8217; settings add another layer of protection against cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868722/whatsapp-strict-account-settings-cyberattacks</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:01:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868722</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is launching new "Strict Account Settings" that add even more protections against cyberattacks. The feature is built for people at a high-risk of attacks - such as journalists or public figures - and automatically blocks attachments and media from senders you don't know, while silencing calls from unknown contacts. The new setting limits other [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Sue the White House Over an AI Deepfake?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/can-you-sue-the-white-house-over-an-ai-deepfake-2000714219</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714219</guid>
      <description>The Trump regime's abuse of AI has opened up new legal questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s more affordable AI Plus plan rolls out to all markets, including the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/googles-ai-plus-plan-rolls-out-to-all-markets-including-the-u-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086571</guid>
      <description>Gemini 3 Pro and other AI tools are now available globally through the Google AI Plus plan, which is $7.99 per month in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These New &#8216;KPop Demon Hunter&#8217; Toys Will Takedown Your Wallet</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kpop-demon-hunters-toys-merchandise-dolls-release-date-hasbro-mattell-2000714461</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714461</guid>
      <description>Hasbro and Mattel are taking 'KPop Demon Hunters' to the stores with dolls, NERF weapons, and even UNO and Monopoly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI launches Prism, a new AI workspace for scientists</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/openai-launches-prism-a-new-ai-workspace-for-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086665</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has launched a new scientific workspace program called Prism, which integrates AI into existing standards for composing research papers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases Prism, a Claude Code-like app for scientific research</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-releases-prism-a-claude-code-like-app-for-scientific-research-180000454.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a96e543-e735-4e89-8c6c-db959c08a68c</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is releasing a new app called Prism today, and it hopes it does for science what coding agents like Claude Code and its own Codex platform have done for programming.&#160;Prism builds on Crixet, a cloud-based LaTeX platform the company is announcing it acquired today. For the uninitiated, LaTeX is a typesetting system for formatting scientific documents and journals. Nearly the entire scientific community relies on LaTeX, but it can make some tasks, such as drawing diagrams through TikZ commands, time-consuming to do. Beyond that, LaTeX is just one of the software tools a scientist might tur...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google AI Plus is now available in the US for $8 a month</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-ai-plus-is-now-available-in-the-us-for-8-a-month-180000175.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbd3aae1-4c4f-433c-abf9-d2d04959ae4e</guid>
      <description>Google AI Plus, the company&#8217;s most affordable AI subscription plan, is now rolling out in the US. It will cost you $8 a month for its features, though you can get it for $4 a month for the first two months for a limited time only. AI Plus gives you access to 200GB of storage, as well as access to the Gemini 3 Pro model, Deep Research and Nano Banana Pro inside the Gemini app. Nano Banana Pro generates images that look so realistic, they&#8217;re nearly indistinguishable from ordinary photos snapped on phones. Google even had to limit its usage due to high demand. A subscription to AI Plus also expan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CEOs pushing back on ICE could be &#8216;a tipping point&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479325/the-dean-of-minneapolis-business-hopes-ceos-pushing-back-on-ice-is-a-tipping-point</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479325/the-dean-of-minneapolis-business-hopes-ceos-pushing-back-on-ice-is-a-tipping-point</guid>
      <description>After weeks of silence, 60 of the state&#8217;s business leaders issued a call for &#8216;de-escalation&#8217; that&#8217;s been criticized as too weak. A long-time former Minneapolis CEO provides insight on the statement.
ICE&#8217;s occupation in Minnesota has lasted weeks, and until a couple of days ago, the state&#8217;s major corporations, quick to issue statements in wake of George Floyd&#8217;s shooting in 2020, had been largely silent. When Fast Company reached out to several heavy hitters in mid-January, including Target and Best Buy, there was no response.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to train your brain like your muscles, according to a neurologist</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480126/how-to-train-your-brain-like-your-muscles-neurologist</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480126/how-to-train-your-brain-like-your-muscles-neurologist</guid>
      <description>Just like muscles, the brain has limits. 
If you have ever lifted a weight, you know the routine: challenge the muscle, give it rest, feed it, and repeat. Over time, it grows stronger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid Trump attacks and weaponized sanctions, Europeans look to rely less on US tech</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/amid-trump-attacks-and-weaponized-sanctions-europeans-look-to-rely-less-on-us-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086633</guid>
      <description>European governments are looking to move away from U.S. tech and reclaim their digital sovereignty at a time of unpredictability and volatility in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert Insights</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tag/trpc</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GngCbbjotX4e9F6KRjvN3J</guid>
      <description>All TechRadar Pro stories tagged TRPC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 products that transformed my business trips from chaotic to super productive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/14-products-that-transformed-my-business-trips-from-chaotic-to-super-productive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gBgkEURSsuKjKNLSieZSie</guid>
      <description>From getting lost in the back streets of Paris to epic delays caused by volcanoes, I've had plenty of adventures whilst working away from home. Now, I have curated a list of the products I wouldn't leave home without.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos lance son premier nouveau produit depuis plus d&#8217;un an</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sonos/2957269_sonos-lance-son-premier-nouveau-produit-depuis-plus-dun-an</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sonos/2957269_sonos-lance-son-premier-nouveau-produit-depuis-plus-dun-an</guid>
      <description>
Vous vous souvenez de Sonos ? Apr&#232;s une ann&#233;e de silence radio et un fiasco logiciel qui a co&#251;t&#233; sa place au patron, la marque revient enfin aux affaires.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to add Freely's free streaming to your existing TV? This 4K HDR box might be the perfect upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/want-to-add-freelys-free-streaming-to-your-existing-tv-this-4k-hdr-box-might-be-the-perfect-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HGLSJ2uYeuFMDDKVmjHkPM</guid>
      <description>Free channels, regular streaming services, and TiVo's software &#8211; but should it be cheaper?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The price gap between Waymo and Uber is narrowing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/the-price-gap-between-waymo-and-uber-is-narrowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086568</guid>
      <description>Data collected and analyzed by Obi suggest a shift is underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This popular free YouTube function could be locked into its paid Premium plan &#8212; and I won't be happy if I have to sign up for another subscription service</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/this-popular-free-youtube-function-could-be-locked-into-its-paid-premium-plan-and-i-wont-be-happy-if-i-have-to-sign-up-for-another-subscription-service</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wNfPn2efh3Z2xYdWEW73zX</guid>
      <description>A new YouTube experiment shows that its free-to-use playback-speed tool could be locked into the YouTube Premium plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp introduces an advanced security mode to protect against hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/whatsapp-introduces-an-advanced-security-mode-to-protect-against-hackers-174144598.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5143d3f4-1bde-4508-8633-31f5c71dfb6e</guid>
      <description>Meta's WhatsApp just introduced something called Strict Account Settings, a tool "that further protects your account from highly sophisticated cyber attacks." This is a one-click button in the settings that automatically initiates a series of defenses.
So what does it do? It blocks media and attachments from unknown senders, disables link previews and silences calls from unknown senders. This results in a more restrictive experience, but hopefully a safer one.
The company says this isn't necessarily for regular users, as conversations are already protected by end-to-end encryption. Instead, th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: This free VPN extension was hijacking CyberGhost's free servers &#8211; here's what it means for your privacy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/exclusive-this-free-vpn-extension-was-hijacking-cyberghosts-free-servers-heres-what-it-means-for-your-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RJLszg42BcpEEmAUBaAiBd</guid>
      <description>TechRadar experts discovered that the 'BiuBiu VPN' Chrome extension was misusing CyberGhost&#8217;s resources. Here's all we know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Walking Pad Deals: Save $150 and More (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/walking-pad-deals-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977a8d38ad4d08d0dc3c325</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re working from home or just trying to hit your step goals, these walking pad deals make it easy to move every day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe finally adds a Clarity and Dehaze layer to Photoshop &#8211; and I can't believe it took this long</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/adobe-finally-adds-a-clarity-and-dehaze-layer-to-photoshop-and-i-cant-believe-it-took-this-long</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">v6NfHvP9y9ZNuPhomzomq6</guid>
      <description>"Control, realism, and precision" - the latest Photoshop updates from Adobe target fast-paced creative professional workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un drone 4K &#224; moins de 200 &#8364; ? C&#8217;est possible pendant les soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957085_un-drone-4k-a-moins-de-200-e-cest-possible-pendant-les-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957085_un-drone-4k-a-moins-de-200-e-cest-possible-pendant-les-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Le drone Potensic ATOM SE est un drone grand public l&#233;ger, &#233;quip&#233; d'un capteur 4K, fourni avec une t&#233;l&#233;commande et surtout propos&#233; &#224; un prix tr&#232;s attractif. Pendant les soldes d'hiver, AliExpress l'affiche &#224; 181,69 euros avec ses accessoires, alors que le bundle &#233;tait auparavant vendu &#224; environ 300 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you live in the UK, you probably won&#8217;t be able to visit Pornhub anymore</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/if-you-live-in-the-uk-you-probably-wont-be-able-to-visit-pornhub-anymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086598</guid>
      <description>Pornhub parent company Aylo will restrict access from U.K. users, rather than comply with age verification mandates, which the company said it believes have not succeeded in promoting online safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Swears It Didn&#8217;t Ban Sharing the Name &#8216;Epstein,&#8217; as Gavin Newsom Announces Investigation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tiktok-swears-it-didnt-ban-sharing-the-name-epstein-as-gavin-newsom-announces-investigation-2000714521</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714521</guid>
      <description>The scrutiny follows a rocky first week under new U.S. ownership./</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
