<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:29:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>VCs deploy &#8216;kingmaking&#8217; strategy to crown AI winners in their infancy</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/vcs-deploy-kingmaking-strategy-to-crown-ai-winners-in-their-infancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071641</guid>
      <description>While VCs have long used big investments to spur category winners, they are taking this strategy to new extremes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fantastic Breville Barista Express is still at a record-low price after Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/the-fantastic-breville-barista-express-is-still-at-a-record-low-price-after-black-friday</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wTn8iipN2rxAisfvMn4sRM</guid>
      <description>The Breville Barista Express is a premium coffee machine with a new tasty discount still available after Black Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&amp;#8217;s head of UI design is leaving for Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837654/apple-meta-alan-dye-designer</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T15:13:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837654</guid>
      <description>Alan Dye, who has led Apple&#8217;s UI design team since 2015, is leaving to join Meta as its chief design officer, Bloomberg reports. He&#8217;ll join Meta on December 31st, and Meta is opening a design studio and giving Dye oversight of design for &#8220;hardware, software and AI integration for its interfaces,&#8221; according to Bloomberg. Dye [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean 'fake worker' scheme caught live on camera</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/north-korean-fake-worker-scheme-caught-live-on-camera</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pPkykhbEtn4DQsEwJusT6c</guid>
      <description>Researchers trapped Lazarus operators with sandbox environments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des astronomes ont retrouv&#233; la trace de deux &#233;toiles qui sont pass&#233;es pr&#232;s du Syst&#232;me solaire !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/etoile-astronomes-ont-retrouve-trace-deux-etoiles-sont-passees-pres-systeme-solaire-128171/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 21:07:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/etoile-astronomes-ont-retrouve-trace-deux-etoiles-sont-passees-pres-systeme-solaire-128171/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Elles semblent fixes dans notre ciel. Pourtant, toutes les &#233;toiles sont en mouvement. Et deux d&#8217;entre elles ont rendu une visite &#224; notre Soleil. C&#8217;&#233;tait il y a plus de 4&#160;millions d&#8217;ann&#233;es. Mais les traces sont toujours l&#224;&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coup de tonnerre chez Apple&#160;: le patron du design file chez Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/coup-de-tonnerre-chez-apple-le-patron-du-design-file-chez-meta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1313617</guid>
      <description>C'est un sacr&#233; coup dur pour Apple, qui n'arrive d&#233;cid&#233;ment plus &#224; retenir ses talents. La firme &#224; la pomme subit une nouvelle d&#233;fection majeure avec le d&#233;part d'Alan Dye, le patron du design des interfaces. Il rejoint Meta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;End-to-end encrypted&#8217; smart toilet camera is not actually end-to-end encrypted</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/end-to-end-encrypted-smart-toilet-camera-is-not-actually-end-to-end-encrypted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072343</guid>
      <description>Kohler, the makers of a smart toilet camera, can access customers' data stored on its servers, and can use customers&#8217; bowl pictures to train AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company backed by Donald Trump Jr.&#8217;s firm nabs $620M government contract</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/company-backed-by-donald-trump-jr-s-firm-nabs-620m-government-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072196</guid>
      <description>Vulcan Elements, a rare-earth magnets startup, has secured a $620 million contract from the U.S. defense department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Nova Forge could be your company's cue to start building custom AI models</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/aws-nova-forge-could-be-your-companys-cue-to-start-building-custom-ai-models</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">REJjLQmnAhEAMYBv7hZjp3</guid>
      <description>AWS has a host of new AI models, and a brand-new way to build and customize them exactly how you like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are my 25 favorite deals from REI&#8217;s Cyber Week sale</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/837519/best-rei-cyber-week-sale-2025-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:49:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837519</guid>
      <description>REI took a hike during Black Friday, but the retailer is back with a full week of deals. Now through December 8th, REI is hosting a Cyber Week sale that offers big discounts on gadgets and gear designed for the outdoors. If you&#8217;re planning to hit the slopes this winter, now&#8217;s a good time to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William Shatner&#8217;s View of the Prime Directive Is Pure Kirk</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/william-shatner-star-trek-prime-directive-kirk-2000695209</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695209</guid>
      <description>Speaking at a recent 'Star Trek' convention, the star argued that the franchise's most fundamental rule is made to be broken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Pete Gets a Pass for Signalgate</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/report-pete-gets-a-pass-for-signalgate-2000695193</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695193</guid>
      <description>Republicans are already spinning the report as a "nothing burger."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After NYC implemented congestion pricing, Chicago became America&#8217;s worst city for traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453455/chicago-traffic-worse-than-nyc-congestion-pricing</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453455/chicago-traffic-worse-than-nyc-congestion-pricing</guid>
      <description>A new report from transportation analytics company INRIX shows people are spending more time in their cars in major cities across the country.
If you feel like you spent more time sitting in traffic this year than last, you&#8217;re not alone.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was hoping for Babel Fish realtime audio translation, and while the InnAIO AI Translator T9is impressive, it's not there yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/innaio-ai-translator-t9-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">J22jjGG5QadqDk7jUnPgcR</guid>
      <description>This compact device uses a MagSafe connector to attach to your phone and then utilises an app to provide voice-to-voice, voice-to-text, photo and text translation to a huge variety of languages in almost, but not quite, real time. What's more, it's able to use an AI version of your own voice for audio playback in different languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTubers Are Making AI Slop for Babies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youtubers-are-making-ai-slop-for-babies-2000695171</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695171</guid>
      <description>As if usual content for children isn't bad enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify&#160;Wrapped&#8217;s genius marketing taps into individuality and belonging</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453511/spotify-wrapped-genius-marketing</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453511/spotify-wrapped-genius-marketing</guid>
      <description>Spotify Wrapped works because it nails the balance between competing needs: the desire to belong and the desire to stand out. 
Even before this year&#8217;s Spotify Wrapped dropped, I had a hunch what mine would reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation is making an MLB The Show mobile game</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837614/sony-playstation-mlb-the-show-mobile-game</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:19:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837614</guid>
      <description>MLB The Show is coming to iOS and Android. Sony has revealed MLB The Show Mobile, which it says is &#8220;a new standalone experience built from the ground up to deliver realistic baseball gameplay on mobile devices.&#8221;&#160; The game is live now only in the Philippines (here&#8217;s a Google Play link for the game), and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This haptic mattress topper lets you feel a movie while you fall asleep during it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837482/woojer-haptic-wellness-mat-vibrations-bluetooth</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:15:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837482</guid>
      <description>Woojer is best known for its vibrating vests and belt straps that let you feel the sounds from games, movies, and music. Now the company has taken that same haptic technology and incorporated it into a new mattress topper called the Woojer Mat that will let you feel those same vibrations across your entire body [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 best noise-cancelling headphones we use, love, and recommend</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/roundup/best-noise-cancelling-headphones-2025-tested</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07AzGC7S8pr0ZUfRemujF71</guid>
      <description>We put the top noise-cancelling headphones and earbuds from Bose, Sony, and Apple to the test. Overall, Sony has the best active noise cancellation in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tonight, the future of deep tech will be explained to you at StrictlyVC Palo Alto</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/tonight-the-future-of-deep-tech-will-be-explained-to-you-at-strictlyvc-palo-alto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071117</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday evening at Playground Global in Palo Alto, some very smart people who are building things you don't understand yet will explain what's coming. This is the final StrictlyVC event of 2025, and truly, the lineup is ridiculous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market hovers near all-time high on Fed rate cut expectations and retail rally</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453620/stocks-markets-near-all-time-high-interest-rates-retail-biotech</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T19:09:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453620/stocks-markets-near-all-time-high-interest-rates-retail-biotech</guid>
      <description>American Eagle Outfitters was another winner and rallied 16.1% after the retailer reported a better profit than expected.
The U.S. stock market is drifting near its record levels on Wednesday following mixed reactions to profit reports from&#160;Macy&#8217;s, Marvell Technologies, and other companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crucial is shutting down &#8212; because Micron wants to sell its RAM and SSDs to AI companies instead</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837594/crucial-ram-ssd-micron-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:01:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837594</guid>
      <description>Micron is retiring the Crucial brand, marking the end of its line of budget-friendly solid-state drives (SSDs) and RAM kits, as reported earlier by VideoCardz. In an announcement on Wednesday, Micron says winding down its consumer-focused business will &#8220;improve supply and support for our larger, strategic customers in faster-growing segments&#8221; &#8212; a.k.a. AI companies. The [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI Dark Horse Is Rewriting the Rules of Game Design</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/tecent-3d-models-video-game-design-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692dd71d85bfdf284befa045</guid>
      <description>The Chinese video game giant Tencent is now building some of the world&#8217;s best 3D AI models. This could have implications far outside gaming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight Radiation Reached 20-Year High During Recent Solar Outburst, Scientists Confirm</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/flight-radiation-reached-20-year-high-during-recent-solar-outburst-scientists-confirm-2000695147</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695147</guid>
      <description>And as Airbus reminded us last week, we're not ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fintech firm Marquis alerts dozens of US banks and credit unions of a data breach after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/fintech-firm-marquis-alerts-dozens-of-us-banks-and-credit-unions-of-a-data-breach-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072283</guid>
      <description>Marquis said ransomware hackers stole reams of banking customer data, containing personal information and financial records, as well as Social Security numbers, belonging to hundreds of thousands of people. The number of affected people is expected to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Are Back in Theaters This Month</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ninja-turtles-short-film-sequel-chrome-alone-2-interview-2000694698</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694698</guid>
      <description>'Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Chrome Alone 2 - Lost in New Jersey' is a short film coming to theaters December 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 more cookware products could be poisoning your food with lead: FDA expands list of dangerous kitchen ware</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453523/9-more-cookware-products-could-be-poisoning-your-food-with-lead-fda-expands-list-of-dangerous-kitchen-ware-recall-warning</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453523/9-more-cookware-products-could-be-poisoning-your-food-with-lead-fda-expands-list-of-dangerous-kitchen-ware-recall-warning</guid>
      <description>The agency has issued yet another warning about certain brass and aluminum imported cookware that could be leaching toxic chemicals.
The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) has once again&#160;expanded its warning on certain&#160;brands of imported cookware, this time adding nine additional products that may leach significant levels of lead into food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek v3.2: Whats new and how does it compare to ChatGPT?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/deepseek-v3-2-models-released</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0200Hy2atk7kJZcrYC6qRuo</guid>
      <description>The Chinese AI startup DeepSeek has released not one but two new powerful AI models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best fitness trackers and watches we&#8217;ve tested</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T13:34:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker</guid>
      <description>Fitness trackers have come a long way from the simple bands that tracked steps and little else. Modern trackers can monitor everything from your heart health to how well you&#8217;ve recovered from a hard bout of training. Even flagship smartwatches, which used to be lackluster trackers, have become pretty adept workout companions. Whatever your fitness [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent says White House may &#8216;veto&#8217; Fed presidents under a new residency rule</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453612/federal-reserve-presidents-veto-trump-administration-bessent</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:33:12</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453612/federal-reserve-presidents-veto-trump-administration-bessent</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Vetoing&#8217; regional bank presidents would represent another effort by the Trump administration to exert more control over the Fed.
Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said Wednesday he would push a new requirement that the Federal Reserve&#8216;s regional bank presidents live in their districts for at least three years before taking office, a move that could give the White House more power over the&#160;independent agency....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ugly Pebble 2 Duo is the smartwatch for me</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/837388/pebble-2-duo-review</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837388</guid>
      <description>Smartwatches have become health gadgets. Over the last five years or so, Apple, Garmin, Google, Samsung, and practically every other company wanting to strap their wares to your wrist have emphasized exercise integrations, sleep tracking, hypertension monitoring, and more. The most expensive among these devices are also satellite communicators, because now that you have a [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People love this company&#8217;s automatic espresso machines. Can these new accessories make it an everything coffee brand?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452696/terra-kaffe-demi-aero-milk-frother-aeris-tumbler</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452696/terra-kaffe-demi-aero-milk-frother-aeris-tumbler</guid>
      <description>The brand is complementing its super-automatic coffee machines with a cold brew maker, a line of glassware, and a milk frother that can make matcha.
As the &#8220;fourth wave&#8221; of coffee begins to take shape, companies that are embracing modern&#8212;and, increasingly, automated&#8212;coffee making are working to balance their tech with the craft of brewing.&#160;Terra Kaffe is one of them....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic reportedly planning one of the biggest IPOs ever as race with OpenAI heats up</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453478/anthropic-ipo-ai-boom</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453478/anthropic-ipo-ai-boom</guid>
      <description>The Claude chatbot maker is said to be exploring a public listing that could top $300 billion in valuation, testing investor appetite for high-burn AI firms.
One of the world&#8217;s biggest AI startups might be eyeing a massive IPO.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
