<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:25:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The best Android phones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23674658/best-android-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T17:18:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23674658/best-android-phone</guid>
      <description>The Android ecosystem is all about choice. While iPhone owners have a smaller pool of new devices to pick from when it&#8217;s time to upgrade, there&#8217;s a wider range of choices on Android. Some Android phones even fold in half! Imagine. On the flip side, all that choice can make for some hard decisions. Here&#8217;s [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Oddly-Specific Monopoly Set Will Curb Your SDCC Travel Nightmares</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/monopoly-san-diego-edition-comic-con-2000700471</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700471</guid>
      <description>Of course 'Monopoly: San Diego Edition' includes multiple Comic-Con-related locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford Effectively Kills the Biden-Era Dream of All-Electric Trucks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ford-effectively-kills-the-biden-era-dream-of-all-electric-trucks-2000700476</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700476</guid>
      <description>The Ford F-150 Lightning was a symbol of the electric future in pickup truck form. It&#8217;s now dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best e-reader to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23769068/best-ebook-readers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T17:07:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23769068/best-ebook-readers</guid>
      <description>Any ebook reader will let you cram a Beauty and the Beast-sized library&#8217;s worth of books in your pocket, but so will your phone. An ebook reader offers a more book-like reading experience, with fewer distractions and less eye strain, and many include extra features, like adjustable frontlighting. Some really are pocketable. Others are waterproof [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first online chess game happened in December 1844 &#8212; Yes, 181 years ago, two teams played Chess 60km away using the electrical telegraph</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-first-online-chess-game-happened-in-december-1844-yes-181-years-ago-two-teams-played-chess-60km-away-using-the-electrical-telegraph</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4WiMi46imHo2NaE4yvi4SX</guid>
      <description>The 1844 Washington&#8211;Baltimore telegraph chess match started remote play, inspiring later international competitions, teletype games, and massive online platforms today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch NBA Cup Final 2025: live stream Spurs vs Knicks online from anywhere, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/basketball/nba-cup-final-2025-san-antonio-spurs-vs-new-york-knicks</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pjho5wZytpPUPchV9MNwVK</guid>
      <description>How to watch 2025 NBA Cup Final live streams online, with Victor Wembanyama and Jalen Brunson set to light up the Spurs vs Knicks clash in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiFlix shows us what Netflix would have been like 100 years ago</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/wikiflix-shows-us-what-netflix-would-have-been-like-100-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076595</guid>
      <description>On WikiFlix, a Netflix-inspired archive of public domain films, you can watch movies like "It's a Wonderful Life" and "Noseferatu" for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A vague study on Nazi bots created chaos in the Taylor Swift fan universe</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/845725/taylor-swift-gudea-report-rolling-stone-social-media-discourse-bots</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T16:30:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845725</guid>
      <description>On December 9th, Rolling Stone published a story that some saw as a bombshell: a network of coordinated, "inauthentic" social media accounts had a hand in the weekslong discourse that trailed the release of Taylor Swift's recent album, The Life of a Showgirl. It was a big deal for those in the Swiftie/anti-Swiftie universe. Immediately [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data&#8217;s in: And it says the job market is still rough</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461564/the-datas-in-and-it-says-the-job-market-is-still-rough</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461564/the-datas-in-and-it-says-the-job-market-is-still-rough</guid>
      <description>The new jobs report confirms what many workers likely already know: Most employers aren&#8217;t hiring. What does this mean for people who are job hunting? 
The latest employment numbers have dropped&#8212;and the job market still looks tough for workers.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIFA lowers some World Cup ticket prices to $60 after fan backlash</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461657/fifa-world-cup-tickets-60-fan-backlash</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461657/fifa-world-cup-tickets-60-fan-backlash</guid>
      <description>The number of $60 tickets for each game is likely to be in the hundreds, rather than thousands.
FIFA slashed the price of some World Cup tickets for teams&#8217; most loyal fans following a global backlash and some will get $60 seats for the final instead of being asked to pay $4,185.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 16-inch battery-powered portable monitor has a higher resolution than the Liquid Retina XDR display on the Apple MacBook Pro &#8212; and it will last at least 6 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-16-inch-battery-powered-portable-monitor-has-a-higher-resolution-than-the-liquid-retina-xdr-display-on-the-apple-macbook-pro-and-it-will-last-at-least-6-hours</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FohfxJcsh28Nh9CcJVadRD</guid>
      <description>VChance DU16 is a 16-inch 4K portable monitor with HDR, aluminum build, battery operation, USB-C connectivity, and professional usability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New &#8216;CRASH Clock&#8217; Warns of 2.8-Day Window Before Likely Orbital Collision</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-crash-clock-warns-of-2-8-day-window-before-likely-orbital-collision-2000700374</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700374</guid>
      <description>The CRASH Clock is a new metric for measuring the risks of satellite congestion in low-Earth orbit. Its calculations are disturbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Defaults Free Users to Cheapest Model to Cut Back on Costs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-defaults-free-users-to-cheapest-model-to-cut-back-on-costs-2000700346</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700346</guid>
      <description>They're betting people won't notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraft Heinz gets a new CEO ahead of company split: Can Steve Cahillane turn around the ailing food giant?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461623/kraft-heinz-gets-a-new-ceo-ahead-of-company-split-can-steve-cahillane-turn-around-the-ailing-food-giant</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461623/kraft-heinz-gets-a-new-ceo-ahead-of-company-split-can-steve-cahillane-turn-around-the-ailing-food-giant</guid>
      <description>The former head of Kellanova is taking the helm after years of declining sales and slow growth, with stock down 75% since 2017.
Kraft Heinz announced on Tuesday that new CEO Steve Cahillane will join the food giant to help steer its split into two companies. The former head of Kellanova joins the ailing food giant after years of declining sales and slow growth, and as shares are down 75% since 2017....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What tech would the Fallout cast steal from the show?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/fallout-season-2-interview-walton-goggins-aaron-moten-geneva-robertson</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">067F4AQuUf90QvzrPBdGacN</guid>
      <description>What technology would "Fallout" stars Walton Goggins, Aaron Moten, and showrunner Geneva Robertson-Dworet want in their lives?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X updates its terms, files countersuit to lay claim to the &#8216;Twitter&#8217; trademark after newcomer&#8217;s challenge</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/x-updates-its-terms-files-countersuit-to-lay-claim-to-the-twitter-trademark-after-newcomers-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076669</guid>
      <description>X's new terms of service say that no one can use the Twitter name, trademarks, logos, and more without written consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford is canceling the F-150 Lightning in a major EV pullback, but don&#8217;t count U.S. electric vehicles out yet</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461285/ford-cancels-f-150-lightning-american-ev-industry-dead</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:01:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461285/ford-cancels-f-150-lightning-american-ev-industry-dead</guid>
      <description>Although the sector&#8217;s future is cloudier than it once was, experts say a eulogy for automakers&#8217; electric dreams would be premature.
The country&#8217;s automotive future doesn&#8217;t look as electric as carmakers had once hoped. But it doesn&#8217;t mean the EV industry is entirely dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Kingsley Also Can&#8217;t Believe He&#8217;s Starring in &#8216;Wonder Man&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ben-kingsley-wonder-man-marvel-trevor-2000700301</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700301</guid>
      <description>From 'Iron Man 3' to 'Shang-Chi' and now Disney+, the Oscar winner marvels at his Marvel longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Australia vs England: live stream 3rd Ashes Test for *FREE* from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/australia-vs-england-3rd-ashes-test-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">H2hDxrfP4DfodtmJxyDPj5</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch the 3rd Ashes Test at Adelaide from anywhere in the world as Australia and England battle in cricket&#8217;s most famous Test series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai and Kia to offer free anti-theft repairs for millions of cars under a multistate settlement</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461651/kia-hyundai-multistate-settlement-free-anti-theft-repairs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461651/kia-hyundai-multistate-settlement-free-anti-theft-repairs</guid>
      <description>The companies must also pay up to $4.5 million of restitution to people whose vehicles were damaged by thieves.
Automakers Hyundai and Kia must offer free repairs to millions of models under a settlement announced Tuesday by Minnesota&#8217;s attorney general, who led an effort by dozens of states that argued the vehicles weren&#8217;t equipped with proper anti-theft technology, leaving them vulnerable to theft....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows Instacart may be charging some shoppers 20% more for the same product</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/study-shows-instacart-may-be-charging-some-shoppers-20-more-for-the-same-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076612</guid>
      <description>The delivery app has claimed that price testing is part of a longstanding practice in retail sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Replay 2025 is here to recap your PC gaming habits</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/steam-replay-2025-is-here-to-recap-your-pc-gaming-habits-205430951.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a6ef28b-843d-488a-a963-9b0b23d99c6b</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Tis the season for gift-giving, family feasts and companies turning their harvested user data into lighthearted recaps. Valve's take on the year-end rewind, Steam Replay, is now available. It follows similar offerings from Spotify, Apple Music, PlayStation and, increasingly, just about every service you use. Hell, even Uber and The New York Times somehow justified getting in on the action this year.This is the fourth edition of Valve&#8217;s wrap-up, which looks back on the titles you spent the most time with in 2025. You&#8217;ll find your top games, the number of titles you played, achievements unlocke...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The last Xbox update of 2025 includes a handy Wireless Headset upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/the-last-xbox-update-of-2025-includes-a-handy-wireless-headset-upgrade-204500386.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98bf3009-0025-4eb3-86f5-80ffdee3a4e2</guid>
      <description>As part of its last Xbox-focused software update of the year, Microsoft is improving the Bluetooth performance of the Xbox Wireless Headset to make it work even better with Windows 11. Microsoft released the latest Wireless Headset as an accessory for Xbox Series X/S and PC, but as of this update, Xbox Wireless Headset owners on Windows will now have a leg up on their console counterparts thanks to support for Bluetooth Low Energy (LE) Audio.Microsoft says that supporting Bluetooth LE Audio will let the headset offer lower latency audio, better battery life, richer stereo sound and the ability...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Games has a year-in-review thing now too</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nyt-games-has-a-year-in-review-thing-now-too-203000878.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d55947b4-c371-4675-b57c-98d16edec17f</guid>
      <description>The New York Times is getting in on the year-end roundup bandwagon. The publication's new Year in Games wraps up stats about which of its daily puzzles and brain-teasers readers played over the course of 2025. People can get their own personalized reports, or just look over the community stats for the Wordle, Connections, Spelling Bee and Strands games. The Year in Games reviews are available on the iOS and Android apps for The New York Times, as well as on a dedicated mobile web page.Annual analysis of all your activities has become a common feature for lots of services. Reports like Spotify ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market falls after mixed data on the economy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461644/stock-market-mixed-economy-jobs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461644/stock-market-mixed-economy-jobs</guid>
      <description>The mixed data initially sent Treasury yields lower in the bond market. 
The U.S. stock market is drifting lower on Tuesday following&#160;mixed data&#160;on the&#160;economy&#8217;s strength, which did little to clear uncertainty about where interest rates may be heading.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
