<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:27:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI signs deal, worth $10 billion, for compute from Cerebras</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/openai-signs-deal-reportedly-worth-10-billion-for-compute-from-cerebras/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082833</guid>
      <description>The collaboration will help OpenAI models deliver faster response times for more difficult or time consuming tasks, the companies said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Congressman Wants to Make ICE Agents Wear QR Codes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dem-congressman-wants-to-make-ice-agents-wear-qr-codes-2000710345</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710345</guid>
      <description>There's this analog device called a badge that has worked wonders for generations, maybe consider that too?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micron says it's 'trying to help consumers' in RAM crisis despite killing its Crucial brand &#8211; and PC owners have got even angrier as a result</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/micron-says-its-trying-to-help-consumers-in-ram-crisis-despite-killing-its-crucial-brand-and-pc-owners-have-got-even-angrier-as-a-result</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kJCVK3JXHyviNmt33UxnRB</guid>
      <description>Micron is even more unpopular after trying to defend its decision to shut down the Crucial brand of consumer RAM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network appears to be having technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Verizon customers on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even the network provider&#8217;s own status page struggled to load, likely due to the number of customers trying to access it.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally, at least for some users. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started grow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 advocacy groups call on Apple and Google to ban Grok, X over nonconsensual deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/28-advocacy-groups-call-on-apple-and-google-to-ban-grok-x-over-nonconsensual-deepfakes-215048460.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4e0f782-5b85-4fe4-b119-5b7e4576952a</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk isn't the only party at fault for Grok's nonconsensual intimate deepfakes of real people, including children. What about Apple and Google? The two (frequently virtue-signaling) companies have inexplicably allowed Grok and X to remain in their app stores &#8212; even as Musk's chatbot reportedly continues to produce the material. On Wednesday, a coalition of women's and progressive advocacy groups called on Tim Cook and Sundar Pichai to uphold their own rules and remove the apps.The open letters to Apple and Google were signed by 28 groups. Among them are the women&#8217;s advocacy group Ultravio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash and Uber Eats Cost Delivery Workers Millions of Dollars in Tips, NYC Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doordash-and-uber-eats-cost-delivery-workers-millions-of-dollars-in-tips-nyc-says-2000710487</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710487</guid>
      <description>A new report from the city claims app design changes made tipping harder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More worrying tech supply chain news - no, it's not more RAM troubles, but this vital material could be set to cause issues sooner than expected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/finally-some-good-supply-chain-news-no-its-not-more-ram-but-this-vital-material-is-set-to-enjoy-a-boom-year-which-should-be-great-news-for-everyone</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wRChMhP9PBHLgiNapmsxu6</guid>
      <description>Copper demand is rising fast due to electrification, data centers, and renewable energy, while supply struggles and recycling cannot meet needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon&#8217;s wireless network is down for many people nationwide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861956/verizon-is-down-outage-cell-wireless-service-sos-mode</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T16:40:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861956</guid>
      <description>The first big outage of 2026 is here, as Verizon customers across the US, including several of our phones, complain that service has been spotty or nonexistent starting at around noon ET, with phones switching to SOS Mode and being unable to connect. This cell service outage follows a "software issue" that cut off service [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Heads Say &#8216;Joker: Folie &#224; Deux&#8217; Was Good, You Guys Are Just Mean</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/joker-2-folie-a-deux-warner-bros-todd-phillips-joaquin-phoenix-2000710250</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710250</guid>
      <description>We're two years divorced from Todd Phillips' 'Joker' sequel, and the studio is still claiming the disappointing DC film was merely misunderstood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naya Connect is a modular mechanical keyboard system for the indecisive</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862123/naya-connect-modular-mechanical-keyboard-kickstarter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T16:38:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862123</guid>
      <description>Naya has already shipped one successful Kickstarter for a weird keyboard. The Naya Create was an ergonomic split deck with four swappable controller addons: a touchpad, a trackball, a rotary encoder, or a 6DoF spatial mouse. The Connect takes that modular concept, applies it to a more traditional flat keyboard form factor, and expands the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.&#8217;s FDA Pulls Warning About Fake Autism Treatments</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rfk-jr-s-fda-pulls-warning-about-fake-autism-treatments-2000710367</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710367</guid>
      <description>The webpage previously noted that there is no cure for autism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Hurst cast as Kratos for live-action God of War show</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/ryan-hurst-cast-as-kratos-for-live-action-god-of-war-show-211655396.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c4ada36-d4aa-42b3-a369-27c1e0f7d547</guid>
      <description>Amazon's upcoming God of War live-action TV adaptation has cast Ryan Hurst as its Kratos. Sony announced the casting today on X with a brief post and an image of both Hurst and Kratos in full scowl mode. Hurst is already sporting a very Kratos-style beard, so he's already got the right vibe going for him. He has past credits on familiar shows such as Sons of Anarchy and The Walking Dead. The upcoming Amazon series also isn't his first rodeo acting in this universe; Hurst voiced Thor in the video game God of War Ragnarok. But the most important question with this casting news is whether Hurst w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>In a chaotic world, one thing you can count on is your own common-sense steps toward better cybersecurity. January is a great time to grab a subscription for yourself or a loved one, as a few holiday sales are (inexplicably) still happening. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart online trackers.
We strongly recommend using a VPN, but you might get stuck with a substandard app if you jump on the very first deal you see. You might also mistakenly end up paying more than you want...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Launches Investigation Into Grok&#8217;s Nonconsensual Sexual Images</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/california-investigation-grok-xai-nudes-attorney-general-2000710374</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710374</guid>
      <description>The AG said that "the avalanche of reports detailing the non-consensual, sexually explicit material that xAI has produced" is shocking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming Just Greenlit America&#8217;s Largest Data Center Project, and Locals Are Bracing for Impact</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wyoming-just-greenlit-americas-largest-data-center-project-and-locals-are-bracing-for-impact-2000710447</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710447</guid>
      <description>The commissioners of Laramie County, Wyoming, unanimously voted to build a data center campus that will be designed to scale to 10 gigawatts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Just Absolutely Gutted the Best Part of Quest VR Headsets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meta-just-absolutely-gutted-the-best-part-of-quest-vr-headsets-2000710320</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710320</guid>
      <description>It is, once again, a very bad moment for VR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Dilbert&#8217; taught white-collar workers how to talk about hating work</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475080/dilbert-taught-white-collar-workers-how-to-talk-about-hating-work</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475080/dilbert-taught-white-collar-workers-how-to-talk-about-hating-work</guid>
      <description>How the controversial cartoonist broke ground with ever-relevant office life critiques.
Scott Adams, the creator of the uber-popular and satirical comic strip Dilbert, has died. He passed away on January 13, after announcing his diagnosis of metastatic prostate cancer last spring. He was 68.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s first original video podcasts feature Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/netflixs-first-original-video-podcasts-feature-pete-davidson-and-michael-irvin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082820</guid>
      <description>As Netflix tries to take down YouTube&#8217;s dominance in the podcast space, it's getting new originals with Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon didn&#8217;t have to go far to find its live-action Kratos</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/862089/god-of-war-kratos-casting-amazone-prime-video</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T15:47:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862089</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced the first cast member of its God of War live-action adaptation on Prime Video. Ryan Hurst, known for his work as Opie in Sons of Anarchy and Beta in The Walking Dead, will play the titular God of War, Kratos. Though the casting might come as a bit of a disappointment to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Being Marketed Like This?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-is-avengers-doomsday-being-marketed-like-this-2000706181</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706181</guid>
      <description>Marvel's been doling out 'Avengers: Doomsday' info in two different ways, and they both tell us what the film's ambitions are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even AI skeptic Linus Torvalds is getting involved in 'vibe coding' - so could this herald a new dawn for Linux? Probably not...</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/even-ai-skeptic-linus-torvalds-is-getting-involved-in-vibe-coding-so-could-this-herald-a-new-dawn-for-linux-probably-not</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hm6mf83BHE7sAJ2Ufoqi7h</guid>
      <description>Torvalds says he briefly used AI for a hobby project, reinforcing pragmatic limits, skepticism toward hype, and caution around critical software development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX offers free Starlink access to Iranian demonstrators amid Internet blackout</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474999/starlink-spacex-iran-free-internet</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:34:10</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474999/starlink-spacex-iran-free-internet</guid>
      <description>Starlink is banned in Iran by telecommunication regulations.
Iranian demonstrators&#8217; ability to get details of&#160;bloody nationwide protests&#160;out to the world has been given a strong boost, with SpaceX&#8217;s Starlink satellite internet service dropping its fees to allow more people to circumvent the Tehran government&#8217;s strongest attempt ever to prevent information from spilling outside its borders, activists said Wednesday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization VII comes to Apple Arcade in February</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/civilization-vii-comes-to-apple-arcade-in-february-203000754.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c585f358-08d1-4793-ad2a-3ea102210515</guid>
      <description>The App Store is a home for many kinds of apps (including, inexplicably, one that lets users undress strangers without their consent). But hey, it also has games! And soon the store's Apple Arcade service will include one more: the not-so-highly rated Civilization VII.Apple announced on Wednesday that Sid Meier's Civilization VII will arrive almost exactly a year after launch. The game is already available for Apple devices, but its arrival on Apple Arcade will be a first.Civilization VII arrives on Apple Arcade on February 5.Firaxis Games / Apple&#8220;Free (for Apple Arcade subscribers)&#8221; may be th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilt 2.0&#8217;s low-interest premium card takes on Chase Sapphire Reserve&#8212;with mortgage and rent rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474985/bilt-credit-card-2-0-new-premium-rewards-for-mortgage-rent-low-interest-rate-loyalty-points-perks-chase-sapphire-reserve</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474985/bilt-credit-card-2-0-new-premium-rewards-for-mortgage-rent-low-interest-rate-loyalty-points-perks-chase-sapphire-reserve</guid>
      <description>Bilt is shaking up the credit card rewards race with a new offering&#8212;but the points system is complicated. Here&#8217;s what to know.
As Americans struggle with an affordability crisis&#8212;high inflation and an even higher cost of living, especially when it comes to housing&#8212;Bilt is launching three new, low interest credit cards with rates capped at 10% on new purchases for the first year&#8212;including a premium card offering with a $495 annual fee....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
