<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:19:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 8 most comfortable office chairs that saved our backs in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-8-most-comfortable-office-chairs-that-saved-our-backs-in-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XUzL6mKfkKxFeiKkTB8eoR</guid>
      <description>As TechRadar Pro's office furniture editor, I test office chairs for a living - and these are the most comfortable seats my team and I reviewed this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Samsung's "First Look" CES 2026 presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/how-to-watch-samsungs-first-look-ces-2026-presentation-190027604.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99e05139-49a3-486e-a22a-1ec128284043</guid>
      <description>NurPhoto via Getty Images
Samsung is arguably the 800-pound gorilla of CES, with a full spectrum of products that range from phones and computers to refrigerators to AI assistants and rolling robots. But for CES 2026, the company is shaking up the schedule a bit: Instead of its longtime midday Monday press conference position, the Korean giant will front-run the entire show with a Sunday night presentation.
Samsung has already given a few hints as to what's on the agenda, but what we're really hoping to see is an update on the Ballie robot &#8212; a star of previous CES presentations that ostensibly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are over 55 new Hulu movies arriving in January 2026 &#8212; these are the 3 I'd recommend streaming first</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/there-are-over-55-new-hulu-movies-arriving-in-january-2026-these-are-the-3-id-recommend-streaming-first</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TMXomKTScY7aQzrJvf9HuH</guid>
      <description>Catch new movies Hacksaw Ridge and Heat, as well as the second season of boxing drama A Thousand Blows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta buys Manus for $2 billion to power high-stakes AI agent race</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/meta-buys-manus-for-usd2-billion-to-power-high-stakes-ai-agent-race</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EYwT5w4Si4FZ2LVAJtcbcR</guid>
      <description>Meta&#8217;s $2 billion acquisition of Manus signals a major shift toward AI agents that can autonomously handle real work, not just generate responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Sony Honda Afeela CES 2026 press conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/how-to-watch-the-sony-honda-afeela-ces-2026-press-conference-130048622.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55dc3f84-855b-40ed-9b3d-0dc382a60c59</guid>
      <description>
Sony's CES 2026 press conference is just days away, but this year has a twist: Instead of an overview of Sony's electronics, video game and Hollywood studio plans for the new year, the presser will apparently have a more narrow focus: electric vehicles. That's because the traditional end-of-press-day slot isn't just Sony, but rather Sony Honda Mobility &#8212; the joint venture responsible for the Afeela 1 electric car that has been showcased at CES for the better part of a decade. This year, however, we'll also apparently get to see a an all-new concept model at the event, too.&#160;
How to watch the S...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January's PS Plus Monthly Games include Need for Speed Unbound and Disney Epic Mickey: Rebrushed</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/januarys-ps-plus-monthly-games-include-need-for-speed-unbound-and-disney-epic-mickey-rebrushed-182335673.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0abd41e-aa15-43e4-9207-23de76881669</guid>
      <description>Sony has revealed the first batch of PlayStation Plus Monthly Games for 2026. There are three titles to play this month, all of which drop on January 6. As always, you&#8217;ll retain access to these games as long as your subscription remains active.

First up, there's Need For Speed Unbound. This is a racing game that came out at the tail-end of 2022 and was the first entry in the franchise for several years before that. It has a unique visual style, thanks to cel-shaded graphics, with all kinds of vehicles to choose from. There are street racing challenges, weekly qualifiers and a minigame that ha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This SmarterMail vulnerability allows Remote Code Execution - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-smartermail-vulnerability-allows-remote-code-execution-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sK6asFAvDaCFCkgzJwYuC7</guid>
      <description>A maximum-severity flaw was just patched, and users are urged to apply the fix immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From robovacs for small homes to a Roomba for your lawn, here are 4 things we can expect to see from iRobot &#8211; according to the CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/from-robovacs-for-small-homes-to-a-roomba-for-your-lawn-here-are-4-things-we-can-expect-to-see-from-irobot-according-to-the-ceo</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oNDgjRWsu8qaPHr2wX3Hgf</guid>
      <description>Exclusive: There are some intriguing plans for the original robot vacuum brand following recent company takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 10 Most Anticipated Movies of Early 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/our-10-most-anticipated-movies-of-early-2026-2000702768</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702768</guid>
      <description>Sam Raimi, Pixar, Ghostface, and Ryan Gosling all check in with big movies in the next three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got a 4K Blu-ray player for Christmas? Here are 6 discs I've tested that should get you started</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/got-a-4k-blu-ray-player-for-christmas-here-are-6-discs-ive-tested-that-should-get-you-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XsdsGc64MKkn5aqvW3L4sR</guid>
      <description>If you're just getting into the world of 4K Blu-ray, I've picked 6 discs you should buy to kickstart your collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG reveals its version of Samsung's Frame TV &#8212; but the screen tech might not be what you're hoping for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lg-reveals-its-version-of-samsungs-frame-tv-but-the-screen-tech-might-not-be-what-youre-hoping-for</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yPrcTykgMmR2i8KESontwm</guid>
      <description>LG's Gallery TV doesn't have OLED: it's a mini-LED TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a USPS rule change could impact election ballots in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468030/how-a-usps-rule-change-could-impact-election-ballots-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T17:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468030/how-a-usps-rule-change-could-impact-election-ballots-in-2026</guid>
      <description>Many states rely on postmarks to validate ballots&#8212;but that system is about to change.
It&#8217;s the sort of thing you might not notice until it really matters, but the U.S. Postal Service recently changed how it defines the &#8220;postmark&#8221; on a piece of mail&#8212;warning that the postmark date is not a reliable indicator of when you actually mailed something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the LG press conference at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-lg-press-conference-at-ces-2026-190159474.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6eb7981-0913-4e7b-bd66-4bc9abdcb17b</guid>
      <description>LG
For years, LG has kicked off CES press day with the first event of the morning &#8212; and 2026 will be no different. The Korea-based corporation is theming its presentation as  "Innovation in Tune with You," and &#8212; if it follows the template of past presentations &#8212; it will highlight both the consumer electronics and large appliance sides of its mammoth global businesses.
Like nearly all tech-centric events these days, expect AI to be the binding theme of the LG presentation at CES 2026. Just be aware that, like Apple, LG has its own customized abbreviation for AI: "Affectionate Intelligence." The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay true to your New Years cleaning resolutions with $150 off the Dyson Ball Animal 3 vacuum</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-31-dyson-ball-animal-3-vacuum-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002VXBXSinXBT24fIntjC4V</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 31, save $150 on the the Dyson Ball Animal 3 vacuum at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
