<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:27:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia d&#233;clare la guerre &#224; Tesla : Alpamayo et la puce Rubin sur une Mercedes CLA pour faire mieux que le FSD</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2931271_nvidia-declare-la-guerre-a-tesla-alpamayo-et-la-puce-rubin-sur-une-mercedes-cla-pour-faire-mieux-que-le-fsd</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2931271_nvidia-declare-la-guerre-a-tesla-alpamayo-et-la-puce-rubin-sur-une-mercedes-cla-pour-faire-mieux-que-le-fsd</guid>
      <description>
C'est la d&#233;monstration de force du CES 2026. Pendant que Tesla garde son FSD jalousement ferm&#233;, Nvidia offre la m&#234;me technologie au reste du monde. La nouvelle Mercedes CLA embarque Alpamayo, une IA capable de voir, penser et conduire. Le monopole de Tesla sur l'autonomie vit peut-&#234;tre ses derni&#232;res heures.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's still one episode of Stranger Things season 5 left to watch &#8212; and it drops on Netflix next week</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/theres-still-one-episode-of-stranger-things-season-5-left-to-watch-and-it-drops-on-netflix-next-week</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">C2YowiWJHyssYhP7xaU4m</guid>
      <description>Stranger Things season 5 isn&#8217;t quite over yet thanks to this surprise Netflix special fans cannot miss, and it'll make 'conformity gate' a distant memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet &#8216;Cloud-9,&#8217; a New Type of Object That Shows What a Failed Galaxy Looks Like</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meet-cloud-9-a-new-type-of-object-that-shows-what-a-failed-galaxy-looks-like-2000706031</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706031</guid>
      <description>Astronomers have finally confirmed the existence of RELHICs&#8212;a long-theorized class of dark, starless clouds from the early universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers use 'Blue Screen of Death' malware to target victims</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-use-blue-screen-of-death-malware-to-target-victims</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FvNJUBBhyMMqiSinuSCys3</guid>
      <description>A new campaign is targeting the European hospitality industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickstart a healthy January 2026 with this Nutribullet Blender for &#163;69</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/juicers-blenders/kickstart-a-healthy-january-2026-with-this-nutribullet-blender-for-gbp69</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FzEkNtiR7eoTyRMVKY8KAj</guid>
      <description>Amazon cuts the price of the four-star Nutribullet Blender 900 to &#163;69, making it an excellent buy for your new year health kick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel releases the third trailer for Avengers: Doomsday &#8212; and it teases some menacing mutant mayhem for the X-Men</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/marvel-releases-the-third-trailer-for-avengers-doomsday-and-it-teases-some-menacing-mutant-mayhem-for-the-x-men</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pP98TXZcXzrYXqGP8yJKwZ</guid>
      <description>The third teaser for Avengers: Doomsday has landed online &#8211; and it spells trouble for Professor X, Magneto, and Cyclops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin, Coros, Apple&#8230; voici les marques de montres les plus populaires chez les coureurs en France</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2930651_garmin-coros-apple-voici-les-marques-de-montres-les-plus-populaires-chez-les-coureurs-en-france</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2930651_garmin-coros-apple-voici-les-marques-de-montres-les-plus-populaires-chez-les-coureurs-en-france</guid>
      <description>
Le m&#233;dia fran&#231;ais Run'ix, d&#233;di&#233; &#224; la course &#224; pied, a publi&#233; le classement des marques de montres les plus utilis&#233;es par sa communaut&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer Thinks AI Headphones With Cameras Can Take On Meta&#8217;s Ray-Bans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/razer-thinks-ai-headphones-with-cameras-can-take-on-metas-ray-bans-2000705583</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705583</guid>
      <description>Everyone wants in on the AI wearable game, but Razer is offering a slightly different take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer Made Its AI Gaming Assistant Into a Waifu Hologram</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/razer-made-its-ai-gaming-assistant-into-a-waifu-hologram-2000705679</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705679</guid>
      <description>Yes, you read that right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell unveils a massive 52-inch 6K ultrawide monitor at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/dell-unveils-a-massive-52-inch-6k-ultrawide-monitor-at-ces-2026-140024029.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f50d6f99-01f1-45ee-9af4-32825a117ff2</guid>
      <description>Dell has unveiled an ultrawide, curved 52-inch 6K monitor at CES 2026. This productivity behemoth is designed for stock traders, engineers and other data professionals. Dell claims the UltraSharp 52 Thunderbolt Hub Monitor is the world's first 52-inch ultrawide curved 6K monitor (but with that many qualifiers almost anything can be a world first).
Given Dell&#8217;s experience in the monitor realm, this could be a dream display for professionals who handle vast data sets such as trading platforms, AutoCAD, 3D rendering software, spreadsheets and more. It sports a 120Hz refresh rate on an IPS Black p...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The X-Men Are Back in the Next &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avengers-doomsday-trailer-x-men-cyclops-xavier-magneto-2000703799</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703799</guid>
      <description>Marvel's latest look at its next 'Avengers' adventure teases the arrival of mutants into the MCU proper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer Shoves All Its Wackiest Immersion Products Into a Single Gaming Chair</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/razer-shoves-all-its-wackiest-immersion-products-into-a-single-gaming-chair-2000705332</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705332</guid>
      <description>Razer's got your back if you want spine-tingling haptics and sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs&#8217; Early Apple Items Are Going Up for Auction&#8212;Along With His Bow Ties</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/steve-jobs-ephemera-auction-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695c09e7eb5da3dc323a9145</guid>
      <description>Some of the objects came from Steve Jobs&#8217; childhood bedroom. They&#8217;re being made available by his stepbrother, John Chovanec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring and Watch Duty Team Up to Keep a Closer Eye on Wildfires</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ring-watch-duty-team-up-wildfire-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695c0d968bbcecf91be2ebbb</guid>
      <description>In a move to help alert people to the spread of nearby blazes, Ring is partnering with Watch Duty to let users share their videos on the wildfire tracking app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pila makes the power station pretty</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/844583/pila-makes-the-power-station-pretty</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844583</guid>
      <description>Pila Energy's home batteries are now available to preorder with deliveries expected to begin in February 2026. These power stations are meant to be seen, unlike most batteries in this class that are better suited for job sites than designer lofts. Pila's home batteries are designed to keep critical devices like a fridge running during [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell made a big-ass 52-inch 6K Thunderbolt display</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/846600/dell-52-ultrasharp-thunderbolt-64-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846600</guid>
      <description>The world's first 52-inch 6K monitor has arrived in Dell's UltraSharp 52 Thunderbolt Hub Monitor, which was announced at CES 2026. It's a 21:9 aspect ratio screen that's slightly curved (4200R) and can display up to 6,144 x 2,560 at up to 120Hz refresh rate (with VRR support). Its IPS Black panel type offers deeper [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell&#8217;s new 4K QD-OLED monitor offers true 10-bit color</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/846633/dell-4k-32-qdoled-color-grading-specs-ultrasharp</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846633</guid>
      <description>Dell announced at CES 2026 that it'll launch the UltraSharp 32 4K QD-OLED Monitor on February 24th for $2,599.99. Despite having released a productivity-focused 4K QD-OLED of the same size in 2025 that regularly sold for well under $1,000, its new one costs more mainly due to having greater color accuracy for creative professionals. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Bot is an AI agent that sits on your desk</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851270/vibe-bot-is-an-ai-agent-that-sits-on-your-desk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851270</guid>
      <description>Smart whiteboard manufacturer Vibe is expanding further into hybrid work hardware with the Vibe Bot, a physical AI device that can serve as a voice assistant, a smart webcam, and an AI note-taker, designed for office desks and meeting rooms. Despite the name, Vibe Bot is definitely not a robot. In fact it's closer to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer&#8217;s new controller has TMR sticks and ultra-low latency Bluetooth for use with TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852022/razers-new-controller-has-tmr-sticks-and-ultra-low-latency-bluetooth-for-use-with-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852022</guid>
      <description>Razer is announcing a new Wolverine V3 BT controller at CES 2026 that's designed for TVs. It's the world's first gamepad to use ultra-low latency Bluetooth, allowing it a sub-3ms response time, and the first accessory to launch under LG's "Designed for LG Gaming Portal" program. But since it's been developed in collaboration with LG, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring&#8217;s Mobile Security Trailer provides 360-degree coverage anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852890/ring-mobile-security-elite-camera-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852890</guid>
      <description>Ring is introducing a host of new security devices and technologies, including a new line of security cameras and a mobile trailer equipped with a camera that can cover large areas. While these devices were developed mostly for enterprise-level security, they can be purchased and used for home and other uses as well. To begin, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer made a concept gaming chair with speakers, RGB lights, and rumble</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854601/razer-concept-gaming-chair-speakers-rgb-lights-rumble</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854601</guid>
      <description>Razer is combining its various gaming chair add-ons of speakers, RGB lighting, and force feedback into one proof of concept: Project Madison. It features dual RGB light strips in the top corners, a pair of THX-certified speakers with spatial audio (which can act as the rear channels in 5.1 or 7.1 audio setups), and six [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aqara came to CES with something to prove</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854695/aqara-came-to-ces-with-something-to-prove</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854695</guid>
      <description>Aqara came to Vegas with a number of smart home firsts in its rapidly growing portfolio. It's showcasing an impressive smart lock that unlocks on approach, a thermostat with support for Apple's Adaptive Temperature and Clean Energy Guidance, a Matter-enabled camera, and a pair of sensors to track human occupants and objects. The Camera Hub [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer is making an AI anime waifu hologram for your desk</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854705/razer-ai-anime-waifu-hologram-desk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854705</guid>
      <description>Razer's Project Ava AI game coach from last year's CES is taking a new form for 2026: a tiny holographic anime girl in a capsule you can put on your desk. Anime girls in pods were already a thing at CES 2025, but Razer's take on it is much smaller and desk-friendly. The new Project [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer&#8217;s AI wearable is a headset with built-in cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854756/razer-concept-ai-wearable-headphones-project-motoko</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854756</guid>
      <description>Razer announced a concept AI wearable at CES that resembles a pair of wireless headphones (or Razer's Barracuda gaming headsets, to be precise), with two camera lenses built into the ear cups. The current iteration of Project Motoko is powered by an unspecified Qualcomm Snapdragon chip and uses dual first-person-view cameras positioned at eye level [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Ring doorbells get fire alerts, an app store and new sensors</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/amazons-ring-doorbells-get-fire-alerts-an-app-store-and-new-sensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080190</guid>
      <description>The new Ring Sensors can detect motion, openings, glass breakage, and smoke, and can also monitor carbon monoxide levels, leaks, temperature changes, and air quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wireless charging, super-fast unlocking, and built-in solar panels &#8211; the next generation of smart locks from CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/ces-2026-smart-locks</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PhsS72WLaXDnbzuSaNEFZW</guid>
      <description>Home security is a hot topic at CES, with locks that are smarter, more secure, and simpler to use than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA's G-Sync Pulsar tech can minimize motion blur for gamers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/nvidias-g-sync-pulsar-tech-can-minimize-motion-blur-for-gamers-140000058.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48f42961-91d1-4d73-8904-23270bcb06ea</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA has unveiled the G-Sync Pulsar, which it calls the &#8220;latest evolution of [its] pioneering VRR (variable refresh rate) technology,&#8221; at CES 2026. The new tech promises a gaming experience that&#8217;s free of stutter with buttery smooth motion, which is made possible by pulsing the display&#8217;s backlight. G-Sync Pulsar displays have multiple horizontal backlight sections that are pulsed independently from top to bottom, unlike traditional displays whose backlight is always on. When the backlight is always active, the image fades from one frame to the next. The displays with the new tech give pixels...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer's Project Madison concept chair has reactive lighting, immersive audio and multi-zone haptics</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/razers-project-madison-concept-chair-has-reactive-lighting-immersive-audio-and-multi-zone-haptics-140000118.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a19338c-cd40-463e-b114-a860d93c938e</guid>
      <description>Razer is once again thinking big about what a gaming chair can do, and its concept for CES 2026 isn't just a chair but an entire multisensory experience to match whatever's happening on-screen. The concept, called Project Madison, combines reactive lighting, spatial audio and multi-zone haptic feedback to make the player feel more immersed in the in-game environment. We're talking Razer Chroma light strips along the head flaps, THX Spatial Audio for 5.1 or 7.1 surround sound and six haptic motor actuators powered by Razer Sensa HD Haptics to bring the physical sensations of a game to life. One...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer's Project Motoko is a concept gaming headset that doubles as an AI wearable</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/razers-project-motoko-is-a-concept-gaming-headset-that-doubles-as-an-ai-wearable-140000534.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c794e1d-0014-4482-945d-0226a493ff49</guid>
      <description>We see plenty of far-out ideas on the CES show floor, and this year Razer brought in a concept piece called Project Motoko. The device is Razer's take on blurring the line between a gaming headset and an AI-powered wearable for daily life. Or it's a way for Ghost in the Shell fans to feel affronted by Razer taking The Major's name in vain, take your pick.&#160;Project Motoko is powered by Qualcomm's Snapdragon platforms. The headset has a pair of first-person view cameras positioned at eye level that can support real-time object and text recognition. It also has a wide field of attention that can c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring relaunches its suite of smart home sensors</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/ring-relaunches-its-suite-of-smart-home-sensors-140000667.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56efeb3d-b14a-48a6-ac82-f62d3b16dd0c</guid>
      <description>Ring turned up to CES with a whole host of announcements, including a revamped range of home sensors. Ring Sensors (for that is their name) is a new lineup of tools, built on Amazon&#8217;s Sidewalk low-power networking protocol. That includes updated versions of its door, window and break glass sensors, as well as a new OBD-II car alarm, motion detectors and panic buttons. You&#8217;ll be able to pre-order the new car alarm today, while the rest of the new sensors will be available at some point in March. And, in tandem with that news, Amazon is announcing that Sidewalk is expanding outside of the US, st...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu le Dell UltraSharp 52 : l&#8217;&#233;cran 6K qui remplace 4 moniteurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926303_jai-vu-le-dell-ultrasharp-52-lecran-6k-qui-remplace-4-moniteurs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926303_jai-vu-le-dell-ultrasharp-52-lecran-6k-qui-remplace-4-moniteurs</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez deux &#233;crans ? Trois ? Quatre ? Arr&#234;tez tout. J'ai pos&#233; les yeux sur le Dell UltraSharp 52 Thunderbolt Hub, et c'est une vision assez terrifiante d'efficacit&#233;. C'est une dalle unique de 52 pouces en 6K qui remplace tout votre bazar de c&#226;bles. C'est impressionnant, m&#234;me si le choix de la dalle va faire d&#233;battre.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birdbuddy unveils its most affordable 'mini' bird feeder camera &#8212; and it can identify birds by their song</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/birdbuddy-unveils-its-most-affordable-mini-bird-feeder-camera-and-it-can-identify-birds-by-their-song</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cm2weZCvEK4gyYjiFR7jcH</guid>
      <description>Birdbuddy unveils its smallest and most accessible bird feeder camera yet &#8211; the Birdbuddy 2 Mini &#8211; and it can ID birds by visual and audio cues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici la nouvelle arme d&#8217;Uber pour battre Tesla dans la guerre des taxis autonomes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lucid/2931063_voici-la-nouvelle-arme-duber-pour-battre-tesla-dans-la-guerre-des-taxis-autonomes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lucid/2931063_voici-la-nouvelle-arme-duber-pour-battre-tesla-dans-la-guerre-des-taxis-autonomes</guid>
      <description>
L'alliance entre Lucid, Uber et Nuro franchit un nouveau cap avec la pr&#233;sentation au CES 2026 d'un taxi autonome premium bas&#233; sur le SUV &#233;lectrique Gravity. Objectif affich&#233; : d&#233;ployer plus de 20 000 v&#233;hicules dans les cinq prochaines ann&#233;es.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retour vers le futur&#160;: HP red&#233;couvre l&#8217;ordinateur &#171;&#160;tout-en-un&#160;&#187; dans un clavier</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/retour-vers-le-futur-hp-redecouvre-lordinateur-tout-en-un-dans-un-clavier.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318414</guid>
      <description>L'histoire (de l'informatique) repasse les plats. HP a red&#233;couvert les ordinateurs qui tiennent dans un clavier avec l'Eliteboard G1a ! Alors certes, on est loin d'une machine ultra-puissante, mais ce PC tout-en-un ultra-compact assume pleinement sa vocation : un poste de travail discret, facile &#224; d&#233;ployer et suffisamment v&#233;loce pour les usages bureautiques....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un casque gamer avec 90h d&#8217;autonomie : l&#8217;Asus ROG Pelta chute enfin sous les 100 &#8364; en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2605313_un-casque-gamer-avec-90h-dautonomie-lasus-rog-pelta-chute-sous-les-100-euros-en-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2605313_un-casque-gamer-avec-90h-dautonomie-lasus-rog-pelta-chute-sous-les-100-euros-en-2026</guid>
      <description>
Depuis la nouvelle ann&#233;e 2026, il y a de tr&#232;s bonnes affaires &#224; saisir c&#244;t&#233; Tech, comme ce casque wireless Asus ROG Pelta disponible &#224; 99,99 euros sur Amazon, au lieu de 149 euros habituellement. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer poursuit son offensive dans les trottinettes &#233;lectriques avec un nouveau mod&#232;le abouti</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/trottinette-electrique/2930767_acer-poursuit-son-offensive-dans-les-trottinettes-electriques-avec-un-nouveau-modele-abouti</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/trottinette-electrique/2930767_acer-poursuit-son-offensive-dans-les-trottinettes-electriques-avec-un-nouveau-modele-abouti</guid>
      <description>
Toujours dans cette volont&#233; de grignoter des parts &#224; Segway-Ninebot et Xiaomi, le groupe ta&#239;wanais Acer lance une nouvelle trottinette Acer Predator Storm Pro &#224; double suspension, avec un &#233;clairage personnalisable et une puissance soutenue.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PlayStation tech patent called Ghost Player will take over players' games when they get stuck</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/new-playstation-tech-patent-called-ghost-player-will-take-over-players-games-when-they-get-stuck</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zsnnBwDKvjGQTFHUKsYs2V</guid>
      <description>Sony has patented new AI technology that will take control of PlayStation games when the player gets stuck, offering limited to comprehensive solutions to problems. The system would also be trained on gameplay videos from YouTube and Twitch, as well as PSN data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris court finds 10 people guilty of cyberbullying Brigitte Macron</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/paris-court-finds-10-people-guilty-of-cyberbullying-brigitte-macron-195500994.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f9f3597-08dc-42a1-8337-e67318bbf482</guid>
      <description>A Paris court has found 10 people guilty of cyberbullying Brigitte Macron, wife of President of France Emmanuel Macron, the BBC reports. The judge found that the defendants made false claims about Macron's gender and sexuality, and "malicious remarks" about the 24-year age gap between Macron and her spouse.Of the ten defendants, only one received a firm prison sentence of six months, according to&#160;LeMonde. Eight others received suspended sentences (effectively probation in France) of four to eight months, while the 10th person received a fine and was required to attend a sensitivity training co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trois duplex en direct de Las Vegas et une tripot&#233;e de produits atypiques : rendez-vous ce soir pour un Unlock Talk de folie</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2930261_trois-duplex-en-direct-de-las-vegas-et-une-tripotee-de-produits-atypiques-rendez-vous-ce-soir-pour-un-unlock-talk</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2930261_trois-duplex-en-direct-de-las-vegas-et-une-tripotee-de-produits-atypiques-rendez-vous-ce-soir-pour-un-unlock-talk</guid>
      <description>
Direction Las Vegas et le Consumer Electronics Show (CES) pour la nouvelle ann&#233;e 2026. Comme &#224; l'accoutum&#233;e, Unlock Talk couvre le salon am&#233;ricain depuis Paris et la Ville du Vice, avec une &#233;mission Twitch sp&#233;cialement d&#233;di&#233;e o&#249; auront lieu pas moins de trois Duplex en direct.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung corrige enfin le plus gros d&#233;faut des &#233;crans pliants</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2930627_samsung-corrige-enfin-le-plus-gros-defaut-des-ecrans-pliants</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2930627_samsung-corrige-enfin-le-plus-gros-defaut-des-ecrans-pliants</guid>
      <description>
Samsung profite du CES 2026 pour d&#233;voiler la nouvelle version de ses &#233;crans pliables sans la caract&#233;ristique pliure centrale avec le Galaxy Z Fold 8.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the new Lego Smart Brick actually do? Here are 3 ways it seriously upgrades your models</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/what-does-the-new-lego-smart-brick-actually-do-here-are-3-ways-it-seriously-upgrades-your-models</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fNagC3ritZEfZP82dvZFMH</guid>
      <description>Like the look of the Lego Smart Brick? These are the key things you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus announces new ROG Flow Z13-KJP gaming tablet, along with a stunning collection of gaming accessories in collaboration with Kojima Productions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/asus-announces-new-rog-flow-z13-kjp-gaming-tablet-along-with-a-stunning-collection-of-gaming-accessories-in-collaboration-with-kojima-productions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Bu4yegnmQrmdvMVRxqxisF</guid>
      <description>Asus Republic of Gamers (ROG) has announced its brand new ROG Flow Z13-KJP gaming tablet launching mid-late Q1 2026, along with a collection of limited-edition accessories designed in collaboration with Kojima Productions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP price is on the rise today as crypto markets show early signs of a rebound: Here are 2 reasons why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469658/xrp-price-rising-today-2-reasons-why-crypto-token-going-up</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T13:17:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469658/xrp-price-rising-today-2-reasons-why-crypto-token-going-up</guid>
      <description>After struggling to gain ground since last summer, the token is outpacing Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies this week, likely for a few reasons. 
Popular cryptocurrency XRP had a lackluster 2025, starting the year at around $2.32 per token while finishing at around the $1.84 mark. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing your BlackBerry? The Clicks Communicator brings back the physical keyboard &#8211;and a 3.5mm headphone jack</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/android/missing-your-blackberry-the-clicks-communicator-brings-back-the-physical-keyboard-and-a-3-5mm-headphone-jack</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UaRRTixYDd2eSrRaMVApZU</guid>
      <description>A physical keyboard, a headphone jack, a microSD card slot... what year are we in again?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta reporte le lancement en France de ses nouvelles lunettes Ray-Ban Display</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/meta-reporte-le-lancement-en-france-de-ses-nouvelles-lunettes-ray-ban-display.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318401</guid>
      <description>Il faudra prendre son mal en patience pour porter des Ray-Ban Display en France. Meta a en effet annonc&#233; le report du lancement international de ses lunettes connect&#233;es avec &#233;cran, &#224; l'heure actuelle uniquement commercialis&#233;es aux &#201;tats-Unis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Microslop' is heading for Edge &#8211; major browser redesign is inspired by Copilot, and it's already seriously unpopular</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/microslop-is-heading-for-edge-major-browser-redesign-is-inspired-by-copilot-and-its-already-seriously-unpopular</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zUL52JmaTDFi4GNZrizNc5</guid>
      <description>Revamped browser design is symptomatic of a bigger problem that Microsoft is facing here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;Europe tient-elle son miracle ? Voici la batterie solide qui promet 273 ans de dur&#233;e de vie</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2931023_leurope-tient-elle-son-miracle-voici-la-batterie-solide-qui-promet-273-ans-de-duree-de-vie</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2931023_leurope-tient-elle-son-miracle-voici-la-batterie-solide-qui-promet-273-ans-de-duree-de-vie</guid>
      <description>
On nous promet la batterie solide "pour bient&#244;t" depuis dix ans. Et l&#224;, surprise : une start-up finlandaise affirme que c'est pr&#234;t, l&#224;, tout de suite, sur une moto. Avec une dur&#233;e de vie quasi-infinie de 100 000 cycles. L'annonce est impressionnante, mais elle soul&#232;ve plus de questions qu'elle ne donne de r&#233;ponses.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a subscription-free Whoop band? This screenless rival could be the voice-led wearable you&#8217;re looking for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/looking-for-a-subscription-free-whoop-band-this-screenless-rival-could-be-the-voice-led-wearable-youre-looking-for</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Azvr7BWm4Rt6ZT4csUvsS</guid>
      <description>Luna has launched a new fitness wearable at CES 2026 that comes with no subscription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#8217;s &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Land Is Serving Up a New Shade of Milk</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-star-wars-land-pink-milk-2000705825</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705825</guid>
      <description>Blue milk made sense. Green milk fit too. But now, starting this week, there's pink milk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway's Navimow brand unveiled a new line of robotic lawn mowers at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/segways-navimow-brand-unveiled-a-new-line-of-robotic-lawn-mowers-at-ces-2026-130007014.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b8854e-85cc-4e08-aee8-992000b9a41f</guid>
      <description>Segway, the maker of Steve Wozniak's favorite mode of self-balancing transport, has released a new series of robotic lawn mowers under its Navimow brand, designed for all manner of Roomba-esque mowing action. The lineup includes four residential series and was unveiled at CES 2026.
Navimow's lineup includes the flagship X4 Series for large yards up to 1.5 acres in size. Its AWD system can handle slopes up to 40 degrees and it sports dual 180-watt cutting motors. The largest mode, the X450 will retail for $3,000. A smaller X430 rated for yards up to 1 acre will go for $2,500.
The Navimow i2 ser...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugreen launches a smart home security platform at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/ugreen-launches-a-smart-home-security-platform-at-ces-130000389.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b61f0e10-971e-4d0f-a261-02969862e042</guid>
      <description>Ugreen makes plenty of things, but you&#8217;re probably familiar with the name in the context of its NAS systems (should that be NASes? Who knows). Naturally, the company has turned up to CES 2026 with the former, but it&#8217;s also branching out into home security. It&#8217;s announcing SynCare, an AI infused all-in-one surveillance platform which, it rather boldly claims, will become an &#8220;attentive, integrated guardian&#8221; of your home.Leading the pack is the SynCare Video Doorbell with head-to-toe 4K video, intelligent detection and 24/7 recording &#8212; especially if you&#8217;ve got it hooked up to your Ugreen NAS. Tha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway launches two more e-bikes at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/segway-launches-two-more-e-bikes-at-ces-130000152.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6228cc32-3766-4468-b41d-98a5e95f02c7</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m no psychologist, but I get a sense Segway turned up to CES 2026 with something to prove after last year. Certainly, it&#8217;s gone out of its way to prove its micromobility bona fides with the press, who perhaps were a bit too sniffy that scooter people were launching an e-bike. This year, Segway&#8217;s not just launching two more mainstream e-bikes, but an electric dirt bike, all of which are crammed with the sort of tech that might just make everyone halt their sniffiness.First up, there&#8217;s the Myon, a chunky step-through with a decent-sized pannier rack for folks who want to go far and carry a bit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR, transmission int&#233;grale et pentes de 84 % : ces tondeuses ultra compl&#232;tes sont pr&#234;tes &#224; affronter les jardins ultra-complexes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robots-tondeuses/2926531_lidar-transmission-integrale-et-pentes-de-84-ces-tondeuses-ultra-completes-sont-pretes-a-affronter-les-jardins-ultra-complexes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robots-tondeuses/2926531_lidar-transmission-integrale-et-pentes-de-84-ces-tondeuses-ultra-completes-sont-pretes-a-affronter-les-jardins-ultra-complexes</guid>
      <description>
Oubliez la simple guerre des c&#226;bles p&#233;rim&#233;triques, c'est d&#233;sormais de l'histoire ancienne. Pour ce CES 2026, Segway Navimow passe &#224; la vitesse sup&#233;rieure en injectant des technologies de pointe, LiDAR, IA et transmission int&#233;grale, dans pas moins de quatre nouveaux robots. De la petite pelouse de ville aux terrains de football, la marque veut tout automatiser.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Devenir astronaute, c&#8217;est repousser les limites &#187; : Sophie Adenot pr&#234;te pour une mission hors norme dans l'espace</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-devenir-astronaute-cest-repousser-limites-sophie-adenot-prete-mission-hors-norme-espace-129827/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-devenir-astronaute-cest-repousser-limites-sophie-adenot-prete-mission-hors-norme-espace-129827/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le premier vol de Sophie Adenot approche &#224; grands pas. L'astronaute fran&#231;aise doit partir &#224; bord de la station spatiale internationale le 15 f&#233;vrier prochain. Lors d'une conf&#233;rence de presse, elle a partag&#233; ses impressions et se dit pr&#234;te et impatiente de relever ce d&#233;fi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Colbert reacts to Trumps attack on Venezuela</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/stephen-colbert-trump-venezuela</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03YD8xXaJI9dSNTXe1ptv91</guid>
      <description>Stephen Colbert has reacted to the U.S. attack on Venezuela in his first "Late Show" monologue of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch ASB Classic 2026 in Auckland: live stream WTA tennis online, start time, what TV channel?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tennis/asb-classic-2026-auckland-wta-tennis</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rhmAU86PhM6BojXGGDi7KU</guid>
      <description>Watch free trial tennis streams today in the season's first WTA event from Auckland, New Zeland &#8211; 2026 ASB Classic TV channels, broadcasters and streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Performance defines the PC experience&#8217; &#8212; Samsung aims to take down Apple with its new Galaxy Book6 laptops and Intel&#8217;s latest tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/performance-defines-the-pc-experience-samsung-aims-to-take-down-apple-with-its-new-galaxy-book6-laptops-and-intels-latest-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27LeeQiXgPmu4gsiZ4yKK8</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s new Galaxy Book6 laptops "combine unparalleled speed and power with dependable AI" &#8211; could these be the MacBook-killers PC users have been waiting for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ways to walk for fitness, from rucking to the viral 'Japanese walking' trend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/7-ways-to-walk-for-fitness-from-rucking-to-the-viral-japanese-walking-trend</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UFnHx6Kx3PvVp9ZD3UEok9</guid>
      <description>7 walking workouts you need to know about, from beginner-friendly, low-impact routines to tougher sweat sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Suunto 9 Peak Pro &#224; -60 % : une montre id&#233;ale pour les sportifs au budget serr&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930427_la-suunto-9-peak-pro-a-60-une-montre-ideale-pour-les-sportifs-au-budget-serre</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930427_la-suunto-9-peak-pro-a-60-une-montre-ideale-pour-les-sportifs-au-budget-serre</guid>
      <description>
Propos&#233;e &#224; seulement&#160;199 euros&#160;au lieu de 499 euros, la Suunto 9 Peak Pro devient une vraie bonne affaire et se trouve &#234;tre un choix malin pour les runners et traileurs au budget serr&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free fait le m&#233;nage&#160;: pourquoi vous pouvez d&#233;sinstaller Freebox Connect d&#232;s aujourd&#8217;hui</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/free-fait-le-menage-pourquoi-vous-pouvez-desinstaller-freebox-connect-des-aujourdhui.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318382</guid>
      <description>C'&#233;tait dans l'air, c'est d&#233;sormais officiel : Free fusionne Freebox Connect avec son application principale. Gestion du Wi-Fi, factures et contr&#244;le parental sont enfin r&#233;unis dans une interface unique et simplifi&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
