<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:26:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Razr Fold : le premier smartphone pliable au format livre de la marque en images</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2927445_motorola-razr-fold-le-premier-smartphone-pliable-au-format-livre-de-la-marque-a-fuite</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2927445_motorola-razr-fold-le-premier-smartphone-pliable-au-format-livre-de-la-marque-a-fuite</guid>
      <description>
Alors que Motorola s'est jusqu'ici cantonn&#233; au march&#233; des smartphones &#224; clapet, une fuite r&#233;v&#232;le l'existence du &#171; Razr Fold &#187;. Ce mod&#232;le, au format livre, viendrait directement concurrencer les r&#233;f&#233;rences de Samsung et Google d&#232;s 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Tamagotchi clone is designed to help you keep your plants alive</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/this-tamagotchi-clone-is-designed-to-help-you-keep-your-plants-alive-172000982.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e3ec84b-6255-44f7-92fe-86356445f512</guid>
      <description>Tamagotchi ripoffs are alive and well at CES 2026, and SoildTech's spin on the idea is to stick a virtual pet in the dirt to help you stop killing your plants. Senso combines a plant health sensor and a Tamagotchi-like device, offering insights into the conditions of a houseplant's environment and a gamified way of keeping up with them.&#160;If a plant is in need of watering or could use some lighting adjustments, little characters will offer you quests to complete those tasks. And by taking care of your plant properly, you'll also be helping those characters' virtual home planet thrive. (A world t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm&#8217;s Next PC Chip Promises Even Better Battery Life Than Before</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/qualcomms-next-pc-chip-promises-even-better-battery-life-than-before-2000704445</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704445</guid>
      <description>Rounding out the Snapdragon X2 lineup is a mid-range chip that hopes to outperform Intel and AMD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo Ultimate 3E : la manette Xbox-PC qui va humilier la manette Elite de Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/manette-de-jeu/2929441_8bitdo-ultimate-3e-la-manette-xbox-pc-qui-va-humilier-la-manette-elite-de-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/manette-de-jeu/2929441_8bitdo-ultimate-3e-la-manette-xbox-pc-qui-va-humilier-la-manette-elite-de-microsoft</guid>
      <description>
La manette parfaite existe-t-elle ? 8BitDo s'en approche dangereusement. Oubliez les gadgets inutiles, voici l'Ultimate 3E. Pr&#233;sent&#233;e &#224; Las Vegas, elle embarque des joysticks TMR et une modularit&#233; exemplaire. Sur le papier, c'est un sans-faute technique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>En direct de Las Vegas pour le CES 2026 et une double Matinale Tech&#8217; : on commence l&#8217;ann&#233;e sur les chapeaux de roues sur Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2632585_en-direct-de-las-vegas-pour-le-ces-2026-et-une-double-matinale-tech-on-commence-lannee-sur-les-chapeaux-de-roues-sur-twitch</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2632585_en-direct-de-las-vegas-pour-le-ces-2026-et-une-double-matinale-tech-on-commence-lannee-sur-les-chapeaux-de-roues-sur-twitch</guid>
      <description>
Notre programme Twitch de la semaine du lundi 5 janvier 2026, c&#8217;est juste ici : nous vous donnons rendez-vous mardi, mercredi, jeudi et vendredi sur notre cha&#238;ne Frandroidlive, autant pour siroter votre caf&#233; devant notre Matinale Tech' que pour profiter de deux &#233;ditions sp&#233;ciales CES 2026 !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plier du linge, faire la cuisine et la vaisselle&#160;: un robot domestique &#224; tout faire chez SwitchBot</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/plier-du-linge-faire-la-cuisine-et-la-vaisselle-un-robot-domestique-a-tout-faire-chez-switchbot.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318232</guid>
      <description>Les robots n'en sont pas encore &#224; envahir l'int&#233;rieur de nos maisons, exception faite des robots aspirateurs. Mais l'industrie veut creuser ce sillon et pr&#233;pare des mod&#232;les bien plus polyvalents. C'est le cas de SwitchBot qui vient de pr&#233;senter le onero H1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung red&#233;finit la d&#233;mesure au CES 2026 avec un t&#233;l&#233;viseur Micro RGB de 130 pouces</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/samsung-redefinit-la-demesure-au-ces-2026-avec-un-televiseur-micro-rgb-de-130-pouces.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318179</guid>
      <description>Le g&#233;ant cor&#233;en a profit&#233; du salon de Las Vegas pour d&#233;voiler la premi&#232;re technologie Micro RGB en 130 pouces au monde. Plus qu'un &#233;cran, le mod&#232;le R95H se veut une &#339;uvre d'art architecturale</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocci's AI note-taking ring aims to do much more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/voccis-ai-note-taking-ring-aims-to-do-much-more-170536442.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">077b48ca-bb71-4f3d-8011-4c96b24bfe8f</guid>
      <description>One trend emerging from CES 2026 is wearable microphones you can use to dictate your thoughts. Vocci is one such gadget, a titanium ring with a single button capable of recording audio for up to eight hours on a charge. Unlike some of its competitors, Vocci isn&#8217;t just for catching your own thoughts as they spring forth from your scalp. Instead, you&#8217;ll be able to record whole conversations and meetings from the comfort of your proximal phalanx.&#160;Users can start and end recordings by double clicking the ring&#8217;s single button, while single clicks are used to mark important moments within the record...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satya Nadella wants us to stop calling AI "slop" - good luck with that</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/satya-nadella-wants-us-to-stop-calling-ai-slop-good-luck-with-that</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8Z5mvBLpDuwuH4aDB88hgV</guid>
      <description>Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella envisions a world where AI systems will work in conjunction to produce transformative results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glasses-free 3D displays are making an unlikely comeback &#8211; as Samsung reveals &#8216;world&#8217;s first&#8217; 6K monitor with real-time eye tracking</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/monitors/glasses-free-3d-displays-are-making-an-unlikely-comeback-as-samsung-reveals-worlds-first-6k-monitor-with-real-time-eye-tracking</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">D4XGKL5VWYG2gGNznTEoGM</guid>
      <description>First, it was the 'world's first' glasses-free PC handheld in 2025, and now, it's the 'world's first' glasses-free 3D 6K gaming monitor from Samsung.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon retire pr&#232;s de 150 &#8364; sur le dernier Surface Laptop 13 de Microsoft, un ordinateur portable performant sous Snapdragon X Plus</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2929081_amazon-retire-pres-de-150-e-sur-le-dernier-surface-laptop-13-de-microsoft-un-ordinateur-portable-performant-sous-snapdragon-x-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2929081_amazon-retire-pres-de-150-e-sur-le-dernier-surface-laptop-13-de-microsoft-un-ordinateur-portable-performant-sous-snapdragon-x-plus</guid>
      <description>
Compact, l&#233;ger et facile &#224; glisser dans un sac, le Microsoft Surface Laptop 13 (2025) repr&#233;sente une bonne affaire pour ceux qui veulent un ultraportable &#233;l&#233;gant et pratique &#224; transporter au quotidien. Bonne nouvelle, il s'affiche &#224; un prix plus avantageux sur Amazon : 968,81 euros contre 1 099 euros &#224; sa sortie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La nouvelle r&#233;f&#233;rence en mati&#232;re de casque gaming haut de gamme&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/audeze/2926395_la-nouvelle-reference-en-matiere-de-casque-gaming-haut-de-gamme</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/audeze/2926395_la-nouvelle-reference-en-matiere-de-casque-gaming-haut-de-gamme</guid>
      <description>
Audeze annonce officiellement le Maxwell 2, un nouveau casque gaming sans fil pour PC et consoles. Il veut offrir une fid&#233;lit&#233; audio renforc&#233;e, un confort am&#233;lior&#233; et une connectivit&#233; plus fluide pour les joueurs exigeants.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audeze has unveiled the Maxwell 2 gaming headset at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/audeze-has-unveiled-the-maxwell-2-gaming-headset-at-ces-2026-170056068.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a46955d0-b239-4652-b999-204c1c55722a</guid>
      <description>Audeze has unveiled the second generation of its Maxwell gaming headset at CES 2026. The Maxwell 2 is a comprehensive refresh aimed at competitive players and anyone seeking more immersive audio when gaming on PC or consoles. The original Maxwell headset was our pick for best premium gaming headset in 2025.
The headline upgrade is Audeze&#8217;s patent-pending SLAM technology, which the brand claims improves spatial cues while delivering &#8220;punchier&#8221; bass. Maxwell 2 pairs that with 90mm planar magnetic drivers, which offer a wide frequency range of 10Hz to 50kHz. Audeze says the result is clearer deta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGIMI's Titan Noir Max 4K projector has a dynamic IRIS for increased contrast</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/xgimis-titan-noir-max-4k-projector-has-a-dynamic-iris-for-increased-contrast-170044625.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc6c7651-cb49-4ad3-b82e-8f4e898e23c4</guid>
      <description>XGIMI, which burst on the scene in 2025 with several impressive projectors, has unveiled its latest high-end model called the Titan Noir Max. The new model revealed at CES 2026 has many of the bells and whistles found on professional-level projectors including a dynamic IRIS system for improved contrast, along with a new thermal system designed to boost brightness.
The Titan Noir Max has a design to XGIMI's Titan model announced last year, but it's taller and a bit squarer with an elegant grille-like pattern on the front. As with other XGIMI models, it features a laser light engine and 4K vide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Pocket-Sized Lab Might Prevent You From Going Into Anaphylactic Shock</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-pocket-sized-lab-might-prevent-you-from-going-into-anaphylactic-shock-2000705496</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705496</guid>
      <description>A person goes to the emergency room in the U.S. every 10 seconds over an allergic reaction to food. Could this gadget bring the numbers down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check In for the First Trailer for &#8216;They Will Kill You&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/they-will-kill-you-trailer-zazie-beetz-2000699567</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699567</guid>
      <description>Zazie Beetz is a housekeeper ready to clean up with violence in the action-horror-comedy flick 'They Will Kill You.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audeze upgrades its Maxwell gaming headset with magnetic ear pads</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851457/audeze-maxwell-2-gaming-headset-sony-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851457</guid>
      <description>Audeze - the headphone-maker now owned by Sony - announced a refreshed version of its Maxwell gaming headset at CES on Monday, offering roomier ear pads that attach magnetically for easy replacement. The Maxwell 2 for PlayStation is available now for $329, while the Xbox version costs $349, though both support Windows, macOS, Nintendo Switch, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosch is taking on Dyson with its first cordless stick vacuums in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851573/bosch-unlimited-9-10-cordless-stick-vacuum-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851573</guid>
      <description>Bosch has announced it's releasing its first ever cordless stick vacuum in the US, the Bosch Unlimited 10 and 9. While Dyson tends to dominate the conversation in the US, Bosch has long been a major player in Europe, making its debut in the US cordless stick vacuum market a notable one. Bosch says the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosch&#8217;s fancy coffee machine is getting Alexa Plus</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853818/bosch-smart-coffee-machine-alexa-plus-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853818</guid>
      <description>At CES this week, Bosch announced the launch of its Personal AI Barista, Powered by Alexa Plus, and teased a new AI-powered cooking feature coming to its connected appliances. Coming to its Bosch 800 Series fully automatic espresso machines, the upgrade allows Alexa users to talk with the machine via an Echo smart speaker "as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm&#8217;s next-gen Snapdragon X2 laptops are here &#8212; and they brought a new friend</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853851/qualcomm-snapdragon-x2-plus-elite-laptops-price-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853851</guid>
      <description>In September, Qualcomm announced the Snapdragon X2 Elite and X2 Elite Extreme, the laptop chips that, it claimed, would be "the fastest and most efficient processors for Windows PCs." They might finally give Intel and AMD a run for their money. Now, CES 2026 is bringing us the first actual laptops based on both that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HP OmniStudio X&#8217;s webcam can watch your work desk</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853937/hp-omnistudio-all-in-one-desktop-2026-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853937</guid>
      <description>HP has announced several spec bumps for its 2026 computing hardware lineup at CES, and its all-in-one desktop PCs are no exception. The latest 27-inch OmniStudio X is being updated with Intel's next-gen processors and Nvidia's RTX 5050 GPU with 8GB of VRAM, alongside new features that make it easier to share your work with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP&#8217;s latest OmniBooks are getting chip bumps and OLED screens</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854240/hp-omnibook-ultra-14-3-5-7-x-laptop-updates-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854240</guid>
      <description>HP has announced a revamped lineup of OmniBook productivity laptops at CES, including its latest AI-focused flagship Ultra model. While pricing and availability haven't yet been revealed, we know the upcoming HP OmniBook Ultra 14 is ditching its previous AMD Ryzen AI 300-series CPUs in favor of Intel's Panther Lake and Qualcomm's Snapdragon X2 series [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2026 BMW iX3 voice assistant will be powered by Alexa+</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/the-2026-bmw-ix3-voice-assistant-will-be-powered-by-alexa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079548</guid>
      <description>BMW is finally getting the next-generation Alexa voice assistant and it&#8217;s coming with a generative AI upgrade. Amazon said Monday that the 2026 BMW iX3 will be equipped with Alexa+, the same generative AI tech that launched in millions of the e-commerce giant&#8217;s smart devices last year. This will be the first vehicle to come [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audeze announces the Maxwell 2 gaming headset, an overhaul of its predecessor, that is targeted firmly at audiophile gamers &#8212; and you can buy it now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/audeze-announces-the-maxwell-2-gaming-headset-an-overhaul-of-its-predecessor-that-is-targeted-firmly-at-audiophile-gamers-and-you-can-buy-it-now</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VRjQ6dhQCA4r2bgLYbEfD9</guid>
      <description>The Audeze Maxwell 2 has just been announced by the premium audio brand, and we've got the key details on its upgrades and enhancements right here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGIMI, best known for projectors, launches its own smart glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/xgimi-best-known-for-projectors-launches-its-own-smart-glasses-170000968.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54390b93-e1df-4254-8d11-df10a104845a</guid>
      <description>Projector maker XGIMI has turned up at CES to launch its own range of AR glasses, but don&#8217;t get the champagne out too soon. MemoMind is a new brand under which its AI-infused eyewear will be sold, with two distinct units arriving at some point in the near future. The company says it has leveraged its know-how in optics and engineering to produce glasses which are unobtrusively light, all the better for blending into your daily life. Fashionistas will even be overjoyed to learn the glasses&#8217; ship in eight different frame styles, five different temple designs and can be worn with prescription len...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brisk It brings its AI cooking tech to an indoor oven at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/brisk-it-brings-its-ai-cooking-tech-to-an-indoor-oven-at-ces-2026-170000705.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66ad8cbc-ae0e-4eb7-b58f-aab0c65f5519</guid>
      <description>Brisk It has shown off AI-enabled smart grills at CES before now, but for 2026, the company is taking its cooking tech indoors. With the Neoma multi-function countertop oven, the company offers AI features that can serve as both sous chef and nutritionist, helping you create dishes that fit your budget, diet and other lifestyle needs. The Brisk It Agentic AI can also help with meal planning and grocery orders on top of automatic cooking cycles for recipes it selects. The Neoma has a temperature range from 90 to 450 degrees Fahrenheit and cooking times of one minute up to twelve hours. This mea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HP Omnibook Ultra 14 at CES 2026: Super sleek and surprisingly durable</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/the-hp-omnibook-ultra-14-at-ces-2026-super-sleek-and-surprisingly-durable-170000330.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9ac6338-dc52-4aa7-91dc-7d2224b8f773</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, HP is showing off its latest flagship consumer laptop: The Omnibook Ultra 14.  It features an all-new super thin design that&#8217;s much tougher than it looks.&#160;According to HP, the Omnibook Ultra 14 is the &#8220;world&#8217;s most durably slim 14-inch consumer notebook,&#8221; which is a somewhat convoluted way of saying the system remains quite portable &#8212; just 0.42 inches thick &#8212; while still passing 20 different military standard tests (MIL-STD-810) for things like shock resistance, drops and extreme temperatures. The whole system is crafted from aluminum, though instead of taking a unibody approach l...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm unveils Snapdragon X2 Plus chip at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/qualcomm-unveils-snapdragon-x2-plus-chip-at-ces-170000392.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5598381-513b-4fef-be01-bcdeb1b9df16</guid>
      <description>CES tends to bring a wave of news from chipmakers, and Qualcomm has used this year's event to announce the Snapdragon X2 Plus laptop processor. This is a more modest version of the flagship Snapdragon X2 Elite chip that Qualcomm unveiled in September.&#160;The Snapdragon X2 Elite will be available in the coming generation of Windows 11 Copilot+ PCs and its integrated Hexagon NPU can deliver the 80 TOPS performance benchmark for powering artificial intelligence tasks. The chip is also equipped with a third-generation Qualcomm Oryon CPU with either six cores or ten cores. For comparison, the Snapdrag...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D&#8217;immenses &#233;toiles pourraient donner naissance aux trous noirs au c&#339;ur des galaxies</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-immenses-etoiles-pourraient-donner-naissance-trous-noirs-coeur-galaxies-w2t8-129730/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-immenses-etoiles-pourraient-donner-naissance-trous-noirs-coeur-galaxies-w2t8-129730/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>On &#233;tudie depuis presque 50 ans ce qui se produit lorsqu'une &#233;toile passe trop pr&#232;s d'un trou noir supermassif. Cela a conduit &#224; des pr&#233;dictions v&#233;rifi&#233;es, mais aussi &#224; d'autres qui ne l'ont pas &#233;t&#233;. Une nouvelle simulation num&#233;rique a probablement donn&#233; la cl&#233; d'une &#233;nigme &#224; ce sujet en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm X2 Plus : une nouvelle puce ARM &#224; l&#8217;autonomie record pour PC portable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/qualcomm/2928617_qualcomm-x2-plus-une-nouvelle-puce-arm-a-lautonomie-record-pour-pc-portable</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/qualcomm/2928617_qualcomm-x2-plus-une-nouvelle-puce-arm-a-lautonomie-record-pour-pc-portable</guid>
      <description>
Au CES de Las Vegas, Qualcomm vient de lever le voile sur sa nouvelle plateforme Snapdragon X2 Plus, petite s&#339;ur du X2 Elite. Une puce qui se destine &#224; l'entr&#233;e de gamme des PC ARM, avec des performances en nette hausse.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra l&#233;ger, puce Qualcomm X2, &#233;cran Oled : HP sort le grand jeu avec son nouveau PC OmniBook Ultra 14</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hp/2923513_ultra-leger-puce-qualcomm-x2-ecran-oled-hp-sort-le-grand-jeu-avec-son-nouveau-pc-omnibook-ultra-14</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hp/2923513_ultra-leger-puce-qualcomm-x2-ecran-oled-hp-sort-le-grand-jeu-avec-son-nouveau-pc-omnibook-ultra-14</guid>
      <description>
HP a profit&#233; du CES 2025 pour annoncer la nouvelle version de son OmniBook Ultra 14. Un ultraportable qui gagne encore en l&#233;g&#232;ret&#233;, configurable avec les derni&#232;res puces Intel et Qualcomm ainsi qu'avec un &#233;cran Oled 120 Hz.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snap up your first drone for less with this big saving on the DJI Mini 4K</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/drones/snap-up-your-first-drone-for-less-with-this-big-saving-on-the-dji-mini-4k</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Xk488j45JQwch8s2FwZVsK</guid>
      <description>Get drone ready as the DJI Mini 4K drops to &#163;215 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I finally tried the Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold and couldn't believe my eyes and hands &#8212; I just hope it doesn't cost a fortune</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/i-finally-tried-the-samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-and-couldnt-believe-my-eyes-and-hands-i-just-hope-it-doesnt-cost-a-fortune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PPn5AC45UN7RobSnGYkcqh</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold is a remarkable feat of engineering with serious productivity potential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On ne va pas se mentir : si le robot CLOiD de LG plie vraiment le linge, je l&#8217;ach&#232;te</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2929313_on-ne-va-pas-se-mentir-si-le-robot-cloid-de-lg-plie-vraiment-le-linge-je-lachete</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2929313_on-ne-va-pas-se-mentir-si-le-robot-cloid-de-lg-plie-vraiment-le-linge-je-lachete</guid>
      <description>
LG vient peut-&#234;tre de tuer le game du CES avant m&#234;me l'ouverture des portes. Son nouveau concept, la "Zero Labor Home", repose sur CLOiD, un robot majordome aux bras articul&#233;s cens&#233; g&#233;rer vos corv&#233;es les plus p&#233;nibles. Oui, m&#234;me le pliage de t-shirts. Trop beau pour &#234;tre vrai ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick! The January sales feature up to &#163;400 off our favourite TVs this week &#8211; but not for much longer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/quick-the-january-sales-feature-up-to-gbp400-off-our-favourite-tvs-this-week-but-not-for-much-longer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gWSCMJCRoHpTLRyfKeTnUH</guid>
      <description>The January sales are winding down soon &#8211; here are the best TV deals to catch before it's too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Motors doubled EV output in 2025 after early Gravity SUV struggles</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/lucid-motors-doubled-ev-output-in-2025-after-early-gravity-suv-struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079675</guid>
      <description>Lucid built more than 18,000 EVs in 2025 and delivered more than 15,000 after a tough start to the year -- still a far cry from the high bar it set in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best AirPods deals you can get right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21302051/best-apple-airpods-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:48:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21302051/best-apple-airpods-deals</guid>
      <description>If you know where to look, you can often score discounts on Apple&#8217;s ever-expanding AirPods lineup. Both the AirPods Max and AirPods 4 (with and without ANC) now consistently receive sizable discounts, as do the newer AirPods Pro 3. While recent shopping events like Black Friday and Cyber Monday delivered some of the steepest discounts [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG TVs at CES 2026: A stunning Wallpaper set, glorious Micro RGB colors and a better Gallery TV</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/lg-tvs-at-ces-2026-a-stunning-wallpaper-set-glorious-micro-rgb-colors-and-a-better-gallery-tv-033739600.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d852af20-a0db-4d1d-8922-0ed895316e13</guid>
      <description>We typically see LG TV announcements a bit before CES, but this year the company had a surprise in store. CES 2026 marks the return of LG's ultra-thin "Wallpaper" TV. The latest version sports a gorgeous OLED screen and wireless connectivity, and it's about as thin as a pencil. We were able to check out the new Wallpaper TV during a CES preview event, along with LG&#8217;s Gallery and Micro RGB sets. The company also announced refreshed OLED and LED sets for this year, but it's clear that 2026 will be filled with intriguing TVs for a variety of consumers.LG's 2026 Wallpaper OLED TVDevindra Hardawar ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les astronomes ont eu du mal &#224; y croire : cet amas de galaxie extr&#234;me fait vaciller leur compr&#233;hension de l&#8217;Univers jeune</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/amas-galaxies-astronomes-ont-eu-mal-y-croire-cet-amas-galaxie-extreme-fait-vaciller-leur-comprehension-univers-jeune-129802/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:45:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/amas-galaxies-astronomes-ont-eu-mal-y-croire-cet-amas-galaxie-extreme-fait-vaciller-leur-comprehension-univers-jeune-129802/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>SPT2349-56.&#160;Depuis qu&#8217;ils l&#8217;ont d&#233;couvert, les astronomes s&#8217;&#233;tonnent de ce qu&#8217;ils observent de cet amas de galaxies qui &#233;voluent dans l'Univers lointain. Et ils viennent juste d&#8217;y faire une d&#233;couverte d&#233;concertante de plus. Une d&#233;couverte qui pourrait remettre en question leurs mod&#232;les...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a trouv&#233; le Wall-E du CES 2026 : il est mignon, hors de prix et&#8230; il n&#8217;a pas de bras</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/robots/2929287_on-a-trouve-le-wall-e-du-ces-2026-il-est-mignon-hors-de-prix-et-il-na-pas-de-bras</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/robots/2929287_on-a-trouve-le-wall-e-du-ces-2026-il-est-mignon-hors-de-prix-et-il-na-pas-de-bras</guid>
      <description>
Vous r&#234;viez d'avoir Wall-E dans votre salon ? Zeroth Robotics l'a fait au CES 2026. Le robot W1 a les chenilles, la bouille sympa et un design industriel soign&#233;. Le probl&#232;me ? Il co&#251;te 5 599 dollars, n'a pas de bras et se d&#233;place tr&#232;s lentement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU gears up for even more tough tech enforcement in 2026 as Trump warns of retaliation</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/eu-gears-up-for-even-more-tough-tech-enforcement-in-2026-as-trump-warns-of-retaliation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Jn6nMxgwwmKeTJBtrqk4cE</guid>
      <description>US Trade Rep says America might have to use "every tool at its disposal" to counter Europe's "unreasonable measures."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the AMD CES 2026 keynote with CEO Lisa Su live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-amd-ces-2026-keynote-with-ceo-lisa-su-live-190012438.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c864a817-a6e7-423f-ab33-fb69dbcbdab4</guid>
      <description>You'll want to tune into AMD's kickoff for CES 2026 today if you're interested in the company's latest AI development and (possibly) new Ryzen chips. This is where the company will lay out its vision for AI applications across its consumer and enterprise offerings. The presentation &#8212; which is the lead keynote for CES 2026 &#8212; will be led by CEO Dr. Lisa Su.
We'll tell you how to tune in to the livestream and what else you can expect to see.
How to watch AMD's keynote live
Dr. Su will deliver a keynote speech from the Palazzo Ballroom at the Venetian on Monday, January 5 at 9:30PM ET (6:30PM PT)....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs v&#233;los pliants &#233;lectriques en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2757651_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-velos-pliants-electriques-en-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2757651_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-velos-pliants-electriques-en-2025</guid>
      <description>
De 16 ou 20 pouces, moteur avant ou arri&#232;re, syst&#232;mes de pliages divers et vari&#233;s, nous avons test&#233; pour vous les v&#233;los &#233;lectriques pliants les plus r&#233;put&#233;s du march&#233;. Suivez le guide&#160;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Hisense CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-hisense-ces-2026-press-conference-live-190040504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9486b306-eae4-49da-a805-9b5cf78d2fb9</guid>
      <description>Xinhua News Agency via Getty Images
Hisense is typically best known for its affordable electronics and home appliances, from TVs to refrigerators. But at CES 2025, the China-based company showed off its premium side with a massive 136-inch micro LED TV &#8212; now available for a jaw-dropping $100,000. So what's in store for this year's show? New leadership, for starters.
The company has two new hires, including Chief Marketing Officer Sarah Larsen and Chief Commercial Officer James Fishler. In a press release, Hisense said Fishler's experience in home entertainment, appliances and HVAC is important...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starlink Is About to Enter a New Conflict Zone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starlink-is-about-to-enter-a-new-conflict-zone-2000705523</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705523</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s satellite megaconstellation will provide free broadband internet access to Venezuela following the U.S. incursion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Air, Gravity EVs Get a Much-Needed Map Update</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lucid-air-gravity-evs-get-a-much-needed-map-update-2000705467</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705467</guid>
      <description>Lucid&#8217;s EVs will use HERE location data to improve EV routing and advanced driving features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin could be gearing up for an exciting but overdue Health Status upgrade &#8211; here&#8217;s what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-trackers/garmin-could-be-gearing-up-for-an-exciting-but-overdue-health-status-upgrade-heres-what-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfBFGrdL6tpozMgearTBQH</guid>
      <description>Garmin's Health Status feature has one small setback, but this new upgrade could allow you to keep tabs on health trends over longer time periods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep your home warm with the Google Nest Learning Thermostat, now only $230</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/854979/google-nest-thermometer-8bitdo-everboom-deals-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:14:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854979</guid>
      <description>While everyone is paying attention to the cool new stuff being exhibited at CES at this very moment, there are some good deals to be had on devices that are already available but equally cool. For example, the fourth-gen Google Nest Learning Thermostat, which our reviewer called &#8220;a stunner,&#8221; is now available for $229.99 at [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Knight confirms 35% of A Thousand Blows season 2 is based on real-life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/steven-knight-confirms-35-percent-of-a-thousand-blows-season-2-is-based-on-real-life</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WRaLyQFxgYQ6NkgSAvRHgW</guid>
      <description>What&#8217;s true in A Thousand Blows season 2? Steven Knight breaks down the real-life events that inspired the next chapter of the historical crime drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec les OpenWear Stereo Pro, Xiaomi propose des &#233;couteurs ouverts et pas chers gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2928883_avec-les-openwear-stereo-pro-xiaomi-propose-des-ecouteurs-ouverts-et-pas-chers-grace-a-cette-offre</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2928883_avec-les-openwear-stereo-pro-xiaomi-propose-des-ecouteurs-ouverts-et-pas-chers-grace-a-cette-offre</guid>
      <description>
Les Xiaomi OpenWear Stereo Pro sont des &#233;couteurs ouverts sans-fil dans un &#233;crin premium, qui se posent autour de l'oreille comme des bijoux, disponibles &#224; 115,31 euros au lieu de 149,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une cyberattaque a frapp&#233; l&#8217;Office fran&#231;ais de l&#8217;immigration et de l&#8217;int&#233;gration, des millions de donn&#233;es vol&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/cyberattaque-frappe-office-francais-immigration-integration.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318175</guid>
      <description>Les donn&#233;es personnelles de centaines de milliers d&#8217;&#233;trangers en France se retrouvent en vente sur le dark web. L&#8217;Office fran&#231;ais de l&#8217;immigration et de l&#8217;int&#233;gration a en effet &#233;t&#233; pirat&#233; par le biais d'un prestataire tiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's new 45W charger from CES is already $10 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/ankers-new-45w-charger-from-ces-is-already-10-off-160707324.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker introduced a nifty little charger at CES 2026, which is a refresh of the pre-existing Nano Charger. It's already on sale for $30, which is a discount of $10. These are preorders, however, with shipments officially going out on January 20.
The 45W charger includes a screen that displays real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to ensure a longer battery lifespan. 


To that end, it works with just about everything. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $20 smart scale is the easiest way to track your 2026 health wins</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-renpho-smart-scale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">061e6gvYlICMvHg8HPWJcHT</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 5, you can get the Renpho Smart Scale for $19.99, down from $34.99, at Amazon. That's a 43% discount or $15 in savings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundcore Is Trying to Fix the Worst Problem With Open Wireless Earbuds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/soundcore-is-trying-to-fix-the-worst-problem-with-open-wireless-earbuds-2000705179</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705179</guid>
      <description>The AeroFit 2 Pro wireless earbuds can shapeshift into open-ear and ANC modes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon veut r&#233;duire le temps perdu &#224; choisir quelque chose &#224; la t&#233;l&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/amazon-veut-reduire-le-temps-perdu-a-choisir-quelque-chose-a-la-tele.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318194</guid>
      <description>Amazon rafra&#238;chit et surtout acc&#233;l&#232;re son interface Fire TV, en se donnant pour mission de r&#233;duire le temps pass&#233; &#224; scroller pour trouver quelque chose &#224; regarder. Et dans la foul&#233;e, le g&#233;ant du commerce en ligne lance une nouvelle gamme de t&#233;l&#233;s connect&#233;es &#224; afficher au mur fa&#231;on tableau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing the Alliwava U58 mini PC, I realized I&#8217;d seen this platform before - and with a little effort, this could have been great</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/alliwava-u58-mini-pc-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Udxk3CiSZGTye5SmjUZWAo</guid>
      <description>The Alliwava U58 offers plenty of functionality, but lacks the performance of mini PCs with more modern chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Is Still Killing a Disturbing Number of Americans, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/covid-19-is-still-killing-a-disturbing-number-of-americans-study-finds-2000705483</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705483</guid>
      <description>Between 2022 and 2024, covid-19 killed roughly 100,000 Americans annually, new research by CDC scientists shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's Soundcore Work AI voice recorder offers transcription in an ultra-compact form factor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/ankers-soundcore-work-ai-voice-recorder-offers-transcription-in-an-ultra-compact-form-factor-160030844.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">584da5c1-6cf1-4105-a4b2-9a4950e76dd1</guid>
      <description>Anker's sub-brand Soundcore just announced a new AI voice recorder at CES 2026. The appropriately-named Work voice recorder is primarily intended for professionals, but also seems useful for students and anyone else who wants an AI to transcribe conversations.
To that end, the company promises 97-percent transcription accuracy via the AI algorithm. The affiliated app will also provide summaries of conversations, like many modern AI tools. Users can double-tap the gadget during important parts of a conversation to ensure it gets preferential treatment.
Anker/Soundcore 
None of this is really th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker unveils a new lineup of chargers and docks at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/anker-unveils-a-new-lineup-of-chargers-and-docks-at-ces-2026-160021195.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a59925-1c86-46f9-b8b4-44c46f9069f6</guid>
      <description>Anker, one of the leaders in third-party chargers, has unveiled a new portfolio of "smart" chargers and docks at CES 2026. The company says the lineup adds improved visual interfaces, faster Qi2 wireless charging and "upgraded ecosystems" for the latest line of iPhone models.
First up is the Anker Nano Charger, which features a smart display, 180-degree foldable prongs and provides up to 45W of power. The plug can identify the exact iPhone model connected and then deliver the right amount of power for your phone. Anker says the Nano uses three-stage power delivery and a "Care Mode" that the co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eufy just revealed a tech-heavy baby bottle washer at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/eufy-just-revealed-a-tech-heavy-baby-bottle-washer-at-ces-160021666.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe2ebe3-51a1-4f7f-8139-4f32f7b3e51d</guid>
      <description>Anker's sub-brand Eufy just revealed a high-tech baby bottle washer at CES 2026. The Bottle Washer S1 is filled to the brim with nifty features that should please frazzled parents.
It's been designed to clean deeper than rival models. The Bottle Washer S1 features a built-in water softener, a first in the product category, which should help remove stubborn minerals. It also includes proprietary HydroBlast technology that cleans baby bottles from every angle. This is assisted by the inclusion of a multi-layer rotating spray.
It sterilizes up to 212 degrees Fahrenheit and dries in just 40 minute...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundcore's Nebula P1i portable projector launches in early 2026 for $369</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/soundcores-nebula-p1i-portable-projector-launches-in-early-2026-for-369-160020321.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e0b60a4-b5e9-4bb0-9f39-456659e13820</guid>
      <description>If you had your eye on Nebula P1 projector but $799 is too rich for your blood, Soundcore has a new option at CES 2026. The Anker affiliate just unveiled the 1080p Nebula P1i portable projector that's less than half the price and even more portable, albeit with less brightness.&#160;
Instead of detachable speakers like the Nebula P1, the P1i's speakers are embedded in the projector and can be flipped open and tilted through 180 degrees. It also lacks the P1's tilting projector body and instead offers a stand that can incline the projector from zero to 12 degrees.&#160;
Though it offers the same 1080p ma...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's new AeroFit 2 earbuds can switch between open-ear and ANC form factors</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/ankers-new-aerofit-2-earbuds-can-switch-between-open-ear-and-anc-form-factors-160014977.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39d9829e-e044-4b85-a493-4fe2cd29ec83</guid>
      <description>Open-ear wireless earbuds are great for running, when keeping some awareness of the world around you is necessary, but not so good when you want premium audio features that require a good seal, like active noise cancellation. At CES 2026, Anker is trying to change that with the Soundcore AeroFit 2 Pro, the company's first open-ear earbuds that offer ANC.
The Soundcore AeroFit 2 Pro features a similar adjustable ear-hook design to Anker's previous AeroFit 2 and AeroFit, but with one extra level of adjustment to help the earbuds create more of a seal in your ear. That change, plus tweaks to the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo's Ultimate 3E gamepad for Xbox offers swappable button modules and joysticks</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/8bitdos-ultimate-3e-gamepad-for-xbox-offers-swappable-button-modules-and-joysticks-160011248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b17f40-a1c7-4317-ac2c-b0ac8a06d512</guid>
      <description>8BitDo just revealed a new gamepad at CES and it's a doozy. The Ultimate 3E Controller for XBox is a modular marvel that should suit just about any configuration preference. That's because many elements are swappable.
There are two different button modules, each with a different feel when pressing down. There are several joystick options, including standard, tall and thick-neck designs. The controller even ships with a pair of D-pad options. One is intended for precision and the other for "smooth, directional rolls."
8BitDo
There are other bells and whistles here. The Ultimate 3E offers a 1000...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Course &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; Has Made a Billion Dollars Already</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avatar-fire-and-ash-box-off-2000705494</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705494</guid>
      <description>The future's bright and full of box office records on Pandora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker Teases a New Whole Home Hybrid Battery Backup System</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anker-teases-a-new-whole-home-hybrid-battery-backup-system-2000705254</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705254</guid>
      <description>The company says it&#8217;s the first of its kind, but remains mum on the specifics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo&#8217;s new wireless Xbox controller has swappable ABXY button switches</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/848331/8bitdo-ultimate-3e-controller-xbox-wireless-tmr-swappable-joysticks</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848331</guid>
      <description>8BitDo's second officially licensed wireless Xbox controller is also its most expensive gamepad to date. The 8BitDo Ultimate 3E Controller for Xbox follows last August's Ultimate 3-mode Controller for Xbox - Rare 40th Anniversary Edition with some excellent upgrades, less branding, and a big price hike. It's got tunneling magnetoresistance (TMR) joysticks, Hall effect triggers [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s powerful new Eufy S2 robot vacuum doubles as an aromatherapy diffuser</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/850483/eufy-robot-vacuum-omni-s2-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850483</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Anker debuted the Eufy S2, a powerful robot vacuum and mop hybrid that cleans your floors while also perfuming your home. According to the company, the robovac features a built-in "aromatherapy system" with scent options that include bamboo, sage, bergamot, lychee, citrus, and basil. The idea is to perfume your space while [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Max sticks with its tried and tested formula for The Pitt season 2 &#8212; and it&#8217;s the best medicine possible</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/the-pitt-season-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LFP3p5QLsUdk3Udxfg5ieD</guid>
      <description>I've been counting down the days until the return of hit HBO Max show The Pitt season 2, and I'm pleased so say I wasn't disappointed &#8211; and you won't be either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 5 days in, the best fitness headphones of 2026 have already been announced &#8212; if they&#8217;ll stick the landing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/only-5-days-in-the-best-fitness-headphones-of-2026-have-already-been-announced-if-theyll-stick-the-landing</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6XS9yRqV3b4ohmdaqUH4nf</guid>
      <description>The Anker Soundcore Aerofit 2 Pro are open earbuds that can switch over to become standard fitness 'phones, fixing problems with the form factor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker Soundcore unveils open earbuds that can adapt to be ear-sealing ANC buds too &#8212; is this the best of both audio worlds?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/anker-soundcore-unveils-open-earbuds-that-can-adapt-to-be-ear-sealing-anc-buds-too-is-this-the-best-of-both-audio-worlds</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4xSj39y5TDFXTKfWEqNa79</guid>
      <description>Anker's new adaptable earbuds are tiny transformers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's CES smart home lineup includes a $1,600 Eufy robovac</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/ankers-ces-smart-home-lineup-includes-a-1600-eufy-robovac-160000133.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d15ea7-428b-47b4-a860-f46048114046</guid>
      <description>It seems like only a few years ago that Anker made nothing more than batteries and chargers. But 15 years into its history, the company's CES portfolio continues to illustrate how much it's expanded. Among other announcements, the company has a new robot vacuum, video doorbell, outdoor light and smart lock. They're all rolling out under Anker's Eufy smart home brand.The company hopes its Eufy Clean Robot Vacuum Omni S2 will be your next robovac. The $1,600 device vacuums with 100 AW suction, and it mops, too. Anker claims the vac works on shag carpets up to about 2 inches (5 cm) in pile height...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab expands its gaming lineup at CES with keyboards, mice and headsets</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/jlab-expands-its-gaming-lineup-at-ces-with-keyboards-mice-and-headsets-160000419.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71e227ca-776e-415e-9cbc-9a90ddc7245a</guid>
      <description>JLab, known for quality consumer audio that doesn't break the bank, is diving further into gaming. At CES 2026, the company has new keyboards, mice and headsets aimed at gamers. Sticking with the brand's "bang for your buck" angle, they're available in three reasonably priced tiers.The entry-level tier adopts the Nightfall brand name, which JLab already used on its 2023 gaming headphones. (They're still available and now come in pink and white colors, alongside the preexisting black.) Joining them is a $40 "ultra-light" mouse that weighs 53g. Also costing $40 is a Nightfall keyboard that the c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab adds ANC to its tiny wireless  earbuds for CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/jlab-adds-anc-to-its-tiny-wireless-earbuds-for-ces-2026-160000342.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c005e93b-7857-49e8-b831-a47b62090bec</guid>
      <description>JLab is following up its ultra-affordable JBuds Mini from 2023 with a new model that supports active noise cancellation at CES 2026. The JBuds Mini ANC are still as tiny as the company's previous wireless earbuds, but now offer customizable ANC for the same $40 price.In comparison to the company's JLab Go POP+, which is only $30, JLab says its new model features a 50 percent smaller charging case, and 30 percent smaller earbuds. The JBuds Mini ANC comes in gray, dark blue, red and pink, and is IP55-rated for dust and sweat resistance. JLab says the Mini ANC get 6.5 hours of battery life per ea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Teens spend hour-plus on their phones at school</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/teens-spend-an-hour-on-phones-at-school</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06SUnKzhxmt0EftVkEqiInX</guid>
      <description>Teens are on Instagram, TikTok, Snapchat, and YouTube while at school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pitt Season 2 review: Big changes ahead for Noah Wyles stellar medical drama</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/the-pitt-season-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03c9euQAhw3vczOCFxoQxiz</guid>
      <description>Emmy-winning drama "The Pitt" remains captivating in Season 2, with new characters upsetting the balance in just the right way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Soundcore introduces new open earbuds with active noise cancellation</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-soundcore-sleep-a30-special-aerofit-2-pro-release</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00bbDCSHTOM7OMPIv9CbueR</guid>
      <description>The Soundcore Sleep A30 Special earbuds will be available as of Jan. 6, with the AeroFit Pro 2 earbuds following shortly after.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le syst&#232;me Tizen des TV et vid&#233;oprojecteurs Samsung &#233;volue avec encore plus d&#8217;IA</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2929151_le-systeme-tizen-des-tv-et-videoprojecteurs-samsung-evolue-avec-encore-plus-dia</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2929151_le-systeme-tizen-des-tv-et-videoprojecteurs-samsung-evolue-avec-encore-plus-dia</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES 2026 de Las Vegas, Samsung a pr&#233;sent&#233; plusieurs &#233;volutions int&#233;ressantes pour son syst&#232;me Tizen qui anime les TV et les vid&#233;oprojecteurs de la marque.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: The latest news, surprises, strange tech, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is here. See the latest news on bleeding-edge tech, EV advancements, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fantastic SteelSeries Arctis GameBuds have returned to their lowest ever price at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-fantastic-steelseries-arctis-gamebuds-have-returned-to-their-lowest-ever-price-at-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">h6TFnuYQ26nyxenHiSMi5o</guid>
      <description>The SteelSeries Arctis GameBuds are a fantastic earbud option for gamers, and right now we're highlighting them selling at a lowest-ever Amazon price in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Govee lamps light up CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-govee-lights-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ph2VEXc6Q83imoYSj5P6o</guid>
      <description>Three new Govee flagship lamps and lighting options were announced at CES 2026, as well as tech advancements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Razr Fold leak suggests Samsung Galaxy Z Fold has major compeition</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/motorola-razr-fold-leak-samsung-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05iFtmwbqhS0eC5rBzvzqX6</guid>
      <description>Motorola's rumored book-style foldable device might have what it takes to stand up to Samsung's Galaxy Z Fold line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi vous ne devriez plus vous faire filmer par les webcams des lieux touristiques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/pourquoi-vous-ne-devriez-plus-vous-faire-filmer-par-les-webcams-des-lieux-touristiques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318163</guid>
      <description>Les cam&#233;ras qui filment et diffusent en permanence un lieu touristique doivent aussi respecter le r&#232;glement europ&#233;en sur les donn&#233;es personnelles. Elles ne sont pas cens&#233;es collecter des donn&#233;es personnelles et donc filmer des personnes dans leur quotidien, a rappel&#233; la CNIL, qui a proc&#233;d&#233; &#224; plusieurs contr&#244;les.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular debloating tool now has fresh powers to strip out Windows 11's AI features &#8211; but I'd proceed with caution</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/a-popular-debloating-tool-now-has-fresh-powers-to-strip-out-windows-11s-ai-features-but-id-proceed-with-caution</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UzLiZUScTVNAABceyRhPpC</guid>
      <description>Hate AI in Windows 11? You're not alone judging by the popularity of AI debloating tools, and this one just got a major update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Egypt vs Benin for *FREE* &#8212; live stream AFCON 2025/26 knockout tie, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/egypt-vs-benin-afcon-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wdfoh9VHVuBNg4A6A2LYe9</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Egypt vs Benin live streams for FREE from anywhere, as Salah and Marmoush aim to find their range in the AFCON last 16 clash in Agadir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 will be smarter, safer and with a much better soundtrack. Here's why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/phone-accessories/2026-will-be-smarter-safer-and-with-a-much-better-soundtrack-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EmLrJUQfPTDFvi3fT4hn8S</guid>
      <description>Baseus raises the bar in mobile digital, smart audio and smart security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix drops emotional trailer for Stranger Things Season 5 documentary</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/netflix-stranger-things-5-making-of-documentary-trailer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04zGO9dxw7S0bQBsRRMPSVq</guid>
      <description>Netflix has dropped a trailer for "One Last Adventure: The Making of Stranger Things 5", a behind-the-scenes documentary for the final season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Series 11 is at the lowest price we've ever seen</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/the-apple-watch-series-11-is-at-the-lowest-price-weve-ever-seen-154609747.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9398dfc3-7cc2-4fa1-ba51-8f9fa52c78af</guid>
      <description>The Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for the lowest price we've ever seen. You can pick up the smartwatch for $300, which is 25 percent off its regular price, a discount of $100. Discounts tend to increase as we get closer to September, when the next generation of Apple Watch is typically announced.
The Series 11 is our best overall smartwatch pick, and we gave it a score of 90 out of 100 in our hands-on review. We were impressed with the battery life, which lasted longer than the 24 hours it's rated for in our testing. We also liked how lightweight and thin the watch is. The 9.7mm thick case ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DS va bient&#244;t lancer une voiture &#233;lectrique et hybride cruciale pour la marque : voici les premi&#232;res images du DS N&#176;7</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ds-automobiles/2928655_ds-va-bientot-lancer-une-voiture-electrique-et-hybride-cruciale-pour-la-marque-voici-les-premieres-images-du-ds-n7</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ds-automobiles/2928655_ds-va-bientot-lancer-une-voiture-electrique-et-hybride-cruciale-pour-la-marque-voici-les-premieres-images-du-ds-n7</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s le succ&#232;s du DS 7 Crossback, le fleuron fran&#231;ais de Stellantis, DS, s'appr&#234;te &#224; offrir une deuxi&#232;me g&#233;n&#233;ration &#224; son SUV best-seller. Ce mod&#232;le, probablement d&#233;nomm&#233; DS N&#176;7, partagera de nombreux &#233;l&#233;ments techniques avec le 3008 &#233;lectrique de chez Peugeot.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Withings Body Scan 2 smart scale promises to be your &#8216;longevity station&#8217; &#8211; thanks to over 60 biomarkers that predict your future health</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/the-withings-body-scan-2-smart-scale-promises-to-be-your-longevity-station-thanks-to-over-60-biomarkers-that-predict-your-future-health</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nieFbqCPsPkkeU7PBnxUXC</guid>
      <description>Withings&#8217; Body Scan 2 is a new smart scale that is packed with AI and advanced health-measuring tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette bague connect&#233;e ajoute des fonctions bien utiles et encore trop rares sur le march&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2929065_cette-bague-connectee-ajoute-des-fonctions-bien-utiles-et-encore-trop-rares-sur-le-marche</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2929065_cette-bague-connectee-ajoute-des-fonctions-bien-utiles-et-encore-trop-rares-sur-le-marche</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES de Las Vegas, RingConn a lev&#233; le voile sur sa troisi&#232;me g&#233;n&#233;ration de bague connect&#233;e. La nouvelle RingConn Gen 3 profite notamment de deux nouveaut&#233;s particuli&#232;rement commodes. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les 10 smartphones les plus populaires de la semaine sur Frandroid : l&#8217;ann&#233;e commence comme elle a termin&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2491986_les-10-smartphones-les-plus-populaires-de-la-semaine-sur-frandroid-lannee-commence-comme-elle-a-terminee</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2491986_les-10-smartphones-les-plus-populaires-de-la-semaine-sur-frandroid-lannee-commence-comme-elle-a-terminee</guid>
      <description>
Pour notre top 10 des smartphones les plus populaires de la semaine sur Frandroid, certaines marques prennent le dessus. Sur ce classement, nous retrouvons Samsung, Xiaomi et OnePlus.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch today's Bosch CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/how-to-watch-todays-bosch-ces-2026-press-conference-live-130020554.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9086383-b545-4c70-a9ca-34644261e45c</guid>
      <description>You might think of Bosch as the modern European equivalent to what the GE brand once was in America. It's a home appliance name (thanks to its partnership with Siemens), but the German multinational brand's core business is really about providing the underlying technology and engineering that powers cars, homes and factories around the world. That focus is reflected at CES 2026, where much of what Bosch is unveiling is intended to be licensed to other companies rather than sold as Bosch-branded products on store shelves.
Case in point is Bosch's automotive plans at CES. The company is showcasi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 could be the year we move beyond smartphones &#8212; led by a Sam Altman and Jony Ive-designed AI device</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/2026-could-be-the-year-we-move-beyond-smartphones-led-by-a-sam-altman-and-jony-ive-designed-ai-device</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BxVARcp4mzFhDyPXRNTg4G</guid>
      <description>2026 could mark the beginning of the post-smartphone era, with OpenAI betting on a Jony Ive-designed, audio-first AI device to redefine how we interact with technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $90 Kindle deal is the best way to finally tackle your TBR list</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-kindle-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036dWGLKPwa3lZhqw6gKMt2</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 5, you can get Amazon's 2024 Kindle (16GB RAM) in Matcha or Black for just $89.99, down from $109.99, at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung unveiled AI-powered products at CES 2026: Everything announced from the year's first press conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/samsung-unveiled-ai-powered-products-at-ces-2026-everything-announced-from-the-years-first-press-conference-230059247.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f895c55-a52d-430d-945c-f98a90fd611d</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 kicked off with a big press conference from one of the biggest companies at the show: Samsung. The tech giant held its "first look" presentation to show off new home products and make a plethora of AI-infused announcements. New TVs, speakers, projectors and more were among the headliners, along with updated gaming monitors and soundbars.
Many of the products announced on stage were not actually new, but instead had been dripped out by Samsung recently. Like its minimalist Music Studio speakers or new Micro RGB TVs. We did get a closer look a previously undisclosed set, a flagship 130-...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
