<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:41:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Novo Nordisk&#8217;s Latest Weight Loss Drug Might Be Its Best Yet&#8212;and a Much-Needed Win</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/novo-nordisks-new-weight-loss-drug-might-be-its-best-yet-and-a-much-needed-win-2000725962</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725962</guid>
      <description>Over a 24 week period, people on UBT251 lost up to 20% of their body weight on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon has reportedly given Anthropic until Friday to let it use Claude as it sees fit</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/the-pentagon-has-reportedly-given-anthropic-until-friday-to-let-it-use-claude-as-it-sees-fit-203549467.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02865f17-7bf6-415a-b262-346a028b08ae</guid>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth will reportedly give Anthropic until Friday to drop certain guardrails for military use, as reported by Axios. The outlet also reported that CEO Dario Amodei met with Hegseth yesterday as the Pentagon ratcheted up pressure on the AI company to give in to its demands.
The makers of Claude have reportedly been offered an ultimatum: Either yield to the government's demands to remove limits for certain military applications, or potentially be forced to tailor its AI model to the government's needs under the Defense Production Act.
Anthropic, for its part, has said th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram head pressed on lengthy delay to launch teen safety features, like a nudity filter, court filing reveals</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/instagram-head-pressed-on-lengthy-delay-to-launch-teen-safety-features-like-a-nudity-filter-court-filing-reveals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096211</guid>
      <description>An email chain with Instagram head Adam Mosseri indicated the company was aware of teen safety issues in DMs in 2018, but didn't launch its unwanted nudity filter until 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founders of long-lost weather app Dark Sky return with a new forecast platform, and it&#8217;s already better than Apple&#8217;s unreliable flagship weather predictions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/founders-of-long-lost-weather-app-dark-sky-return-with-a-new-forecast-platform-and-its-already-better-than-apples-unreliable-flagship-weather-predictions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">M2eGKyxYtSMz8xHW7PWUxd</guid>
      <description>After parting ways with Apple, Dark Sky founders are back with a new forecast app, Acme Weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Leaders Warn European War on American Big Tech Comes With Real Security Risks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/military-leaders-warn-european-war-on-american-big-tech-comes-with-real-security-risks-2000726045</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726045</guid>
      <description>Military officials say Europe is too dependent on U.S. tech to break away now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft says OpenClaw is "not appropriate to run on a standard personal or enterprise workstation" &#8212; so should you be worried?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/microsoft-says-openclaw-is-unsuited-to-run-on-standard-personal-or-enterprise-workstation-so-should-you-be-worried</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4kbMpGMyfHPrQkRShnqdQA</guid>
      <description>Microsoft warns OpenClaw&#8217;s design blends automation and persistent credentials, creating structural risks unsuitable for standard personal or enterprise workstations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Now Own an Official Version of the Superior &#8216;Star Trek&#8217; Mug</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-deep-space-nine-official-coffee-mug-raktajino-2000726005</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726005</guid>
      <description>After Picard's tea mug made a comeback a few years ago, it's time for the better 'Trek' mug&#8212;and better beverage&#8212;to get the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sent an AI-generated push alert that included a racial slur</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-sent-an-ai-generated-push-alert-that-included-a-racial-slur-195951493.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9620b47a-f76a-47b1-9cf6-52dbfc742d0a</guid>
      <description>Google sent out an AI-generated news alert that included the N-word, according to reporting by Deadline. The push notification featured a link to a story by The Hollywood Reporter regarding an incident at the recent BAFTA Film Awards. The word appeared in the notification under the link.
This was first spotted by Instagram user Danny Price, who accompanied a screengrab with a caption reading "what an interesting Black History Month this has turned out to be." Google has since apologized and said that it has "removed the offensive notification" and is "working to prevent this from happening aga...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Bluetooth Speaker Is on Sale for $50 Off Right Now</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/jbl-flip-7-deal-0223/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699c92e1c3e34b153305c790</guid>
      <description>JBL's fabulous Flip 7 speaker is on super sale for $100. Grab this go-anywhere companion on the cheap before the nice weather hits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File-Sharing Network Soulseek Has Been Flooded With AI Homer Simpson Cover Songs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/file-sharing-network-soulseek-has-been-flooded-with-ai-homer-simpson-cover-songs-2000725979</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725979</guid>
      <description>Slop has come for the pirates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's the first teaser for A24's adaptation of The Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/heres-the-first-teaser-for-a24s-adaptation-of-the-backrooms-194300513.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e668cff7-af1a-4f2f-800f-7a2fea33e1d6</guid>
      <description>Three years after announcing plans to produce a film based on the viral YouTube short, The Backrooms (Found Footage) in 2023, A24 has released the first teaser for its adaptation. Backrooms, as the film is now called, is directed by the short's original creator, Kane Parsons, and will be released on May 29, 2026.The teaser offers little to go on for anyone who hasn't watched the original short or the series of videos Parsons made after it, but it is replete with The Backrooms' hallmark: ominous liminal spaces. Layered over footage of stranger and stranger rooms (or perhaps one room becoming th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More startups are hitting $10M ARR in 3 months than ever before</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/more-startups-are-hitting-10m-arr-in-3-months-than-ever-before/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096218</guid>
      <description>AI has brought the startup world the rise of startups that instantly hit multimillion ARR. Stripe revealed some data that shows how common this has become.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple mental health apps riddled with high severity security flaws &#8212; data of millions put at risk, so be on your guard</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/multiple-mental-health-apps-riddled-with-high-severity-security-flaws-data-of-millions-put-at-risk</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">s3erQ5e8r2JHSK6LHkcmbL</guid>
      <description>Researchers found 1,500 vulnerabilities in 10 popular apps, including dozens of high-severity flaws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo will start offering robotaxi rides in four more cities</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/waymo-will-start-offering-robotaxi-rides-in-four-more-cities-192841871.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdd4cda2-0dbc-430c-aaa1-5f0862d4e827</guid>
      <description>Waymo had set out some big plans for expanding its autonomous vehicle taxi program across the US in 2025 and it appears to be continuing that pace into 2026. Today, the company announced that the first public riders can begin using its fully autonomous ride-hailing service in Dallas, Houston, San Antonio and Orlando.&#160;To start, these robotaxi rides will only be available for a small number of people with the Waymo app in those cities. "We will be inviting new riders on a rolling basis to ensure a seamless experience across our initial service areas, as we meaningfully scale our operations ahead...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $20 on Our Favorite Gaming Headset</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/arctis-nova-3-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699de7e8d54c22d6c9a69616</guid>
      <description>The SteelSeries Arctis Nova 3 have excellent compatibility and a comfortable, lightweight fit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord is delaying its global age verification rollout</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/883852/discord-age-verification-global-walkback-delay</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T14:17:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883852</guid>
      <description>Discord won't roll out age verification globally on its platform next month as previously announced, and says in a blog post that it's delaying the launch until the second half of 2026. "The way this landed, many of you walked away thinking we're requiring face scans and ID uploads from everyone just to use Discord. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram&#8217;s TV app is launching on Google TV devices</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/instagrams-tv-app-is-launching-on-google-tv-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096265</guid>
      <description>By bringing Reels to TVs, Instagram looking to better compete with YouTube, which&#160;largely dominates the TV space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#8217;s Curiosity Finds Crunchy Nodules Where Ancient Martian Water Once Stood</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasas-curiosity-finds-crunchy-nodules-where-ancient-martian-water-once-stood-2000725891</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725891</guid>
      <description>Curiosity has been exploring a region filled with boxwork formations, which formed billions of years ago when water leaked through rock cracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury sanctions Russian zero-day broker accused of buying exploits stolen from U.S. defense contractor</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/treasury-sanctions-russian-zero-day-broker-accused-of-buying-exploits-stolen-from-u-s-defense-contractor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096189</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Treasury announced it was imposing sanctions against a Russian broker of zero-day exploits, its founder and two affiliates, citing a threat to U.S. national security. Another affiliated zero-day broker in the United Arab Emirates was also sanctioned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maul Kinda Regrets Wanting to Be Rid of the Jedi in &#8216;Shadow Lord&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/maul-kinda-regrets-wanting-to-be-rid-of-the-jedi-in-shadow-lord-2000725990</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725990</guid>
      <description>The former Sith apprentice has a slight change of heart in the upcoming 'Star Wars' animated show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google adds a way to create automated workflows to Opal</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/google-adds-a-way-to-create-automated-workflows-to-opal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096036</guid>
      <description>Google is adding a new feature to Opal to create automated workflows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi la nouvelle perc&#233;e d&#8217;ASML change tout</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/processeurs/2988547_pourquoi-la-nouvelle-percee-dasml-change-tout</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/processeurs/2988547_pourquoi-la-nouvelle-percee-dasml-change-tout</guid>
      <description>
Vous ne connaissez peut-&#234;tre pas ASML, mais cette entreprise hollandaise poss&#232;de les cl&#233;s de votre vie num&#233;rique. En boostant la puissance de ses machines &#224; 1 000 W, elle vient de s'assurer que nos futurs produits technologiques ne soient pas de simples luxes inaccessibles.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Likely the Largest Breach in U.S. History&#8217;: What You Need to Know About the Conduent Fiasco</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/likely-the-largest-breach-in-u-s-history-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-conduent-fiasco-2000725930</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725930</guid>
      <description>The known size of the breach keeps growing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify and Liquid Death release a limited-edition speaker shaped like&#8230; an urn?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/spotify-and-liquid-death-release-a-limited-edition-speaker-shaped-like-an-urn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096232</guid>
      <description>Spotify and Liquid Death launched what might be the wildest product of the year: a speaker shaped like a urn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony reveals the Death Stranding 2 required PC specs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/sony-reveals-the-death-stranding-2-required-pc-specs-184411856.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08428548-4956-470f-953b-9ace20dc3a2a</guid>
      <description>We're less than a month from the availability of Death Stranding 2: On the Beach on PC, and today Sony released the required specs. Despite designer Hideo Kojima being known for spectacle in his projects, the minimum specs are quite reasonable. The low graphics preset runs on an NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660 or AMD Radeon RX 5500 XT 8GB, and that will give players average performance of 1080p at 30 frames per second, which is rough but at least makes the game available for players who haven&#8217;t upgraded in awhile. Intel Core i3-10100 or AMD Ryzen 3 3100 are the recommended GPUs for that graphics tier....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
