<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:29:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon has a new leader for its &amp;#8216;AGI&amp;#8217; group as it plays catch-up on AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846721/amazon-new-agi-leader-peter-desantis-rohit-prasad</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T15:28:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846721</guid>
      <description>Amazon's head of artificial general intelligence (AGI), Rohit Prasad, is leaving the company next year as it reaches an "inflection point" in its development of the technology, CEO Andy Jassy announced on Wednesday. As part of the change, Peter DeSantis, a senior vice president at Amazon Web Services, will helm a new division focused on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Sues TV Makers, Claiming They Can Collect Images of What Viewers Are Watching</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/texas-sues-tv-makers-claiming-they-can-collect-images-of-what-viewers-are-watching-2000700858</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700858</guid>
      <description>Texas AG Ken Paxton claims the companies are "illegally recording Americans&#8217; devices inside their own homes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study links Amazon's algorithmic pricing with erratic, inflated costs for school districts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/study-links-amazons-algorithmic-pricing-with-erratic-inflated-costs-for-school-districts-202047988.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df5f1b96-cfd9-42dd-bde4-f0b9ac8c35bd</guid>
      <description>When it comes to convenience, it&#8217;s hard to beat Amazon. And that rationale isn&#8217;t limited to consumers: Many local districts shopping for supplies with public funds apply the same logic. But the Institute for Local Self-Reliance (ILSR) published a study earlier this month (via The American Prospect) that illustrates the cost of that bargain. It suggests that Amazon&#8217;s &#8220;dynamic pricing&#8221; has led many schools and other localities to overpay for supplies.Public schools and local governments have historically bought supplies by soliciting competitive bids from local suppliers. Those vendors then resp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video game hardware sales had a historically bad November in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846693/video-game-hardware-sales-november-2025-circana</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T15:14:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846693</guid>
      <description>Spending on video game hardware during November totalled $695 million, a drop of 27 percent compared to last year, according to market analyst company Circana, "This is the lowest video game hardware spending total for a November month since the $455M reached during the November 2005 tracking period," Circana says. In addition, 1.6 million units [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube just won THE Oscars, and the iconic show is set to leave ABC in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/youtube-just-won-the-oscars-and-the-iconic-show-is-set-to-leave-abc-in-2029</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AGHytSvJgvAiw5mwojaSa3</guid>
      <description>The Oscars are heading to YouTube in 2029. Here's what that means.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une &#233;tude alerte que des collisions en cha&#238;ne de satellites pourrait d&#233;buter en 2,8 jours en cas de panne !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/satellite-etude-alerte-collisions-chaine-satellites-pourrait-debuter-28-jours-cas-panne-128716/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:07:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/satellite-etude-alerte-collisions-chaine-satellites-pourrait-debuter-28-jours-cas-panne-128716/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;orbite terrestre basse ressemble de plus en plus au p&#233;riph&#233;rique parisien aux heures de pointe. Les risques de collision augmentent. Et les scientifiques pr&#233;sente un &#171;&#8201;cas limite&#8201;&#187;, pas si rare que &#231;a, dont les cons&#233;quences pourraient s&#8217;&#233;taler sur plusieurs d&#233;cennies&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P&#233;nurie de RAM : pr&#233;parez-vous &#224; payer plus pour avoir la m&#234;me chose ou pire, &#224; payer plus pour avoir moins</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/memoire/2913977_penurie-de-ram-preparez-vous-a-payer-plus-pour-avoir-la-meme-chose-ou-pire-a-payer-plus-pour-avoir-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/memoire/2913977_penurie-de-ram-preparez-vous-a-payer-plus-pour-avoir-la-meme-chose-ou-pire-a-payer-plus-pour-avoir-moins</guid>
      <description>
Entre les centres de donn&#233;es IA qui raflent tout et une p&#233;nurie de DRAM qui pourrait durer jusqu'en 2028, le march&#233; du hardware plonge dans une zone de turbulences in&#233;dite. C'est votre portefeuille qui va douiller.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Bluetooth trackers for Apple and Android phones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23769840/best-bluetooth-trackers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T14:56:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23769840/best-bluetooth-trackers</guid>
      <description>Some people rarely lose things. Wallets are always exactly where they&#8217;re supposed to be, keys never go missing, and remotes never slip between the couch cushions. And then there&#8217;s the rest of us &#8212; the folks who can&#8217;t ever seem to find the thing that was right there a few seconds ago. For us, there [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IA appliqu&#233;e au Qu&#233;bec | SCALE AI investit dans 24&#160;nouveaux projets</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-17/ia-appliquee-au-quebec/scale-ai-investit-dans-24-nouveaux-projets.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:47:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1023e3098af333dbf6a06db9be76514</guid>
      <description>SCALE IA, la grappe canadienne en intelligence artificielle (IA), investira 73,3&#160;millions dans 24&#160;nouvelles initiatives d&#8217;IA appliqu&#233;e au Qu&#233;bec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will stream the Oscars &#8212; exclusively &#8212; beginning in 2029</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/youtube-will-stream-the-oscars-exclusively-beginning-in-2029/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077032</guid>
      <description>The news highlights YouTube's growing dominance in the television space and a major shift as streaming takes on more live events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is 'pausing' third-party VR headsets from ASUS and Lenovo</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/meta-is-pausing-third-party-vr-headsets-from-asus-and-lenovo-193622900.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f912c80-b1d9-46ad-a2e8-53f16f155d66</guid>
      <description>Last year, Meta announced that it was opening up its VR operating system to other headset makers, starting with ASUS and Lenovo. Now, it seems that Meta is pumping the brakes on the effort and those third-party Horizon OS headsets might never actually launch.The company has "paused" the program,  Road to VR  reported. Meta confirmed the move in a statement to Engadget, saying that it's instead focusing on "building the world-class first-party hardware and software needed to advance the VR market." ASUS and Lenovo didn't immediately respond to a request for comment. Both companies have said lit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than half of workers say they really "love" Excel - and surprisingly enough, it's younger workers who are apparently more infatuated</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/more-than-half-of-workers-say-they-really-love-excel-and-surprisingly-enough-its-younger-workers-who-are-apparently-more-infatuated</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dYYYNyHVukwDoSCLSEvGMY</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Excel remains essential across generations, with younger finance professionals embracing its advanced features, while AI integration enhances modern workflow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now there's a robot app store because we all want our bots to kick like Bruce Lee</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/now-theres-a-robot-app-store-because-we-all-want-our-bots-to-kick-like-bruce-lee</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mRMPgtXvrdAE8y6j7MEJs6</guid>
      <description>Unitree has launched the first known robot app store, which provides canned actions that you can upload or download and add to your robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is pausing its dream of sharing Quest&#8217;s Horizon OS with third-party headset makers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/meta-is-pausing-its-dream-of-sharing-quests-horizon-os-with-third-party-headset-makers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076975</guid>
      <description>The company said that it would revisit opportunities for third-party partnerships in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Toys of 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/best-toys-collectibles-2025-star-wars-lego-2000700345</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700345</guid>
      <description>io9's purveyors of plastic joy look back on their favorites of the year, from 'Star Wars' goodness to robot model kits, Lego, and plenty more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Non-Political&#8217; Creators Have Outsized Influence on Audience&#8217;s Politics, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/non-political-creators-have-outsized-influence-on-audiences-politics-study-finds-2000700841</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700841</guid>
      <description>Measuring the Joe Rogan effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 Flash arrives with reduced costs and latency &#8212; a powerful combo for enterprises</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/gemini-3-flash-arrives-with-reduced-costs-and-latency-a-powerful-combo-for</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5GUZ1JhDwvYPFkf9ATytEw</guid>
      <description>Enterprises can now harness the power of a large language model that's near that of the state-of-the-art Google&#8217;s Gemini 3 Pro, but at a fraction of the cost and with increased speed, thanks to the newly released Gemini 3 Flash.The model joins the flagship Gemini 3 Pro, Gemini 3 Deep Think, and Gemini Agent, all of which were announced and released last month.Gemini 3 Flash, now available on Gemini Enterprise, Google Antigravity, Gemini CLI, AI Studio, and on preview in Vertex AI, processes information in near real-time and helps build quick, responsive agentic applications.&#160;The company said i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le &#171; Mal Aim&#233; &#187; d&#233;figur&#233; ? Intermarch&#233; fait marche arri&#232;re et ne proposera pas les photos par IA dans les photomatons</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2913123_le-mal-aime-defigure-intermarche-cede-finalement-a-lia-pour-surfer-sur-le-buzz</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2913123_le-mal-aime-defigure-intermarche-cede-finalement-a-lia-pour-surfer-sur-le-buzz</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s s'&#234;tre vu f&#233;liciter pour l'absence d'IA &#224; la cr&#233;ation de son spot de pub, Intermarch&#233; va utiliser l'IA.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This cute little Behringer synthesizer sounds massive and costs just $49</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/this-cute-little-behringer-synthesizer-sounds-massive-and-costs-just-49-191513007.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7cf7538-f43f-4182-aa84-60cdb675778f</guid>
      <description>Behringer is no stranger to remaking classic synthesizers and selling them at much cheaper price points. However, this latest release may just take the budget-friendly cake. The company just introduced the UB-1 Micro, previously called the Spirit, a portable analog synth inspired by the Oberheim Matrix line that costs just $49.
Despite the price tag, this thing still manages to sound extremely beefy. It features a pair of digitally controlled oscillators (DCOs) based on the Oberheim Matrix 6 analog chip. The monophonic/duophonic synth boasts two LFOs to control filters and tuning and an arpegg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best stocking stuffer ideas you can shop for $50 or less</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-best-stocking-stuffer-ideas-you-can-shop-for-50-or-less-130049822.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32df60b9-ebc7-4bd2-a9e6-0777477036d5</guid>
      <description>The big ticket tech gifts may get the lion's share of attention during the holidays, but it's surprising how much people appreciate small and thoughtful accessories and gadgets. We picked out a dozen such stocking stuffers for under $50 &#8212; perfect for a little something extra for a loved one or a welcome gift for a coworker. Just be sure to check the shipping windows to make sure these handy gizmos will arrive in time. Here are some of our favorite techie gift ideas that come in at $50 or less.
Best stocking stuffers for $50 or less


























Check out the rest of our gift ideas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Very Best Gifts for Dads of Christmas 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-very-best-gifts-for-dads-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6937095a008ae88504a14ec6</guid>
      <description>Dads are traditionally tough to shop for&#8212;let me help with these handpicked gift ideas for fathers with great taste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI toys are telling kids how to find knives, and senators are mad</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/846573/ai-toys-built-on-openais-chatgpt-inappropriate-content-senators-letter</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T14:03:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846573</guid>
      <description>Sexual fetish content. How to light a match. Where to find knives in the home. These are all conversation topics that recently-recalled children's toys - built atop AI chatbots like OpenAI's GPT-4o - are capable of bringing up to children. On Tuesday, U.S. senators Marsha Blackburn (R-Tenn.) and Richard Blumenthal (D-Conn.) sent a letter to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X &#8216;Bid Adieu&#8217; to the Twitter Brand, but Now It&#8217;s Suing to Keep It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/x-bid-adieu-to-the-twitter-brand-but-now-its-suing-to-keep-it-2000700860</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700860</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s company is suing a startup that wants to resurrect Twitter, claiming it never gave up the brand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nex Playground is a fine entry-level video game console for preschoolers, elderly individuals and anyone interested in light fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nex-playground-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zf4ZDJemhRyt3DgaLd9dRF</guid>
      <description>A motion control-only gadget that&#8217;s cheaper than the Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation 5, Xbox Series and PC yet almost manages to stand next to them uniquely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the stunning collapse of Believer Meats, the $600 million lab-grown meat startup</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462102/believer-meats-stunning-collapse-600-million-cooling-cultured-meat-industry</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462102/believer-meats-stunning-collapse-600-million-cooling-cultured-meat-industry</guid>
      <description>How Believer went from sizzle to fizzle in a matter of weeks, the latest blow to the once-promising alternative meat industry. 
Last month, Believer Meats was basking in acclaim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco says Chinese hackers are exploiting its customers with a new zero-day</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/cisco-says-chinese-hackers-are-exploiting-its-customers-with-a-new-zero-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076962</guid>
      <description>Cisco said it discovered a Chinese hacking campaign targeting its customers by exploiting a zero-day in some of the company's most popular products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars will exclusively air on YouTube starting in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/the-oscars-will-exclusively-air-on-youtube-starting-in-2029-181545531.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aadd9da4-bf4f-4282-81c6-149564519e84</guid>
      <description>The entertainment industry&#8217;s most well-known awards show is heading to streaming. The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences (AMPAS) has announced that the Academy Awards, popularly known as the Oscars, will exclusively air on YouTube starting in 2029. The new deal means the awards show is abandoning its long-time partnership with ABC (owned by frequent Oscars heavyweight, The Walt Disney Company), though the Oscars will continue to air on the network through its 100th anniversary in 2028.The Academy Awards will be joined by other Academy events and programming on the Oscars YouTube chann...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Didn&#8217;t Make My Old-Ass Smart Speaker Feel Any Less Dumb</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gemini-didnt-make-my-old-ass-smart-speaker-feel-any-less-dumb-2000700763</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700763</guid>
      <description>Gemini for Home has its perks, but I don't know that free users will feel the "next-gen" of it all compared with the old Google Assistant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans are fine with giving cash as holiday gifts, new poll finds</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462221/holiday-gifts-cash-poll-new-years-eve</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462221/holiday-gifts-cash-poll-new-years-eve</guid>
      <description>The poll found about two-thirds of Americans under 45 say cash is a &#8216;very&#8217; acceptable holiday gift.
Welcome to exhausted America 2025: Most adults are more than a little fine with&#160;doling out cash as gifts, and many plan to be asleep before midnight on New Year&#8217;s Eve, according to a new AP-NORC poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal user beware - experts warn subscriptions being abused to send fake purchase emails</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/paypal-user-beware-experts-warn-subscriptions-being-abused-to-send-fake-purchase-emails</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GAZGohYdmoNrqpo9fNae5X</guid>
      <description>A legitimate PayPal platform is being abused to bypass email protections and send phishing messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Loses the Oscars to the Home of MrBeast and &#8216;Hot Ones&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oscars-streaming-youtube-2029-2000700856</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700856</guid>
      <description>YouTube will stream the Super Bowl of the movies starting in 2029.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars will stream on YouTube in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846560/youtube-the-oscars-streaming-2029</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:30:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846560</guid>
      <description>The Oscars are headed to YouTube - in a few years. "Beginning in 2029, the Oscars will broadcast exclusively on YouTube for free globally and on YouTube TV in the U.S.," YouTube announced. YouTube's coverage will include the red carpet, behind the scenes content, and Governors Ball access. The deal runs through 2033, according to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 22 best gift ideas for the remote worker in your life</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-22-best-gift-ideas-for-the-remote-worker-in-your-life-140037336.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7354ab-106c-4b9a-ab03-3baa917ca395</guid>
      <description>For many folks, working from home is simply the new normal. If you&#8217;re looking to treat someone who spends most of their time in the home office, this holiday season is as good a time as any to make their daily routine a little more convenient. As a collection of remote workers ourselves, we at Engadget have rounded up a few gift ideas that should add a bit more delight to the WFH life.
Best gifts for remote workers












































Check out the rest of our gift ideas here. This article originally appeared on Engadget at https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
