<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:59:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient&#8217;s heat pumps get new smarts to enable old building retrofits</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/gradients-heat-pumps-get-new-smarts-to-enable-old-building-retrofits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088864</guid>
      <description>Gradient's heat pumps fit in windows, minimizing installation times. Now, it is introducing software to make those units more intelligent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tiny-but-mighty Minisforum MS-01 is a "small form factor dream" that tackles big workloads &#8212; and it's just $775 for a limited time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-tiny-but-mighty-minisforum-ms-01-is-a-small-form-factor-dream-that-tackles-big-workloads-and-its-just-usd775-for-a-limited-time</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MPyv3fhHWpMZUKk8QUQW5M</guid>
      <description>Minisforum MS-01 mini PC is powered by Intel&#8217;s Core i5-12600H, with 32GB of DDR5 memory and a 1TB SSD, and is currently priced at just $775 at Newegg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Lead Exposure Really Declining? A Century of Hair Holds the Answer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/is-lead-exposure-really-declining-a-century-of-hair-holds-the-answer-2000717249</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717249</guid>
      <description>Before the agency, lead levels were shockingly higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony's WH-1000XM6 headphones are down to a record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/sonys-wh-1000xm6-headphones-are-down-to-a-record-low-price-175038776.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4519507c-493c-4bae-a537-e3800e375935</guid>
      <description>Sony's wireless WH-1000XM6 headphones are on sale for $398 via Amazon. This is a record-low price, as it drops $62 from the price tag. The sale applies to all three colorways.
These easily topped our list of the best wireless headphones. They are, in a word, fantastic. The headphones are packed with premium features, like advanced ANC. There are a whopping 12 ANC microphones throughout and a brand-new chip to power the feature. The end result? It successfully blocks background noise at medium and high frequencies, including the human voice. 


The sound quality is extremely pleasing to the ear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Club is producing short video dramas and building a social network around them</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/watch-club-microdrama-video-social-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089080</guid>
      <description>Watch Club will house microdramas and fan discussions in the same app, creating a fandom-focused social media experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Are All in on Boosting Fraud Allegations in California</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/republicans-boosting-fraud-allegations-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696a8411f85864716b5ca613</guid>
      <description>Right-wing influencers who were instrumental in spreading allegations of fraud in Minnesota ahead of ICE's surge are now going after a number of California&#8217;s social welfare programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, Ubisoft did actually announce The Division: Definitive Edition but no one saw it, and it's not a remake or remaster like fans expected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/no-ubisoft-did-actually-announce-the-division-definitive-edition-but-no-one-saw-it-and-its-not-a-remake-or-remaster-like-fans-expected</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yqZJvjmEViCgDPVfpJYUP7</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft has released Tom Clancy's The Division: Definitive Edition for PlayStation, Xbox, and PC, after advertisements for the game leaked last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit founders launch Luffu, a way to integrate your family's health data</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/fitbit-founders-launch-luffu-a-way-to-integrate-your-familys-health-data-173251994.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3377d239-4e88-40f2-9319-933d33bc277d</guid>
      <description>Fitbit's founders have a new startup. Two years after leaving Google, James Park and Eric Friedman announced a new platform that shifts the focus from the individual to the family. They say the Luffu mobile app "uses AI quietly in the background" to collect and organize family health information."At Fitbit, we focused on personal health &#8212; but after Fitbit, health for me became bigger than just thinking about myself," Park said in a press release. The app is particularly focused on the "CEO of the family" &#8212;  the person who manages appointments, prescriptions and other health-related tasks.But t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;&#233;l&#233;gance du MacBook Air M4 13&#8243; &#224; port&#233;e de main gr&#226;ce &#224; cette r&#233;duction de 265 &#8364; pour une dur&#233;e tr&#232;s limit&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2964903_lelegance-du-macbook-air-m4-13-a-portee-de-main-grace-a-cette-reduction-de-265-e-pour-une-duree-tres-limitee</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2964903_lelegance-du-macbook-air-m4-13-a-portee-de-main-grace-a-cette-reduction-de-265-e-pour-une-duree-tres-limitee</guid>
      <description>
L'ultraportable embl&#233;matique d'Apple est sur le devant de la sc&#232;ne avec sa puce M4 capable de g&#233;rer le multit&#226;che &#224; retrouver pour 934 euros sur Cdiscount au lieu de 1199 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're not going to go down the road of pay-to-win or trapping you to buy monetized products' &#8212; Sea of Remnants developer discusses microtransactions in the upcoming free-to-play game</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/were-not-going-to-go-down-the-road-of-pay-to-win-or-trapping-you-to-buy-monetized-products-sea-of-remnants-developer-discusses-microtransactions-in-the-upcoming-free-to-play-game</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">X4G6CihSHQjPdyaBzh2Bi8</guid>
      <description>A Sea of Remnants developer talks about the upcoming game's monetization systems and promises that they will be fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian hackers are targeting a new Office 365 zero-day, so patch now or face attack</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/russian-hackers-are-targeting-a-new-office-365-zero-day-so-patch-now-or-face-attack</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">umGgboN9aZvgBojSZ5ZG9i</guid>
      <description>Ukraine's defenders have spotted a new hacking attack using a freshly fixed Office flaw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter&#8217;s New Measurements: Flatter, Squashed, Still the Biggest Boy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jupiters-new-measurements-flatter-squashed-still-the-biggest-boy-2000717242</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717242</guid>
      <description>"Textbooks will need to be updated."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Director of &#8216;Wall-E&#8217; Has a New Movie That Looks Like a Mini &#8216;Cloud Atlas&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-director-of-wall-e-has-a-new-movie-that-looks-like-a-mini-cloud-atlas-2000717272</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717272</guid>
      <description>Rashida Jones, Kate McKinnon, and Daveed Diggs star in 'In the Blink of an Eye,' out February 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Le niveau de haine est tel qu&#8217;il doit partir &#187; : chez Ubisoft, des salari&#233;s r&#233;clament la t&#234;te d&#8217;Yves Guillemot</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2965183_le-niveau-de-haine-est-tel-quil-doit-partir-chez-ubisoft-des-salaries-reclament-la-tete-dyves-guillemot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2965183_le-niveau-de-haine-est-tel-quil-doit-partir-chez-ubisoft-des-salaries-reclament-la-tete-dyves-guillemot</guid>
      <description>
Les repr&#233;sentants de Solidaires Informatique ont exprim&#233; clairement leur souhait de voir le patron d'Ubisoft quitter ses fonctions.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lotus Health nabs $35M for AI doctor that sees patients for free</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/lotus-health-nabs-35m-for-ai-doctor-that-sees-patients-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089121</guid>
      <description>This AI doctor is licensed in all 50 states, the startup says. The deal was led by CRV and Kleiner Perkins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le bug du Patch Tuesday qui emp&#234;che certains PC Windows 11 de s&#8217;&#233;teindre se propage &#224; Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-bug-du-patch-tuesday-qui-empeche-certains-pc-windows-11-de-seteindre-se-propage-a-windows-10.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323981</guid>
      <description>La premi&#232;re mise &#224; jour de l&#8217;ann&#233;e de Windows a cr&#233;&#233; des probl&#232;mes en cascade chez les utilisateurs. Apr&#232;s avoir touch&#233; principalement les machines sous Windows 11, le bug qui emp&#234;che les machines de s&#8217;&#233;teindre s&#8217;&#233;tend &#224; pr&#233;sent aux PC sous Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 things you need to know before giving financial gifts</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485977/morningstar-personal-finance-gifts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T17:11:24</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485977/morningstar-personal-finance-gifts</guid>
      <description>If you have gifting to loved ones on your mind, here are some considerations related to taxes and logistics. Gifting logistics Unless you&#8217;re writing a check from your bank account, the logistics of gifting funds can get a bit complicated. If you want to gift from your IRA, your only option is to sell a [&#8230;]
If you have gifting to loved ones on your mind, here are some considerations related to taxes and logistics....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police raid X&amp;#8217;s Paris office as UK investigation continues</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/873142/french-police-raid-x-investigation</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T12:10:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873142</guid>
      <description>A raid on X's Paris office was carried out by the Paris prosecutor's cybercrime unit on Tuesday with Europol and French police as part of an ongoing investigation that expanded in July to include Grok. As previously reported by Reuters, Elon Musk and former X CEO Linda Yaccarino were also summoned for hearings in April. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google voudrait en finir avec ChromeOS en 2034</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/google-voudrait-en-finir-avec-chromeos-en-2034.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323982</guid>
      <description>La fusion d'Android et de Chrome OS pour les PC n'est pas pr&#232;s d'arriver. Des documents de justice montrent que Google compte prendre son temps avant de lancer &#171; Aluminium OS &#187;, le nom de code de ce projet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts for coffee lovers in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/the-best-gifts-for-coffee-lovers-in-2026-184515579.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b63475d-e4f0-4226-bc2d-a30d95f5990d</guid>
      <description>When it comes to making a great cup at home, us coffee nerds are constantly learning and love to try new things. Whether the person you&#8217;re shopping for is a newly indoctrinated pour over lover or obsessive over every brewing parameter, we&#8217;ve compiled a list of the best gear for coffee geeks that you can get. Spanning brewing, grinding and, of course, drinking, we&#8217;ve got a range of options that can help the java geek in your life expand their at-home setup or just try something new. And for the person that already has it all, we&#8217;ve got something for them too.
Best gifts for coffee lovers






...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comment faire un partage de connexion sur un smartphone Android ou iPhone&#8201;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/comment-faire/tutoriaux/345546_tuto-comment-partager-la-connexion-de-son-mobile-avec-un-autre-appareil</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/comment-faire/tutoriaux/345546_tuto-comment-partager-la-connexion-de-son-mobile-avec-un-autre-appareil</guid>
      <description>
Un probl&#232;me de Wi-Fi pour vous connecter depuis votre ordinateur ? Pas de souci, vous pouvez partager votre connexion 4G ou 5G depuis votre smartphone et le transformer en hotspot Wi-Fi (ou point d'acc&#232;s Wi-Fi en fran&#231;ais) pour vous connecter depuis n'importe o&#249;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Switch is Nintendo&amp;#8217;s best-selling console &#8212; and its most transformative</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/873098/nintendo-switch-era-best-selling-console</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873098</guid>
      <description>Nintendo has had plenty of highs over its few decades in the video game industry. Popularizing home consoles with the NES, introducing new audiences to games through the Wii's motion controls, and the touchscreen Trojan horse that was the Nintendo DS, to name a few. But often these successes were followed by missteps; the Wii [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arsenal vs Chelsea Free Streams: How to watch Carabao Cup 2025-26 semi-final online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/arsenal-vs-chelsea-carabao-cup-2025-26-semi-final-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dTDsdyjGvgunAbebrtPoxj</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch free streams of Arsenal vs Chelsea from anywhere in the world in this Carabao Cup 25-26 semi-final second leg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much do VPNs cost?</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-much-do-vpns-cost-170000567.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fac04803-35b8-43c9-8be5-eca5a7af23b6</guid>
      <description>So you've decided you need a virtual private network to hide your browsing activity from your ISP, change your virtual location, stay safe on public Wi-Fi and enjoy all the other benefits. The inevitable next question is: "Should I pay for one? If so, how much?"All the best VPNs cost money, but it can be hard to tell an overpriced service apart from one that's priced according to its value. On this page, I'll share the costs for top VPN services, calculate the industry average and explain what makes VPNs cost as much as they do. At the end, I'll share a few tips for making a VPN fit your budge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks' serverless database slashes app development from months to days as companies prep for agentic AI</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/databricks-serverless-database-slashes-app-development-from-months-to-days</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7vT1HYBxdk5W1SMKSSdEXH</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Databricks coined the term 'data lakehouse' to describe a new type of data architecture that combines a data lake with a data warehouse. That term and data architecture are now commonplace across the data industry for analytics workloads.Now, Databricks is once again looking to create a new category with its Lakebase service, now generally available today. While the data lakehouse construct deals with OLAP (online analytical processing) databases, Lakebase is all about OLTP (online transaction processing) and operational databases. The Lakebase service has been in development s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone on TikTok is &#8216;regulating their nervous system&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485280/everyone-on-tiktok-is-regulating-their-nervous-system</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485280/everyone-on-tiktok-is-regulating-their-nervous-system</guid>
      <description>What this even means&#8212;and how you can do it on your own to reduce anxiety.
&#8220;Me everyday bc my nervous system doesn&#8217;t know the difference between a busy day at work or being attacked by a tiger,&#8221; a TikTok post reads.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even Dell can't escape RAM crisis price hikes &#8212; but I've found 5 laptop deals that can save you up to $650 on top-rated devices</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/even-dell-cant-escape-ram-crisis-price-hikes-but-ive-found-5-laptop-deals-that-can-save-you-up-to-usd650-on-top-rated-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qYSyfkxAnEdPeqpqteH7eL</guid>
      <description>The RAM and storage crisis is causing price hikes across the industry, but if you're shopping for a laptop today, you can still save up to $650 with these 5 best deals I've found in the Dell Tech Days sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Project Zomboid Server Hosting of 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/best-project-zomboid-server-hosting-of-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">W8vaYQBBJ5ynqUXuyLQee4</guid>
      <description>The best Project Zomboid server hosting doesn't have to be expensive or lack features. I've picked out all the best options for your zombie killing ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police search X office in Paris, summon Elon Musk for questioning</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/french-police-search-x-office-in-paris-summon-elon-musk-for-questioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089111</guid>
      <description>The Paris prosecutor&#8217;s office announced that it is expanding a criminal investigation into X for alleged crimes, including the possession and distribution of child sexual exploitation material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla lance ses nouveaux panneaux solaires qui peuvent produire de l&#8217;&#233;lectricit&#233; m&#234;me &#224; l&#8217;ombre (ou presque)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2964793_tesla-lance-ses-nouveaux-panneaux-solaires-qui-peuvent-produire-de-lelectricite-meme-a-lombre-ou-presque</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2964793_tesla-lance-ses-nouveaux-panneaux-solaires-qui-peuvent-produire-de-lelectricite-meme-a-lombre-ou-presque</guid>
      <description>
Le g&#233;ant am&#233;ricain Tesla pr&#233;sente une nouvelle s&#233;rie de panneaux solaires destin&#233;s aux particuliers. Ces mod&#232;les sont optimis&#233;s pour une installation plus simple et une production solaire plus efficace.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : voici les ultimes offres &#224; saisir pour ce dernier jour de promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_soldes-dhiver-2026-voici-les-ultimes-offres-a-saisir-pour-ce-dernier-jour-de-promotions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_soldes-dhiver-2026-voici-les-ultimes-offres-a-saisir-pour-ce-dernier-jour-de-promotions</guid>
      <description>
Il ne faut pas se le cacher, la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes est souvent le moment o&#249; l'on trouve les meilleures offres, car les e-commer&#231;ants comme Amazon, Fnac, Darty ou encore Boulanger veulent &#233;couler les derniers stocks. Et c'est encore plus le cas pendant le dernier jour de l'&#233;v&#233;nement... 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les emplois occup&#233;s par les femmes plus expos&#233;s &#224; l&#8217;intelligence artificielle</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-03/les-emplois-occupes-par-les-femmes-plus-exposes-a-l-intelligence-artificielle.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:50:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6399e9c679de3f2f9012944b105a4cab</guid>
      <description>Les emplois souvent occup&#233;s par des femmes et par des travailleurs qui ont une formation universitaire sont plus expos&#233;s &#224; l&#8217;intelligence artificielle que d&#8217;autres, indique mardi l&#8217;Institut de la statistique du Qu&#233;bec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs SSD M.2 internes (ou externe) pour votre PlayStation 5 en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/912747_quel-disque-dur-et-ssd-externe-choisir-pour-la-ps5</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/912747_quel-disque-dur-et-ssd-externe-choisir-pour-la-ps5</guid>
      <description>
Plus de place pour les jeux sur votre PlayStation&#160;5 ou PS5 Pro toute neuve&#8201;? Ajoutez-lui donc un SSD interne NVMe ou un disque SSD externe pour ne plus jamais avoir &#224; supprimer de titres. Voici notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs mod&#232;les. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN slashes prices for Valentine&#8217;s Day &#8211; here&#8217;s how to save up to 81%</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-slashes-prices-for-valentines-day-heres-how-to-save-up-to-81-percent</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MVVNcrH8q3yKs4XEJJQzaQ</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN Valentine's deal brings discounts on all one-year and two-year plans until February 16. Here's how to get your VPN bargain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai visit&#233; l&#8217;usine de batteries Porsche : pourquoi ce v&#233;ritable joyau technologique en Europe m&#8217;a laiss&#233; un sentiment d&#8217;amertume</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/porsche/2961783_jai-visite-lusine-de-batteries-porsche-pourquoi-ce-veritable-joyau-technologique-en-europe-ma-laisse-un-sentiment-damertume</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/porsche/2961783_jai-visite-lusine-de-batteries-porsche-pourquoi-ce-veritable-joyau-technologique-en-europe-ma-laisse-un-sentiment-damertume</guid>
      <description>
J'ai visit&#233; la premi&#232;re usine europ&#233;enne de Porsche qui produit les batteries du nouveau Cayenne &#233;lectrique. Une plong&#233;e dans un univers ultra robotis&#233; et impressionnant, clairsem&#233; de d&#233;ceptions qui prouvent le retard pris par l'Europe sur l'Asie dans le domaine.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to keep your Minecraft server safe and secure</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/how-to-keep-your-minecraft-server-safe-and-secure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bwDb3PQUBZ66fzoBGoGtGH</guid>
      <description>Running your own Minecraft server is very satisfying but does incur some risk. Here's how to minimize that risk and run a successful server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les derniers stocks tablettes tactiles sont en train de s&#8217;&#233;couler avant la fin des soldes d&#8217;hiver ! Le top des derni&#232;res offres</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941463_les-derniers-stocks-tablettes-tactiles-sont-en-train-de-secouler-avant-la-fin-des-soldes-dhiver-le-top-des-dernieres-offres</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941463_les-derniers-stocks-tablettes-tactiles-sont-en-train-de-secouler-avant-la-fin-des-soldes-dhiver-le-top-des-dernieres-offres</guid>
      <description>
Pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d'hiver, les tablettes tactiles se mettent le mieux possible en avant avec des r&#233;ductions sans commune mesure. Boud&#233;s il n'y a pas si longtemps encore, ces appareils ont maintenant les faveurs des consommateurs, notamment pendant les soldes d'hiver.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears grow as Freeview could get switched off in 2034 &#8212; but there&#8217;s a major silver lining that could come from it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/fears-grow-as-freeview-could-get-switched-off-in-2034-but-theres-a-major-silver-lining-that-could-come-from-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7HY4PiwLSiZojDa82t2XC5</guid>
      <description>&#8220;It&#8217;s 2026 not 1950&#8221; &#8211; instead of keeping Freeview on life support for the sake of it we should focus on building something better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Corruption Allegations Levied at Trump Over Newly Revealed UAE Crypto Deal</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/more-corruption-allegations-levied-at-trump-over-newly-revealed-uae-crypto-deal-2000716952</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716952</guid>
      <description>U.S. Senator Chris Murphy called the reported deal &#8220;mind-blowing corruption.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are 7 OLED TVs that I personally recommend watching the Super Bowl on  &#8212; Samsung, LG and Sony from $599.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/here-are-7-oled-tvs-that-i-personally-recommend-watching-the-super-bowl-on-samsung-lg-and-sony-from-usd599-99</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">C8jB24XgXWyRLtKQ3PpoK8</guid>
      <description>Here are 7 OLED TVs that I'm personally recommending to watch the Super Bowl on, including deals from Samsung, Sony, and LG starting at just $599.99</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gr&#226;ce &#224; cette r&#233;duction de 42 %, les lunettes AR premium Xreal One Pro transforment votre quotidien en grand &#233;cran permanent</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2964755_grace-a-cette-reduction-de-42-les-lunettes-ar-premium-xreal-one-pro-transforment-votre-quotidien-en-grand-ecran-permanent</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2964755_grace-a-cette-reduction-de-42-les-lunettes-ar-premium-xreal-one-pro-transforment-votre-quotidien-en-grand-ecran-permanent</guid>
      <description>
Les Xreal One Pro sont la version luxe des Xreal One, des lunettes de r&#233;alit&#233; augment&#233;e qui fonctionnent comme un &#233;cran externe d'ordinateur, &#224; retrouver pour 485,58 euros sur AliExpress au lieu de 850 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing May Drop a Cheaper Phone and Headphones Soon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nothing-may-drop-a-cheaper-phone-and-headphones-soon-2000717196</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717196</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to argue over a new Nothing phone design?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FSR Redstone : pourquoi la nouvelle it&#233;ration du FSR va changer la vie des joueurs &#233;quip&#233;s en AMD [Sponso]</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/2957487_amd-fsr-redstone-pourquoi-la-nouvelle-iteration-du-fsr-va-changer-la-vie-des-joueurs-equipes-en-amd</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/2957487_amd-fsr-redstone-pourquoi-la-nouvelle-iteration-du-fsr-va-changer-la-vie-des-joueurs-equipes-en-amd</guid>
      <description>
D&#233;ploy&#233; en fin d&#8217;ann&#233;e derni&#232;re, le FSR Redstone, la technologie software made in AMD pour am&#233;liorer la qualit&#233; visuelle des jeux vid&#233;o, est une petite r&#233;volution. Pourquoi ? Parce que le constructeur a revu sa conception du FSR de A &#224; Z en travaillant sur une suite de fonctionnalit&#233;s reposant sur l&#8217;IA pour booster les performances de ses GPU.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is killing off some popular standalone OneDrive and SharePoint plans because they aren't profitable enough</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-is-killing-off-some-popular-standalone-onedrive-and-sharepoint-plans-because-they-arent-profitable-enough</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UnKHpTWqb7Y6kzufmsTWqR</guid>
      <description>Microsoft says low customer demand and "unintended or nonstandard usage" caused it to pull the plug on these OneDrive/SharePoint plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney announces Josh D&#8217;Amaro will be its new CEO after Iger departs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/disney-announces-josh-damaro-will-be-its-new-ceo-after-iger-departs-161616420.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b869bc02-ed87-4970-b5ce-b0d8cf50fc73</guid>
      <description>Stop me if you've heard this one before. Disney has announced a successor to outgoing CEO Bob Iger, effective in March. Josh D&#8217;Amaro, current chairman of Disney Experiences, was tapped for the role in a unanimous vote by the company's board of directors.
D&#8217;Amaro has been at Disney for 28 years, where he oversaw theme parks, cruises and consumer products including video games. The company had previously appointed Bob Chapek, the Disney Parks chairman at the time, as successor to Bob Iger in 2020. At the time, Iger had served as CEO since 2005. But Chapek only lasted until 2022, when Bob Iger re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Colbert&#8217;s &#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Role Is Driving Me Nuts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-stephen-colbert-rant-2000716950</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716950</guid>
      <description>The late-night host's role as the academy announcer feels like the show at its least sincere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris Authorities Raid the Offices of Elon Musk&#8217;s X</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paris-authorities-raid-the-offices-of-elon-musks-x-2000717234</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717234</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk and former X CEO Linda Yaccarino have also been summoned for questioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What tech CEOs and executives have said about ICE&#8217;s actions in Minnesota</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/what-tech-ceos-and-executives-have-said-about-ice-in-minnesota/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088364</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration&#8217;s approach to immigration has reached a level of violence that the tech industry cannot ignore. Here's how tech leaders are responding to the moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February&#8217;s Xbox Game Pass additions include High on Life 2, Madden NFL 26 and Avatar: Frontiers of Pandora</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/februarys-xbox-game-pass-additions-include-high-on-life-2-madden-nfl-26-and-avatar-frontiers-of-pandora-160656985.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5fba9c4-cc75-4f2e-ab26-11efefc813b7</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has revealed the first wave of Xbox Game Pass additions for February, and it feels like there's a bit of something for everyone this time around. Two of the titles land on the service today across the Game Pass Ultimate, Premium and PC Game Pass tiers: Final Fantasy II (cloud, Xbox Series X/S and PC) and Like A Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii (cloud, console, handheld and PC). Final Fantasy II is a "remodeled 2D take" on the classic 1988 RPG, while Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii is a wild-looking spin-off of the main Like a Dragon series with pirates and naval combat.Madden NFL 26 is hittin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Code was down, forcing developers to take a long coffee break</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/873093/claude-code-down-outage-anthropic</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T11:05:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873093</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's Claude AI models experienced a major outage today, impacting products like Claude Code. Developers were seeing a 500 error when trying to use Claude Code, and Anthropic said that it was seeing elevated error rates on its APIs "across all Claude models." Anthropic quickly identified the root cause and implemented a fix within around [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: Everything we're expecting from the S26 launch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-everything-were-expecting-from-the-s26-launch-130000556.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup. Official invites have yet to be shared, but the date is widely expected to be near the end of the month.Whenever it does happen, Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hands-on coverage of Samsung's new smartphones soon after they're announced. While we wait for an official invite, he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our chances of seeing a new Nvidia-powered handheld PC with RTX 5070-level power are improving &#8211; but I'd expect the price to be a dealbreaker</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cpu/our-chances-of-seeing-a-new-nvidia-powered-handheld-pc-with-rtx-5070-level-power-are-improving-but-id-expect-the-price-to-be-a-dealbreaker</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">x5gZqX6oBVCjss6wtK2TQT</guid>
      <description>I smell a new Nvidia handheld PC on the horizon, thanks to fresh chip teases from Jensen Huang, but let's hope I haven't jinxed it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dyson PencilVac is finally available and costs $600</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/the-dyson-pencilvac-is-finally-available-and-costs-600-160059016.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94c7af1d-7d09-4fb7-bbf2-d5edda445028</guid>
      <description>The Dyson PencilVac stick vacuum is finally available for purchase in the US after being revealed
. It costs $600. The company says this is the "world's slimmest vacuum cleaner." We haven't broken out any rulers to confirm that statement, but it's certainly a ridiculously thin stick vac.
It achieves this thinness by using a motor inspired by the company's
. This is a small motor that can actually rest in the shaft, so there's not a noticeable bulge where the components have been placed. This stick vacuum is actually, well, a stick. Just take a look at it.



  A vacuum being emptied.
 

  Dyso...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These speakers are what you&#8217;d find in the center of an art, molecular science and hi-fi Venn diagram and I want them</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/speakers/these-speakers-are-what-youd-find-in-the-center-of-an-art-molecular-science-and-hi-fi-venn-diagram-and-i-want-them</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZfAk7yVxGNyyGZvB8gMy5o</guid>
      <description>Love music, love interior design, want something that combines both on your wall? Meet Ultrasonic's Molecular Audio system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I didn't even know Netflix was on the PS3, but it won't matter soon &#8212; the streaming app will leave the console after 16 years next month</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/i-didnt-even-know-netflix-was-on-the-ps3-but-it-wont-matter-soon-the-streaming-app-will-leave-the-console-after-16-years-next-month</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MpqjdUL5Xwu3BdQgYBiPgj</guid>
      <description>Netflix is being removed from the PlayStation 3 on March 2, 2026, after 16 years of support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I didn&#8217;t expect to love Dyson&#8217;s PencilVac Fluffycones &#8211; but I did</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/872981/dyson-pencilvac-fluffycones-vacuum-hands-on-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872981</guid>
      <description>As The Verge's resident robot vacuum reviewer, I don't have a lot of time (or space) in my life for stick vacs, and frankly, the ones I have used have largely disappointed me. Top-heavy, bulky, always getting clogged or running out of battery - they're so&#8230; manual. But then I met PencilVac Fluffycones, Dyson's new [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI Prestige 14 Flip AI+ review: An ultraportable for Arc Raiders, thanks to Intel's Panther Lake</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/msi-prestige-14-flip-ai-review-an-ultraportable-for-arc-raiders-thanks-to-intels-panther-lake-160000606.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fc77d5d-0224-47ff-93bd-72847f18de59</guid>
      <description>MSI Prestige 14 Flip AI+ is a surprisingly powerful ultraportable held back by a clunky trackpad. It's a shame, really, because it's very well-designed and thanks to Intel&#8217;s Panther Lake CPU, it can even run games like Arc Raiders without breaking a sweat. It also has more ports than most thin and light machines, its OLED screen is great for productivity work and at three pounds it's easy to carry around all day. But curse its mechanical trackpad &#8212; why does it even exist when Apple, Microsoft and others have been able to implement excellent haptic touchpads for years? Come on now.


Hardware
W...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
