<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:45:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Helldivers 2&amp;#8217;s new &amp;#8216;slim&amp;#8217; version saves 131GB of space on your drive</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/836948/helldivers-2-file-size-decrease</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T15:32:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836948</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been short on storage on your PC, the latest Helldivers 2 beta update might help. The developers said Tuesday they&#8217;ve managed to cut down the PC file size for Helldivers 2 by about 85 percent, freeing up enough space for at least one or two more large games.&#160; In a post on the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Can Detect Buried Objects Without Touching Them, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/humans-can-detect-buried-objects-without-touching-them-study-finds-2000684179</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000684179</guid>
      <description>We apparently have more in common with some shorebirds than we previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microreactor startup Antares raises $96M for land, sea, and space-based nuclear power</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/02/microreactor-startup-antares-raises-96m-for-land-sea-and-space-based-nuclear-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072000</guid>
      <description>Antares is designing and building small modular reactors that it plans to deploy for commercial, space, and defense applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Max&amp;#8217;s Mad Men 4K release is the opposite of a remaster</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/836922/hbo-max-man-men-4k-errors-red-in-the-face-lionsgate</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T15:14:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836922</guid>
      <description>Though HBO Max was very proud to announce that it would be the first platform to stream Mad Men in 4K, the show's new rollout has been an absolute mess. When HBO Max subscribers fired up the app yesterday hoping to see Don Draper and company in glorious 4K, many were dismayed to see that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Sims 4 DLC is an official SpongeBob collab</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-next-sims-4-dlc-is-an-official-spongebob-collab</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kUS5HH5R9ttyjLx2DpsUvk</guid>
      <description>Two Spongebob DLC packs are coming to The Sims 4, perfect for building your own pineapple under the sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walmart's Cyber Monday sale is extended &#8211; here are 55 deals worth buying from Apple, Ninja, Shark, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/walmarts-cyber-monday-sale-is-extended-here-are-55-deals-worth-buying-from-apple-ninja-shark-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WZmx3KoasND5F2xd9rCe2k</guid>
      <description>Walmart's Cyber Monday sale has been extended, and I've rounded up today's 55 best deals on AirPods, TVs, air fryers, vacuums, laptops, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 3-monitor dock lacks aesthetic charm, but when it comes to performance, the StarTech 150US-USB4DockTriple is spot on.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/startech-150us-usb4-docktriple-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q9ZkNPduqF3aud7JHbwrnR</guid>
      <description>StarTech hardware is known for professional computing solutions at relatively affordable prices. Here this USB4 docking station provides solid triple 4K display support and reliable performance for any professional needing easy access to ports on the desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Quietly Rolls Back Its AI Anime Dubs After Massive Backlash</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-anime-ai-dub-backlash-removal-2000694695</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694695</guid>
      <description>As quickly as they arrived, many of Prime Video's controversial generated dubs have been removed from the streamer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 55 Best Shows on Disney+, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (December 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-shows-disney-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">632c75aa74ce5b82a68ef323</guid>
      <description>The Beatles Anthology, Percy Jackson and the Olympians, and Fire and Water: Making The Avatar Films are just a few of the shows you should be watching on Disney+ this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock&#8217;s powerful Saros 10 robovac is still at its lowest price ever</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/836687/roborock-saros-10-cyber-week-2025-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836687</guid>
      <description>Black Friday and Cyber Monday brought some of the best deals of the year on robot vacuums. One of the handful of great discounts remaining is on the Roborock Saros 10, which we recently crowned the runner-up in our buying guide to the best robovac you can buy. This robovac and mop hybrid is still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chase&#8217;s newest Sapphire Lounge, complete with champagne service, makes a case for its $795 price tag</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91451338/chase-sapphire-airport-lounge-amex-platinum-competetion</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91451338/chase-sapphire-airport-lounge-amex-platinum-competetion</guid>
      <description>Locked in a rewards arms race with Citi, Amex, and Capital One, the finance giant leans into lavishness for its new lounge at the Harry Reid Airport.
In the high-stakes premium travel race of 2025, every major credit card issuer is trying to claim the loyalty of affluent travelers&#8212;and airport lounges have become the most visible battleground. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"The world is not slowing down" - AWS CEO says AI agents will be bigger than the Internet, so act now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-world-is-not-slowing-down-aws-ceo-says-ai-agents-will-be-bigger-than-the-internet-so-act-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SsS8uPVvRhvUyCyAJ92qyX</guid>
      <description>With AI agents becoming more important than ever, AWS CEO Matt Garman reveals what the company has planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT had some issues earlier, but it&#8217;s back &#8212; here&#8217;s what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/chatgpt-outage-december-openai</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dUYn64GnUKPjg2JrkvsXhD</guid>
      <description>Whether you were trying to ask ChatGPT for help with an email or any other query, it's clear that the AI chatbot had some issues today, December 2, 2025.  Read on for TechRadar's live reporting of ChatGPT's increased errors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I swear by this Dyson stick vac, especially now it&#8217;s cheaper than ever for Cyber Week</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/i-swear-by-this-dyson-stick-vac-especially-now-its-cheaper-than-ever-for-cyber-week</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">m95To3Hd7nB3KyDRQ3j3eP</guid>
      <description>This sci-fi Dyson stick vac with a frickin' laser is a steal at $399 in the Cyber Week sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday-Cyber Monday shoppers spent more online and in person this year, driving $44.2 billion in sales</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/black-friday-cyber-monday-shoppers-total-spending-more-online-in-person</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05BR6Wj2NJzOSW6FIWhfWxM</guid>
      <description>Shoppers spent quite a bit of money between Black Friday and Cyber Monday this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Switch 2 is still on sale at multiple retailers if you missed out during Cyber Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/836519/nintendo-switch-2-mario-kart-world-bundle-walmart-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T14:48:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836519</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest surprises of Cyber Monday was the excellent discount we saw on the Nintendo Switch 2 Mario Kart World console bundle, which dropped in price by $50. We expected the price to return to normal once the shopping holiday ended, but &#8212; surprise, surprise &#8212; it&#8217;s still going strong. Several major retailers [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 157 Best Cyber Week Deals&#8212;Save up to 57% Off Gear We Love</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/cyber-monday-deals-2025-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69271d9a58e4e06eb6f254cb</guid>
      <description>Cyber Monday is over, but many deals are still available, at least for now. These are the absolute best discounts on gear we've tested ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Dell donates over $6 billion to &#8216;Trump accounts&#8217; for kids: Here&#8217;s who&#8217;s eligible to claim $250 per child</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452341/michael-dell-donates-over-6-billion-to-trump-accounts-for-kids-heres-whos-eligible-to-claim-250-per-child</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452341/michael-dell-donates-over-6-billion-to-trump-accounts-for-kids-heres-whos-eligible-to-claim-250-per-child</guid>
      <description>The gift from Michael and Susan Dell, announced on Tuesday, funds a program from Trump&#8217;s One Big Beautiful Bill Act.
Michael Dell, along with his wife Susan, announced on Tuesday they are donating $6.25 billion to so-called &#8220;Trump accounts&#8221;&#8212;a program that gives $1,000 of &#8220;free money&#8221; from the federal government to children in the U.S. born on, or after, January 1, 2025 through the end of 2028, while Trump is in office....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Machine today, Steam Phones tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/820656/valve-interview-arm-gaming-steamos-pierre-loup-griffais</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T14:42:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=820656</guid>
      <description>It's a big deal that Valve is making a game console. But I'm beginning to think the Steam Machine may end up a footnote in gaming history. What if Valve could bring PC games not just to its own living room consoles, but also to the Arm chips that billions of people have in their [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The spectacle of Bryan Johnson and his livestreamed shrooms trip</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/02/the-spectacle-of-bryan-johnson-and-his-livestreamed-shrooms-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071937</guid>
      <description>Bryan Johnson livestreamed his shrooms trip -- which included both Grimes and Marc Benioff -- as part of his controversial longevity research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s AI chief paid the price for the company&#8217;s stalled progress</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452240/apple-ai-chief-john-giannandrea-dismissed-google-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452240/apple-ai-chief-john-giannandrea-dismissed-google-ai</guid>
      <description>John Giannandrea&#8217;s dismissal is more complicated than the headlines suggest, but it also marks the start of a new approach to AI at the company.&#160;
Apple&#8217;s AI boss, John Giannandrea, is stepping down after seven years on the job. Apple&#8217;s stock price got a slight boost on the news, as some investors saw Apple signaling a new urgency to bring AI to its devices....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market holds steady as bond yields and bitcoin stabilize</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452544/stock-market-bitcoin-bonds-stabilize</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452544/stock-market-bitcoin-bonds-stabilize</guid>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500 rose 0.1%, coming off its&#160;first loss in six days. 
The U.S. stock market is holding relatively steady on Tuesday as both bond yields and&#160;bitcoin&#160;stabilize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 50+ best Christmas gifts for 2025: Find unique gift ideas youd never think of on your own</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-christmas-gifts-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01mTr31ooZ4Eybv8IFlh3Gh</guid>
      <description>To find the best Christmas gifts, Mashable reporters and editors review products all year long, and we love recommending holiday gift ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20+ Cyber Monday Lego deals still live: We found Star Wars, Botanicals, Icons, and Disney sets still on sale</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-cyber-monday-lego-deals-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06npYcRcqDBTLaTbg8c2NsC</guid>
      <description>20+ Lego sets are still on sale after Cyber Monday, from the retiring Star Wars Tantive IV to a Target-exclusive Lego Botanicals set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HBO Max 4K Stream of Mad Men Included Visible Crew Members on the Puke Pump</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hbo-max-4k-stream-mad-men-included-visible-crew-members-2000694657</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694657</guid>
      <description>Very on brand for HBO Max.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Taps Preacher Who Blames Vaccines for Cancer, Compares Covid Tracking to Nazi Germany</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rfk-jr-taps-preacher-who-blames-vaccines-for-cancer-compares-covid-tracking-to-nazi-germany-2000694531</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694531</guid>
      <description>Kirk Milhoan has claimed without evidence that the covid-19 shots caused spikes in cancer and miscarriages. Now he's helping shape the country's vaccine policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Data Might Determine How Much You Pay for Eggs</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/algorithmic-pricing-eggs-ny-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692e095fd5e5956e7dc4edc1</guid>
      <description>A newly enacted New York law requires retailers to say whether your data influences the price of basic goods like a dozen eggs or toilet paper, but not how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Google AI veteran to replace outgoing Apple exec John Giannandrea</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-and-google-ai-veteran-to-replace-outgoing-apple-exec-john-giannandrea</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">S28XwpEYPFNhk7yYrbuZQd</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s ML and AI Strategy SVP is leaving next year, but ex-Microsoft AI VP Amar Subramanya is joining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android&amp;#8217;s new &amp;#8216;Call Reason&amp;#8217; flags important calls before you even pick up</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/836838/android-beta-call-reason</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T14:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836838</guid>
      <description>Android users will soon have an option to add an &#8220;urgent&#8221; indicator to their calls, which shows up on the receiver&#8217;s incoming call screen and in their call history if they don&#8217;t pick up. It&#8217;s a new feature in beta testing in the Phone by Google app, Call Reason, that will only work for people [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Movie Industry Kept Trying to Make Popcorn Buckets Happen Again This Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-movie-industry-kept-trying-to-make-popcorn-buckets-happen-again-this-year-2000694230</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694230</guid>
      <description>The viral 'Dune: Part Two' sandworm emerged in early 2024, and its impact is still being felt whether we like it or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is bringing AI-powered notification summaries to more Android devices</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/836490/google-android-16-update-ai-notification-summaries</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836490</guid>
      <description>More Android phones will soon support AI-powered notification summaries. The feature comes bundled in the latest version of Android 16 and rolled out on Pixel devices last month, but now other phone makers like Samsung can begin adding it to their devices. Unlike Apple&#8217;s version of the feature for iOS, Google is limiting it to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android 16&#8217;s latest update ushers in a more frequent release schedule</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/836832/android-16-qpr2-release-timeline-update</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836832</guid>
      <description>The latest update for Android 16 has arrived, marking the official end to Google&#8217;s annual release schedule. Compared to the major Android 16 launch in June, the new 16 QPR2 release is a minor update that expands features for notifications, icons, calling screens, and more, and signals the start of Google&#8217;s long-awaited plans to release [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android 16 adds AI notification summaries, new customization options, and more</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/02/android-16-adds-ai-notification-summaries-new-customization-options-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071800</guid>
      <description>The rollout of the new Android 16 features, which are first coming to Pixel devices, marks a new chapter in how Android updates work, as the company is shifting from a single yearly update to more frequent releases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold's folding mechanism looks odd, but it's the right call on a crucial design decision</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-z-trifolds-folding-mechanism-looks-odd-but-its-the-right-call-on-a-crucial-design-decision</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vj2c7hSUUVamv8hu8t5ep5</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold is finally official, and while Samsung&#8217;s first multi-fold device might look a bit peculiar, I think it&#8217;s taken the right approach with an important design feature</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Android 16 update has landed &#8211; here are the 7 biggest features</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/android/the-next-android-16-update-has-landed-and-these-are-the-7-biggest-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ruMbNw4bWWoBrNXHEYzsa</guid>
      <description>A new version of Android 16 has landed with all sorts of new features and improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione hearing: Officer recalls arrest at McDonald&#8217;s</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452539/luigi-mangione-hearing-officer-detwiler-recalls-arrest</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452539/luigi-mangione-hearing-officer-detwiler-recalls-arrest</guid>
      <description>The officer at one point started whistling over the restaurant&#8217;s holiday-season music to &#8216;make him think that nothing was different about this call than any other call.&#8217;
A Pennsylvania police officer responding to a tip from the manager of a McDonald&#8217;s testified Tuesday about confronting&#160;Luigi Mangione&#160;during the intense manhunt last year for UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson&#8217;s killer....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon lance sa nouvelle puce IA sur fond de concurrence accrue</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-02/amazon-lance-sa-nouvelle-puce-ia-sur-fond-de-concurrence-accrue.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:55:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87c94ea768393dbbba1decf108d9c73f</guid>
      <description>La filiale d&#8217;Amazon d&#233;di&#233;e &#224; l&#8217;informatique &#224; distance (cloud), Amazon Web Services (AWS), a d&#233;voil&#233; mardi sa nouvelle puce d&#233;di&#233;e au d&#233;veloppement et au fonctionnement de l&#8217;intelligence artificielle (IA), un processeur pr&#233;sent&#233; comme &#233;conomique alors que la concurrence s&#8217;acc&#233;l&#232;re sur ce march&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kobo remote is finally here &#8212; buy it alongside the discounted Kobo Libra Colour</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/kobo-remote-shop-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ZPD3ZlaPCRYGGTUZXPHBl</guid>
      <description>Buy a Kobo remote for your e-reading experience</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
