<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 22:30:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenClaw creator Peter Steinberger joins OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/15/openclaw-creator-peter-steinberger-joins-openai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 22:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093271</guid>
      <description>OpenAI said OpenClaw will live on as an open source project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime NPR host David Greene sues Google over NotebookLM voice</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/15/longtime-npr-host-david-greene-sues-google-over-notebooklm-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 22:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093266</guid>
      <description>The longtime host of NPR&#8217;s &#8220;Morning Edition,&#8221; is suing Google, alleging that the male podcast voice in the company&#8217;s NotebookLM tool is based on him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung unveils new premium OLED monitor technology - but will 'tandem OLED' really make all that much difference?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/samsung-unveils-new-premium-oled-monitor-technology-but-will-tandem-oled-really-make-all-the-difference</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DQNiZ8yBckcaCrh6BXNttQ</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s Penta Tandem OLED technology enhances brightness, efficiency, and lifespan, bringing new standards to 4K and 5K monitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator Zero showrunner confirms the Netflix anime has been canceled after one season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/terminator-zero-showrunner-confirms-the-netflix-anime-has-been-canceled-after-one-season-211656840.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83c4e1c7-52e0-4632-b360-7d0e259138a5</guid>
      <description>If you've been wondering what's next for Netflix's Terminator Zero in the time since its first season, we finally have an update, and it's a bummer. Responding to a fan on social media, showrunner Mattson Tomlin said this weekend that the show has been canceled. Despite being generally well received, Tomlin noted that "at the end of the day not nearly enough people watched it."It was cancelled. The critical and audience reception to it was tremendous, but at the end of the day not nearly enough people watched it. I would&#8217;ve loved to deliver on the Future War I had planned in season&#8217;s 2 and 3, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony Dials In For Another &#8216;Charlie&#8217;s Angels&#8217; Movie</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-dials-in-for-another-charlies-angels-movie-2000722281</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722281</guid>
      <description>Another old franchise means another reboot, and the latest to get pulled off the shelf is 'Charlie's Angels' (again).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic and the Pentagon are reportedly arguing over Claude usage</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/15/anthropic-and-the-pentagon-are-reportedly-arguing-over-claude-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093256</guid>
      <description>The apparent issue: whether Claude can be used for mass domestic surveillance and autonomous weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Apple Intelligence already dead? A massive 96% of you say don&#8217;t use it, and Tim Cook should be worried</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/is-apple-intelligence-already-dead-a-massive-96-percent-of-you-say-dont-use-it-and-tim-cook-should-be-worried</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xiCz7ySxx8TGMorDMitLwB</guid>
      <description>I was actually shocked at the percentage of TechRadar readers who aren't suing Apple Intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The official Pok&#233;mon pinball machine has an animatronic Pikachu and a Master Ball plunger</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/the-official-pokemon-pinball-machine-has-an-animatronic-pikachu-and-a-master-ball-plunger-204915013.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa9d5417-97c2-49f7-af1b-e37ed1cc0197</guid>
      <description>At a staggering starting price of $6,999, you have a better chance of buying a bicycle in Cerulean City than getting your hands on the official Pok&#233;mon pinball machine. The collaboration between The Pok&#233;mon Company International and Stern Pinball is undoubtedly nostalgic, letting you battle with a team that includes Bulbasaur, Charmander, Squirtle and Pikachu, as well as catch up to 182 different Pok&#233;mon, mostly from the Kanto region, with more to be added.
Besides catching 'em all and tracking your growing Pok&#233;dex on Stern Pinball's dedicated app, you can do Gym Battles in four different biom...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
