<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:11:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>All the ways TikTok is broken:&#160;here&#8217;s&#160;what&#8217;s real&#160;and what&#8217;s&#160;not</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868379/tiktok-us-trump-oracle-broken-rumors-power-outage</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T21:10:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=868379</guid>
      <description>While social media rumors have suggested the errors are examples of censorship, more than a day after the issues began, TikTok USDS says the problems are the result of a power outage at a data center that it is working to resolve. Rumors of censorship targeting anti-ICE protesting or attempting to block discussion of Jeffrey [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Garmin actually want their devices to break in these labs' I went to Garmin's closely guarded Kansas HQ to find out why its watches are so expensive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/garmin-actually-want-their-devices-to-break-in-these-labs-i-went-to-garmins-closely-guarded-kansas-hq-to-find-out-why-its-watches-are-so-expensive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HTbJdHPnKXLGQUh9hcjyES</guid>
      <description>From brutal stress tests to a robot-run warehouse, here&#8217;s what surprised me 'behind the scenes' at Garmin&#8217;s home in Kansas City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea&#8217;s Edenlux set for U.S. debut of eye-strain wellness device</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/south-koreas-edenlux-set-for-u-s-debut-of-eye-strain-wellness-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085854</guid>
      <description>Edenlux builds wearable tech to protect and train your eyes, inspired by its founder&#8217;s personal vision recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm backs SpotDraft to scale on-device contract AI with valuation doubling toward $400M</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/qualcomm-backs-spotdraft-to-scale-on-device-contract-ai-with-valuation-doubling-toward-400m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085977</guid>
      <description>SpotDraft now processes over 1 million contracts annually using its AI tool, with contract volumes up 173% year-over-year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My hands-on experience of the Asus Ascent GX10 was a radical one that is only relevant to those actively engaged in AI development</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/hands-on-asus-ascent-gx10-mini-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">v898BwmLG2D85FF9gzYnaJ</guid>
      <description>Designed for the development of AI models, the Asus Ascent GX10 breaks conventional PC design rules to deliver a focused solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident Evil 9 Requiem is almost upon us: here are the five games in the franchise I'd recommend playing beforehand</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/resident-evil-9-requiem-is-almost-upon-us-here-are-the-five-games-in-the-franchise-id-recommend-playing-beforehand</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">C92JmMisEbENjQgS7tWWoJ</guid>
      <description>It's time to face the past, just like Grace Ashcroft will, and these are the five Resident Evil games I'd suggest playing before Resident Evil 9 Requiem arrives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google pays $68M to settle claims its voice assistant spied on users</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/google-pays-68-million-to-settle-claims-its-voice-assistant-spied-on-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086376</guid>
      <description>Google did not admit wrongdoing in the settlement of the class-action case, which accused the firm of "unlawful and intentional interception and recording of individuals&#8217; confidential communications without their consent and subsequent unauthorized disclosure of those communications to third parties."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP shipped without authentication. Clawdbot shows why that's a problem.</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/security/mcp-shipped-without-authentication-clawdbot-shows-why-thats-a-problem</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7hQbUa2R0BehgdNev7oWhr</guid>
      <description>Model Context Protocol has a security problem that won't go away.When VentureBeat first reported on MCP's vulnerabilities last October, the data was already alarming. Pynt's research showed that deploying just 10 MCP plug-ins creates a 92% probability of exploitation &#8212; with meaningful risk even from a single plug-in.The core flaw hasn't changed: MCP shipped without mandatory authentication. Authorization frameworks arrived six months after widespread deployment. As Merritt Baer, chief security officer at Enkrypt AI, warned at the time: "MCP is shipping with the same mistake we've seen in every...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A TikTok US power outage caused a 'cascading systems failure' leading to multiple bugs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/a-tiktok-us-power-outage-caused-a-cascading-systems-failure-leading-to-multiple-bugs-173426490.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c92f4e5-a484-40cc-b29f-ef5732fb73d6</guid>
      <description>If your TikTok feed has felt a little off lately, it's not just you. TikTok says is still working to fix its service in the US following a power outage at one of its data centers that's caused &#8220;multiple bugs&#8221; in the app. TikTok users have reported problems logging in and uploading videos, as well as strange behavior from the "for you" algorithm. Creators have also noticed that new uploads are seemingly getting o views or likes and that in-app earnings have disappeared. "Since yesterday we&#8217;ve been working to restore our services following a power outage at a U.S. data center impacting TikTok an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI chip startup Ricursive hits $4B valuation two months after launch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/ai-chip-startup-ricursive-hits-4b-valuation-two-months-after-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086318</guid>
      <description>Ricursive joins Recursive and Unconventional AI in raising massive funds at multi-billion valuations out of the gate.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
