<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:24:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation is making an MLB The Show mobile game</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837614/sony-playstation-mlb-the-show-mobile-game</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:19:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837614</guid>
      <description>MLB The Show is coming to iOS and Android. Sony has revealed MLB The Show Mobile, which it says is &#8220;a new standalone experience built from the ground up to deliver realistic baseball gameplay on mobile devices.&#8221;&#160; The game is live now only in the Philippines (here&#8217;s a Google Play link for the game), and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This haptic mattress topper lets you feel a movie while you fall asleep during it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837482/woojer-haptic-wellness-mat-vibrations-bluetooth</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:15:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837482</guid>
      <description>Woojer is best known for its vibrating vests and belt straps that let you feel the sounds from games, movies, and music. Now the company has taken that same haptic technology and incorporated it into a new mattress topper called the Woojer Mat that will let you feel those same vibrations across your entire body [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tonight, the future of deep tech will be explained to you at StrictlyVC Palo Alto</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/tonight-the-future-of-deep-tech-will-be-explained-to-you-at-strictlyvc-palo-alto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071117</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday evening at Playground Global in Palo Alto, some very smart people who are building things you don't understand yet will explain what's coming. This is the final StrictlyVC event of 2025, and truly, the lineup is ridiculous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crucial is shutting down &#8212; because Micron wants to sell its RAM and SSDs to AI companies instead</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/837594/crucial-ram-ssd-micron-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:01:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837594</guid>
      <description>Micron is retiring the Crucial brand, marking the end of its line of budget-friendly solid-state drives (SSDs) and RAM kits, as reported earlier by VideoCardz. In an announcement on Wednesday, Micron says winding down its consumer-focused business will &#8220;improve supply and support for our larger, strategic customers in faster-growing segments&#8221; &#8212; a.k.a. AI companies. The [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI Dark Horse Is Rewriting the Rules of Game Design</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/tecent-3d-models-video-game-design-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692dd71d85bfdf284befa045</guid>
      <description>The Chinese video game giant Tencent is now building some of the world&#8217;s best 3D AI models. This could have implications far outside game design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight Radiation Reached 20-Year High During Recent Solar Outburst, Scientists Confirm</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/flight-radiation-reached-20-year-high-during-recent-solar-outburst-scientists-confirm-2000695147</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695147</guid>
      <description>And as Airbus reminded us last week, we're not ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fintech firm Marquis alerts dozens of US banks and credit unions of a data breach after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/fintech-firm-marquis-alerts-dozens-of-us-banks-and-credit-unions-of-a-data-breach-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072283</guid>
      <description>Marquis said ransomware hackers stole reams of banking customer data, containing personal information and financial records, as well as Social Security numbers, belonging to hundreds of thousands of people. The number of affected people is expected to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Are Back in Theaters This Month</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ninja-turtles-short-film-sequel-chrome-alone-2-interview-2000694698</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694698</guid>
      <description>'Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Chrome Alone 2 - Lost in New Jersey' is a short film coming to theaters December 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best fitness trackers and watches we&#8217;ve tested</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T13:34:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker</guid>
      <description>Fitness trackers have come a long way from the simple bands that tracked steps and little else. Modern trackers can monitor everything from your heart health to how well you&#8217;ve recovered from a hard bout of training. Even flagship smartwatches, which used to be lackluster trackers, have become pretty adept workout companions. Whatever your fitness [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent says White House may &#8216;veto&#8217; Fed presidents under a new residency rule</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453612/federal-reserve-presidents-veto-trump-administration-bessent</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:33:12</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453612/federal-reserve-presidents-veto-trump-administration-bessent</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Vetoing&#8217; regional bank presidents would represent another effort by the Trump administration to exert more control over the Fed.
Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said Wednesday he would push a new requirement that the Federal Reserve&#8216;s regional bank presidents live in their districts for at least three years before taking office, a move that could give the White House more power over the&#160;independent agency....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ugly Pebble 2 Duo is the smartwatch for me</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/837388/pebble-2-duo-review</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837388</guid>
      <description>Smartwatches have become health gadgets. Over the last five years or so, Apple, Garmin, Google, Samsung, and practically every other company wanting to strap their wares to your wrist have emphasized exercise integrations, sleep tracking, hypertension monitoring, and more. The most expensive among these devices are also satellite communicators, because now that you have a [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People love this company&#8217;s automatic espresso machines. Can these new accessories make it an everything coffee brand?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452696/terra-kaffe-demi-aero-milk-frother-aeris-tumbler</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452696/terra-kaffe-demi-aero-milk-frother-aeris-tumbler</guid>
      <description>The brand is complementing its super-automatic coffee machines with a milk frother that can make matcha, a cold brew maker, and glassware.
As the &#8216;fourth wave&#8217; of coffee begins taking shape, companies that are embracing modern&#8212;and increasingly, automated&#8212;coffee making are working to balance their tech with the craft of brewing.&#160;Terra Kaffe is one of them....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic reportedly planning one of the biggest IPOs ever as race with OpenAI heats up</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453478/anthropic-ipo-ai-boom</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453478/anthropic-ipo-ai-boom</guid>
      <description>The Claude chatbot maker is said to be exploring a public listing that could top $300 billion in valuation, testing investor appetite for high-burn AI firms.
One of the world&#8217;s biggest AI startups might be eyeing a massive IPO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's push to overrule AI regulation falters as Republicans split</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/trumps-push-to-overrule-ai-regulation-falters-as-republicans-split</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WnfRThbo5sB6zP798sZBvh</guid>
      <description>Trump says state-level AI regulations are hampering US growth as Chinese competition intensifies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temu sued in Arizona over alleged data theft and misleading consumers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453605/temu-arizona-mayes-lawsuit-data-theft-misleading-consumers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T18:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453605/temu-arizona-mayes-lawsuit-data-theft-misleading-consumers</guid>
      <description>Arizona&#8217;s AG says Temu deceives customers about the quality of its low-cost products and collects a shocking amount of sensitive data without user consent.
Arizona Attorney General Kris Mayes announced Tuesday that Arizona is the latest state to sue Temu and its parent company PDD Holdings Inc. over allegations that the Chinese online retailer is stealing customers&#8217; data....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 best headphones of 2025 &#8212; see the top contenders from Sony, Apple, Bose, and Beats</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/roundup/best-headphones-2025-tested</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00qrsf3wCFjMiU3WmxGY9h9</guid>
      <description>We tested the best headphones from Sony, Bose, Apple, Marshall, and Bowers &amp; Wilkins. See all the wireless and noise-cancelling cans we personally recommend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Seems to Agree on Smart Glasses</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nobody-seems-to-agree-on-smart-glasses-2000695082</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695082</guid>
      <description>Like the wacky Android phones of yesteryear, smart glasses are a bit like the Wild West right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeds vs Chelsea live streams: How to watch Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/leeds-vs-chelsea-premier-league-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TtZbhiJfqqSMbSQ758S9FQ</guid>
      <description>We'll show how to watch Leeds vs Chelsea in the Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy department hands out $800M in grants for small nuclear reactors</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/energy-department-hands-out-800m-in-grants-for-small-nuclear-reactors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072254</guid>
      <description>The Tennessee Valley Authority and Holtec were awarded substantial grants to build one reactor in Tennessee and two more in Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab the Anker Solix F2000 portable power station for 58% off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-3-anker-solix-f2000-portable-power-station-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03ibqHtah44eGH3C5pXifcZ</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 3, get the Anker Solix F2000 portable power station for 58% off at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T commits to ending DEI programs while seeking government approval</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/att-dei-fcc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03apW5GvYYEeVe4qzb4TrIH</guid>
      <description>AT&amp;T announces end to all DEI policies in an attempt to secure billion dollar purchasing deal from Brendan Carr-led FCC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anyone can try to edit Grokipedia 0.2 but Grok is running the show</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/837431/grokipedia-update-editing-mess</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T12:47:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837431</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk envisions Grokipedia - xAI's AI-generated, anti-woke spin on Wikipedia - as a definitive monument to human knowledge, something complete and truthful enough to etch in stone and preserve in space. In reality, it's a hot mess, and it's only getting worse now that anyone can suggest edits. Grokipedia was not always editable. When [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We&#8217;re Green With Envy Over Columbia&#8217;s New &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Collection</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-columbia-jackets-endor-2000695129</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695129</guid>
      <description>Endor is the theme for the company's latest, highly sought-after line of 'Star Wars' jackets and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic hires lawyers as it preps for IPO</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/03/anthropic-hires-lawyers-as-it-preps-for-ipo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072188</guid>
      <description>Anthropic is reportedly prepping for an IPO that could come as early as 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette sonde f&#234;te ses 30 ans et elle est devenue l&#8217;instrument solaire le plus productif de l&#8217;histoire : voici ce qu&#8217;elle a vu</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/soleil-cette-sonde-fete-30-ans-elle-devenue-instrument-solaire-plus-productif-histoire-voici-ce-quelle-vu-128191/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:41:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/soleil-cette-sonde-fete-30-ans-elle-devenue-instrument-solaire-plus-productif-histoire-voici-ce-quelle-vu-128191/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le 2&#160;d&#233;cembre 1995, l&#8217;Agence spatiale europ&#233;enne (ESA) et la Nasa lan&#231;aient Soho, l&#8217;Observatoire solaire et h&#233;liosph&#233;rique. Les donn&#233;es qu&#8217;il a renvoy&#233;es en 30 ans ont r&#233;volutionn&#233; le regard que les astronomes posent sur notre &#201;toile. Et m&#234;me un peu plus&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"A disaster waiting to happen" &#8211; The privacy tech world reacts to the new Chat Control bill</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/a-disaster-waiting-to-happen-the-privacy-tech-world-reacts-to-the-new-chat-control-bill</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Lyq2cNSRxuhTyGGNCvzt8</guid>
      <description>While an agreemnet on "voluntary" chat scanning has now been reached, Italy, the Czech Republic, Poland, and the Netherlands are still against the compromise. And privacy experts aren't celebrating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40-inch Samsung Odyssey G7 curved gaming monitor is still at a record-low price after Cyber Monday</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-3-samsung-odyssey-monitor-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02Cy2hDdtl3ZTdd7kthQr0W</guid>
      <description>The 40-inch Samsung Odyssey G7 curved gaming monitor is on sale for $696.99, down from the list price of $1,199.99. That's a 42% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour r&#233;duire leur d&#233;pendance &#224; la Chine, les industries europ&#233;ennes bient&#244;t contraintes de se fournir en partie en Europe&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/pour-reduire-leur-dependance-a-la-chine-les-industries-europeennes-bientot-contraintes-de-se-fournir-en-partie-en-europe.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1313376</guid>
      <description>Des biens critiques, jusque-l&#224; fournis par la Chine, seraient bient&#244;t obligatoirement fabriqu&#233;s en Europe : c'est l'id&#233;e d'une future loi europ&#233;enne qui sera pr&#233;sent&#233;e le 10 d&#233;cembre prochain &#224; Bruxelles. Elle pourrait contraindre nos industries &#224; s'approvisionner obligatoirement aupr&#232;s d'entreprises du Vieux continent, dans certains secteurs cl&#233;s. Reste &#224; d&#233;finir les seuils, les composants et les produits concern&#233;s : autant d'&#233;l&#233;ments sur lesquels la Commission europ&#233;enne resterait divis&#233;e....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thursday's Cold Moon Is the Last Supermoon of the Year. Here's How and When to View It</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/cold-moon-supermoon-december-how-to-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693043999cc8afb0969c31e9</guid>
      <description>The best opportunity to view this spectacle will be shortly after sunset on December 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liverpool vs Sunderland live streams: watch Premier League 2025/26 match</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/liverpool-vs-sunderland-premier-league-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9Jtoem63WnDB4qbYB9SQYd</guid>
      <description>We'll show you all the ways you can watch Liverpool vs Sunderland in the Premier League this Wednesday, as Arne Slot looks for successive EPL wins.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
