<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:33:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ring claims it&amp;#8217;s not giving ICE access to its cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866003/ring-ice-camera-access-flock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T15:30:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866003</guid>
      <description>Ring's partnership with Flock is sparking renewed online backlash this week, with influencers calling for people to smash their Ring cameras and claiming the company is part of the surveillance state amid heightened concerns over ICE actions. Flock is an AI-powered surveillance camera company that has reportedly allowed government agencies - including ICE - to [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We had to do a lot of technological work that was sort of unprecedented ... which was really challenging and exciting," Crossplay producer on the effort to bring The New York Times' first two-player game to life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/we-had-to-do-a-lot-of-technological-work-that-was-sort-of-unprecedented-which-was-really-challenging-and-exciting-crossplay-producer-on-the-effort-to-bring-the-new-york-times-first-two-player-game-to-life</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xvXwNrUjsYr7xKQGNW2obE</guid>
      <description>TechRadar speaks with New York Times Senior Producer Jeff Petriello about the origins of the newly launched Crossplay, its hidden easter eggs, and what&#8217;s next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have your say: do you actually use Apple Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/have-your-say-do-you-actually-use-apple-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qV3vD8VSZvhkMa9iqd3Jn8</guid>
      <description>Apple Intelligence hasn't won over a lot of TechRadar, but let me know if you use it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack is launching a TV app, and not everyone is happy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866054/substack-tv-app-beta-launch-newsletters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T15:21:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866054</guid>
      <description>Substack announced Thursday it's launching Apple TV and Google TV apps that audiences can use for videos and livestreams - and early reactions suggest not all users are thrilled. Subscribers can watch videos and livestreams from creators they follow, but the app will also have a recommendations-based "For You" feed that mixes in other creators' [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When a Chinese Battery Factory Comes to Town</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/chinese-battery-makers-are-building-factories-across-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697163956c03e6376fe6f8f2</guid>
      <description>Chinese firms are building battery plants from Europe to North America, promising jobs while prompting local concerns about the environment, politics, and who really benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Is Running Dangerously Low on Blood Right Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/america-is-running-dangerously-low-on-blood-right-now-2000713020</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713020</guid>
      <description>Extreme winter weather and a bad flu season have fueled a severe shortage in the national blood supply over the past month, according to the American Red Cross.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fable will let you be a heartless landlord this fall</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/fable-will-let-you-be-a-heartless-landlord-this-fall-200409310.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4285c05-03ad-4886-9d2c-f5d4762464a3</guid>
      <description>After half a decade of waiting, Microsoft finally offered an extended preview of its long-awaited reboot of the beloved Fable RPG franchise on Thursday. During the company&#8217;s recent Developer Direct showcase, Playground Games, best known for its works on the Forza Horizon series, shared nearly 11 minutes of gameplay footage and commentary related to the upcoming title. The new game will feature a fully open world for players to explore, with locations from previous Fable games like Bowerstone making a return.  Playground didn&#8217;t say exactly where the new game takes place in the Fable timeline. I...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Tank Chair&#8217; Proves Ultra&#8209;Violent Manga Can Still Hit With Heart</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tank-chair-proves-ultra%e2%80%91violent-manga-can-still-hit-with-heart-2000713010</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713010</guid>
      <description>Manabu Yashiro's slept-on mecha-wheelchair series fuses 'Kamen Rider' grit with 'Dorohedoro' chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 28 Best Movies on Apple TV, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (January 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64342bc05ffa737db431afc0</guid>
      <description>F1: The Movie, CODA, and Highest 2 Lowest are just a few of the movies you should be watching on Apple TV this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Fine announces delightful-looking multiplayer pottery game Kiln</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/double-fine-announces-delightful-looking-multiplayer-pottery-game-kiln-195837155.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab113a0-119d-4149-8b39-1fd0985ea75a</guid>
      <description>Double Fine has been on a tear with its smaller projects lately. The popular indie game developer is following up last year's atmospheric adventure game Keeper with a new title in a totally different direction. As its Double Fine founder Tim Schaefer attempted to say five times fast during today's Xbox Developer Direct, Kiln is an "online multiplayer pottery party brawler" that boasts exactly the sort of colorful, clever fun that fans have come to expect from the studio.&#160;Kiln is a game with two facets: creation and destruction. On the creation side, players get to design a ceramic vessel of th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack now has a TV app</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/substack-now-has-a-tv-app-195408592.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cad4782e-89f8-4401-b62a-617b27bcfec7</guid>
      <description>It was only 16 months ago that Substack expanded into live video. Since then, it's become a widely adopted medium on the platform, including by its ever-growing list of cable news expats. Now, the company has decided it's ready for a bigger screen. Starting today, you can install a new Substack TV app on Apple TV and Google TV devices.Substack describes the app's initial launch as focusing on "reliable, high-quality viewing" for the platform's long-form videos. It centers around video posts and livestreams from the creators and publications you follow. There's also a "For You" section that com...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The state attorneys general are as mad as you are</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/865882/democratic-state-attorney-general-rayfield-ellison</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:52:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865882</guid>
      <description>The sun was already beginning to set as Portlanders in weatherproof jackets and fleeces lined up around Revolution Hall. It wasn't yet 5PM on a Wednesday but the crowd was gathering well before the town hall was scheduled to begin. Just a day earlier, news outlets reported that Minnesota Attorney General Keith Ellison had been [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Attempts to Sell &#8216;Cyberpunk 2077&#8217; VR Mod to CD Projekt RED, Gets Bad News</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/developer-attempts-to-sell-cyberpunk-2077-vr-mod-to-cd-projekt-red-gets-bad-news-2000712991</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712991</guid>
      <description>Maybe don't try to sell your paid mod to the company whose Terms of Service you appear to be violating?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring is adding a new content verification feature to videos</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/ring-is-adding-a-new-content-verification-feature-to-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085208</guid>
      <description>Ring says the new feature will identify if video edits have been made, even if they're minor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google DeepMind CEO is &#8216;surprised&#8217; OpenAI is rushing forward with ads in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/google-deepmind-ceo-is-surprised-openai-is-rushing-forward-with-ads-in-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085101</guid>
      <description>Google DeepMind CEO Demis Hassabis says the tech giant isn't pressuring him to insert ads into the AI chatbot experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Site ManyVids Descends Into AI Psychosis</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/porn-site-manyvids-descends-into-ai-psychosis-2000713033</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713033</guid>
      <description>Good luck jerking off to this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe VR Doesn&#8217;t Need Meta After All</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/maybe-vr-doesnt-need-meta-after-all-2000713026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713026</guid>
      <description>Meta's commitment might be wavering, but other entrants in the VR field feel stronger than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A major game publisher is shutting studios and killing six titles &#8212; here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479225/a-major-game-publisher-is-shutting-studios-and-killing-six-titles-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479225/a-major-game-publisher-is-shutting-studios-and-killing-six-titles-heres-why</guid>
      <description>The Assassin&#8217;s Creed maker says it must radically reorganize to survive, slashing costs and refocusing its portfolio through 2028.
One of the giants of the gaming business has tumbled off a cliff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Fire TV Stick 4K Plus is on sale for just $18 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/865230/amazon-fire-tv-stick-4k-plus-iphone-air-magsafe-battery-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:28:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865230</guid>
      <description>In February, Amazon plans to roll out a much-needed revamp of Fire TV OS, one that seemingly takes a cue from Google&#8217;s TV platform. The forthcoming UI redesign will introduce better organization, support for Alexa Plus, and quicker performance to the aging OS, the latter of which has been a crux of the platform&#8217;s issues [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk just told Davos that Tesla will sell humanoid robots next year, really, he swears</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/elon-musk-just-told-davos-that-tesla-will-sell-humanoid-robots-next-year-really-he-swears-192515568.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94dc5929-855e-4d3b-9085-d49bc6d27ffe</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk just took the stage at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland and announced that Tesla's Optimus humanoid robot will be sold to the public by the end of next year. Musk is the master of unrealistic timetables, but this may be the nuttiest one yet. These are humanoid robots that are supposed to be able to do just about any task a human can do.
Musk, as usual, gave himself an out if the robots don't start rolling off the assembly line in 2027, saying that they'll only be released when Tesla is "confident that it&#8217;s very high reliability, very high safety and the range of functio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans&amp; thinks coordination is the next frontier for AI, and they&#8217;re building a model to prove it</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/humans-thinks-coordination-is-the-next-frontier-for-ai-and-theyre-building-a-model-to-prove-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085222</guid>
      <description>Humans&amp;, a new startup founded by alumni of Anthropic, Meta, OpenAI, xAI, and Google DeepMind, is building the next generation of foundation models for collaboration, not chat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out - this devious new Android malware clicks on hidden browser ads to put you at risk</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/watch-out-this-devious-new-android-malware-clicks-on-hidden-browser-ads-to-put-you-at-risk</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iNbFeqptBx5FNV3TJ97KyF</guid>
      <description>Malware uses AI to mimic authentic human behavior and trick traditional defenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines are preparing for major disruptions this weekend&#8212;here&#8217;s how to benefit from it</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479277/airlines-are-preparing-for-major-disruptions-this-weekend-heres-how-to-benefit-from-it</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T19:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479277/airlines-are-preparing-for-major-disruptions-this-weekend-heres-how-to-benefit-from-it</guid>
      <description>Travelers may be rebooked automatically, but that may not be your best option.
If you have travel plans this weekend and don&#8217;t necessarily need to travel, you may be in luck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 is leaking like a faucet now: Possible specs, colors, and release date</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/everything-we-know-about-samsung-galaxy-s26-leaks-rumors-specs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03GNxXxEZ563hZE1gfDdaeY</guid>
      <description>What do we know about the upcoming Samsung Galaxy S26? A lot, actually, including the potential colors, specs, camera, price, and release date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fable is coming to PS5 when it finally launches this fall</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865305/fable-xbox-playground-games-developer-direct-2026-ps5-pc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:04:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865305</guid>
      <description>Xbox showed off new footage of its Fable reboot during its Developer Direct on Thursday and announced that the game is set to launch this autumn for Xbox, PC, and PS5. The new Fable is an open-world action RPG. In addition to letting you customize your character and your combat skills, you can also do [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mario Kart World adds a team option in Knockout Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/mario-kart-world-adds-a-team-option-in-knockout-tour-190348248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8831619d-2a03-427a-ae4c-f54ddb841377</guid>
      <description>Mario Kart World received a free update today that brings a team option to its Knockout Tour mode. Initially, the Knockout races in this Nintendo Switch 2 launch title were only for solo drivers, challenging players to finish ahead of enough other competitors or get eliminated from the series. It was one of the highlights of the game in our review, and this new wrinkle should bring plenty more fun chaos to the racetrack.In the team mode, players compete either in two teams of twelve, three teams of eight or four teams of six. If you don't have enough people to fill out a team CPU drivers will ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Cobra Kai&#8217; Is Getting the Dream Physical Release It Deserves</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cobra-kai-is-getting-the-dream-physical-release-it-deserves-2000713011</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713011</guid>
      <description>All six seasons of the hit Netflix show are coming to Blu-ray, with a few new commentaries to boot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Claude Code Is Reshaping Software&#8212;and Anthropic</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/claude-code-success-anthropic-business-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697129ce8c25eb9b6d63a92c</guid>
      <description>WIRED spoke with Boris Cherny, head of Claude Code, about how the viral coding tool is changing the way Anthropic works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Disinformation Swarms Are Coming for Democracy</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-powered-disinformation-swarms-are-coming-for-democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fae551d9eb7b4565d30e5</guid>
      <description>Advances in artificial intelligence are creating a perfect storm for those seeking to spread disinformation at unprecedented speed and scale. And it&#8217;s virtually impossible to detect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best laptops you can get</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21250695/best-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21250695/best-laptops</guid>
      <description>Buying the right laptop can be stressful. It&#8217;s likely one of the pricier tech purchases you&#8217;ll make, and there are a ludicrous number of models, sizes, form factors, and configurations to pick from. We review a wide swath of them here at The Verge, and we&#8217;re constantly considering what&#8217;s best and who it&#8217;s best for. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA lighting trends for 2026: give your home a lift with lamps and smart lights from just $3</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-lights/ikea-lighting-trends-for-2026-give-your-home-a-lift-with-lamps-and-smart-lights-from-just-usd3</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nNsGzCCRaP3obrGyKzfDiY</guid>
      <description>Bold and beautiful lighting to give your space the ultimate glow-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack launches a TV app</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/substack-launches-a-tv-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085113</guid>
      <description>The move comes as Substack has been investing more heavily in video and livestreaming, as it looks to compete with platforms like YouTube and Patreon for both creators and viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nioh 3 : voici les configurations sur PC, &#224; quoi s&#8217;attendre ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2951711_nioh-3-voici-les-configurations-sur-pc-a-quoi-sattendre</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2951711_nioh-3-voici-les-configurations-sur-pc-a-quoi-sattendre</guid>
      <description>
Le troisi&#232;me opus de la s&#233;rie de jeux Nioh sort tr&#232;s bient&#244;t. Quelles sont les configurations attendues pour pouvoir en profiter ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Our Favorite Smart Plugs for Apple Users Is $15 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/meross-smart-plug-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69725f1e904332ad78632c84</guid>
      <description>The Meross Smart Plug Mini boasts excellent compatibility and slim construction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this the end of Epic and Google&#8217;s feud?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/865178/epic-v-google-settlement-before-judge</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T13:55:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865178</guid>
      <description>Today, I am sitting in the courtroom that may decide the fate of Android. Epic CEO Tim Sweeney is here. Google Android boss Sameer Samat is here. Together, they'll try to convince Judge James Donato that they're no longer enemies - that Google's illegal monopoly on Android app stores can be resolved with a mutual [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s a new look at Beast of Reincarnation, from the team behind Pok&#233;mon</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/865588/beast-of-reincarnation-trailer-date-pokemon-game-freak</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T13:55:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865588</guid>
      <description>It's been a bit of a wait, but a big new game from Pok&#233;mon developer Game Freak is almost here. During the Xbox Developer Direct showcase, the studio showed off more gameplay for its action RPG Beast of Incarnation, and confirmed that it will be launching in the summer of 2026 on the PS5, Xbox, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silk in diapers? P&amp;G&#8217;s unusual plan to boost sales in China</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479470/silk-in-diapers-pgs-unusual-plan-to-boost-sales-in-china</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T18:53:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479470/silk-in-diapers-pgs-unusual-plan-to-boost-sales-in-china</guid>
      <description>Procter &amp; Gamble is introducing silk-lined diapers in China to drive premium sales as birth rates fall and consumer spending weakens.
With birth rates down around the world, Procter &amp; Gamble is leaning into premium diapers to bolster sales figures. Specifically, the conglomerate is planning to sell diapers made with silk fibers in China, the company&#8217;s second-largest market, in hopes of attracting new parents....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla launches robotaxi rides in Austin with no human safety driver</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/tesla-launches-robotaxi-rides-in-austin-with-no-human-safety-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085158</guid>
      <description>Not all of Tesla's fleet in Austin will be fully driverless. Per Tesla's AI lead Ashok Elluswamy, the company will be "starting with a few unsupervised vehicles mixed in with the broader robotaxi fleet with safety monitors, and the ratio will increase over time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Seekers Want to Know What the Hell Is Going on With AI-Based Hiring Decisions: Lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/job-seekers-want-to-know-what-the-hell-is-going-on-with-ai-based-hiring-decisions-lawsuit-2000712967</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712967</guid>
      <description>Eightfold, an AI company that makes human resources software, is being sued over one of its hiring tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked rumors: When it is, what devices well see</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-unpacked-2026-date-rumors</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05j2FQG07QPzUeZjBoI8J3D</guid>
      <description>Samsung has to show off its next batch of Galaxy phones soon, but when exactly will that be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Actually Need the Best Gaming CPU?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/do-you-actually-need-the-best-gaming-cpu-2000713038</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713038</guid>
      <description>AMD&#8217;s new Ryzen 7 9850X3D seems powerful, though it's not a massive leap over what we already have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta seeks to limit evidence in child safety case</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/meta-seeks-to-limit-evidence-in-child-safety-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085084</guid>
      <description>Meta is set to go on trial in New Mexico for allegedly failing to protect minors. The company is requesting a broad swath of information not be allowed to be presented in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rare, Deadly Fungus Is Making People Sick in Tennessee</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-rare-deadly-fungus-is-making-people-sick-in-tennessee-2000712977</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712977</guid>
      <description>At least 36 cases of histoplasmosis and possibly one death have been reported in the state since last fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Bezos and Blue Origin want to help provide high-speed satellite internet across the globe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/jeff-bezos-and-blue-origin-want-to-help-provide-high-speed-satellite-internet-across-the-globe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gpAshKjDifBSkLd2Wh45UQ</guid>
      <description>Blue Origin will offer a LEO/MEO satellite internet network for enterprises and governments, but not consumers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
