<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:27:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google agrees to $68 million settlement in voice assistant privacy lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/google-agrees-to-68-million-settlement-in-voice-assistant-privacy-lawsuit-222405727.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d84325-522c-4b7d-8f85-6d20504147c0</guid>
      <description>Google has agreed to a $68 million settlement regarding claims that its voice assistant inappropriately spied on smartphone users. Plaintiffs claimed that the company&#8217;s Google Assistant platform began listening to them after it misheard conversations that sounded like its wake words. The suit argued that private information that Google Assistant shouldn't have heard was then used to deliver those individuals targeted ads.&#160;Reuters reported that Google denied wrongdoing in the suit, but according to court papers, the company agreed to a settlement in order to avoid the risk and costs of litigati...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic CEO Worries Humanity May Not be &#8216;Mature&#8217; Enough for Advanced AI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anthropic-ceo-worries-humanity-may-not-be-mature-enough-for-advanced-ai-2000714187</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714187</guid>
      <description>When has that ever stopped us?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir Defends Work With ICE to Staff Following Killing of Alex Pretti</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/palantir-ice-dhs-alex-pretti-killing-workers-slack-minneapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977722e2193fa0a6abfeb69</guid>
      <description>&#8220;In my opinion ICE are the bad guys. I am not proud that the company I enjoy so much working for is part of this,&#8221; one worker wrote on Slack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rian Johnson Shares His Preferred Vision for the Future of &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rian-johnson-shares-his-preferred-vision-for-the-future-of-star-wars-2000714139</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714139</guid>
      <description>'The Last Jedi' director thinks the galaxy far, far away should pass to a new generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A coin-op gaming PC &#8212; and one that can cloak its hardware innards &#8212; here are 3 of the weirdest, coolest new PC cases</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/desktop-pcs/a-coin-op-gaming-pc-and-one-that-can-cloak-its-hardware-innards-here-are-3-of-the-weirdest-coolest-new-pc-cases</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QEK9bKmhYLfUXzsVvPiRzU</guid>
      <description>A DIY project for a PC that's turned on by inserting a coin, and a case that can go from opaque to transparent at the touch of a button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where does Google&#8217;s AI get its health advice? A study points to YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481019/where-does-googles-ai-get-its-health-advice-a-study-points-to-youtube</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481019/where-does-googles-ai-get-its-health-advice-a-study-points-to-youtube</guid>
      <description>A study of 50,000+ health searches found Google&#8217;s AI Overviews cited YouTube more than any hospital, clinic, or health agency.
Every month, around two billion people see AI Overviews, Google&#8217;s AI-powered search feature that generates summaries to users&#8217; queries. Now, a new study is revealing a concerning pattern among some of these responses: When asked health-related questions, AI Overviews appears to turn to YouTube significantly more often than trusted medical sites....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok&#8217;s New US Owners Are Off to a Very Rocky Start</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tiktoks-new-us-owners-are-off-to-a-very-rocky-start-2000714159</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714159</guid>
      <description>Thousands of American TikTok users have reported having issues with the app this past weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Extracted season 2 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/extracted-season-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pLgR362PSdLKpPLnaemJHJ</guid>
      <description>Want to watch Extracted season 2 online from anywhere? Stream every desperate fight and decision for food, shelter, and survival in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Data Center Outage Triggers Trust Crisis for New US Owners</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-ice-videos-censorship-allegations-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69715b25db278578d8ddf24a</guid>
      <description>The technical failure coincided with TikTok&#8217;s ownership transition, leading users to question whether videos criticizing ICE raids in Minnesota were being intentionally censored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinod Khosla publicly disavows Keith Rabois&#8217; comments on ICE shooting</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/vinod-khosla-publicly-disavows-keith-rabois-comments-on-ice-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086059</guid>
      <description>Unwavering Trump loyalist and VC Keith Rabois caused his colleague  and his firm's founder to distance themseves from his comments on ICE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordic Equestrian Project Asks Horses if They Want Blankets or Not</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nordic-equestrian-project-asks-horses-if-they-want-blankets-or-not-2000714006</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714006</guid>
      <description>Researchers have taught horses to communicate their preferences with symbols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch American Idol 2026 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/american-idol-season-24-online</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HFNBqhyf6L73JGrtUspEz6</guid>
      <description>Format changes bring fresh voting, new rounds, and Monday premieres. Here&#8217;s how you can watch American Idol 2026 online and from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTubers sue Snap for alleged copyright infringement in training its AI models</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/youtubers-sue-snap-for-alleged-copyright-infringement-in-training-its-ai-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086257</guid>
      <description>The YouTubers claim Snap, like others, used AI datasets meant for research and academic use to train its AI models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook Attends White House Screening of &#8216;Melania&#8217; Movie, Prompts Calls for Apple Boycott</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tim-cook-attends-white-house-screening-of-melania-movie-prompts-calls-for-apple-boycott-2000714041</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714041</guid>
      <description>The Apple CEO doesn't seem shy about getting cozy with the Trump regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'.ai' websites are booming - and making millions for this tiny Caribbean nation</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ai-websites-are-booming-and-making-millions-for-this-tiny-caribbean-nation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cr2cPvGyHacjtaPnK6LjXU</guid>
      <description>Google, x.ai, Perplexity and other AI startups are all helping to fund critical infrastructure upgrades in Anguilla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota CEOs&#8217; call for &#8216;de-escalation&#8217; isn&#8217;t enough. Here&#8217;s why.</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481076/minnesota-ceos-call-for-de-escalation-isnt-enough-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481076/minnesota-ceos-call-for-de-escalation-isnt-enough-heres-why</guid>
      <description>Target, Best Buy, 3M and General Mills and other huge firms&#8217; top bosses finally broke their silence in a not-so-strongly worded letter about ICE. Experts say they missed the mark.
CEOs of Minnesota&#8217;s biggest companies signed a public letter calling for &#8220;immediate de-escalation of tensions&#8221; after weeks of silence following Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) descending upon the state, which has led to civilian deaths, abductions, economic stand-stills and a profound disruption of daily life....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hidden flaw is prompting Nissan to recall thousands of newer vehicles</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481056/a-hidden-flaw-is-prompting-nissan-to-recall-thousands-of-newer-vehicles</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T21:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481056/a-hidden-flaw-is-prompting-nissan-to-recall-thousands-of-newer-vehicles</guid>
      <description>The recall affects Frontier, Altima, Sentra, and Kicks models built in Michigan and Mexico.
Nissan is recalling thousands of its 2025 and 2026 vehicles due to a flaw which could potentially cause the door to open while driving, increasing the risk of injury or a crash, according to a notice from the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Will Close Out Season 2 With Early Episode Drops</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-will-close-out-season-2-with-early-episode-drops-2000714125</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714125</guid>
      <description>The Prime Video series shifts to Tuesday releases starting this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Department cancels contracts with Booz Allen Hamilton after Trump tax leak</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481345/treasury-department-cancels-contracts-booz-allen-hamilton-trump-tax-leak</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T21:02:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481345/treasury-department-cancels-contracts-booz-allen-hamilton-trump-tax-leak</guid>
      <description>In 2024, former IRS contractor Charles Edward Littlejohn of Washington, D.C., was sentenced to five years in prison after pleading guilty to the leak.
The U.S. Treasury Department has cut its contracts with Booz Allen Hamilton, after a former contractor who worked for the firm was charged and subsequently imprisoned for leaking tax information to news outlets about thousands of the country&#8217;s wealthiest people, including&#160;President Donald Trump....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If Cancer Holds the Key to New Treatments for Alzheimer&#8217;s Disease?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/what-if-cancer-holds-the-key-to-new-treatments-for-alzheimers-disease-2000714005</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714005</guid>
      <description>Scientists have found a possible explanation for why cancer patients are less likely to develop Alzheimer's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s the tech powering ICE&#8217;s deportation crackdown</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/heres-the-tech-powering-ices-deportation-crackdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3045548</guid>
      <description>From phone spyware and facial recognition to phone unlocking technology and databases and more, this tech powers Trump's deportation machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XR glasses have had one major issue &#8212; and Xreal just solved it with a free update</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/xr-glasses-have-had-one-major-issue-and-xreal-just-solved-it-with-a-free-update</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">g5jUqy5zT3RjQ59uZrqHqg</guid>
      <description>I already thought my XR glasses were incredible, and now they can turn my favorite films and games into 3D thanks to a free update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should people be taking their shoes off at work?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480550/should-people-be-taking-shoes-off-at-work</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480550/should-people-be-taking-shoes-off-at-work</guid>
      <description>At some startups and tech companies, dress codes are getting even more casual.
The post-commute changing from sneakers to office-friendly pumps is something well-known to many workers. But could it become a thing of the past?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google aims to take the sting out of scheduling meetings with a new Gemini feature</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-aims-to-take-the-sting-out-of-scheduling-meetings-with-a-new-gemini-feature-204853761.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f2b42d8-9b02-4137-8a08-043c4c3bad7e</guid>
      <description>Google is rolling out a Gemini feature that could turn out to be pretty useful for many folks. It's a Google Calendar tool that can help figure out the best time to schedule a meeting, taking into account attendees' schedules. When creating a meeting, you can click the "Suggested times" option and Gemini will look at the availability that people have marked on their calendar and potential conflicts. You'll then be able to choose from a list of suggested time slots.But the time you pick may not work for everyone. So if multiple people decline the meeting invite, you can reschedule by going to t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal Winter Storm Leaves Hundreds of Thousands Without Power. How Long Will Outages Last?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/brutal-winter-storm-leaves-hundreds-of-thousands-without-power-how-long-will-outages-last-2000714176</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714176</guid>
      <description>With no end to the frigid temperatures in sight, people across the Southeastern U.S. may be unable to heat their homes for several days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMK reveals super-affordable new mini PC - but with this outdated hardware, it might actually be a good thing you'll probably never be able to get one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/gmk-reveals-super-affordable-new-mini-pc-but-with-this-outdated-hardware-it-might-be-a-good-thing-youll-probably-never-be-able-to-get-one</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vz3CXphNyTjtfBZfvHThkn</guid>
      <description>GMK G3 Pro is a compact mini PC with an older Intel i3 CPU, flexible memory, and storage, but alternatives offer better value for money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge hears arguments for Trump&#8217;s immigration crackdown in Minneapolis</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481153/shooting-minneapolis-protests-ice-immigration-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T20:34:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481153/shooting-minneapolis-protests-ice-immigration-lawsuit</guid>
      <description>Lawyers for the state and the Twin Cities argued that the situation is so dire as to require the court to halt the federal government&#8217;s immigration enforcement actions.
A federal judge began hearing arguments Monday on whether she should halt, at least temporarily,&#160;the immigration crackdown&#160;in Minnesota that has led to the&#160;fatal shootings&#160;of two people by government officers....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We're sorry for this disruption and hope to resolve it soon&#8217;: TikTok&#8217;s USA arm explains why it&#8217;s still not working for many</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/were-sorry-for-this-disruption-and-hope-to-resolve-it-soon-tiktoks-usa-arm-explains-why-its-still-not-working-for-many</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rLHBwnnFTKo2tooDpX9bLf</guid>
      <description>Many U.S. TikTok users are still experiencing feed, upload, and playback issues as the company works to restore service following a reported data center outage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>34 Volunteers From Around the World Will Help NASA Track the Artemis 2 Mission</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/34-volunteers-from-around-the-world-will-help-nasa-track-the-artemis-2-mission-2000714037</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714037</guid>
      <description>The list includes volunteers ranging from amateur radio enthusiasts to commercial service providers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
