<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:27:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg was initially opposed to parental controls for AI chatbots, according to legal filing</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/mark-zuckerberg-was-initially-opposed-to-parental-controls-for-ai-chatbots-according-to-legal-filing-230110214.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deb08569-f282-473f-830d-d74a58155acd</guid>
      <description>Meta has faced some serious questions about how it allows its underage users to interact with AI-powered chatbots. Most recently, internal communications obtained by the New Mexico Attorney General's Office revealed that although Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg was opposed to the chatbots having "explicit" conversations with minors, he also rejected the idea of placing parental controls on the feature. Reuters reported that in an exchange between two unnamed Meta employees, one wrote that we "pushed hard for parental controls to turn GenAI off &#8211; but GenAI leadership pushed back stating Mark decision....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta blocks links to ICE List, a Wiki that names agents</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-blocks-links-to-ice-list-a-wiki-that-names-agents-231410653.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67d6e353-d481-4157-9714-7e440c097333</guid>
      <description>Meta has started blocking links to ICE List, a website that compiles information about incidents involving Immigrations and Customs Enforcement (ICE) and Border Patrol agents, and lists thousands of their employees' names. It seems that the latter detail is what caused Meta to take action in a move that was first reported by Wired.&#160;ICE List is a crowdsourced Wiki that describes itself as "an independently maintained public documentation project focused on immigration-enforcement activity" in the US. "Its purpose is to record, organize, and preserve verifiable information about enforcement acti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winklevoss Twins Shut Down NFT Marketplace in Another Sign Crypto Art Is Dead</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/winklevoss-twins-shut-down-nft-marketplace-in-another-sign-crypto-art-is-dead-2000714660</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714660</guid>
      <description>You know what's cooler than a million dollars? A .jpeg that's been cataloged on an immutable blockchain that no one wants to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best budget robot vacuums</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23846479/best-budget-robot-vacuum-robot-mop</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T18:09:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23846479/best-budget-robot-vacuum-robot-mop</guid>
      <description>Today&#8217;s robot vacuums are becoming a bit like cars: with all the features, upgrades, and fancy trimmings available these days, it&#8217;s easy to forget that they can just be simple machines that get us from point A to point B. Yes, some bots blow hot air on their bums (mop pads), deftly navigate dog poop, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber Creates &#8216;AV Labs&#8217; To Leverage Data For Future Robotaxi Routes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/uber-creates-av-labs-to-leverage-data-for-future-robotaxi-routes-2000714658</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714658</guid>
      <description>Uber will manage data for its robotaxi tech partners to access and use as they deploy vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles&#8217; Returns to an Era-Appropriate Format</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-returns-to-an-era-appropriate-format-2000714735</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714735</guid>
      <description>The 1990 original is being released in multiple variants on the old classic: VHS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not sure what HDMI port to use? Here's what each port does on your TV, and which devices you should connect to where</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/what-hdmi-port-should-i-use</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mZUqWRt2v5GUoVQ5XKRVG</guid>
      <description>HDMI is the main way you'll connect your external devices to your TV, so it's important to make sure you're connecting to the right ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of smartphone users could be at risk from the SMS sign-in URL issue - here's what you need to look out for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/millions-of-smartphone-users-could-be-at-risk-from-the-sms-sign-in-url-issue-heres-what-you-need-to-look-out-for</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">guK32vEcvsNJkBM4eMhYVR</guid>
      <description>SMS sign-in links frequently expose sensitive data through weak authentication and long-lived, easily guessed URLs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's official &#8211; EVs just outsold gas-powered cars for the first time in Europe, here are 3 reasons why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/its-official-evs-just-outsold-gas-powered-cars-for-the-first-time-in-europe-here-are-3-reasons-why</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PxSa5VTSKw2d4No9bTCtWE</guid>
      <description>EVs outsell petrol cars for the first time. Is this the death knell for fossil fuels?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOC teams are automating triage &#8212; but 40% will fail without governance boundaries</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/security/tier-1-soc-work-becoming-code-architectural-decisions-hours-minutes-response</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3OwrdALAWtGv3ud0Ozz3Xl</guid>
      <description>The average enterprise SOC receives 10,000 alerts per day. Each requires 20 to 40 minutes to investigate properly, but even fully staffed teams can only handle 22% of them. More than 60% of security teams have admitted to ignoring alerts that later proved critical.Running an efficient SOC has never been harder, and now the work itself is changing. Tier-1 analyst tasks &#8212; like triage, enrichment, and escalation &#8212; are becoming software functions, and more SOC teams are turning to supervised AI agents to handle the volume. Human analysts are shifting their priorities to investigate, review, and ma...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The winter storm tested power grids straining to accommodate AI data centers</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/868859/electricity-rates-power-grid-ai-data-center-winter-storm</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T17:28:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868859</guid>
      <description>The colossal winter storm that swept across 34 states left hundreds of thousands of people without electricity. Bitterly cold temperatures lingering after Winter Storm Fern are still testing power grids, already under stress from a rush of new AI data centers. Over the weekend, wholesale electricity prices soared in Virginia, the state with the most [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clawdbot is a viral AI assistant: What it is, how to try it</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/what-is-clawdbot-how-to-try</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">067MTpvSoreOabKW0mNjVgU</guid>
      <description>Clawdbot is a personal AI assistant that's achieved viral status among early adopters and Silicon Valley insiders. So, what is Clawdbot, and how can you try it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First &#8216;Faces of Death&#8217; Teaser Is Here to Remind You That Yes, They Remade &#8216;Faces of Death&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/faces-of-death-remake-trailer-2000714625</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714625</guid>
      <description>The gruesome faux documentary gets a 2026 update framed through some appropriately underground marketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says its investigating its Epstein problem</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tiktok-epstein-investigation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05qcAluKTN33SGXVxVNzT8z</guid>
      <description>TikTok responds to users who found they can't use the word 'Epstein' in their direct messages: it's happening, but inconsistently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French President takes aim at &#8216;American platforms&#8217; and &#8216;Chinese algorithms&#8217; as France moves to ban social media for under-15s</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/french-president-takes-aim-at-american-platforms-and-chinese-algorithms-as-france-moves-to-ban-social-media-for-under-15s</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oQTuPPy6j9DLkw37xzS7EQ</guid>
      <description>&#8216;The emotions of our children and teenagers are not for sale&#8217; &#8211; France wants its own social media ban for minors, and it won&#8217;t be the last we see in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn complex ideas into clear visuals with this $10 Microsoft tool</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-27-microsoft-visio-2021-professional-lifetime-license-for-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01NHcb5R7gOvn1TFdQc2EV9</guid>
      <description>Give a stand-out presentation with this Microsoft Visio 2021 Professional lifetime license for Windows, on sale now for only $9.97 (reg. $249) through Feb. 8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Pegula vs. Anisimova online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pegula-anisimova-australian-open-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">071rALEO0p6rwwt9YlOAkFV</guid>
      <description>Watch Australian Open for free. Live stream Pegula vs. Anisimova in the 2026 Australian Open online for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anduril has invented a wild new&#160;drone flying contest where jobs are the prize</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/anduril-has-invented-a-wild-new-drone-flying-contest-where-jobs-are-the-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086813</guid>
      <description>This is a race series for software programmers and the brainchild of founder Palmer Luckey, he tells TechCrunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok settles as Meta and Google face jury in social media addiction suit</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tiktok-meta-youtube-social-media-addiction-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07x5xaQi1Tn0QoGWLsh2JEB</guid>
      <description>Following Snapchat, TikTok settles out of a jury trial that will put Meta and Google on the witness stand over mental health concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best fitness trackers and watches we&#8217;ve tested</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T16:51:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker</guid>
      <description>Fitness trackers have come a long way from the simple bands that tracked steps and little else. Modern trackers can monitor everything from your heart health to how well you&#8217;ve recovered from a hard bout of training. Even flagship smartwatches, which used to be lackluster trackers, have become pretty adept workout companions. Whatever your fitness [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People are joking about Signal alternatives amid FBI investigation</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/signal-alternative-meme-jokes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05W9CBdzzvFyzL1kBaYWrX9</guid>
      <description>People are making memes and jokes about alternatives to Signal amid the FBI investigation into chats used by Minnesota residents to share ICE information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticketmaster is selling $1,000 Harry Styles tickets. Fans are not having it.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/harry-styles-together-together-tour-tickets-prices-ticketmaster</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04byV5CCPCEFSSSyCWKIBTu</guid>
      <description>Harry Styles fans are outraged online as Ticketmaster prices soar for the pop star's Together, Together tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop upgrades its Firefly-powered generative-AI editing tools</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/adobe-photoshop-upgrades-its-firefly-powered-generative-ai-editing-tools-213737915.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fed77372-b7b0-4872-9c41-6537a756cb0e</guid>
      <description>Adobe Photoshop introduced some new features that are rolling out for creators today. As you'd expect from any service operator in this day and age, there's some AI involved. Adobe has improved the tools for Generative Fill, Generative Expand and Remove that are powered by its Firefly generative AI platform. Using these tools for image editing should now produce results in 2K resolution with fewer artifacts and increased detail all while delivering better matches for the provided prompts. The Reference Image option for Generative Fill has also been upgraded to deliver "geometry-aware results t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluesky teases 2026 roadmap: A better Discover feed, real-time features, and more</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/bluesky-teases-2026-roadmap-a-better-discover-feed-real-time-features-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086636</guid>
      <description>Bluesky is teasing new features  and improvements ranging from the Discover feed to video support.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
