<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:34:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What to do if the Galaxy S26 Ultra is a dud? Well, you could simply opt for the Galaxy Z Fold 7 while it's going cheap</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/what-to-do-if-the-galaxy-s26-ultra-is-a-dud-well-you-could-simply-opt-for-the-galaxy-z-fold-7-while-its-going-cheap</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac8xXn9yhTkRJAqDX6W6gK</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S26 Ultra might blow our minds, but Samsung's other high-end device is still a fantastic device right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le ministre de l&#8217;IA &#224; la recherche d&#8217;investissements en Arabie saoudite et en Inde</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-16/le-ministre-de-l-ia-a-la-recherche-d-investissements-en-arabie-saoudite-et-en-inde.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:14:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8a3bc2075383c9e9d081eb6f5cc2e5a</guid>
      <description>Le ministre de l&#8217;Intelligence artificielle, Evan Solomon, se rend en Arabie saoudite et puis en Inde pour faire suite &#224; sa visite en Allemagne, dans le cadre des efforts pour attirer des investissements dans le secteur technologique.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a dedicated channel for Formula 1 in the Apple TV app now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/theres-a-dedicated-channel-for-formula-1-in-the-apple-tv-app-now-230904295.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c1c19ea-980d-4e4f-96dd-07a2b05520f7</guid>
      <description>Apple continues to double down on its Formula 1 programming, following up on the box office success of its blockbuster movie by adding a dedicated channel for the racing league to the Apple TV app. This section of the streaming service hints at some of what may be coming when the F1 season begins with the kickoff event in Australia next month. The F1 channel has placeholders for practices, qualifying and the grand prix as well as a weekend warm-up show.Although it announced the five-year deal to host F1 broadcasts in the US back in October, we still haven't heard many specifics on how Apple's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fractal Scape has no business offering this many features for a wireless headset at this price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/fractal-design-scape-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LMW6e7GAGAvGvgFvuQd7dM</guid>
      <description>A minimalist wireless headset with a surprisingly affordable price considering how feature-rich it is. It&#8217;s like Apple got into the gaming market &#8211; and became way more generous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I review 4K Blu-rays for a living and these are 6 of the best 4K action movies to show off your home theater</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/i-review-4k-blu-rays-for-a-living-and-these-are-6-of-the-best-4k-action-movies-to-show-off-your-home-theater</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UeWCGFV7xYDte9evyjbAc3</guid>
      <description>Action movies can be a great way to show off your home theater system, and these 6 4K discs are some of the best I've ever tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Rode mics can now connect directly to iPhones and iPads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/more-rode-mics-can-now-connect-directly-to-iphones-and-ipads-230000533.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01b8b9b5-e96a-4c1e-8258-d2d12745283c</guid>
      <description>Rode is rolling out a firmware update for its Wireless Pro and Wireless Go (third-gen) microphones to add a feature called Direct Connect, which was already available for the Wireless Micro. This allows the mics to pair with iPhones and iPads via Bluetooth without the need for a receiver. All you&#8217;ll need is the Rode Capture app. Rode said it&#8217;s able to offer Direct Connect for Wireless Pro and Wireless Go without compromising &#8220;the broadcast-quality audio both wireless systems are known for.&#8221; The feature still supports the option to record from two transmitters in either merged (whereby the audi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My own opinion is that much of the fear is overblown': AWS CEO thinks investors may be worrying about AI risks too much</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/my-own-opinion-is-that-much-of-the-fear-is-overblown-aws-ceo-thinks-investors-may-be-worrying-about-ai-risks-too-much</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zyg6PBM5HQ4XWUchm8bETa</guid>
      <description>Investors worry AI could weaken software margins, while Amazon Web Services reports solid expansion and questions the scale of market panic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile will go offline on April 17</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-will-go-offline-on-april-17-222240967.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed71508e-3698-46ae-a740-a97487832ae3</guid>
      <description>Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile will be no more this spring. According to Activision, servers will be taken offline for this mobile battle royale game on April 17, 2026. The shooter will remain available for current players until that date. This mobile port of the CoD battle royale mode has been on its way to a finale for the past year, with the game studio sharing in May 2025 that the title would be delisted and would not receive new content.For any people who still want to play the military shooter on their phones, there a mobile version of the main game remains available. Call of Duty: Mobile ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Found a Massive Lava Tube Hiding Beneath the Surface of Venus</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-found-a-massive-lava-tube-hiding-beneath-the-surface-of-venus-2000722596</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722596</guid>
      <description>Venus may be hiding a vast network of underground caves carved by ancient lava.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Aerial_Knight&#8217;s DropShot&#8217; Shoots Strong and Lands Well Enough</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/aerial_knights-dropshot-shoots-strong-and-lands-well-enough-2000719683</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719683</guid>
      <description>The game's airborne action makes for some good blasting, even if not all of it soars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BJ&#8217;s Wholesale Club membership prices just dropped to $20 (usually $60)</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-16-one-year-the-club-card-membership-with-bj</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06tw2hIXDSTlSM6bkxyPkdg</guid>
      <description>A BJ's Club Card Membership is now only $20</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
