<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:27:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>10 impossibly small Japanese laptops under 1Kg that you will probably never be able to buy (unless you fly there)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/10-impossibly-small-japanese-laptops-under-1kg-that-you-will-probably-never-be-able-to-buy-unless-you-fly-there</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kuEY7EY7yXYiTtKsbGAmB6</guid>
      <description>Ten impossibly small Japanese laptops under 1kg - but you'll probably never be able to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration seeks to deport hate speech researcher previously sued by X</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/27/trump-administration-seeks-to-deport-hate-speech-researcher-previously-sued-by-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079117</guid>
      <description>A federal judge has temporarily blocked the U.S. Department of State from arresting or deporting Imran Ahmed, CEO of the Center for Countering Digital Hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get an Amazon Echo Dot for Christmas? Discover the 3 features that revolutionized my smart home setup</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-speakers/get-an-amazon-echo-dot-for-christmas-discover-the-3-features-that-revolutionized-my-smart-home-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eqjRj5KaQFTt7a6J8QLjJd</guid>
      <description>Whether you were on the nice list or just decided to treat yourself, I&#8217;m gifting you with three Alexa features you&#8217;ll be glad you tried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Wonder Woman Like This?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-is-wonder-woman-like-this-2000702225</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702225</guid>
      <description>Between 'Wonder Woman 1984' and her game getting canned, the 2020s haven't been Diana's decade. Maybe that'll change with the 2030s?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s the first real look at the Retroid Pocket 6 running PS2 games</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/heres-the-first-real-look-at-the-retroid-pocket-6-running-ps2-games-193624145.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f445a19-9886-407e-930f-449bb0e7c2bd</guid>
      <description>The Retroid Pocket 6 may have gotten off to a rocky start, but the gaming handheld is officially completed and going to see its first shipments soon. The handheld maker revealed the final product shots of the Retroid Pocket 6 in black and orange on X. Along with in-person product pics, Retroid revealed gameplay videos of its handheld, running emulation of PlayStation 2 games.

For those looking to relive some classic Nintendo or PlayStation titles, the Retroid Pocket 6 offers a great entry point into the retro handheld world since it can emulate games up to Nintendo Switch and PS2. However, Re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;m TechRadar&#8217;s reviews editor &#8211; here are the 5 best gadgets I&#8217;ve tested all year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/im-techradars-reviews-editor-here-are-the-5-best-gadgets-ive-tested-all-year</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YH8DQFSiNFJY6Ftt59jD2Z</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m in charge of reviews here at TechRadar &#8211; these are the 5 best gadgets I personally tested in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman is hiring someone to worry about the dangers of AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850537/sam-altman-openai-head-of-preparedness</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-27T14:00:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850537</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is hiring a Head of Preparedness. Or, in other words, someone whose primary job is to think about all the ways AI could go horribly, horribly wrong. In a post on X, Sam Altman announced the position by acknowledging that the rapid improvement of AI models poses "some real challenges." The post goes on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors share what to remember while raising a Series A</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/27/investors-share-what-to-remember-while-raising-a-series-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078443</guid>
      <description>Investors share what founders should remember if looking to raise a Series A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Dolby Atmos FlexConnect to Marshall and KEF getting into the game, 2025 was a great year for soundbars</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/from-dolby-atmos-flexconnect-to-marshall-and-kef-getting-into-the-game-2025-was-a-great-year-for-soundbars</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JAdNisTJSZSCLrVBPiKytV</guid>
      <description>In 2025, we saw models arrive from new brands, stalwarts like Samsung and LG resting on their laurels, and a big change in the form of Dolby Atmos FlexConnect. All in all, it was an interesting year for soundbars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CIOs must lead AI experimentation, not just govern it</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/why-cios-must-lead-ai-experimentation-not-just-govern-it</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gTUdyTUXWZ2FaOVj9JUTG</guid>
      <description>The drumbeat for AI is deafening. We&#8217;re surrounded by a mix of hype, fear and intense pressure to do something with this technology that seems to be advancing at the speed of light. For CIOs and enterprise technology leaders, the path forward can seem murky and fraught with the risk of missteps. But I believe the greatest risk isn't getting it wrong; it's waiting for a &#8220;perfect&#8221; AI strategy while the world races ahead. Real impact with AI doesn't start with flawless, grand designs. It begins with access, trust and a commitment to hands-on learning.My journey with technology, even before my cor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec une baisse de 60 % &#224; la Fnac, la Nacon Revolution X co&#251;te maintenant moins cher qu&#8217;une manette classique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2921395_avec-une-baisse-de-60-a-la-fnac-la-nacon-revolution-x-coute-maintenant-moins-cher-quune-manette-classique</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2921395_avec-une-baisse-de-60-a-la-fnac-la-nacon-revolution-x-coute-maintenant-moins-cher-quune-manette-classique</guid>
      <description>
La Nacon Revolution X offre de nombreuses options de personnalisation pour convenir &#224; tous les styles de jeu. Du c&#244;t&#233; de la Fnac, vous pouvez la retrouver pour 39,99 euros 
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
