<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe-coding startup Lovable raises $330M at a $6.6B valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/vibe-coding-startup-lovable-raises-330m-at-a-6-6b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077319</guid>
      <description>Lovable has seen its valuation more than triple just five months after the company's last funding round in July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V&#233;lo &#233;lectrique Moustache : tout comprendre &#224; la gamme et quel mod&#232;le choisir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/1795057_velo-electrique-moustache-tout-comprendre-a-la-gamme-et-quel-modele-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/1795057_velo-electrique-moustache-tout-comprendre-a-la-gamme-et-quel-modele-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Avec plus de 70&#160;mod&#232;les au catalogue, Moustache propose des v&#233;los &#233;lectriques ciblant chacun un besoin sp&#233;cifique. Voici notre guide pour comprendre leurs diff&#233;rences et bien choisir son VAE parmi cette offre pl&#233;thorique. Quel v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique Moustache choisir ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo pr&#233;parerait des cartouches de Switch 2 avec moins de m&#233;moire, mais pour quoi faire ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nintendo/2915075_nintendo-preparerait-des-cartouches-de-switch-2-avec-moins-de-memoire-mais-pour-quoi-faire</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nintendo/2915075_nintendo-preparerait-des-cartouches-de-switch-2-avec-moins-de-memoire-mais-pour-quoi-faire</guid>
      <description>
Plusieurs sources affirment que des cartouches Switch 2 avec moins de 64 Go de stockage arrivent. Voyons quel serait leur int&#233;r&#234;t.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New data shows that only 1.6 million units of video game hardware were sold in the US in November, making it the worst month since 1995</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/new-data-shows-that-only-1-6-million-units-of-video-game-hardware-were-sold-in-the-us-in-november-making-it-the-worst-month-since-1995</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7xNuK6J9SgVXUPZZeZJfEM</guid>
      <description>Video game hardware and physical software sales just had their worst November in the United States since 1995, despite the holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#8217;t gift earbuds or headphones &#8216;til you read this! My job is testing audio &#8211; these are 6 best cheap buys for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/dont-gift-earbuds-or-headphones-til-you-read-this-my-job-is-testing-audio-these-are-6-best-cheap-buys-for-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3MXQatgm54FiAQi2u7tvWY</guid>
      <description>My pick of the 3 top headphones and 3 best earbuds to give as gifts this Holiday season; all TechRadar approved &#8211; and no product over $80</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 5 will 'be existing in a world where the stories and events of the show happened or are happening', says Todd Howard</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/fallout-5-will-be-existing-in-a-world-where-the-stories-and-events-of-the-show-happened-or-are-happening-says-todd-howard</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">txqZraxiv9RVC8GGoiWhTf</guid>
      <description>Todd Howard, director and executive producer at Bethesda Game Studios, has teased the next Fallout game, confirming that it will be impacted by Amazon's Fallout TV series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's Mac mini M4 is on sale for $479 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-mac-mini-m4-is-on-sale-for-479-right-now-150041630.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4b87d1c-bb4f-4033-b906-fff96c9cb013</guid>
      <description>This time of year is not only a good time to save on gifts, but also to save on tech you may need (or want) for yourself. If you've been thinking about upgrading your computer, you can save right now on Apple's Mac mini M4. The desktop is down to $479, which is 20 percent off its usual price and the same low price we saw during Black Friday.
Apple released the Mac mini M4 in late 2024 and we were impressed with how something so small could be so powerful. We gave it a 90 in our review, thanks to features like its speed and standard 16GB of RAM. The &#8212; currently &#8212; $479 base model also comes with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA reveals warning on Asus software flaw, here's what you need to do to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/cisa-reveals-warning-on-asus-software-flaw-heres-what-you-need-to-do-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kKKmFu97zDzRBhfKWDbnKU</guid>
      <description>A poisoned Asus utility tool was found floating around the web, granting attackers abilities to "perform unintended actions".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psst, Oscar Voters: Guillermo del Toro&#8217;s &#8216;Frankenstein&#8217; Exhibit Is Coming to Hollywood</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/psst-oscar-voters-guillermo-del-toros-frankenstein-exhibit-is-coming-to-hollywood-2000701117</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701117</guid>
      <description>The horror master's passion project has such lavish production design, its relics literally belong in a museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Best Android Phones of 2025, Tested and Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-android-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ad9f8845ac0d714a1b64321</guid>
      <description>Shopping for a phone can be an ordeal. That&#8217;s why we&#8217;ve tested almost every Android phone, from the smartest to the cheapest&#8212;even phones that fold&#8212;to find the ones worth your money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opposed to Data Centers? The Working Families Party Wants You to Run for Office</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/opposed-to-data-centers-the-working-families-party-wants-you-to-run-for-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6941809aef537c700b725051</guid>
      <description>The influential progressive third party announced Thursday that it was putting out a recruitment call for candidates specifically opposed to data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest iPad Air is $400 for the first time and arrives by Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/847156/apple-ipad-air-m3-astro-bot-airpods-pro-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847156</guid>
      <description>If you have $400 and want an iPad, your options are usually kind of limited to either just the base iPad, or better yet, the latest iPad Mini &#8212; if it happens to be on sale when you&#8217;re shopping (it is now, but that&#8217;s not always the case). But right now, you should consider getting [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s new Alexa+ feature adds conversational AI to Ring doorbells</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/amazons-new-alexa-feature-adds-conversational-ai-to-ring-doorbells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077277</guid>
      <description>Amazon said that the feature uses the Ring doorbell's video descriptions to determine who the person in front the camera is based on their uniform, actions, and what they are holding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Ring doorbell can now use Alexa+ to identify who's calling and give them an appropriate greeting</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/your-ring-doorbell-can-now-use-alexa-to-identify-whos-calling-and-give-them-an-appropriate-greeting</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KzSwR6SvjXkrFNT9ttaaPU</guid>
      <description>Alexa+ Greetings can recognize and give instructions to delivery people, greet friends and family, and (politely) turn away cold callers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Enlaps Tikee mini+ 4K timelapse camera &#8211; it&#8217;s a breeze to use, but the extra costs sure do add up</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/enlaps-tikee-mini-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VBvJHz5cyEdMNLUt9g3RFb</guid>
      <description>The Enlaps Tikee mini+ timelapse camera delivers fanatsic image quality alongside ease of use, all with an incredibly simple design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta just u-turned on the best VR announcement it ever made &#8212; and might have handed the win to Android XR</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/meta-just-u-turned-on-the-best-vr-announcement-it-ever-made-and-might-have-handed-the-win-to-android-xr</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfmkPPuAjHrbmbmPTMfL9N</guid>
      <description>Meta has &#8216;paused&#8217; third-party headset partnerships, which feels like a major win for Android XR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuite massive de donn&#233;es &#224; la CAF&#160;: les informations de 8,6 millions de Fran&#231;ais compromises</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fuite-massive-donnees-caf-informations-86-millions-francais-compromises.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315984</guid>
      <description>Une fuite massive frappe la Caisse des Allocations Familiales (CAF). Des pirates ont pu exfiltrer plus de 22 millions de donn&#233;es personnelles. Plus de huit millions de Fran&#231;ais seraient touch&#233;s. Les hackers du minist&#232;re de l'Int&#233;rieur sont bien d&#233;cid&#233;s &#224; montrer qu'ils ne plaisantent pas&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway e-scooters are under half price at Best Buy thanks to huge last-minute price cuts of up to $650</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/e-scooters/segway-e-scooters-are-under-half-price-at-best-buy-thanks-to-huge-last-minute-price-cuts-of-up-to-usd650</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6UKUyx6xJNjBxmByipeCeQ</guid>
      <description>Best Buy's huge last-minute sale is offering some of the best price cuts we've seen all year on Segway e-scooters, with some deals under half price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA r&#233;duirait la production des RTX 50&#160;: vers une nouvelle p&#233;nurie de cartes graphiques en 2026&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/nvidia-reduirait-la-production-des-rtx-50-vers-une-nouvelle-penurie-de-cartes-graphiques-en-2026.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316102</guid>
      <description>Les joueurs PC esp&#233;raient une accalmie, ils risquent de subir une nouvelle temp&#234;te. Selon plusieurs sources industrielles, NVIDIA pr&#233;voit de r&#233;duire drastiquement les livraisons de ses puces graphiques grand public d&#232;s le d&#233;but de l'ann&#233;e prochaine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 : ces deux services plombent secr&#232;tement les performances de votre PC</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2915021_windows-11-ces-deux-services-plombent-secretement-les-performances-de-votre-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2915021_windows-11-ces-deux-services-plombent-secretement-les-performances-de-votre-pc</guid>
      <description>
Deux composants syst&#232;me de Windows 11 sont point&#233;s du doigt pour leur impact n&#233;gatif sur les performances. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour No&#235;l, Amazon d&#233;stocke le tr&#232;s bon OnePlus Nord CE5 &#224; un prix in&#233;dit</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2736705_pour-noel-amazon-destocke-le-tres-bon-oneplus-nord-ce5-a-un-prix-inedit</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2736705_pour-noel-amazon-destocke-le-tres-bon-oneplus-nord-ce5-a-un-prix-inedit</guid>
      <description>
Avec une fiche technique &#233;quilibr&#233;e et peu de compromis, le OnePlus Nord CE5 est un smartphone &#224; consid&#233;rer. Il a belles choses &#224; offrir pour satisfaire la plupart des utilisateurs, le tout pour moins de 250 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts for dads that have everything (but deserve more)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780847/best-dad-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:38:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780847</guid>
      <description>What do you get the man who says he has everything? It's a tough question - and one you have a limited amount of time to answer, given the holidays are nearly upon us. You could try dropping subtle hints or asking friends and family for suggestions, but they might save their best ideas for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI just launched an app store inside ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-just-launched-an-app-store-inside-chatgpt-133049586.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89caa5fe-19d2-470b-8701-8f4bd44880af</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has introduced an app directory that's now available right inside ChatGPT, the company announced. "Apps extend ChatGPT conversations by bringing in new context and letting users take action like order groceries, turn an outline into a slide deck or search for an apartment," the company wrote in a blog post. OpenAI also noted in a help document that "connector" apps like Google Drive are now simply called "apps."
The new apps section (on iOS, Android and web) is divided into Feature, Lifestyle and Productivity categories, letting you connect to commonly used apps and sites like Booking.c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 was the beginning of the end of the TV brightness war</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/841054/tv-brightness-hdr-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841054</guid>
      <description>Much like the audio industry's compression-driven loudness war, which reached its distortion-fueled apex (and not the good kind) with Metallica's Death Magnetic in 2008, the television industry has been having its own battle the past couple of years: the brightness war. Sparked by the introduction of HDR and its higher brightness mastering levels, brands began [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best white elephant gifts worth fighting over for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-10-best-white-elephant-gifts-worth-fighting-over-for-2025-150516281.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">167b1092-71dd-42b0-b152-e8240159f089</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of competing ideas as to what a white elephant gift exchange really is. The origins of the term &#8220;white elephant&#8221; point to one definition: According to legend, the King of Siam would give a white elephant to courtiers who had upset them. It was a far more devious punishment than simply having them executed. The recipient had no choice but to simply thank the king for such an opulent gift, knowing that they likely could not afford the upkeep for such an animal. It would inevitably lead them to financial ruin.While that story is almost certainly untrue, it can inform one approach ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AirPods Pro 3 are back on sale for a record low of $199</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-airpods-pro-3-are-back-on-sale-for-a-record-low-of-199-222806371.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42f7f263-d7c8-4a21-ad07-9121207a6244</guid>
      <description>No need to fret if you missed out on some of the best Black Friday deals this year &#8212; some of them have returned already. Case in point: Apple's AirPods Pro 3, which came out in September this year, are back down to $199. That's an all-time-low price and better than the price it was during Black Friday and Cyber Monday. With the new AirPods Pro, Apple made some big improvements, including better battery life and sound quality, and introduced useful new features, such as Live Translation.


The AirPods Pro 3 are the best AirPods available today, with Apple's H2 chip, and earned a score of 90 out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media is merging with a nuclear fusion company</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847159/trump-media-tae-technologies-merger-nuclear-fusion</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:06:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847159</guid>
      <description>Trump Media, the company that runs social network Truth Social, is pivoting to nuclear fusion. It has announced a merger with California-based fusion power company TAE Technologies and plans to start construction on a fusion power plant in 2026. Trump Media &amp; Technology Group will become the holding company of the new organization, though shareholders [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco says Chinese hackers are exploiting its customers with a new zero-day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/cisco-says-chinese-hackers-are-exploiting-its-customers-with-a-new-zero-day</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cAcZy3FBribm42eBGMyCAL</guid>
      <description>A patch has not yet been released, so Cisco advises rebuilding any affected instances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sony XM5 headphones now come with free earbuds at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-17-sony-free-earbuds-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03bNXjOcQpJBP4ZX3QMNgv7</guid>
      <description>Find the best free earbuds deal at Amazon. Save 52% on the Sony WH-1000XM5 bundle at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Ezviz HB8 Lite : une cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; intelligente, efficace et accessible</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ezviz/2906591_test-ezviz-hb8-lite-une-camera-de-securite-intelligente-efficace-et-accessible</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ezviz/2906591_test-ezviz-hb8-lite-une-camera-de-securite-intelligente-efficace-et-accessible</guid>
      <description>
Avec sa Ezviz HB8 Lite, le sp&#233;cialiste de la cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; connect&#233;e se lance un challenge : proposer un produit offrant une belle qualit&#233; d'image, une IA efficiente pour reconna&#238;tre les humains et une vision rotative &#224; 340 &#176; ! De beaux arguments, que le prix de 129 euros ne fait que renforcer. Sur le papier en tout cas.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultrahuman brings snoring detection and respiratory health tracking to the Ring Air</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/ultrahuman-brings-snoring-detection-and-respiratory-health-tracking-to-the-ring-air-130054901.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">531672c2-6c78-4772-a060-a239c188d3f0</guid>
      <description>The Ultrahuman Ring Air now has the capacity to track snoring and general respiratory health. This is thanks to proprietary technology called Respiratory Health PowerPlug, which is basically a suite of audio analysis tools along with some "advanced biomarker tracking" and AI tomfoolery.
All of this results in "one of the most comprehensive consumer tools ever built for understanding nighttime respiratory stability." It details snoring sessions, of course, but also delivers a holistic and "actionable sleep picture." The company says this "reveals patterns, trends and changes in respiratory heal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tramell Tillman&#8217;s &#8216;Spider-Man: Brand New Day&#8217; Character May Have Been Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tramell-tillman-spider-man-brand-new-day-character-2000701097</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701097</guid>
      <description>Plus, Daisy Ridley leads a swath of new stars joining Ti West's take on 'Christmas Carol'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade your streaming setup with the Fire TV Cube &#8212; save $30 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-fire-tv-cube-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06BOYaWG4b4xWGPOYKu8u8U</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, the Fire TV Cube is discounted at Amazon to $109.99, 21% off its list price of $139.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s the great AGI rebrand</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/845890/ai-companies-rebrand-agi-artificial-general-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845890</guid>
      <description>The cringe comes for us all, and for all our hot new turns of phrase. "Rizz" lost its luster when grandparents started asking about its meaning. Teachers who dressed up as "6-7" on Halloween drove a nail into the coffin of Gen Alpha's rallying cry. And tech CEOs who once trumpeted the quest for "artificial [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FTC is reportedly investigating Instacart over its AI pricing tool</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/the-ftc-is-reportedly-investigating-instacart-over-its-ai-pricing-tool-130000472.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe9cac17-7766-45de-ab3b-cf20e4ad74af</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission has sent Instacart a civil investigative demand, seeking information about its AI-powered pricing tool, according to Reuters. This comes after a recently published pricing experiment study showed that the online grocery delivery app gave different users different prices for the same items from the same store location at the exact same time. Some of the testers saw prices up to 23 percent higher than what the other testers saw, though the average difference for the same list of items was around 7 percent. Those higher prices could cost customers over $1,000 more in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s no such thing as a Republican font</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461588/theres-no-such-thing-as-a-republican-font</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461588/theres-no-such-thing-as-a-republican-font</guid>
      <description>A new study shows that fonts aren&#8217;t inherently partisan&#8212;but humans are.
Last week, two fonts became the unlikely stars of a political messaging firestorm, after the Trump administration replaced Calibri as its official diplomatic font in favor of Times New Roman, claiming that an initial shift to Calibri in 2023 was part of former President Biden&#8217;s &#8220;DEIA&#8221; agenda. The implication was clear: Calibri was framed as a liberal, Democratic font; while Times New Roman took its place as the Trump administration&#8217;s more conservative choice. Now, a new study is revealing the major flaw in this logic: font...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Star Trek Holodeck just got closer &#8211; Apple&#8217;s new AI tool generates 3D scenes from your photos in under a second for VR memories</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/the-star-trek-holodeck-just-got-closer-apples-new-ai-tool-generates-3d-scenes-from-your-photos-in-under-a-second-for-vr-memories</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TiNGDGpgCdudr39S5r95qX</guid>
      <description>Apple has unveiled an AI tool that can convert images from 2D to 3D in under one second.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic: The Gathering Commander Masters Play Booster Box is now almost $70 below market value on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-magic-the-gathering-commander-masters-play-booster-box-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06DaHLjbuoo1At80c22Ildw</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, Magic: The Gathering &#8212; Commander Master Play Booster Box is below market value at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok aurait acc&#232;s &#224; vos faits et gestes sur cette appli de rencontre, selon cette association</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/tiktok-aurait-acces-a-vos-faits-et-gestes-sur-cette-appli-de-rencontre-selon-cette-association.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316056</guid>
      <description>Le r&#233;seau social chinois suivrait ses utilisateurs sur des applications tierces : la plateforme aurait acc&#232;s &#224; des donn&#233;es collect&#233;es par Grindr, l'application de rencontres gay, selon l'association de d&#233;fense de la vie priv&#233;e NOYB. Ce en violation du RGPD, la loi europ&#233;enne qui prot&#232;ge nos donn&#233;es personnelles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiptole launches 4-ounce bowl of meat for the Ozempic age</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462289/chiptole-launches-4-ounce-bowl-of-meat-for-the-ozempic-age</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T12:53:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462289/chiptole-launches-4-ounce-bowl-of-meat-for-the-ozempic-age</guid>
      <description>The move signals that we&#8217;re about to see a lot more GLP-1-centric menus.
Chipotle is officially in its Ozempic era.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN rolls out major Qt update to boost speed and unify desktop apps</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-rolls-out-major-qt-update-to-boost-speed-and-unify-desktop-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Qtym9iZ3VCeDTkccuRkvKS</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is overhauling its desktop apps with a new Qt-based framework. The update is now live on Linux and macOS &#8211; and Windows is next. Here's all you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoneyBook CRM review 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/software-services/honeybook-crm-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9KbjRXSNgLWkjmuASHA69L</guid>
      <description>HoneyBook stands out as a versatile CRM platform designed specifically for creative entrepreneurs and small businesses. It excels in simplifying client management, automating workflows, and integrating essential business tools. While primarily focused on creative industries, its intuitive interface and continual improvements make it a valuable asset for most small businesses....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose QC Ultra Earbuds (2e Gen) : ces &#233;couteurs &#224; l&#8217;ANC in&#233;gal&#233;e sont &#224; prix cass&#233; pour No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2914653_bose-qc-ultra-earbuds-2e-gen-les-ecouteurs-a-lanc-inegalee-sont-a-prix-casse-pour-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2914653_bose-qc-ultra-earbuds-2e-gen-les-ecouteurs-a-lanc-inegalee-sont-a-prix-casse-pour-noel</guid>
      <description>
La seconde it&#233;ration des QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds de Bose,  n&#8217;est pas une simple mise &#224; jour cosm&#233;tique : c&#8217;est une piq&#251;re de rappel sur ce que la marque sait faire de mieux. De quoi glisser ces &#233;couteurs dans la hotte du P&#232;re No&#235;l &#224; 229 euros au lieu de 299 euros chez Boulanger, avec retrait en magasin sous 1 heure ou livraison d&#232;s le 23 d&#233;cembre.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosses are getting tired of AI at work, and preferring to hire humans for "specialist" roles once again</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/bosses-are-getting-tired-of-ai-at-work-and-preferring-to-hire-humans-for-specialist-roles-once-again</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ozA5Y6krXjLXe2TrMLN9JF</guid>
      <description>AI perception is still torn, but the fact is that companies are shifting their hiring strategies rather than fully displacing human workers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
