<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:24:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Isaacman is NASA's new leader</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/jared-isaacman-is-nasas-new-leader-220833691.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf534aea-a343-4253-b8c9-6032d53ab63a</guid>
      <description>NASA has a leader again. On Wednesday, the US Senate confirmed Jared Isaacman as the agency's administrator, with a 67-30 vote. The billionaire entrepreneur (and Elon Musk ally) will have his hands full navigating political waters while managing a severely downsized workforce.You might recall that this wasn't Isaacman's first shot at the job. He was nominated to the post earlier this year. But days before he was scheduled for a confirmation vote, President Donald Trump withdrew his nomination.The reversal reportedly came after the president was told that Isaacman had donated to prominent Democ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Wicked&#8217; Director Jon M. Chu on &#8216;What Makes Art Beautiful&#8217; in the AI Era</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-wicked-director-jon-m-chu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939b3dfcb2dfff8af097e81</guid>
      <description>In this episode of Uncanny Valley, we bring you our conversation with Jon M. Chu from WIRED&#8217;s Big Interview event, fresh on the heels of directing Wicked: For Good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford is switching some battery focus from cars to data centers - with plans for huge 20GWh capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ford-is-switching-some-battery-focus-from-cars-to-data-centers-with-plans-for-huge-20gwh-capacity</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zNZsAYVp3J2GEkFeQLf6V4</guid>
      <description>Ford halts electric pickup production and redirects battery investments toward stationary energy storage for grids, data centers, and residential systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboard's charts are increasingly weighted towards on-demand streaming, but not enough for YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/billboards-charts-are-increasingly-weighted-towards-on-demand-streaming-but-not-enough-for-youtube-220238291.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bf442e1-2011-4fe7-8775-00fec52dae9d</guid>
      <description>YouTube announced that it will no longer share data with Billboard for the creation of the Billboard Hot 100 and other charts because the video platform doesn't believe they're calculated fairly. The issue lies, per YouTube, with how Billboard weighs on-demand streams in its rankings: The publication weighs streams from paid music streaming services over ad-supported streams, and YouTube just so happens to run an ad-supported streaming service.Much like getting a book on The New York Times Bestseller list, landing a spot on the Billboard charts doesn't carry quite the same importance that it o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vesuvius Exploded in August&#8212;So Why Were Pompeii Victims Wearing Heavy Clothing?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/vesuvius-exploded-in-august-so-why-were-pompeii-victims-wearing-heavy-clothing-2000700770</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700770</guid>
      <description>Despite the fact that Mount Vesuvius triggered one of the most infamous ancient tragedies, not everyone agrees on exactly when it took place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>With a good virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart those online trackers that watch you sleep and show you weird personalized ads. Although we strongly recommend using a VPN, jumping on the first deal that comes along might get you stuck with a substandard app. Beyond that, even otherwise respectable VPNs sometimes frame their prices in misleading ways, with advertised deals not always as available as they seem to be.
Even so, there are some great bargains on the table. For the holiday season, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Isaacman confirmed as next head of NASA</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/jared-isaacman-confirmed-as-next-head-of-nasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077127</guid>
      <description>Isaacman will run the space agency at a time when Trump is trying to both downsize it and task it with returning astronauts to the Moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Group Extorts Pornhub Over Premium User Data</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hacker-group-extorts-pornhub-over-premium-user-data-2000700978</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700978</guid>
      <description>If you can't trust a porn site with your credit card, who can you trust?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sigourney Weaver Wishes There Was More &#8216;Galaxy Quest,&#8217; But There Probably Won&#8217;t Be</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sigourney-weaver-wishes-there-was-more-galaxy-quest-but-there-probably-wont-be-2000700972</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700972</guid>
      <description>The actress would like to see DreamWorks re-release the film to honor the late, great Alan Rickman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell reportedly preparing massive price hikes for commercial clients - and warns "Ordering today for future delivery DOES NOT lock in current pricing"</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dell-reportedly-preparing-massive-price-hikes-for-commercial-clients-and-warns-ordering-today-for-future-delivery-does-not-lock-in-current-pricing</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TgSeBqF8xZWtQCQuTHjR8A</guid>
      <description>Dell will increase commercial product prices starting December 17 due to memory shortages, affecting laptops, desktops, mini workstations, and AI-enabled devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta pauses third-party Horizon VR headsets program</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846762/meta-vr-headsets-third-party-program-horizon-os</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T16:24:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846762</guid>
      <description>Meta has "paused" its program to license its VR operating system to other hardware companies so they could build their own headsets using the platform, as reported by Road to VR . With the program, announced in April 2024, Meta announced that it would be licensing the Quest OS headset - which, at the same [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic lawmakers are investigating data centers&#8217; impact on electricity costs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846696/electricity-cost-ai-data-center-democrat-investigation</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T16:12:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846696</guid>
      <description>Sens. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA), Chris Van Hollen (D-MD), and Richard Blumenthal (D-CT) fired off a letter on Tuesday to Google, Microsoft, Amazon, Meta, and several major data center developers to investigate the impact they're having on Americans' utility bills. The move comes as rising electricity rates became an increasingly hot-button issue in the US, which [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Surf Crew Captures a Real-Life Ocean &#8216;Glitch&#8217; That Repeats</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/australian-surf-crew-captures-a-real-life-ocean-glitch-that-repeats-2000700939</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700939</guid>
      <description>The converging waves swirl until they finally break into a 130-foot pillar of saltwater, in a process that scientists have yet to fully explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Secret Santa gift ideas for 2025: Affordable gifts you can still get from Lego, Apple, Yeti and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-secret-santa-gift-ideas-for-2025-affordable-gifts-you-can-still-get-from-lego-apple-yeti-and-more-130014284.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3419426-0b76-49ed-9322-bfc6839435ec</guid>
      <description>Secret Santa gift exchanges are supposed to be fun, but it&#8217;s easy to overthink it. You want a gift that feels thoughtful without being awkward, useful without being boring, and most importantly, affordable. The sweet spot is under $50, which is plenty to find something that fits your recipient&#8217;s personality. Whether you&#8217;re buying for a co-worker you only chat with at the coffee machine, a friend who already has everything or a cousin who never gives you ideas, there are clever options that will make them smile. These picks prove you don&#8217;t need to spend big to win at Secret Santa.
Best Secret S...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheddar Lovers, Rejoice: Eating High-Fat Cheese May Lower Dementia Risk</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cheddar-lovers-rejoice-eating-high-fat-cheese-may-lower-dementia-risk-2000700802</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700802</guid>
      <description>Cheese can be part of a brain-healthy diet and might even help lower dementia risk, researchers in Sweden have concluded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can snag a pair of the Beats Solo 4 headphones for under $100 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/846609/beats-solo-4-wireless-headphones-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846609</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re looking for a gadget to get as a last-minute Christmas gift, we&#8217;ve got your back. The Beats Solo 4 are among the best on-ear headphones we&#8217;ve tested in the last year or two, and they&#8217;re currently down to a new low of $79 ($120 off) in select colors at Walmart. If you prefer [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golf Channel Games 2025 live streams: how to watch golf online for free, teams, stream Scheffler vs McIlory</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/golf/golf-channel-games-2025-live-streams-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">W9E2ynHQs7mvWkhPCsxj7Q</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch The Golf Channel Games 2025 live streams online and without cable from anywhere, as Team Scottie takes on Team Rory at Trump Jupiter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small talk, phone anxiety and more: Gen Z sounds off on office fears</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461788/small-talk-phone-anxiety-and-more-gen-z-sounds-off-on-office-fears</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461788/small-talk-phone-anxiety-and-more-gen-z-sounds-off-on-office-fears</guid>
      <description>Two UK surveys and social media chatter reveal what some of the youngest workers stress out about at work.
Gen Z is never beating the &#8220;unemployable&#8221; allegations.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia stock price takes another hit as Wall Street debates an AI bubble. Here&#8217;s why it&#8217;s down today</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462313/nvidia-stock-price-takes-another-hit-as-wall-street-debates-an-ai-bubble-heres-why-its-down-today</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:58:34</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462313/nvidia-stock-price-takes-another-hit-as-wall-street-debates-an-ai-bubble-heres-why-its-down-today</guid>
      <description>Massive AI spending plans are colliding with fears that the market may be overbuilding too fast.
Concerns about an AI bubble and increased competition are weighing on Nvidia as the stock fell to a three-month low on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube to pull music data from Billboard&#8217;s charts because it doesn&#8217;t like its ranking formula</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/youtube-to-pull-music-data-from-billboards-charts-because-it-doesnt-like-its-ranking-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077066</guid>
      <description>YouTube takes its ball and goes home by pulling Billboard's access to its music data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Warner Brothers-Netflix merger could doom Hollywood film workers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462164/warner-brothers-discovery-netflix-paramount-ellison-sarandos-zaslav</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462164/warner-brothers-discovery-netflix-paramount-ellison-sarandos-zaslav</guid>
      <description>For media moguls, maximizing shareholder value is the only metric that counts
In the months following 2023&#8217;s Writers Guild of America (WGA) and Screen Actors Guild&#8211;American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (SAG-AFTRA) strikes, film-industry workers adopted a refrain: &#8220;Survive &#8216;til &#8216;25&#8221; &#8212;&#160; a meager goal reflecting industry reality. The strikes came shortly after the Covid-19 pandemic ground production to a halt. The dream factory had become a nightmare....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first post-EA FIFA soccer sim will be a Netflix Games exclusive</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-first-post-ea-fifa-soccer-sim-will-be-a-netflix-games-exclusive-204321196.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d3cea94-8666-4f9c-9097-910299d01f87</guid>
      <description>FIFA's first true soccer sim after the end of its EA partnership will be available exclusively on Netflix, the streaming service announced. This "reimagined FIFA football simulation game" will be developed and published by Delphi Interactive, and be available to Netflix subscribers next year, right in time for FIFA World Cup 2026.EA and FIFA maintained a nearly 30 year partnership creating soccer games before they parted ways in 2022. EA continued its soccer series afterward as EA FC, but despite being in talks with "leading game publishers, media companies and investors" about "a major new FI...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America&#8217;s Dirtiest Carbon Polluters, Mapped to Ridiculous Precision</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/americas-dirtiest-carbon-polluters-mapped-to-ridiculous-precision-2000700924</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700924</guid>
      <description>&#8220;The U.S. taxpayers have a right to this data.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Crossing: New Horizons could be killer app for Switch 2 mouse</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/animal-crossing-nintendo-switch-2-mouse-controls</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0571QXC79kEmvob0uWPx6tF</guid>
      <description>The Nintendo Switch 2 version of 'Animal Crossing: New Horizons' could finally justify the system's mouse functionality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RayNeo X3 Pro Review: These AR Smart Glasses May Haunt My Dreams</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rayneo-x3-pro-review-these-ar-glasses-may-haunt-my-dreams-2000699219</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699219</guid>
      <description>I never want to sideload anything ever again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Sense8&#8217; Is a Great Companion Sci-Fi TV Show to &#8216;Pluribus&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sense8-is-a-great-companion-sci-fi-tv-show-to-pluribus-2000700845</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700845</guid>
      <description>The sci-fi series from Vince Gilligan and the Wachowskis share themes on the human condition, making for a compelling double feature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon has a new leader for its &amp;#8216;AGI&amp;#8217; group as it plays catch-up on AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846721/amazon-new-agi-leader-peter-desantis-rohit-prasad</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T15:28:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846721</guid>
      <description>Amazon's head of artificial general intelligence (AGI), Rohit Prasad, is leaving the company next year as it reaches an "inflection point" in its development of the technology, CEO Andy Jassy announced on Wednesday. As part of the change, Peter DeSantis, a senior vice president at Amazon Web Services, will helm a new division focused on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts for pets (and their parents): 35+ ideas that the internet and Mashable reporters stand by</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/gifts/best-gifts-for-pet-owners</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07zYmspiXFHvimLBjJw0sHg</guid>
      <description>We gathered 39 Mashable-approved pet gift ideas, including useful gifts for dog owners, enticing cat beds, and viral pet toys.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
