<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:23:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The AI that scored 95% &#8212; until consultants learned it was AI</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-ai-that-scored-95-until-consultants-learned-it-was-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FNaGhLArww10Oem1tqKYg</guid>
      <description>Presented by SAPWhen SAP ran a quiet internal experiment to gauge consultant attitudes toward AI, the results were striking. Five teams were asked to validate answers to more than 1,000 business requirements completed by SAP&#8217;s AI co-pilot, Joule for Consultants &#8212; a workload that would normally take several weeks.Four teams were told the analysis had been completed by junior interns fresh out of school. They reviewed the material, found it impressive, and rated the work about 95% accurate.The fifth team was told the very same answers had come from AI.They rejected almost everything.Only when as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fal nabs $140M in fresh funding led by Sequoia, tripling valuation to $4.5B</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/fal-nabs-140m-in-fresh-funding-led-by-sequoia-tripling-valuation-to-4-5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074455</guid>
      <description>The round, which was Fal&#8217;s third fundraise this year, also included a secondary sale for early investors, sources tell us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashew Research is going after the $90B market research industry with AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/cashew-research-is-going-after-the-90b-market-research-industry-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074454</guid>
      <description>Cashew Research uses AI to automate the market research process while still collecting real-world data from humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber is installing kiosks for booking rides without the mobile app</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/uber-is-installing-kiosks-for-booking-rides-without-the-mobile-app-220904106.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc6dfd88-b030-4a18-b235-9c4d686df392</guid>
      <description>Uber is rolling out kiosks for travelers to book rideshares without using the mobile app. The company is pitching the service as a convenience for international travelers who may not have a data plan, but it could also be a lifesaver if your phone runs out of juice and you don't have a way to recharge it. A passenger can use the kiosk to enter their destination and desired ride type, then will receive a printed receipt with the details about their booked ride. The first kiosk will debut in Terminal C at LaGuardia Airport in New York City, but Uber said it would have additional locations in air...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram is generating SEO-bait headlines for its users' posts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/instagram-is-generating-seo-bait-headlines-for-its-users-posts-213702800.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59c242a7-fa9a-40b9-9696-8f700703df92</guid>
      <description>It looks like Meta has decided to turn Instagram users into unwitting SEO spam pawns. On Tuesday, 404 Media reported that the platform is generating sensational, likely AI-generated headlines and descriptions for user posts without their knowledge or explicit consent. An Engadget editor has also noticed this on their posts. The headlines are found in the pages&#8217; code and are only visible in search results.The scheme appears to be an effort to boost the Google search ranking of Instagram content. An Instagram post by Engadget&#8217;s Sam Chapman, about a board game he created, received an unwanted gen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slack's CEO is joining OpenAI to find the money to pay for all those data centers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/slacks-ceo-is-joining-openai-to-find-the-money-to-pay-for-all-those-data-centers-220411962.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4359f5b2-ae72-4285-8ff3-3515afea8fee</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has announced that Denise Dresser, the current CEO of Slack, will be the company's new Chief Revenue Officer. Dresser will oversee the company's revenue strategy "across enterprise and customer success," according to OpenAI's announcement, and will presumably play a key role in leading the company towards profitability now that it's reorganized as a public benefit corporation."We're on a path to put AI tools into the hands of millions of workers, across every industry," Fidji Simo, OpenAI's CEO of Products said in the announcement. "Denise has led that kind of shift before, and her expe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Doom Will Toot in the Next Marvel &#8216;Magic: The Gathering&#8217; Set</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/magic-the-gathering-marvel-super-heroes-spoilers-doctor-doom-horn-of-greed-2000697495</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697495</guid>
      <description>He does what he pleases, after all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce bets on agentic AI platform following cautiously optimistic earnings report</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/salesforce-bets-on-agentic-ai-platform-following-cautiously-optimistic-earnings-report</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rLhnfm474Xn6iL7MBz56iW</guid>
      <description>Salesforce raises forecasts - Agentforce credited as driving force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50% Off Verizon Promo Codes | December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/verizon-promo-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">673baed7f6930ddfb4e8d266</guid>
      <description>Save with Verizon coupon codes for $1,100 off Galaxy S25 phones, free iPhone 17 Pros, and up to 50% off plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman tells Jimmy Fallon that AI is the "equalizing force" the world needs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/sam-altman-tells-jimmy-fallon-that-ai-is-the-equalizing-force-the-world-needs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bLrMaMfhD6Go7hrE6deTKM</guid>
      <description>Sam Altman went on the Tonight Show to tout ChatGPT&#8217;s unprecedented potential but also urged caution about AI adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly Discovered &#8216;Hybrid&#8217; Phase of Matter Blurs the Line Between Solid and Liquid</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/newly-discovered-hybrid-phase-of-matter-blurs-the-line-between-solid-and-liquid-2000697462</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697462</guid>
      <description>During this phase, matter exists in a weird, precarious limbo that ultimately determines what it becomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI&#8217;s terrifying new delivery drone is its most powerful so far &#8211; the FlyCart 100 can carry 100kg loads and climb 6,000m mountains</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/drones/djis-terrifying-new-delivery-drone-is-its-most-powerful-so-far-the-flycart-100-can-carry-100kg-loads-and-climb-6-000m-mountains</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XwK9NCRk858xsmvSeyDndU</guid>
      <description>DJI has launched the FlyCart 100 drone for delivering heavy packages in the most difficult environments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX reportedly planning 2026 IPO with $1.5T valuation target</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/spacex-reportedly-planning-2026-ipo-with-1-5t-valuation-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074435</guid>
      <description>The company is looking to raise $30 billion, which would make it the biggest IPO ever, just ahead of Saudi Aramco's in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B Capital founding partner Kabir Narang leaves to launch new investment platform</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/b-capital-founding-partner-kabir-narang-leaves-to-launch-new-investment-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074414</guid>
      <description>Kabir Narang is laying the groundwork for a new investment platform slated for 2026 that will focus on "compounding at the intersection of technology, AI, and global capital flows."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab HP Instant Ink 'loophole' worth almost &#163;126 but you have to be quick &#8212;  print up to 2,100 colour pages in 90 days for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/grab-hp-instant-ink-loophole-worth-almost-gbp126-but-you-have-to-be-quick-print-up-to-2-100-colour-pages-in-90-days-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HPvqzsVheywe2rW37c36R5</guid>
      <description>HP Instant Ink trick gives you months of free printing, but the window won&#8217;t stay open for long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superman and Spider-Man Collide in the First Looks at DC and Marvel&#8217;s Next Big Crossover</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dc-superman-spider-man-1-covers-2000697425</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697425</guid>
      <description>It's out March 25, 2026, and there are 11 covers in total by the likes of Jim Lee, Jorge Jim&#233;nez, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation just launched its 2025 Wrap-Up &#8212; but good luck getting it to load</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/playstation/playstation-just-launched-its-2025-wrap-up-but-good-luck-getting-it-to-load</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V6e8qRrDdDNck6QhAJr5tC</guid>
      <description>PlayStation just launched its 2025 Wrap-Up to show users their top games, total trophies, and hours spent on the platform, but, as with last year, the experience is slow to load for some users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some of our favorite gifts will cost you less than $25</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780844/best-gifts-under-25-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780844</guid>
      <description>Holiday shopping on a budget can feel constricting, especially if you've been invited to a white elephant or need a last-minute stocking stuffer. The good news is that, with this guide, you can leave that stress behind. Whether you're aiming for something practical or fun, we've found plenty of great gifts for under $25 - [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home insurance rates have gone up for 6 million people. How climate change and Trump are making the affordability crisis worse</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457201/home-insurance-rates-have-gone-up-for-6-million-people-how-climate-change-and-trump-are-making-the-affordability-crisis-worse</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457201/home-insurance-rates-have-gone-up-for-6-million-people-how-climate-change-and-trump-are-making-the-affordability-crisis-worse</guid>
      <description>Insurers have also canceled at least 1.4 million policies since 2021, says Climate Power&#8212;and now Trump tariffs could make prices rise 38% faster.
If your home insurance rate has spiked lately, you&#8217;re not alone. And President Trump&#8217;s policies could make it even more expensive.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings barely improved in October, hitting 7.7 million</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457343/job-openings-october-layoffs-rate-inflation</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457343/job-openings-october-layoffs-rate-inflation</guid>
      <description>Job openings have come down steadily since peaking at a record 12.1 million in March 2022.
U.S. job openings barely budged in October, coming in at 7.7 million with ongoing uncertainty over the&#160;direction of the American economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Cursor&#8217;s CEO believes OpenAI, Anthropic competition won&#8217;t crush his startup</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/why-cursors-ceo-believes-openai-anthropic-competition-wont-crush-his-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074040</guid>
      <description>After reaching $1 billion in annualized revenue, Anysphere CEO Michael Truell explained the features his company is focused on building out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google faces a new EU antitrust probe over content used for AI Overviews, YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457338/google-european-union-antitrust-ai-overviews-youtube-content</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T20:58:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457338/google-european-union-antitrust-ai-overviews-youtube-content</guid>
      <description>Regulators are concerned that Google has given itself an unfair advantage by using content for AI search services without paying publishers and content creators.
Google faces fresh&#160;antitrust scrutiny&#160;from European Union regulators, who opened an investigation Tuesday into the company&#8217;s use of online content for its&#160;artificial intelligence models&#160;and services....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Game Awards 2025 on December 11</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/how-to-watch-the-game-awards-2025-on-december-11-205500124.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">269098e7-2878-4a34-a0a5-a42fb9289d29</guid>
      <description>The Game Awards are this week, with the grand showcase for 2025 coming up on Thursday, December 11 at 8PM ET. There's also a pre-show (in case the multi-hour affair just isn't enough TGA for you) and that kicks off at 7:30PM ET. The ceremony will be a mix of honoring games from the past year and debuting trailers for future releases, so expect a couple interesting announcements to emerge from Thursday night. Engadget will be reporting on any big stories as they happen at The Game Awards, but if you want to watch along with us, the whole shebang is available to watch for free on just about ever...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traeger debuts Woodridge Pro Plus grill with Wi-Fi features and built-in storage cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/traeger-debuts-woodridge-pro-plus-grill-with-wi-fi-features-and-built-in-storage-cabinet-205320548.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d939bc73-8997-4834-8859-f898480b8bc1</guid>
      <description>Traeger debuted its Woodridge line of Wi-Fi-enabled pellet grills back in January. The overall theme across the Woodridge, Woodridge Pro and Woodridge Elite is the company&#8217;s reliable performance and features are available for less than the cost of its most premium models. Just before Christmas, the company is adding to the the Woodridge lineup with the Woodridge Pro Plus. 
For $400 more than the Woodridge Pro, this Plus model adds the enclosed storage cabinet from the Woodridge Elite. Instead of an open shelf, the cabinet offers a better option for keep pellet bins and other accessories close ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch One Battle After Another: Streaming details for the Oscar frontrunner</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/how-to-watch-one-battle-after-another</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06Vehgp1LI7aVdzcvzo6IH6</guid>
      <description>Is "One Battle After Another" streaming yet? Find out how to watch the Leonardo DiCaprio movie at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICEBlock app developers sue Trump administration</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ice-block-app-trump-administration-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07n4YjthafYEgHGxJyqoexR</guid>
      <description>App developers argue that the White House's pressure campaign to get Apple and Google to remove ICE trackers amounts to a first amendment violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student loans could resume for millions as Trump administration moves to end SAVE pause</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457356/student-loans-could-resume-for-millions-as-trump-administration-moves-to-end-save-pause</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457356/student-loans-could-resume-for-millions-as-trump-administration-moves-to-end-save-pause</guid>
      <description>A proposed settlement with Missouri would force borrowers in the blocked program to re-enter repayment after nearly a year of legal limbo.
Some bad news for Americans with student loans. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Mouth Wash? The Science Says Yes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/garlic-mouth-wash-the-science-says-yes-2000697393</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697393</guid>
      <description>Researchers reviewed existing evidence on whether mouthwash with garlic extract could be a viable alternative for the current golden standard.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
