<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:40:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Better than flowers - here are my favorite Lego sets from $12.99 that you can build together</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/better-than-flowers-here-are-my-favorite-lego-sets-from-usd12-99-that-you-can-build-together</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RoRfWFhJsgGjTKcUrnMZXU</guid>
      <description>Lego sets you can build together!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Didero lands $30M to put manufacturing procurement on &#8220;agentic&#8221; autopilot</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/didero-lands-30m-to-put-manufacturing-procurement-on-agentic-autopilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092627</guid>
      <description>The Series A was co-led by Chemistry and Headline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Two Years, the Apple Vision Pro Finally Has a YouTube App</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/after-two-years-the-apple-vision-pro-finally-has-a-youtube-app-2000721238</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721238</guid>
      <description>It's been a long road, but the Vision Pro finally has the one thing you'd expect it to have at launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniMax's new open M2.5 and M2.5 Lightning near state-of-the-art while costing 1/20th of Claude Opus 4.6</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/minimaxs-new-open-m2-5-and-m2-5-lightning-near-state-of-the-art-while</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jiokPSrcAZsIBBkZlDATK</guid>
      <description>Chinese AI startup MiniMax, headquartered in Shanghai, has sent shockwaves through the AI industry today with the release of its new M2.5 language model in two variants, which promises to make high-end artificial intelligence so cheap you might stop worrying about the bill entirely. It's also said to be "open source," though the weights (settings) and code haven't been posted yet, nor has the exact license type or terms. But that's almost beside the point given how cheap MiniMax is serving it through its API and those of partners.For the last few years, using the world&#8217;s most powerful AI was l...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest monitor company designed a 4K 48-inch OLED dual-sided smart gaming display with metal feet, a magnetic power socket, and an Alienware-inspired sound system - but who will actually use it?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/worlds-largest-monitor-company-designed-a-4k-48-inch-oled-dual-sided-smart-gaming-display-with-metal-feet-a-magnetic-power-socket-and-an-alienware-inspired-sound-system-but-who-will-actually-use-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CebZPZsEZ2Qqve96EsJYTY</guid>
      <description>GP TV introduces dual-sided 4K OLED display combining gaming design, immersive audio, safety features, and uncertain real-world practicality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic raises another $30B in Series G, with a new value of $380B</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/anthropic-raises-another-30-billion-in-series-g-with-a-new-value-of-380-billion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092578</guid>
      <description>The infusion of funding for the AI startup takes place as it is vying for customers and cultural attention with its competitor, OpenAI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube finally launches a dedicated app for Apple Vision Pro</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/youtube-finally-launches-a-dedicated-app-for-apple-vision-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092625</guid>
      <description>When Apple Vision Pro first came out two years ago, YouTube hesitated to release a dedicated app. Today is the day they officially launch one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best wireless earbuds for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/best-wireless-earbuds-120058222.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52299dcd-39b7-3f30-8524-2c7d79d13daa</guid>
      <description>Wireless earbuds are now the default option for everyday listening, whether you&#8217;re heading out for a commute, fitting in a workout or just watching videos at home. The best wireless earbuds combine reliable connectivity, comfortable fits and sound quality that holds up across music, calls and podcasts, all without the hassle of cables. Most are small enough to disappear into a pocket and pair quickly with phones, tablets and laptops.What sets one pair apart from another often comes down to priorities. Some earbuds lean heavily on active noise cancellation, while others focus on long battery li...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Decides Everyone Needs a Harsh Lesson</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-episode-6-recap-2000721081</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721081</guid>
      <description>'Come, Let's Away' brings 'Starfleet Academy' back to a more classically 'Star Trek' place, leveraging its young heroes in a compelling way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo Asks the DC Public to Pressure Their City Officials</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/waymo-asks-the-dc-public-to-pressure-their-city-officials/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698e1bc7b5b458763ed07ddb</guid>
      <description>Stuck in regulatory limbo, the self-driving-vehicle developer is encouraging residents of Washington, DC, to message public officials to help get its robotaxis onto roads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eureka Ergonomic Axion office chair review: an attractive mid-range throne with great ergonomic features</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/eureka-ergonomic-axion-office-chair-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">snEufawQjGn8DuWiAx7LAX</guid>
      <description>The Axion office chair from Eureka is is a great do-it-all option, suitable for executives and gamers alike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Things: The First Shadow might finally stream on Netflix this year &#8212; here&#8217;s why it&#8217;s required watching for the next chapter in the series</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/stranger-things-the-first-shadow-might-finally-stream-on-netflix-this-year-heres-why-its-required-watching-for-the-next-chapter-in-the-series</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7dCkntd9gowKLNbt3duPV</guid>
      <description>Stranger Things: The First Shadow is superb, and it might be coming Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette com&#232;te va bient&#244;t fr&#244;ler le Soleil et pourrait devenir visible en plein jour</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cette-comete-va-bientot-froler-soleil-pourrait-devenir-visible-plein-jour-131165/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:57:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cette-comete-va-bientot-froler-soleil-pourrait-devenir-visible-plein-jour-131165/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>La com&#232;te C/2026 A1 devrait passer pr&#232;s du Soleil d&#233;but avril et pourrait &#234;tre d&#233;truite &#224; cette occasion. Ce&#160;qui sera surtout l'opportunit&#233; de mener de nombreuses observations astronomiques sur un ph&#233;nom&#232;ne rarement vu par les t&#233;lescopes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Wave of Unexplained Bot Traffic Is Sweeping the Web</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-niche-websites-are-seeing-a-surge-of-mysterious-traffic-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698a90a4fbb792360a1da892</guid>
      <description>From small publishers to US federal agencies, websites are reporting unusual spikes in automated traffic linked to IP addresses in Lanzhou, China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These digital tools are stepping up the global fight against wildlife trafficking</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488633/these-digital-tools-are-stepping-up-the-global-fight-against-wildlife-trafficking</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T19:47:15</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488633/these-digital-tools-are-stepping-up-the-global-fight-against-wildlife-trafficking</guid>
      <description>No single technology will end wildlife trafficking, but these digital tools can enable a shift.
In late 2025, Interpol coordinated a global operation across 134 nations, seizing roughly 30,000 live animals, confiscating illegal plant and timber products, and identifying about 1,100 suspected wildlife traffickers for national police to investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27 beautiful beige-inspired home office finds for creating your calming, neutral workspace</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/27-beautiful-beige-inspired-home-office-finds-for-creating-your-calming-neutral-workspace</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">v35zbCwFRTTTXvPZx9RNK6</guid>
      <description>From champagne beige to stone oat, this is the office furniture, desk accessories, and essential gadgets and decor to create the right vibe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Est&#233;e Lauder tested products sold on Walmart&#8217;s site. What it found led to a lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491776/estee-lauder-tested-products-sold-on-walmarts-site-what-it-found-led-to-a-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491776/estee-lauder-tested-products-sold-on-walmarts-site-what-it-found-led-to-a-lawsuit</guid>
      <description>The beauty giant alleges Walmart sold counterfeit skincare and fragrances online, including products from La Mer and Tom Ford.
Est&#233;e Lauder has accused Walmart of selling counterfeit beauty goods on its website in a lawsuit filed in California federal court earlier this week that namechecks celebrities including Taylor Swift and Beyonc&#233;.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Hull City vs. Chelsea online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/hull-city-chelsea-fa-cup-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06rTB83V3cOJnvm8EmMPCQH</guid>
      <description>How to watch FA Cup for free. Live stream Hull City vs. Chelsea in the FA Cup for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU reportedly opens another probe into Google's ads pricing</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/eu-reportedly-opens-another-probe-into-googles-ads-pricing-194435095.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6edcaf1-ef18-4049-936c-6b1ee50f980c</guid>
      <description>The European Commission has opened a new probe into Google, this time focused on the company's massive online advertising business, Bloomberg reports. European Union regulators have already fined Google billions for violating the Digital Markets Act, and being found guilty of anticompetitive behavior in online advertising could add to that total.While the Commission has yet to announce a formal investigation, Bloomberg writes that it has started contacting Google's customers and competitors for information about its dominance across multiple online advertising markets. Regulators are particula...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romance scam red flags to look out for</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/romance-scammer-red-flags-to-look-out-for</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Q2Dn1xWjs1PkKAqs4WxbX</guid>
      <description>Romance cons are on the rise online, especially due to AI. Here are tips to avoid them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In one swoop, Trump kills US greenhouse gas regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/877371/trump-carbon-pollution-endangerment-finding-repeal-climate-change</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T14:35:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877371</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration just eliminated the landmark finding that has underpinned federal regulations on planet-heating pollution since 2009. For nearly the past two decades, the "endangerment finding" has allowed the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) to craft rules limiting greenhouse gas emissions under the Clean Air Act. Rather than repealing those rules individually, the Trump administration [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Own a Chrysler, Dodge, Jeep, or Ram? You may be under a stop-drive warning</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491783/own-a-chrysler-dodge-jeep-or-ram-you-may-be-under-a-stop-drive-warning</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491783/own-a-chrysler-dodge-jeep-or-ram-you-may-be-under-a-stop-drive-warning</guid>
      <description>Stellantis has issued a stop-drive warning for 225,000 vehicles due to a dangerous Takata airbag defect.
Stellantis, the maker of Chrysler, Dodge, Jeep, Ram, issued a &#8220;do not drive&#8221; warning for certain late-model vehicles, telling drivers not to use their vehicles until defective air bags are replaced, according to a&#160;notice from the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust head overseeing Netflix-Warner merger resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/antitrust-head-overseeing-netflix-warner-merger-resigns-192854114.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c20ecb12-d903-4d88-ba27-b46a36122e38</guid>
      <description>The head of the antitrust division is out at the US Department of Justice. Gail Slater, a former JD Vance adviser and Fox Corp VP, reportedly clashed with Attorney General Pam Bondi. Their longstanding feud is said to have centered around Slater's skepticism of corporate mergers."It is with great sadness and abiding hope that I leave my role as [Assistant Attorney General] for Antitrust today," Slater posted on X. "It was indeed the honor of a lifetime to serve in this role."Although Slater technically resigned, The Guardian reports that she was forced out. The fallout was said to be over her ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker linked to Epstein removed from Black Hat cyber conference website</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/hacker-linked-to-epstein-removed-from-black-hat-cyber-conference-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092535</guid>
      <description>Emails published by the Justice Department revealed cybersecurity veteran Vincenzo Iozzo emailed, and arranged to meet, Jeffrey Epstein multiple times between 2014 and 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration undermines EPA enforcement of Clean Air Act</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/trump-administration-undermines-epa-enforcement-of-clean-air-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092396</guid>
      <description>The EPA's new rule seeks to undo a 2009 finding that allowed the federal government to regulate six greenhouse gases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In defense of wasting time</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488035/in-defense-of-wasting-time</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T19:12:29</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488035/in-defense-of-wasting-time</guid>
      <description>Why the least efficient forms of thinking may be the most valuable in the age of AI
For most of modern management history, wasting time has been treated as a vice. This sensibility can be traced back to Frederick Taylor&#8217;s doctrine of scientific management, which recast work as an engineering problem and workers as components in a machine to be optimized, standardized, and controlled. In reducing human effort to measurable outputs and time-motion efficiencies, Taylorism marked the beginning of the end for seeing people as thinking agents, turning them instead into productivity units not unlike ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two powerful, OLED-equipped gaming laptops are hundreds off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/878209/asus-acer-oled-rtx-5070ti-gaming-laptop-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T14:10:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878209</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re considering a 16-inch gaming laptop, or a more compact 14-inch model, there&#8217;s a deal with your name on it happening right now at Best Buy. The 2025 models of Acer&#8217;s Predator Helios Neo 16S and the Asus ROG Zephyrus G14 are hundreds off, although it&#8217;s the model with the bigger screen that is [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Your data is public': Hacker warns victims after leaking 6.8 billion emails online</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/your-data-is-public-hacker-warns-victims-after-leaking-6-8-billion-emails-online</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3MSNhatMQZkxCpwEzd7V4k</guid>
      <description>Someone posted 150GB of emails to the dark web, claiming to hold 6.8 billion unique email addresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automattic planned to target 10 competitors with royalty fees, WP Engine claims in new filing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/automattic-planned-to-target-10-competitors-with-royalty-fees-wp-engine-claims-in-new-filing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092407</guid>
      <description>WP Engine claims Automattic was going to target more hosting companies with royalty fees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A STI Fungus Is Making Itself Cozy in the US</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-sti-fungus-is-making-itself-cozy-in-the-us-2000721188</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721188</guid>
      <description>More than 30 cases of TMVII have been documented in the Twin Cities metro area since last July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutated Rats Reign in This Ooey-Gooey Clip From &#8216;Cold Storage&#8217; (Exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mutated-rats-reign-in-this-ooey-gooey-clip-from-cold-storage-exclusive-2000713561</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713561</guid>
      <description>Joe Keery ('Stranger Things') and Georgina Campbell ('Barbarian') confront an extreme workplace hazard in the sci-fi horror comedy, arriving February 13.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s President Gave Millions to Trump. He Says It&#8217;s for Humanity</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-president-greg-brockman-political-donations-trump-humanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698a304eec9b9988e9a011d1</guid>
      <description>In an interview with WIRED, Greg Brockman says his political donations support OpenAI's mission&#8212;even if some employees at the company disagree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite the first game's Xbox exclusivity deal, PlayStation is  'still our lead platform' says Squanch Games CEO as High on Life 2 launches this week</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/despite-the-first-games-xbox-exclusivity-deal-playstation-is-still-our-lead-platform-says-squanch-games-ceo-as-high-on-life-2-launches-this-week</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PDNMVCqueZNZjDTqirGcmF</guid>
      <description>Squanch Games CEO Mike Fridley has said releasing High on Life 2 simultaneously on Xbox and PlayStation was a "no-brainer" following the first game's long Xbox exclusivity window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Just Blew American Climate Policy to Smithereens</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-just-blew-american-climate-policy-to-smithereens-2000721247</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721247</guid>
      <description>President Trump and EPA Administrator Lee Zeldin announced the repeal of the endangerment finding, the legal bedrock for the agency's actions against planet-warming pollution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eufy&#8217;s midrange X10 Pro Omni robovac has fallen to its best-ever price</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/877673/eufy-x10-pro-omni-nothing-phone-3-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T13:59:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877673</guid>
      <description>Spring doesn&#8217;t officially kick off until March 20th, but there&#8217;s something to be said about getting a head start on your spring cleaning. Lucky for you, Eufy&#8217;s X10 Pro Omni is currently on sale at Amazon, Walmart, and directly from Eufy (with promo code WS7DV2D5LF9F) for $449.99 ($450 off), matching its lowest price to date. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takeaways from Elon Musks xAI all-hands meeting</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/elon-musk-xai-45-minute-all-hands-meeting-takeaways</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01yMgpL2Yzk0fqKgn91Z6W7</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk had some bizarre things to say at a recent xAI meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Accuses Two Polymarket Bettors of Trading on Classified Military Operations</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/israel-accuses-two-polymarket-bettors-of-trading-on-classified-military-operations-2000721224</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721224</guid>
      <description>Perhaps we could stop and ask why you can bet on military operations in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirPods Pro&#160;3, batterie MagSafe Anker&#160;621 et forfait Coriolis 5G&#160;: les&#160;3&#160;meilleurs bons plans tech de ce jeudi&#160;12&#160;f&#233;vrier&#160;2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2975777_airpods-pro-3-batterie-magsafe-anker-621-et-forfait-coriolis-5g-les-3-meilleurs-bons-plans-tech-de-ce-jeudi-12-fevrier-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2975777_airpods-pro-3-batterie-magsafe-anker-621-et-forfait-coriolis-5g-les-3-meilleurs-bons-plans-tech-de-ce-jeudi-12-fevrier-2026</guid>
      <description>
En ce jeudi frisquet de f&#233;vrier, les bons plans tech sont de sortie, avec plusieurs promotions qui m&#233;ritent le d&#233;tour.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why tech helps Minneapolis more than it helps ICE</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tech-ice-minnesota</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02gXO4vSTmEuAQef2tJ5Ivt</guid>
      <description>In challenging ICE, Minneapolis has mastered signal voice chats, free 3-D printed whistles, and electronic billboards.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
