<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 02:00:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Silksong is getting a free expansion next year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845189/hollow-knight-silksong-sea-of-sorrow-dlc-expansion-switch-2</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T20:13:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845189</guid>
      <description>It's still hard to believe that Hollow Knight: Silksong actually came out this year, but now, we all have a new thing to wait for: the game is getting a free expansion in 2026, titled Sea of Sorrow. Team Cherry calls it the game's "first big expansion." "New areas, bosses, tools, and more!" Team Cherry [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obscure Polish company quietly launches massive 122.88TB PCIe 5.0 immersion cooled SSD &#8212; and no one noticed this world's first except us</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/obscure-polish-company-quietly-launches-massive-122-88tb-pcie-5-0-immersion-cooled-ssd-and-no-one-noticed-this-worlds-first-except-us</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NY6fMjq5fxVYuskWoq27sN</guid>
      <description>A 122.88TB PCIe 5.0 SSD has quietly appeared from a Polish storage vendor, focusing on immersion cooling compatibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG will debut its first Micro RGB television at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/lg-will-debut-its-first-micro-rgb-television-at-ces-010037923.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b73e658-27d0-45a1-b244-32c53e901144</guid>
      <description>LG is getting in on one of the newest trends for televisions with the introduction of Micro RGB. The company will unveil the LG Micro RGB evo at CES 2026, but it shared some preliminary information about the screen today.
Micro RGB is a newer screen technology where rather than white lights, the backlight can be any hue thanks to individually controlled red, green and blue Micro LEDs, offering a wider color array. This approach is a mid-way point between the precision of OLED with its individual pixel lighting, but it offers an upgrade over screens only using mini LEDs.
The television is also ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG enters the RGB LED fray in 2026 with the Micro RGB evo TV</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844885/lg-micro-rgb-evo-led-tv-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844885</guid>
      <description>In what is sure to be the beginning of a slew of announcements, LG has confirmed it is releasing its first flagship RGB TV in 2026. It wasn't a huge secret, considering "a premium LCD TV with Micro RGB technology" won a CES 2026 Innovation Award in November. But it's now certain that the LG [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG reveals Micro RGB evo TV with bold claims of perfect color</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lg-reveals-micro-rgb-evo-tv-with-bold-claims-of-perfect-color</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">up2JpHokWwBtUpdbX4Mf6Y</guid>
      <description>LG is bringing RGB TV tech to CES 2026 with its first Micro RGB evo set, promising an ultra-wide color gamut in three sizes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet traffic grew 19% in 2025, Google remains king</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/cloudflare-year-2025-year-in-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00NovdYuJkkdUWjbTF9cPDH</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare has released a report looking back at online statistics in 2025, and found that overall internet usage grew 19%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCs discuss why most consumer AI startups still lack staying power</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/vcs-discuss-why-most-consumer-ai-startups-still-lack-staying-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076284</guid>
      <description>The next consumer tech revolution may require an introduction of a new personal device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Louisiana's social media age verification law</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/judge-blocks-louisianas-social-media-age-verification-law-001212758.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b68550f4-b1cd-4ee6-8aae-9c1ea91070db</guid>
      <description>A Louisiana law that would have required social media platforms to verify the ages of their users has been blocked by a judge. The law, known as the Secure Online Child Interaction and Age Limitation, was passed in 2023 and required Meta, Reddit, Snap, YouTube Discord and others to implement age verification and parental control features.The ruling came just days before the law, which technically took effect over the summer, would have started to be enforced. In his ruling, Judge John W. deGravelles wrote that the law's "age-verification and parental-consent requirements are both over- and und...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s Chief Communications Officer Is Leaving the Company</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-chief-communications-officer-hannah-wong-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69409a16200fc11cb84c6a78</guid>
      <description>Hannah Wong told staff she is moving on to her &#8220;next chapter.&#8221; The company will be running an executive search to find a replacement, according to a memo.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
