<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:20:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Code is coming to Slack, and that&#8217;s a bigger deal than it sounds</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/claude-code-is-coming-to-slack-and-thats-a-bigger-deal-than-it-sounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073830</guid>
      <description>Anthropic launches Claude Code in Slack, letting developers delegate coding tasks from chat threads. It's part of a shift toward AI-embedded collaboration that could reshape software workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Series 11 just got a big $100 discount ahead of the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/840161/apple-watch-series-11-holiday-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T14:17:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840161</guid>
      <description>We thought Black Friday and Cyber Monday would bring the lowest prices of the year, but apparently not. Right now, you can snag Apple&#8217;s Watch Series 11 in the 42mm configuration with GPS for a new all-time low of $299 ($100 off) at Amazon, Walmart, and Best Buy. That beats the $70 discount we saw [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount just trumped Netflix's Warner Bros deal, but I don't see how this will be good news for any of us</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-just-trumped-netflixs-warner-bros-deal-but-i-dont-see-how-this-will-be-good-news-for-any-of-us</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">u8H5xEJjeZurbGvCAedvW3</guid>
      <description>Just when you thought the Netflix plan to acquire Warner Bros. was all but a done deal, Paramount swoops in, and things just got very interesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National cybercrime network operating for 14 years dismantled in Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/national-cybercrime-network-operating-for-14-years-dismantled-in-indonesia</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ysdxEmfSKFXFNYYvaegmMG</guid>
      <description>A large network of domains, malware, and stolen credentials, has been making rounds for 14 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ron DeSantis Proposes AI Bill of Rights as Trump Says He&#8217;ll Kill State AI Laws</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ron-desantis-proposes-ai-bill-of-rights-as-trump-says-hell-kill-state-ai-laws-2000696828</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696828</guid>
      <description>A MAGA rift?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic is bringing Claude Code to Slack</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839817/anthropic-claude-code-slack-integration</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T14:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839817</guid>
      <description>Slack users can now access Anthropic's Claude Code directly in Slack by tagging Claude on coding-related messages and threads. The new feature is launching today in beta as a research preview. When Claude is tagged, it will now automatically scan the message to see if it's a coding task and, if so, route it to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICEBlock Sues White House Over Pressuring Apple for App Store Removal</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iceblock-sues-white-house-over-pressuring-apple-for-app-store-removal-2000696820</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696820</guid>
      <description>ICEBlock developer Joshua Aaron claims that the removal is a suppression of free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's Claude Code can now read your Slack messages and write code for you</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropics-claude-code-can-now-read-your-slack-messages-and-write-code-for</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5qKOrKzspLDUzNNe31dlsC</guid>
      <description>Anthropic on Monday launched a beta integration that connects its fast-growing Claude Code programming agent directly to Slack, allowing software engineers to delegate coding tasks without leaving the workplace messaging platform where much of their daily communication already happens.The release, which Anthropic describes as a "research preview," is the AI safety company's latest move to embed its technology deeper into enterprise workflows &#8212; and comes as Claude Code has emerged as a surprise revenue engine, generating over $1 billion in annualized revenue just six months after its public deb...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For the First Time, Mutations in a Single Gene Have Been Linked to Mental Illness</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/mutations-in-a-single-gene-have-been-linked-to-mental-illness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6936f402d3110ee85b1e13e9</guid>
      <description>Research links variations in the gene GRIN2A to a higher risk of developing schizophrenia and other forms of mental illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All you need to know about the increasingly complex sale of Warner Bros. Discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456603/warner-brothers-discovery-netflix-paramount-david-ellison-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:50:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456603/warner-brothers-discovery-netflix-paramount-david-ellison-trump</guid>
      <description>A rundown of the deal, how it will be funded, and whether it stands a chance of clearing regulatory review.
The long battle over control of Warner Bros. Discovery took another turn Monday when Paramount Skydance announced a hostile bid for the entertainment giant, following Warner&#8217;s acceptance of a competing offer from Netflix last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta will let Facebook and Instagram users in the EU share less data</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-will-let-facebook-and-instagram-users-in-the-eu-share-less-data-183535897.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28146827-8691-41f3-b999-1d94cad68df3</guid>
      <description>Meta will soon allow Facebook and Instagram users in the European Union to choose to share less data and see less personalized ads on the platform, the European Commission announced. The change will begin to roll out in January, according to the regulator.&#160;"This is the first time that such a choice is offered on Meta's social networks," the commission said in a statement. "Meta will give users the effective choice between: consenting to share all their data and seeing fully personalised advertising, and opting to share less personal data for an experience with more limited personalised adverti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon retire 40 % de son prix &#224; ce chargeur 2-en-1 compatible MagSafe et Qi2</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2902491_amazon-retire-40-de-son-prix-a-ce-chargeur-2-en-1-compatible-magsafe-et-qi2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2902491_amazon-retire-40-de-son-prix-a-ce-chargeur-2-en-1-compatible-magsafe-et-qi2</guid>
      <description>
Ugreen propose de nombreux accessoires pour t&#233;l&#233;phone, et quelques produits qui sortent du lot comme ce chargeur &#224; induction 2-en-1 certifi&#233; Qi2 et MagSafe dont le prix passe de 39 euros &#224; 23 euros seulement sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s next gaming laptop may have a rollable OLED screen that stretches ultrawide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840124/lenovo-rollable-legion-pro-gaming-laptop-rumor</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T13:33:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840124</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has already demonstrated its ability to put rollable OLEDs into laptops by graduating last year from demo concept models to shipping the ThinkBook Plus Gen 6, an actual device you can buy. It has a built-in mechanism that expands the screen vertically to give you more screen real estate for typing and scrolling. However, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s Optimus Robot Collapses in a Hilariously Suspicious Way</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musks-optimus-robot-collapses-in-a-hilariously-suspicious-way-2000696760</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696760</guid>
      <description>Musk says he's going to make 1 million robots per year by 2030.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s ugly, it&#8217;s beautiful, it&#8217;s how you know a game might be a classic</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/840080/square-enix-hd2d-games-octopath-dragon-quest</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840080</guid>
      <description>At their biggest and most expensive, video games all sort of look the same. The reason often comes down to simple economics: More resources means more costs that need to be recouped, and historically the way publishers have done that is by being comically risk-averse. Hence the glut of semi-realistic rocky wastelands that look like [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service drops free admission for MLK Day, Juneteenth, and adds Trump&#8217;s birthday</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456576/national-parks-free-admission-mlk-day-juneteenth-trump-birthday</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456576/national-parks-free-admission-mlk-day-juneteenth-trump-birthday</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration&#8217;s national parks cut free admission on two of the nation&#8217;s most prominent civil rights holidays.
The&#160;National Park Service&#160;will offer free admission to U.S. residents on President Donald Trump&#8216;s birthday next year &#8212; which also happens to be Flag Day &#8212; but is eliminating the benefit for Martin Luther King Jr. Day and Juneteenth....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICEBlock developer sues Trump administration over App Store removal</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840164/iceblock-joshua-aaron-sues-trump-administration-apple-app-store-removeal</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T13:25:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840164</guid>
      <description>Joshua Aaron, the developer of the ICEBlock app, is suing Attorney General Pam Bondi, US Homeland Security Secretary Kirsti Noem, acting director of ICE Todd Lyons, White House "Border Czar" Tom Homan, and other federal officials over the Trump administration's "unlawful threats" made against Aaron and its actions to pressure Apple to pull the app [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's UI executive poached by Meta, and three other executives leave in Apple AI exodus</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/apples-ui-executive-poached-by-meta-and-three-other-executives-leave-in-apple-ai-exodus</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d2CdKCEv5iJqb8g7Mfxam</guid>
      <description>The number of Apple execs leaving the company continues to rise, but most are being replaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFLT stock price: IBM deal to buy Confluent for $11 billion shows investors still think AI is popping</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456429/confluent-cflt-stock-price-ibm-11-billion-deal-shows-investors-still-think-ai-is-popping</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456429/confluent-cflt-stock-price-ibm-11-billion-deal-shows-investors-still-think-ai-is-popping</guid>
      <description>News of the acquisition sent the data streaming platform&#8217;s shares up nearly 30% in trading on Monday.
IBM&#160;announced on Monday it is acquiring&#160;Confluent&#160;for $11 billion, sending shares of the data streaming platform up about 29% in morning trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analogue is weaponizing your nostalgia with these translucent versions of its 3D console</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/analogue-is-weaponizing-your-nostalgia-with-these-translucent-versions-of-its-3d-console-181105740.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea9423b4-bc7b-4736-aada-f5972185fef5</guid>
      <description>Analogue just announced new colorways for its recently-launched Analogue 3D console. The appropriately-named Funtastic limited-edition consoles are heavily inspired by Nintendo's translucent N64 models from the late 1990s. Analogue even borrowed the Funtastic branding.
In other words, these are going for the nostalgic jugular for gamers of a certain age. There's even a see-through green colorway that calls to mind the Nintendo 64 variant that shipped as a bundle with Donkey Kong 64. Just imagine booting up that bad boy as you roam around the house spouting the lyrics of the DK rap song.
Analog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les 3 voitures &#233;lectriques favorites de Survolt&#233;s en d&#233;cembre 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2901877_les-3-voitures-electriques-favorites-de-survoltes-en-decembre-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2901877_les-3-voitures-electriques-favorites-de-survoltes-en-decembre-2025</guid>
      <description>
Les voitures &#233;lectriques demeurent une v&#233;ritable attraction pour le grand public. Voici le top 3 des mod&#232;les que nous avons ador&#233; tester sur Frandroid le mois dernier. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Clears Out This Eureka Vacuum at a Price Several Times Cheaper Than Dyson for Early Christmas</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-clears-out-this-eureka-vacuum-at-a-price-several-times-cheaper-than-dyson-to-wrap-up-cyber-week-2000696026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696026</guid>
      <description>It's time to tidy up now that the holidays are here, so make sure you don't miss out on this deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Way to Play Your N64 Games Now Looks Even Better</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/analogue-3d-nintendo-64-limited-edition-translucent-colors-release-date-2000696835</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696835</guid>
      <description>The Analogue 3D now comes in all the transparent colorways you never got as a kid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Nordic people do to cope with the winter blues</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456537/nordic-norway-sweden-finland-winter-blues</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:00:58</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456537/nordic-norway-sweden-finland-winter-blues</guid>
      <description>From a sunrise alarm clock to morning light therapy, here are some strategies.
The Nordic countries are no strangers to the long, dark winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fictional Characters and Shows We Lost in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-fictional-characters-and-shows-we-lost-in-2025-2000691833</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000691833</guid>
      <description>To all the sci-fi, fantasy, and horror characters, TV series, and other creations that took their final bows this year: we'll miss (most of) you!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A first look at Google&#8217;s Project Aura glasses built with Xreal</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/839392/project-aura-android-xr-software-headsets-ai-glasses</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839392</guid>
      <description>Teased at Google I/O, Project Aura is a collaboration between Xreal and Google. It's the second Android XR device (the first being Samsung's Galaxy XR headset) and is expected to launch in 2026. Putting it on, I get why the term "smart glasses" doesn't exactly fit. Is it a headset? Smart glasses? Both? Those were [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google details security measures for Chrome&#8217;s agentic features</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/google-details-security-measures-for-chromes-agentic-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073679</guid>
      <description>Google details how it is enacting security guardrails before rolling out agentic capabilities on Chrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried the next-gen Android XR prototype smart glasses, and these frames are ready for your close-up</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/i-tried-the-next-gen-android-xr-prototype-smart-glasses-and-these-frames-are-ready-for-your-close-up</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eYUQtduwmg6Eu4pCnwkuwL</guid>
      <description>This is what we want</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win a &#163;1,000 Amazon voucher and free Ring doorbells for your whole street by sharing a Christmas carol</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/win-a-gbp1-000-amazon-voucher-and-free-ring-doorbells-for-your-whole-street-by-sharing-a-christmas-carol</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3nqUBtrgdWaZDc82mwbWMH</guid>
      <description>The competition was inspired by five boys from Denny, Scotland, who were recorded on a Ring doorbell singing for their neighbours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech's biggest winners of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/techs-biggest-winners-of-2025-180000177.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1542a41d-6888-45f4-a033-0aa571d76d1f</guid>
      <description>Every December, the Engadget staff compiles a list of the year&#8217;s biggest winners. We scour over articles from the previous 12 months to determine the people, companies, products and trends that made the most impact over the course of the year. Not all of that influence is positive, however, and some selections may also appear on our list of biggest losers. Still, sit back and enjoy our picks for the biggest winners of 2025.Nintendo Switch 2Playing Mario Kart World on the Switch 2 in handheld mode.Sam Rutherford for EngadgetAside from a big bump in battery life that many were hoping for, Ninten...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's how Google is laying the foundation for our mixed reality future</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/heres-how-google-is-laying-the-foundation-for-our-mixed-reality-future-180000716.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">721b1f85-0f59-46bb-9f5b-7e2bab08822d</guid>
      <description>Today, during the XR edition of The Android Show, Google showed off a bunch of updates and new features headed to its mixed reality OS. And while most of the news was aimed at developers, I got a chance to demo some of the platform's expanded capabilities on a range of hardware including Samsung's Galaxy XR headset, two different reference designs and an early version of Xreal's Project Aura smart glasses and I came away rather impressed. So here's a rundown of what I saw and how it will impact the rapidly growing ecosystem of head-mounted displays.First up was one of Google's reference design...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letterboxd is now doing video rentals&#8212;and it goes hard on indie films. Here&#8217;s what to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456369/letterboxd-video-store-rentals-goes-hard-on-indie-films-heres-what-to-expect</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456369/letterboxd-video-store-rentals-goes-hard-on-indie-films-heres-what-to-expect</guid>
      <description>The movie app&#8217;s new Video Store launches on Wednesday, and its first offerings include festival favorites and deep cuts.
Letterboxd, the movie tracking app and social media platform for cinephiles, first announced its new online film rental platform earlier this year at Cannes Film Festival. Now, more details about the launch date and titles have been revealed....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louvre December strike adds to post-heist woes: How the museum&#8217;s bad year stacks up</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456371/louvre-december-strike-adds-to-post-heist-woes-how-the-museums-bad-year-stacks-up</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456371/louvre-december-strike-adds-to-post-heist-woes-how-the-museums-bad-year-stacks-up</guid>
      <description>A water leak and crumbling infrastructure are just a few of the museum&#8217;s other recent concerns.
On November 26, a water leak at Paris&#8217; Louvre Museum damaged between 300 and 400 historical books in the Egyptology and scientific documentation section. Then, on December 8, workers at the museum voted to initiate a strike over poor working conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinnabon worker fired after racist outburst at customers goes viral</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456502/cinnabon-worker-fired-racist-outburst-customers-viral-tiktok</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456502/cinnabon-worker-fired-racist-outburst-customers-viral-tiktok</guid>
      <description>The employee is recorded giving an obscene hand gesture at customers and exchanging expletives.
A Cinnabon worker in Wisconsin has been fired after a racist outburst directed at two customers went viral, the Georgia-based cinnamon roll chain said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can buy your Instacart groceries without leaving ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/you-can-buy-your-instacart-groceries-without-leaving-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073753</guid>
      <description>Shoppers will be able to go from recipe planning to checkout within the ChatGPT window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble tease une nouvelle montre ronde : le retour inattendu de la Time Round se pr&#233;cise pour le 9 d&#233;cembre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2902675_pebble-tease-une-nouvelle-montre-ronde-le-retour-inattendu-de-la-time-round-se-precise-pour-le-9-decembre</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2902675_pebble-tease-une-nouvelle-montre-ronde-le-retour-inattendu-de-la-time-round-se-precise-pour-le-9-decembre</guid>
      <description>
Pebble a publi&#233; une image myst&#233;rieuse annon&#231;ant une nouveaut&#233; imminente. Tout porte &#224; croire qu'une version modernis&#233;e de la Pebble Time Round est dans les tuyaux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HBO Max will stay' even after Netflix deal says Warner Bros. CEO David Zaslav</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/hbo-max-will-stay-even-after-netflix-deal-says-warner-bros-ceo-david-zaslav</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BG4yBNZHVV5pN6XstWXGp7</guid>
      <description>Move over Mark Twain, this time its HBO Max whose death may have been greatly exaggerated &#8211; according to Warner Bros. Discovery chief David Zaslav.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Discovers Hundreds of New Deep Sea Creatures While Figuring Out How to Mine Their Home</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/company-discovers-hundreds-of-new-deep-sea-creatures-while-figuring-out-how-to-mine-their-home-2000696746</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696746</guid>
      <description>The discovery could hold serious implications for the mining industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Windows 11 apps have a massive RAM problem &#8211; and this app is the worst offender</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/some-windows-11-apps-have-a-massive-ram-problem-and-this-app-is-the-worst-offender</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nQG7zGeoU33KVnVahszUwN</guid>
      <description>Amid a RAM crisis, Discord and a few other applications using Chromium and the Electron framework are causing RAM spikes for PC users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"We're going to be watching really closely" &#8211; politicians around the world are taking inspiration from Australia's social media ban</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/were-going-to-be-watching-really-closely-politicians-around-the-world-are-taking-inspiration-from-australias-social-media-ban</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">s4iLhHjQcAeCSz7N6trAVF</guid>
      <description>As Australia implements its strict age verification regime, worldwide politicians are taking notes. So, which country will be next to kick off teens from social media apps?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sneeit WordPress RCE flaw allows hackers to add themselves as admin - here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/sneeit-wordpress-rce-flaw-allows-hackers-to-add-themselves-as-admin-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EJFE9NfzrmkDqifScjHVfY</guid>
      <description>A critical flaw in a WordPress add-on was recently patched, which allows crooks to add a rogue admin account to the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ comes with even more perks this season: Get 6 free months of DashPass and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-8-disney-plus-perks</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04mj0mjH9Q3EqE09Emo9lfg</guid>
      <description>Disney+ is giving subscribers exclusive perks this season, like six free months of DashPass, discounted Broadway tickets, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Apple product launches to expect in the near future</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/apple-product-launches-to-expect-early-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03LTQuZ6FhNjDDNovhw5Dvx</guid>
      <description>Apple could have some new MacBooks, iPads, and even a new iPhone in the next few months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift your content-creator friend the DJI Mic Mini while its on sale for just $45</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-8-dji-mic-mini-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00xAb7QsbRwh9HnaNp75fCl</guid>
      <description>The DJI Mic Mini is on sale at Target for $45, down from the normal price of $89. That's a 49% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy launches a huge Apple sale &#8212; and it includes AirPods, MacBooks, iPads, and more for record-low prices</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/macbooks/best-buy-launches-a-huge-apple-sale-and-it-includes-airpods-macbooks-ipads-and-more-for-record-low-prices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jZ4B5RFb8SZQ25u85qMJGQ</guid>
      <description>There's a limited-time Apple sale underway at Best Buy, so I've hand-picked the 14 best deals on iPads, MacBooks, Apple Watches, AirPods and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP OmniBook 5 14 review: an OLED is almost enough</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/839858/hp-omnibook-5-14-snapdragon-arm-oled-laptop-review</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839858</guid>
      <description>You know what I love more than OLEDs? Cheap OLEDs. And that's exactly what drew me to the 14-inch HP OmniBook 5. It's a $700 Windows laptop with a Snapdragon X Plus processor and an OLED screen. That means it should have great battery life and a beautiful screen. I consider these important in any [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Trop violent&#160;&#187; : ce patron chinois finit au tapis pour prouver que son robot est r&#233;el</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/trop-violent-ce-patron-chinois-finit-au-tapis-pour-prouver-que-son-robot-est-reel.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314340</guid>
      <description>Dans une vid&#233;o, le PDG d'EngineAI se fait violemment frapper par son robot T800. Un coup de pub brutal pour prouver que la machine est bien r&#233;elle et pr&#234;te au combat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a deal! MSI&#8217;s Windows 11 Pro laptop is under $500 and packs an Intel Core 7 150U processor, 16GB RAM, and a 1TB NVMe SSD &#8212; but at this price, it could sell out at any moment</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-a-deal-msis-windows-11-pro-laptop-is-under-usd500-and-packs-an-intel-core-7-150u-processor-16gb-ram-and-a-1tb-nvme-ssd-but-at-this-price-it-could-sell-out-at-any-moment</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7QrjqWF8LLrEm2rd6zZVe9</guid>
      <description>MSI's laptop is now just $499, a staggering $451 off the usual price of $950, but it won't be around for long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordVPN extends phishing and malware protection to your inbox</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/nordvpn-extends-phishing-and-malware-protection-to-your-inbox</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6vApdhHHVzBcB6n7z4TYKg</guid>
      <description>NordVPN just launched a new email protection feature to stop phishing in its tracks. It scans and flags dodgy links right inside your browser-based email client on macOS and Windows.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
