<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 05:40:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Amazon, HyperX is running a huge $109 discount on the QuadCast 2 S</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/forget-amazon-hyperx-is-running-a-huge-usd109-discount-on-the-quadcast-2-s</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 05:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">B2Fhfq62nu8iicXJJWfTYM</guid>
      <description>Save more when you buy the HyperX QuadCast 2 S in a bundle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s guide to Black Friday 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/808624/black-friday-cyber-monday-guide-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T00:30:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_package&amp;p=808624</guid>
      <description>Now that we&#8217;ve already gathered with friends and family to dine on our favorite foods, the real feast has begun. I&#8217;m talking, of course, about Black Friday and the full weekend of shopping that leads into Cyber Monday on December 1st. Many of the gadgets we recommend to readers have received steep discounts that&#8217;ll likely [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 190 best Black Friday deals you can still shop &#8212; a ton of tech is over half off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/824521/black-friday-2025-best-deals-tech-gadgets-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T00:05:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=824521</guid>
      <description>Now that the Thanksgiving dishes are put away and the last slice of pie is hidden in the back of the fridge, it&#8217;s time to turn your attention to the next major holiday: Black Friday. The biggest shopping day of the year has started, and as expected, there are tens of thousands of deals staring [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Sharge 3-in-1 Power Bank, the best-looking battery I've tested, is on sale for Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/sharge-retractable-3-in-1-power-bank-black-friday-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 05:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fHtLCwtJegsRbPHnkHi6QR</guid>
      <description>This Sharge 3-in-1 retractable power bank isn't just the most stylish battery pack I've tested; it boasts a fantastic feature set, including built-in wall prongs, and is discounted for Black Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The M4 MacBook Air is one of the best Apple deals you can get for Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/832969/black-friday-macbook-air-m4-13-15-inch-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-28T23:35:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=832969</guid>
      <description>Black Friday is packed with plenty of great Apple deals, but one of the most notable is the current discount on the latest MacBook Air. Right now, you can buy the 13-inch MacBook Air M4 with 256GB of storage at Amazon, Best Buy, and Costco starting around $749 ($250 off), which remains the laptop&#8217;s lowest [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 50 handpicked Black Friday deals are still available for $50 or less</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/829553/black-friday-best-cheap-tech-deals-under-50-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-28T23:18:20-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=829553</guid>
      <description>Black Friday is a great time to save on big-ticket items like 4K TVs, laptops, and headphones. But if you&#8217;re on a tight budget this holiday season, there are plenty of worthwhile deals on practical upgrades for $50 or less &#8212; think power banks, smart speakers, location trackers, and entry-level earbuds that punch above their [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the DJI Osmo 360 camera for almost $200 off in Amazons Black Friday sale</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/black-friday-deal-2025-dji-osmo-360-action-camera</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 04:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02nRFM7eBwjiTOI5lq1cEdm</guid>
      <description>The DJI Osmo 360 is great for creators and adventurers. Get it on sale as part of Amazon's Black Friday deals.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
