<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:35:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A16z VC&#160;wants founders to stop stressing over insane ARR numbers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/a16z-vc-wants-founders-to-stop-stressing-over-insane-arr-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090068</guid>
      <description>A16z VC Jennifer Li&#8288;, who oversees some of the firm's fastest growing AI companies, warns founders not to believe every ARR claim made on X.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Predator: Badlands&#8217; Is Roaring Onto Hulu Next Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/predator-badlands-streaming-release-date-2000718653</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718653</guid>
      <description>Sci-fi's odd couple extraordinaire is coming to streaming just in time for Valentine's Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Cops Frequently Got Caught Planting Drugs in 2017</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cops-planting-drugs-2010s-body-cameras-2000718559</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718559</guid>
      <description>Look. All technology comes with a learning curve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X's latest Community Notes experiment allows AI to write the first draft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/xs-latest-community-notes-experiment-allows-ai-to-write-the-first-draft-210605597.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">858633a6-0d81-4f6b-8496-9422e3005804</guid>
      <description>X is experimenting with a new way for AI to write Community Notes. The company is testing a new "collaborative notes" feature that allows human writers to request an AI-written Community Note.&#160;It's not the first time the platform has experimented with AI in Community Notes. The company started a pilot program last year to allow developers to create dedicated AI note writers. But the latest experiment sounds like a more streamlined process.&#160;According to the company, when an existing Community Note contributor requests a note on a post, the request "now also kicks off creation of a Collaborative...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iron Lung&#8217;s path to theaters was unique, even if the movie isn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/874500/iron-lung-theater-box-office-markiplier</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874500</guid>
      <description>As a movie, Iron Lung is occasionally thrilling but mostly forgettable. It's a small-budget horror flick that has some cool ideas and pulls them off in an extremely efficient way, creating a sense of tension that unfortunately never turns into outright scares. But the most important thing about it is what it represents. At a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I compared nearly 20 of the best noise-cancelling headphones, and the two best cheap options have great deals right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/i-compared-nearly-20-of-the-best-noise-cancelling-headphones-and-the-two-best-cheap-options-have-great-deals-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Wh2yPZJRegC3zVHCFmFDgG</guid>
      <description>Don't miss these budget bargains for blocking outside noise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You&#8217;re Sick of This Brutal Cold, Boy Do We Have News for You</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/if-youre-sick-of-this-brutal-cold-boy-do-we-have-news-for-you-2000718571</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718571</guid>
      <description>Although the eastern U.S. is facing another frigid weekend, forecast models suggest temperatures will rise significantly in the latter half of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The price of Bitcoin drops below $65,000</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874603/bitcoin-price-drop-cryptocurrency</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T15:38:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874603</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, Bitcoin's value fell over 10 percent in a single day, dropping to around $64,000, the lowest it has been since the 2024 Presidential election, as CNBC reports. After crossing $100,000 in November 2024 and peaking at over $122,000 in October 2025, the cryptocurrency has been in a steady decline for the last several [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, Jeffrey Epstein Is Probably Not Satoshi Nakamoto</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/no-jeffrey-epstein-is-probably-not-satoshi-nakamoto-2000718652</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718652</guid>
      <description>There are lots of revelations about Epstein's relationship with the crypto world in the files. That's not one of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, where to stream, start time, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-where-to-stream-start-time-and-more-175759112.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is less than a week away. This year's game will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA, and the Bay Area will be host to loads of other football events this week, too, including Thursday's NFL Honors, where we'll learn who this season's MVP is. (That event, which will be held in San Francisco, will air live on NBC and the NFL Network on Thursday at 9...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is that a mini PC or a NES? Acemagic Retro X3 features some familiar casing, but with a welcome hardware boost inside</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-retro-mini-pc-is-a-proper-trip-down-memory-lane-acemagic-retro-x3-brings-back-the-grey-casing-but-with-a-welcome-hardware-boost-inside</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7X3xewCBbJdvZB6khqLm29</guid>
      <description>Acemagic&#8217;s Retro X3 mini PC blends nostalgic beige design with modern Ryzen performance, modular upgrades, and versatile connectivity options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE and CBP&#8217;s Face-Recognition App Can&#8217;t Actually Verify Who People Are</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/cbp-ice-dhs-mobile-fortify-face-recognition-verify-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697909858bd11cb3a1a8e9b6</guid>
      <description>ICE has used Mobile Fortify to identify immigrants and citizens alike over 100,000 times, by one estimate. It wasn't built to work like that&#8212;and only got approved after DHS abandoned its own privacy rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Enters a New Frontier: Trying to Make Money</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-enters-a-new-frontier-trying-to-make-money-2000718558</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718558</guid>
      <description>They're hoping companies will pay for AI agent management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything we know about Valve's new Steam Machine</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/everything-we-know-about-valves-new-steam-machine-200458817.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e72a9441-234d-4d58-a695-5e151176b7bd</guid>
      <description>The Steam Machine is back from the dead. Not as a Valve-supported program for manufacturers to create living room PCs, but instead a home console sibling to the Steam Deck. Valve introduced its second attempt at ruling the living room in a surprise hardware announcement in November 2025, and paired the new Steam Machine with a new Steam Controller and a wireless VR headset it calls the Steam Frame. Since the announcement, as is often the case with Valve, some details remain elusive, however.While we wait for the release of the company's new hardware lineup in 2026, and more information straigh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google reveals Pixel 10a with one subtle change</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/google-pixel-10a-revealed-camera-change</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07C121tipYgIqn4rjl1KEM5</guid>
      <description>Google randomly dropped a video revealing the Pixel 10a.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI launches new agentic coding model only minutes after Anthropic drops its own</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/openai-launches-new-agentic-coding-model-only-minutes-after-anthropic-drops-its-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090041</guid>
      <description>The new model is build to accelerate the capabilities of Codex, the agentic coding tool OpenAI launched earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Rock Springs&#8217; Brings Horror From the Past Into Its Tale of Contemporary Grief</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rock-springs-brings-horror-from-the-past-into-its-tale-of-contemporary-grief-2000716330</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716330</guid>
      <description>Writer-director Vera Miao&#8217;s film, which stars Kelly Marie Tran and Benedict Wong, premiered in the Midnight program at the 2026 Sundance Film Festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a bien d&#233;tect&#233; le code-barres cosmique des trous noirs !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-on-bien-detecte-code-barres-cosmique-trous-noirs-130891/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:59:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-on-bien-detecte-code-barres-cosmique-trous-noirs-130891/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Comment &#234;tre certain&#160;que des objets aussi exotiques que des trous noirs existent bel et bien dans le cosmos observable ? Les astrophysiciens relativistes ont la solution depuis presque un demi-si&#232;cle, mais il a fallu&#160;attendre l'essor puis le d&#233;veloppement de l'astrophysique des ondes...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
