<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:28:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the NVIDIA CES 2026 press conference with Jensen Huang live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-nvidia-ces-2026-press-conference-with-jensen-huang-live-130028602.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a8ad1a0-9035-4f52-a4e0-783ee7c9700b</guid>
      <description>CFOTO via Getty Images
During CES 2025, NVIDIA spent much of its keynote touting its leading position in artificial intelligence. Still, the company managed to squeeze in a few notable hardware announcements, including its RTX 5000-series GPUs and Project Digits desktop supercomputer (later redubbed Spark). For this year's show, the company's website says it's "lighting up CES 2026 with the power of AI." To that end, NVIDIA is going big in Las Vegas, promising hands-on demos in its Fontainebleau booth, replete with the "latest NVIDIA solutions driving innovation and productivity across industr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG's 'Aerominum' Gram Pro laptops feel impossibly light and strong</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lgs-aerominum-gram-pro-laptops-feel-impossibly-light-and-strong-200317743.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abdf8260-a0d5-4757-9469-76666ccad982</guid>
      <description>For years, LG has pushed its ultra-light Gram laptops as a way to stand out from the PC crowd, for better or worse. I was't a big fan of the flex-prone case in the 2017 Gram, and we had similar concerns with the first 17-inch Gram in 2019. But in fairness, it's been a while since we've reviewed one, and we found a lot to like in our preview of last year's AI-equipped model. Now LG is back with a major Gram Pro redesign at CES 2026, which features a new aluminum/magnesium alloy it's dubbed "Aerominum." And finally, it seems LG has found a balance between building a super-light notebook (the 16-...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliro arrives &#8211; the smart lock standard is set to launch this year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/854091/aliro-smart-lock-standard-launches-2026-apple-uwb-nfc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T15:00:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854091</guid>
      <description>The long-delayed smart lock standard Aliro is finally launching. The first specification, which standardizes NFC-based tap-to-unlock and UWB hands-free unlocking for smart locks, will arrive early this year, according to the Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA). "We're delighted to share that Aliro, the CSA's standardized credential and communication protocol that lets trusted smartphones and wearables act [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Dispatch&#8217; Stats Show Millions of Players Put the Work In</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dispatch-stats-show-millions-of-players-put-the-work-in-2000705126</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705126</guid>
      <description>It came in late, but 'Dispatch' became the talk of the town last year as players fell for its gameplay, characters...basically all of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Wants Venezuela's Oil. Getting It Might Not Be So Simple</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-wants-venezuelas-oil-getting-it-might-not-be-so-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695aac1ba9a1aef626dfded0</guid>
      <description>The administration has made it clear that Nicol&#225;s Maduro's capture was tied to Venezuela's vast oil reserves. Much less certain is how US companies will actually access them&#8212;or if they even want to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel beats AMD on sheer value as it ranks 7 CPUs in PassMark's top 10 Price Performance leaderboard &#8212; AMD gets number 1 but it's just an entry level Ryzen 5 on clearance sales</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/intel-beats-amd-on-sheer-value-as-it-ranks-7-cpus-in-passmarks-top-10-price-performance-leaderboard-amd-gets-number-1-but-its-just-an-entry-level-ryzen-5-on-clearance-sales</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXhNktC3rWkfn7iXJmtcAH</guid>
      <description>Intel dominates PassMark&#8217;s price performance rankings as seven of its CPUs appear in the top ten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Lego CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/how-to-watch-the-lego-ces-2026-press-conference-live-130005019.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02a28a6-f21c-46c9-a5e0-dcff1b13d26a</guid>
      <description>picture alliance via Getty Images
Are you a Lego Adult? No guilt implied &#8212; we hear you, whether you enjoy building Death Stars, Starship Enterprises or even just the occasional flower bouquet. But you may be surprised to hear that the Lego Group is set to host its very first press conference at CES 2026. Exactly what it plans to unveil is still under wraps, however. The iconic toy brick maker has offered no clues about what's on the agenda, leaving speculation wide open, from new video games to Formula 1 race cars.
Here's how you can watch Lego's presentation at CES, along with what we think t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins 2026 &#8212; it's *FREE* &#8211; Team UK vs Team Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/how-to-watch-summerwater-on-channel-4-its-free-clone</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5rKjFmJAsVGM88ftBaJmTk</guid>
      <description>The DS are back with a new twist: Team UK vs Team Australia. Here's how to watch Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins 2026 &#8212; it's FREE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Hisense CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-hisense-ces-2026-press-conference-live-190040504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9486b306-eae4-49da-a805-9b5cf78d2fb9</guid>
      <description>Xinhua News Agency via Getty Images
Hisense is typically best known for its affordable electronics and home appliances, from TVs to refrigerators. But at CES 2025, the China-based company showed off its premium side with a massive 136-inch micro LED TV &#8212; now available for a jaw-dropping $100,000. So what's in store for this year's show? New leadership, for starters.
The company has two new hires, including Chief Marketing Officer Sarah Larsen and Chief Commercial Officer James Fishler. In a press release, Hisense said Fishler's experience in home entertainment, appliances and HVAC is important...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG&#160;says its&#160;CLOiD home robot will be folding laundry and making breakfast at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854082/lg-cloid-home-robot-fold-laundry-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T14:13:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854082</guid>
      <description>LG teased that it would be showing off a new robot for a "zero labor home" at CES. We now have a bit more detail on what to expect. The company says that its CLOiD home robot can fetch milk from the fridge, put a croissant in the oven, and even do some laundry, including [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Lenovo Tech World event at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-lenovo-tech-world-event-at-ces-2026-130004983.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fedcbad-9aca-41b8-93db-45c9330ce965</guid>
      <description>We've known for several months now that tech giant Lenovo is hosting its Tech World event at Sphere is Las Vegas during CES week. And like many other tech conglomerates, the world's largest PC manufacturer by units shipped is centering its focus on AI. Lenovo says it will be a "Tech World experience unlike anything CES has seen before." We'll tell you where to livestream the event and what the company has teased so far.
How to watch the Lenovo CES 2026 event live
Lenovo CEO Yuanqing Yang will host the event on Tuesday, January 6 at 8PM ET. You can follow along to the livestream on YouTube once...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested Hori&#8217;s cheap Nintendo Switch 2 camera &#8212; this one flaw makes it hard to recommend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/hori-usb-camera-for-nintendo-switch-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xntRMXJ7eNaHthRop3aKUL</guid>
      <description>Hori&#8217;s Piranha Plant camera didn&#8217;t impress me, so I tested its minimalist alternative instead &#8212; is it any good?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch 2026 Critics&#8217; Choice Awards online &#8212; live stream the film and TV awards ceremony from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/critics-choice-awards-2026-online</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HW5SVHawkUeyCJWEjyJePL</guid>
      <description>Prepare for a star-studded evening as the CCAs honor the best in film and TV from last year. Here's how to watch 2026 Critics&#8217; Choice Awards online anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Intelition' changes everything: AI is no longer a tool you invoke</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/intelition-changes-everything-ai-is-no-longer-a-tool-you-invoke</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ei5mqFLnl4M8VBzk36rE5</guid>
      <description>AI is evolving faster than our vocabulary for describing it. We may need a few new words. We have &#8220;cognition&#8221; for how a single mind thinks, but we don't have a word for what happens when human and machine intelligence work together to perceive, decide, create and act. Let&#8217;s call that process intelition.&#160;Intelition isn&#8217;t a feature; it&#8217;s the organizing principle for the next wave of software where humans and AI operate inside the same shared model of the enterprise. Today&#8217;s systems treat AI models as things you invoke from the outside. You act as a &#8220;user,&#8221; prompting for responses or wiring a &#8220;hu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce moniteur LG 4K de 32&#8243;, avec un bras articul&#233; et qui fait office de Smart TV co&#251;te pr&#232;s de 200 &#8364; de moins</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2924593_ce-moniteur-lg-4k-de-32-avec-un-bras-articule-et-qui-fait-office-de-smart-tv-coute-pres-de-200-e-de-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2924593_ce-moniteur-lg-4k-de-32-avec-un-bras-articule-et-qui-fait-office-de-smart-tv-coute-pres-de-200-e-de-moins</guid>
      <description>
Du haut de sa dalle de 32 pouces, ce moniteur LG peut s'utiliser dans tous les sens et pourra r&#233;pondre &#224; tous vos besoins. Sur le site de la marque, il tombe &#224; 823,99 euros et conna&#238;t une remise de 176 euros.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
