<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:25:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Valve Has the Secret to Playing Your Games Everywhere, and It&#8217;s Not Streaming</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/valve-has-the-secret-to-playing-your-games-everywhere-and-its-not-streaming-2000699887</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699887</guid>
      <description>Sorry, Game Pass, but Steam may soon bring your games to every platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hasbro&#8217;s New &#8216;Deadpool &amp; Wolverine&#8217; Figures Let Cassandra Nova Do That Horrifying Face Thing</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marvel-legends-deadpool-and-wolverine-blade-cassandra-nova-x-23-2000699866</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699866</guid>
      <description>Plus, Wesley Snipe's Blade gets the Marvel Legends action figure he's long deserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#8217;s OpenAI deal is exclusive for just one year  &#8212; then it&#8217;s open season</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/disneys-openai-deal-is-exclusive-for-just-one-year-then-its-open-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076160</guid>
      <description>After the one year is up, Disney is free to sign similar deals with other AI companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's smallest AI supercomputer achieves world record with 120B-parameter LLM support on-device &#8212; what I don't understand, though, is how it does OTA hardware upgrades</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/worlds-smallest-ai-supercomputer-achieves-world-record-with-120b-parameter-llm-support-on-device-what-i-dont-understand-though-is-how-it-does-ota-hardware-upgrades</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BS5FHWi7kJ6Tj738DDhate</guid>
      <description>Tiiny AI Pocket Lab is a pocket-sized Mini PC running large language models offline with optimized CPU and NPU performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV adds Google Cast streaming, but only on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844867/apple-tv-google-cast-android</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T17:11:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844867</guid>
      <description>Now it will be easier for Android users to watch Apple TV content on their TV with the addition of Google Cast support. However, even after this update, Google Cast is only an option on the Android version of Apple TV, not the iOS version. Likewise, the Android version still doesn't support AirPlay. The addition [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#160;bulks up&#160;open source&#160;offerings with an acquisition and new open AI models</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/nvidia-bulks-up-open-source-offerings-with-an-acquisition-and-new-open-ai-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076166</guid>
      <description>Nvidia acquired SchedMD, the lead developer of Slurm, and launched the Nemotron 3 family of open source AI models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested 15 cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T16:50:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Sure, it can take away from the slick design. But using a case relieves me of the worry that the console will accumulate tons of little scratches, or worse. I&#8217;ve tested several types of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG TVs Get Unremovable Microsoft Copilot App</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lg-tvs-get-unremovable-microsoft-copilot-app-2000699870</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699870</guid>
      <description>Users are not thrilled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Spacecraft Got Disturbingly Close to Smashing Into a Starlink Satellite</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chinese-spacecraft-got-disturbingly-close-to-smashing-into-a-starlink-satellite-2000699907</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699907</guid>
      <description>The close call underscores the need for improved coordination between satellite operators, Starlink&#8217;s vice president of engineering said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk about a snappy attack - popular photo booth maker allegedly leaves user images at risk</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/talk-about-a-snappy-attack-popular-photo-booth-maker-allegedly-leaves-user-images-at-risk</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pif9edbeC8sgDPgzFVp3PF</guid>
      <description>Photos taken at booths get uploaded on the internet where they can easily be downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Is Prepping a New Gaston &#8216;Beauty and the Beast&#8217; Spinoff</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-gaston-beauty-and-the-beast-spinoff-2000699896</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699896</guid>
      <description>Luke Evans portrayed the live-action version of the animated role back in the 2017 film, but this will be a new take on the character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 best last-minute Christmas gifts for 2025 that will arrive by December 24</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-12-best-last-minute-christmas-gifts-for-2025-that-will-arrive-by-december-24-140037753.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f10f3474-8a9f-4844-b943-494ef9bdc916</guid>
      <description>The holidays are nearly here and if you&#8217;re a bit behind on your gift shopping, you&#8217;re not alone. The holidays can truly sneak up on you, and this year that&#8217;s been more true than ever. Between wrapping things up at work before some well-deserved time off and making sure you have everything you need to host family and friends, it can be hard to find the time to go to a store to pick out presents. And when you do finally get there, you may be met with half-empty shelves. But this is where the internet comes in handy: you still have time to buy holiday gifts online.USPS, UPS and FedEx have laid ou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford is starting a battery storage business to power data centers and the grid</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/ford-is-starting-a-battery-storage-business-to-power-data-centers-and-the-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076153</guid>
      <description>Ford will invest about $2 billion into the new business over the next two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford Kills the All-Electric F-150 as It Rethinks Its EV Ambitions</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ford-kills-electric-f-150-lightning-for-hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">694061e5cee321741285f378</guid>
      <description>The move comes as a response to the Trump administration's waning support for electrification and a weakening consumer market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasma Turbulence Is Doing Surprising Things Inside Fusion Reactors</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/plasma-turbulence-is-doing-strange-things-inside-fusion-reactors-2000699898</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699898</guid>
      <description>For plasma in fusion reactors, turbulence might be more than a pesky thing to control, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford&#8217;s next F-150 Lightning will have a gas generator as it&#160;pivots away from large EVs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/fords-next-f-150-lightning-will-have-a-gas-generator-as-it-pivots-away-from-large-evs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076127</guid>
      <description>The company is abandoning plans for a brand new all-electric pickup truck codenamed "T3" and ending production of the battery-only Lightning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford&#8217;s big bet on EVs didn&#8217;t pan out &#8212; now it&#8217;s pivoting to hybrids and energy storage</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844813/ford-hybrid-erev-f150-energy-storage-jobs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T16:05:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844813</guid>
      <description>Ford announced a series of changes to its gas- and electric-powered vehicle business aimed at dramatically increasing hybrid vehicle production in the face of slowing EV sales. The automaker also will introduce some new products as part of this plan, including an extended-range EV version of its F-series truck and battery storage systems to meet [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Christmas gift ideas everyone on your 2025 holiday shopping list will love</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-christmas-gift-ideas-everyone-on-your-2025-holiday-shopping-list-will-love-170018978.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4160f992-6cb7-4c9c-b2bb-281bf7cf66e1</guid>
      <description>This time of year has a lot of merry and bright things to be excited about, but it can be stressful if you&#8217;re stumped on what to get your mom, dad, best friend, coworker or kids&#8217; teacher as a holiday gift. Whether you enjoy or dread buying gifts for people, it&#8217;s safe to say we all want to give our loved ones things they will enjoy and appreciate. But there&#8217;s a lot of noise, junk and bad deals disguised as good deals to sift through as we get closer and closer to the holidays.Allow us at Engadget to help you through it. Here, you&#8217;ll find all of our holiday gift guides collected in one place, so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DoomScroll website is an 'endless' library of Doom maps you can pick from and play in your browser</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/new-doomscroll-website-is-an-endless-library-of-doom-maps-you-can-pick-from-and-play-in-your-browser</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Lu3AbBLow6Gw3BNnDajHJ8</guid>
      <description>I was going to be RPG'ing on my PS5 Pro over the holidays, but now I might play Doom in my browser instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 18-to-24 demo is taking over LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453762/the-18-to-24-demo-is-taking-over-linkedin</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453762/the-18-to-24-demo-is-taking-over-linkedin</guid>
      <description>Career pressure is setting in younger and younger.
LinkedIn is often seen as the purview of recruiters and thought leaders. But the professional networking platform is quietly attracting a rather unexpected audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested out GMKtec NucBox M8 and it's an ideal option for space-restricted offices and packs some serious expansion options</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gmktec-nucbox-m8-mini-pc-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VnghAUaYf29Ku7dLdTVPi</guid>
      <description>The compact design features a powerful CPU, which handles productivity with ease, but the GPU is slightly lacking for creative use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV app for Android now supports Google Cast</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/apple-tv-app-for-android-now-supports-google-cast-205642324.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c9080fd-dc6b-4f7b-bcfb-8a396f9b3d55</guid>
      <description>Apple TV is adding Google Cast support to its native Android app. This update allows subscribers to stream Apple TV shows from their smartphones to their televisions. Apple's streaming service only just released the dedicated app for the Android operating system in February 2025. Adding in Google Cast support helps fully integrate the app into the experience for people whose gear is part of the Android ecosystem.
The addition should make it easier for viewers to shift between screens, even mid-episode. It's a very different approach than Netflix, which recently ended Google Cast support for it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Commons announces tentative support for AI &#8216;pay-to-crawl&#8217; systems</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/creative-commons-announces-tentative-support-for-ai-pay-to-crawl-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076085</guid>
      <description>The organization offered support for this idea of an AI marketplace, and  suggested several guiding principles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout season 2's first episode will premiere a little earlier than expected</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/fallout-season-2s-first-episode-will-premiere-a-little-earlier-than-expected-205018028.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc8fddc-d681-4da7-aa64-39d0cd67947b</guid>
      <description>In an era where we often have to twiddle our thumbs for three years before a new season of a TV show we enjoy returns to our screens, the second season of Fallout&#160;has had a relatively short turnaround. It's set to hit Prime Video 20 months after the first batch of episodes. As it turns out, the season two premiere is going to arrive a little earlier than you may have anticipated as well.&#160;
The first episode will now hit Prime Video at 9PM ET on December 16. That's six hours earlier than expected. So if you've been looking forward to catching back up with Lucy, Maximus and The Ghoul, you won't h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie's Marathon will arrive in March</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/bungies-marathon-will-arrive-in-march-200838426.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e26e2f94-5e0c-47a6-9b5b-4d01b9612966</guid>
      <description>
Bungie&#8217;s Marathon has a new release window. The survival extraction shooter was originally set to hit PlayStation 5, Xbox Series X/S and PC in September, but by June, Sony had delayed it indefinitely. Now, with a plagiarism issue largely in the rearview mirror, Bungie has confirmed that Marathon will arrive in March and and plans to sell it for $40.
Alongside the release date and price announcement, Bungie released a 23-minute video that takes a deep dive into the game and shows off the current state of Marathon. New features include proximity chat and a solo mode, while Bungie says it has up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ is now available to stream on Meta's Quest headsets</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/disney-is-now-available-to-stream-on-metas-quest-headsets-203622392.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d569209c-2852-4850-9f9a-9fa978a0d520</guid>
      <description>Meta revealed that Disney+ was coming to its Quest headsets earlier this year during its Connect event. Now, the streaming app and its vast catalog are finally available to Meta's VR users in the United States.Meta recently overhauled the Quest's entertainment experience with a new Horizon TV hub that brings its streaming features into one place. Horizon TV also added support for Dolby Vision and Dolby Atmos sound, both of which Disney+ subscribers can now take advantage of. According to Meta, there are a"select" number of titles available to stream in Dolby Vision 4K HDR, and Disney+ Premium ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightspeed raises record $9B in fresh capital</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/lightspeed-raises-record-9b-in-fresh-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076110</guid>
      <description>The massive fund haul will allow the Silicon Valley firm to continue to invest in cash hungry AI startups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Downloads of &#8216;One Battle After Another&#8217; Contain Dangerous Malware</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/illegal-downloads-of-one-battle-after-another-contain-dangerous-malware-2000699788</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699788</guid>
      <description>The movie starts streaming at HBO Max on Dec. 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PS5, PlayStation Portal, and Sony&#8217;s DualSense are still on sale for a limited time</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/844698/sony-ps5-playstation-portal-dualsense-controller-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844698</guid>
      <description>Sony&#8217;s annual PlayStation sale has been going on for nearly a month now, offering discounts on everything from the PlayStation 5 Digital Edition and PlayStation Portal to Sony&#8217;s standard DualSense controller. However, the end of the sale is quickly approaching, with Sony&#8217;s website showing that some deals are set to expire as soon as Friday, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A water-cooled AMD AI 14-inch tablet with 16 CPU cores, a 5060-class GPU, and 128GB RAM is exactly what I need for Christmas &#8212; I don't think it will cost less than $2000, though</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/a-water-cooled-amd-ai-14-inch-tablet-with-16-cpu-cores-a-5060-class-gpu-and-128gb-ram-is-exactly-what-i-need-for-christmas-i-dont-think-it-will-cost-less-than-usd2000-though</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uM949sSMWfACiNHrdmoZsD</guid>
      <description>OneXPlayer&#8217;s Super X is a 14-inch hybrid tablet-laptop with AMD Ryzen AI Max+ 395, 128GB RAM, and liquid cooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stretch fabric is nearly impossible to recycle&#8212;but this startup just made it simple</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459816/stretch-fabric-is-nearly-impossible-to-recycle-this-startup-reinvented-it</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459816/stretch-fabric-is-nearly-impossible-to-recycle-this-startup-reinvented-it</guid>
      <description>Your old yoga pants are a recycling nightmare. A startup called Return to Vendor found a new solution&#8212;by redesigning the molecules in nylon.
Stretch fabrics are notoriously hard to process. When your old leggings wear out, they will probably end up in a landfill&#8212;even if you try to drop them off for recycling. But a Manhattan startup has developed a new material that could finally make this corner of the apparel industry circular....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
