<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:28:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla is finally doing unsupervised robotaxi rides</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/866165/tesla-robotaxi-unsupervised-austin-texas-safety-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T16:23:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866165</guid>
      <description>Tesla is finally doing unsupervised robotaxi trips in Austin, Texas, according to a video posted on X. Elon Musk reposted the video, congratulating Tesla's AI team for the milestone. For months, Tesla's robotaxis in Austin and San Francisco have included safety monitors with access to a kill switch in case of emergency - a fallback [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Evidence Melts the Stonehenge Glacier Theory</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-evidence-melts-the-stonehenge-glacier-theory-2000713126</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713126</guid>
      <description>It seems like glaciers weren't helpful in the construction of the famous prehistoric monument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious FTX Exec Caroline Ellison Is Out of Federal Custody</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/notorious-ftx-exec-caroline-ellison-is-out-of-federal-custody-2000713133</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713133</guid>
      <description>SBF's ex-girlfriend was released early after cooperating in the FTX fraud case. Is anyone hiring?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Cool Details We Spotted in the &#8216;Maul&#8212;Shadow Lord&#8217; Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-maul-shadow-lord-trailer-breakdown-2000713065</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713065</guid>
      <description>Our first proper look at Darth Maul's new animated series brings some interesting ties to other areas of the 'Star Wars' galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Garmin kept accidentally calling people in the shower &#8212; here's the simple fix</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-trackers/my-garmin-kept-accidentally-calling-people-in-the-shower-heres-the-simple-fix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86XE5fDWYeqgYg2btuyDNU</guid>
      <description>My Garmin watch has a life of its own in the shower &#8212; here's how to set up a touchscreen locking hot key.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Good luck, the rest of you&#8217;: Volvo taunts Ford and Volkswagen and says it's overcome 'painful' software issues with new EX60</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/good-luck-the-rest-of-you-volvo-taunts-ford-and-volkswagen-and-says-its-overcome-painful-software-issues-with-new-ex60</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NPBASEWFZvWryK7LFrx7BR</guid>
      <description>Volvo unveils the upcoming EX60 electric SUV, which it claims is a game changer. But it still has a huge task on its hands to make customers forget about the EX90 software debacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Sure Made Lots of Predictions at Davos</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-sure-made-lots-of-predictions-at-davos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697256adfad3dcdb3fa877e9</guid>
      <description>Humanoid robots, space travel, the science of aging&#8212;Musk was willing to weigh in on all of it at this week's World Economic Forum. But his predictions rarely work out the way he says they will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 and Outlook are down for many &#8211; here's everything we know about issues affecting the apps, as a disruption is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/microsoft-outlook-365-outage-january-22-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TdGHkE25WjzLirHS4oh76D</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has confirmed an issue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Ellison extends deadline for Warner Bros. Discovery takeover offer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/david-ellison-extends-deadline-for-warner-bros-discovery-takeover-offer-204752313.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9a88ff9-8c85-4305-a835-21506b4531ac</guid>
      <description>Paramount Skydance CEO David Ellison is apparently still hopeful that investors will approve his $108.4 billion hostile takeover of Warner Bros. Discovery. Paramount Skydance announced Thursday that it's extending its all-cash offer to acquire the storied studio, and giving investors until February 20, 2026 to accept. The company's previous offer expired on January 21, but with a lawsuit in the works and a revised Netflix deal to compete with, Paramount Skydance wants to stay in the conversation.Netflix and Warner Bros. Discovery originally announced their $82.7 billion acquisition agreement i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's biggest memory rival has a clever plan to make SSDs bigger (but not cheaper) &#8212; split-cell 5-bit flash sounds like RAID-0 on hard drives, but for SSD</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/samsungs-biggest-ssd-rival-has-a-clever-plan-to-make-ssd-bigger-but-not-cheaper-split-cell-5-bit-flash-sounds-like-raid-0-on-hard-drives-but-for-ssd</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zgdHLELu8u2F6M6FqiUnaH</guid>
      <description>SK Hynix introduces split-cell 5-bit NAND flash that increases SSD capacity, improves speed, and extends endurance without increasing costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring says it&amp;#8217;s not giving ICE access to its cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866003/ring-ice-camera-access-flock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T15:30:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866003</guid>
      <description>Ring's partnership with Flock is sparking renewed online backlash this week, with influencers calling for people to smash their Ring cameras and claiming the company is part of the surveillance state amid heightened concerns over ICE actions. Flock is an AI-powered surveillance camera company that has reportedly allowed government agencies - including ICE - to [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We had to do a lot of technological work that was sort of unprecedented ... which was really challenging and exciting," Crossplay producer on the effort to bring The New York Times' first two-player game to life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/we-had-to-do-a-lot-of-technological-work-that-was-sort-of-unprecedented-which-was-really-challenging-and-exciting-crossplay-producer-on-the-effort-to-bring-the-new-york-times-first-two-player-game-to-life</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xvXwNrUjsYr7xKQGNW2obE</guid>
      <description>TechRadar speaks with New York Times Senior Producer Jeff Petriello about the origins of the newly launched Crossplay, its hidden easter eggs, and what&#8217;s next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have your say: do you actually use Apple Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/have-your-say-do-you-actually-use-apple-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qV3vD8VSZvhkMa9iqd3Jn8</guid>
      <description>Apple Intelligence hasn't won over a lot of TechRadar, but let me know if you use it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack is launching a TV app, and not everyone is happy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866054/substack-tv-app-beta-launch-newsletters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T15:21:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866054</guid>
      <description>Substack announced Thursday it's launching Apple TV and Google TV apps that audiences can use for videos and livestreams - and early reactions suggest not all users are thrilled. Subscribers can watch videos and livestreams from creators they follow, but the app will also have a recommendations-based "For You" feed that mixes in other creators' [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When a Chinese Battery Factory Comes to Town</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/chinese-battery-makers-are-building-factories-across-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697163956c03e6376fe6f8f2</guid>
      <description>Chinese firms are building battery plants from Europe to North America, promising jobs while prompting local concerns about the environment, politics, and who really benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter storm 2026: You&#8217;ve seen the warnings. Here&#8217;s how to prepare for extreme cold, ice, and snow</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479444/winter-storm-2026-how-to-prepare-for-extreme-cold-ice-snow-weather-warnings-blizzard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T20:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479444/winter-storm-2026-how-to-prepare-for-extreme-cold-ice-snow-weather-warnings-blizzard</guid>
      <description>Weather conditions could be dangerous for up to 230 million Americans this weekend, with everything from sleet to blizzards in the forecast.
Everyone is talking about it in group chats, at the supermarket, and at the gas pump. No, it&#8217;s not Heated Rivalry&#8212;it is the &#8220;monster&#8221; winter storm that is set to hit the U.S. this weekend, traveling from Texas across the Southwest, into the Southeast, and finally into the Mid-Atlantic states and into New England....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Is Running Dangerously Low on Blood Right Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/america-is-running-dangerously-low-on-blood-right-now-2000713020</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713020</guid>
      <description>Extreme winter weather and a bad flu season have fueled a severe shortage in the national blood supply over the past month, according to the American Red Cross.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fable will let you be a heartless landlord this fall</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/fable-will-let-you-be-a-heartless-landlord-this-fall-200409310.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4285c05-03ad-4886-9d2c-f5d4762464a3</guid>
      <description>After half a decade of waiting, Microsoft finally offered an extended preview of its long-awaited reboot of the beloved Fable RPG franchise on Thursday. During the company&#8217;s recent Developer Direct showcase, Playground Games, best known for its works on the Forza Horizon series, shared nearly 11 minutes of gameplay footage and commentary related to the upcoming title. The new game will feature a fully open world for players to explore, with locations from previous Fable games like Bowerstone making a return.  Playground didn&#8217;t say exactly where the new game takes place in the Fable timeline. I...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Tank Chair&#8217; Proves Ultra&#8209;Violent Manga Can Still Hit With Heart</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tank-chair-proves-ultra%e2%80%91violent-manga-can-still-hit-with-heart-2000713010</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713010</guid>
      <description>Manabu Yashiro's slept-on mecha-wheelchair series fuses 'Kamen Rider' grit with 'Dorohedoro' chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 28 Best Movies on Apple TV, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (January 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64342bc05ffa737db431afc0</guid>
      <description>F1: The Movie, CODA, and Highest 2 Lowest are just a few of the movies you should be watching on Apple TV this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Fine announces delightful-looking multiplayer pottery game Kiln</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/double-fine-announces-delightful-looking-multiplayer-pottery-game-kiln-195837155.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab113a0-119d-4149-8b39-1fd0985ea75a</guid>
      <description>Double Fine has been on a tear with its smaller projects lately. The popular indie game developer is following up last year's atmospheric adventure game Keeper with a new title in a totally different direction. As its Double Fine founder Tim Schaefer attempted to say five times fast during today's Xbox Developer Direct, Kiln is an "online multiplayer pottery party brawler" that boasts exactly the sort of colorful, clever fun that fans have come to expect from the studio.&#160;Kiln is a game with two facets: creation and destruction. On the creation side, players get to design a ceramic vessel of th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack now has a TV app</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/substack-now-has-a-tv-app-195408592.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cad4782e-89f8-4401-b62a-617b27bcfec7</guid>
      <description>It was only 16 months ago that Substack expanded into live video. Since then, it's become a widely adopted medium on the platform, including by its ever-growing list of cable news expats. Now, the company has decided it's ready for a bigger screen. Starting today, you can install a new Substack TV app on Apple TV and Google TV devices.Substack describes the app's initial launch as focusing on "reliable, high-quality viewing" for the platform's long-form videos. It centers around video posts and livestreams from the creators and publications you follow. There's also a "For You" section that com...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The state attorneys general are as mad as you are</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/865882/democratic-state-attorney-general-rayfield-ellison</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:52:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865882</guid>
      <description>The sun was already beginning to set as Portlanders in weatherproof jackets and fleeces lined up around Revolution Hall. It wasn't yet 5PM on a Wednesday but the crowd was gathering well before the town hall was scheduled to begin. Just a day earlier, news outlets reported that Minnesota Attorney General Keith Ellison had been [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Attempts to Sell &#8216;Cyberpunk 2077&#8217; VR Mod to CD Projekt RED, Gets Bad News</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/developer-attempts-to-sell-cyberpunk-2077-vr-mod-to-cd-projekt-red-gets-bad-news-2000712991</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712991</guid>
      <description>Maybe don't try to sell your paid mod to the company whose Terms of Service you appear to be violating?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring is adding a new content verification feature to videos</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/ring-is-adding-a-new-content-verification-feature-to-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085208</guid>
      <description>Ring says the new feature will identify if video edits have been made, even if they're minor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google DeepMind CEO is &#8216;surprised&#8217; OpenAI is rushing forward with ads in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/google-deepmind-ceo-is-surprised-openai-is-rushing-forward-with-ads-in-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085101</guid>
      <description>Google DeepMind CEO Demis Hassabis says the tech giant isn't pressuring him to insert ads into the AI chatbot experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Site ManyVids Descends Into AI Psychosis</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/porn-site-manyvids-descends-into-ai-psychosis-2000713033</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713033</guid>
      <description>Good luck jerking off to this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe VR Doesn&#8217;t Need Meta After All</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/maybe-vr-doesnt-need-meta-after-all-2000713026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713026</guid>
      <description>Meta's commitment might be wavering, but other entrants in the VR field feel stronger than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A major game publisher is shutting studios and killing 6 titles&#8212;here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479225/a-major-game-publisher-is-shutting-studios-and-killing-six-titles-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479225/a-major-game-publisher-is-shutting-studios-and-killing-six-titles-heres-why</guid>
      <description>The maker of &#8216;Assassin&#8217;s Creed&#8217; says it must radically reorganize to survive, slashing costs and refocusing its portfolio through 2028.
One of the giants of the gaming business has tumbled off a cliff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Fire TV Stick 4K Plus is on sale for just $18 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/865230/amazon-fire-tv-stick-4k-plus-iphone-air-magsafe-battery-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:28:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865230</guid>
      <description>In February, Amazon plans to roll out a much-needed revamp of Fire TV OS, one that seemingly takes a cue from Google&#8217;s TV platform. The forthcoming UI redesign will introduce better organization, support for Alexa Plus, and quicker performance to the aging OS, the latter of which has been a crux of the platform&#8217;s issues [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
