<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:30:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Rubio Orders State Dept to Stop Using Calibri Font in Anti-DEI Push</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marco-rubio-orders-state-dept-to-stop-using-calibri-font-in-anti-dei-push-2000698012</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698012</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Switching to Calibri achieved nothing except the degradation of the department&#8217;s official correspondence," Rubio's memo said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The scramble to launch data centers into space is heating up</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841887/data-center-space-solar-power-aetherflux-lunch</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T15:13:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841887</guid>
      <description>A startup developing technologies to harness solar power in space is throwing its hat in with big tech companies attempting to build out data centers that orbit Earth. The US-based company, Aetherflux, announced on Tuesday that it plans to launch its first data center satellite in early 2027 - the first piece of a larger [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google adds prompt injection defenses to Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/google-adds-prompt-injection-defenses-to-chrome</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HnSZeSNLdGNKbCF6wJFtAR</guid>
      <description>There's an AI that checks what the other AIs are doing and makes sure they're not tricked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum severity React2Shell flaw exploited by North Korean hackers in malware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/maximum-severity-react2shell-flaw-exploited-by-north-korean-hackers-in-malware-attacks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HZLYE8hHenkVefvKukCQvF</guid>
      <description>Sysdig finds evidence of Contagious Interview actors abusing React2Shell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel loses its latest challenge to 16-year-old EU antitrust case</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/intel-loses-its-latest-challenge-to-16-year-old-eu-antitrust-case-200746004.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dde264b0-f2a7-4d22-933f-926286bfe1ba</guid>
      <description>Intel will have to pay up in an antitrust case dating back to 2009, Reuters reported on Wednesday. The company has lost its challenge against a &#8364;376 million ($438.7 million) regulatory fine levied by the European Commission. However, Intel managed to get the amount reduced to 237 million euros ($276.6 million).The case began in 2009, when mobile computing was in its infancy and netbooks (remember those?) were all the rage in the PC space. At the time, the EU ruled that Intel violated antitrust laws on multiple fronts. First, it used illegal hidden rebates to push rivals out of the PC processor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des essais &#233;tranges en orbite &#224; 36&#8239;000 km de la Terre : que pr&#233;paraient ces deux satellites chinois ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-essais-etranges-orbite-36-000-km-terre-preparaient-ces-deux-satellites-chinois-128412/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:03:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-essais-etranges-orbite-36-000-km-terre-preparaient-ces-deux-satellites-chinois-128412/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Alors que les &#201;tats-Unis viennent de d&#233;signer la Chine comme leur principal adversaire, cette derni&#232;re a r&#233;alis&#233; une avanc&#233;e technologique significative dans le domaine spatial. Deux satellites chinois ont en effet d&#233;montr&#233; des capacit&#233;s op&#233;rationnelles in&#233;dites en orbite, qui pourraient bien...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify tests more personalized, AI-powered &#8216;Prompted Playlists&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/spotify-tests-more-personalized-ai-powered-prompted-playlists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074868</guid>
      <description>The playlists can factor in world knowledge, go back to your listening history from day one, and be refreshed daily or weekly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Grinch Stole Modern Christmas</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-the-grinch-stole-modern-christmas-2000697520</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697520</guid>
      <description>From his storybook legacy to his modern-day anti-holiday influence, the Grinch has become an enduring face of the holidays&#8212;sincerely or otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best white elephant gifts worth fighting over for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-10-best-white-elephant-gifts-worth-fighting-over-for-2025-150516281.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">167b1092-71dd-42b0-b152-e8240159f089</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of competing ideas as to what a white elephant gift exchange really is. The origins of the term &#8220;white elephant&#8221; point to one definition: According to legend, the King of Siam would give a white elephant to courtiers who had upset them. It was a far more devious punishment than simply having them executed. The recipient had no choice but to simply thank the king for such an opulent gift, knowing that they likely could not afford the upkeep for such an animal. It would inevitably lead them to financial ruin.While that story is almost certainly untrue, it can inform one approach ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch New Zealand vs West Indies Test 2 on TVNZ+ &#8212; it's *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/new-zealand-vs-west-indies-test-2-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">h2tfxEyk9b9apwzEhrMns</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on how to watch New Zealand vs West Indies Test 2 on TVNZ+ for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world premieres and other hotness from The Game Awards 2025 Day of the Devs stream</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-world-premieres-and-other-hotness-from-the-game-awards-2025-day-of-the-devs-stream-200000447.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b31f45a5-f2c5-43c4-8442-3ad71203036e</guid>
      <description>You gotta love that post-Day of the Devs showcase feeling. The organization, founded by Double Fine Productions and iam8bit, consistently highlights top-tier games from independent developers across the globe, providing space for creators to share their stories in both online and in-person events. This year&#8217;s Day of the Devs: The Game Awards Digital Showcase was an hour-long celebration of 22 upcoming indie games, including six world premieres and three release date announcements.Settle in and bask in the afterglow with us:World PremieresVirtue and a Sledgehammer - DeconstructeamDeconstructeam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI Answers the Question, &#8216;What if Product Placement was Significantly Worse?&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xai-answers-the-question-what-if-product-placement-was-significantly-worse-2000697957</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697957</guid>
      <description>Sometimes innovation is two steps back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I couldn&amp;#8217;t fix it with iFixit&#8217;s AI FixBot</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/841252/ifixit-fixbot-hands-on-ai-chatbot</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T14:44:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841252</guid>
      <description>My classic Sony CRT television won't power on. My living room is chilly because my Mitsubishi heat pump isn't putting out enough hot air. I want my Japanese N64 to play US games, too, but I've been too busy to pop the hood. What if I had an AI companion to talk me through? iFixit [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview Energy wants to beam energy from space to existing solar farms</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/overview-energy-wants-to-beam-energy-from-space-to-existing-solar-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074859</guid>
      <description>The stealthy startup plans to use a network of satellites to harvest sunlight and send it to Earth using infrared lasers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus Game Catalog additions for December include Assassin's Creed Mirage</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/ps-plus-game-catalog-additions-for-december-include-assassins-creed-mirage-193731745.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b23e575-f459-4042-bda4-a1f5f53f9470</guid>
      <description>Sony just announced December's Game Catalog additions for PS Plus subscribers and it's a pretty decent lineup. All of these titles will be ready to play on December 16, except Skate Story which is already available.

Speaking of Skate Story, it's a really weird skateboarding sim that's set in a glass-covered world. The reviews have been positive, with many people praising the outlandish story, surreal locations and the satisfying trick mechanics. It's made by Sam Eng, who was behind the indie shooter Zarvot. This new game is only available for PS5 subscribers.

Assassin's Creed Mirage will be ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit is testing verification</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841879/reddit-verification-test</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T14:33:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841879</guid>
      <description>Reddit is starting to test verified profiles, the company announced today. Users who are verified as part of this "limited alpha test" will have a gray checkmark next to their username "across profiles, communities, feeds, post detail pages, and search results." For this "initial test," Reddit says it's "selected a group of public figures and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube TV Wants to Unbundle the Cable Package That Streamers Were Meant to Kill in the First Place</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youtube-tv-wants-to-unbundle-the-cable-package-that-streamers-were-meant-to-kill-in-the-first-place-2000697966</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697966</guid>
      <description>The video platform&#8217;s cable streaming service is introducing cheaper genre-specifying channel bundles next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only Core Ultra 265U laptop with a VGA port and a DVD writer just launched &#8212; and yes, it HAS to be in Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-only-core-ultra-265u-laptop-with-a-vga-port-and-a-dvd-writer-just-launched-and-yes-it-has-to-be-in-japan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UkAVPUjJ7MgpJbWfagxhtQ</guid>
      <description>Japan continues to welcome new laptops with retro features, and the NEC VersaPro VX-R blends modern Intel processors with aging connectors effectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sundance 2026 lineup will feature Charli XCX, Olivia Wilde, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458252/sundance-film-festival-2026-lineup</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T19:23:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458252/sundance-film-festival-2026-lineup</guid>
      <description>The 2026 festival kicks off on Jan. 22 and runs through Feb. 1.
Charli XCX&#160;is making a trip to the&#160;Sundance Film Festival&#160;in January. The pop singer-songwriter appears in three films premiering at the 2026 festival, including a mockumentary that she produced and stars in. Programmers on Wednesday unveiled a lineup of 90 feature films set for the festival&#8217;s&#160;last hurrah in Park City, Utah....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm Donor With a Cancer-Causing Gene Fathered at Least 197 Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sperm-donor-with-a-cancer-causing-gene-fathered-at-least-197-kids-2000697978</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697978</guid>
      <description>Because only part of the man's sperm carried the mutation, only the second round of genetic testing revealed the problem. By then, it was already too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Mova E40 Ultra : un aspirateur robot ultra complet &#224; un prix tout petit</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mova/2901181_test-du-mova-e40-ultra-un-aspirateur-robot-ultra-complet-a-un-prix-tout-petit</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mova/2901181_test-du-mova-e40-ultra-un-aspirateur-robot-ultra-complet-a-un-prix-tout-petit</guid>
      <description>
Les robots aspirateurs laveurs ont atteint un niveau d'efficacit&#233; impressionnant, tandis que leur tarif a eu tendance &#224; s'envoler, franchissant all&#232;grement la barre symbolique des 1 000 euros pour les mod&#232;les les plus aboutis. C&#8217;est l&#224; qu&#8217;intervient le Mova E40 Ultra, qui reprend les bases du nettoyage autonome en y ajoutant des fonctionnalit&#233;s avanc&#233;es, tout en affichant un positionnement tarifaire ultra-agressif pour se faire une place sur le podium.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many States Say They&#8217;ll Defy RFK Jr.&#8217;s Changes to Hepatitis B Vaccination</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/many-states-say-theyll-defy-rfk-jrs-changes-to-hepatitis-b-vaccination/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6931f49f4dde9e188d87dc69</guid>
      <description>Most Democratic-led states will continue to recommend the hepatitis B vaccine at birth, despite a CDC advisory panel&#8217;s vote against it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft issues patches for 56 security flaws - all 'important' severity or above</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/microsoft-issues-patches-for-56-security-flaws-all-important-severity-or-above</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vqT6MQpRjigNziqdbjrtC</guid>
      <description>Most are privilege escalation flaws, and one was exploited in the wild as a zero-day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 steps you can take right now to be safer online</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/12-steps-you-can-take-right-now-to-be-safer-online-130008335.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd157863-8848-4531-9463-d25adbb84ca8</guid>
      <description>There's a fundamental question you can ask of both the internet and real life: "How do I enjoy my time here without taking unnecessary risks?" In grass-touching meatspace, you can cut out processed foods, carry pepper spray and avoid skydiving without a partner.
But the best methods for staying safe online aren't as intuitive. The internet is a massive town square where people are constantly bellowing deeply personal facts about themselves. It's no surprise that it's become a breeding ground for scams, theft and other criminal activity.
Given the breadth of dangers, it may feel easier to throw...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSHA investigating new crane accident at SpaceX&#8217;s Starbase facility</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/osha-investigating-new-crane-accident-at-spacexs-starbase-facility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074210</guid>
      <description>A subcontractor says he was crushed by a metal support, breaking his hip, knee, and tibia. He's suing SpaceX and the construction company who employed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here Are All the Awesome-Sounding Genre Films Coming to Sundance 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sundance-2026-genre-films-2000697939</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697939</guid>
      <description>New films by Kogonada, Cathy Yan, Andrew Stanton, and more will be playing at the legendary festival next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Rubio bans Calibri font at State Department for being too DEI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/marco-rubio-bans-calibri-font-at-state-department-for-being-too-dei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074832</guid>
      <description>Calibri, which could make documents easier to read for the vision impaired, was apparently installed in 2023 by the department&#8217;s then-DEI office. Rubio&#8217;s memo has designated Times New Roman as his tenure&#8217;s official font, stating it will &#8220;restore decorum and professionalism&#8221; to documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department: Calibri font was a DEI hire</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/state-department-calibri-font-was-a-dei-hire-190454957.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932020b6-d08b-49f5-99c8-27f75cf56f05</guid>
      <description>The US Department of State is unwinding a 2023 decision to use san-serif Calibri font on all official communications and switching to Times New Roman instead, The New York Times reports. In a memo obtained by NYT titled "Return to Tradition: Times New Roman 14-Point Font Required for All Department Paper," Secretary of State Marco Rubio frames the change as a way to return professionalism to the State Department."Switching to Calibri achieved nothing except the degradation of the department&#8217;s official correspondence," Rubio said in the memo. That's because the font is "informal" and clashes wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August&amp;#8217;s founders are back with a smart front door</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/841622/doma-smart-door-august-smart-lock-makers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841622</guid>
      <description>It looks like someone may have finally done the smart door right. Doma Home, a new company from the creators of the August smart lock, has announced its first product: the Doma Intelligent Door. A motorized smart door that automatically opens as you approach and closes after you enter, the Doma door also features built-in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s 5K Studio Display is down to its lowest price in months</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/841647/apple-studio-display-monitor-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841647</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s Studio Display is an investment even while Amazon and Best Buy have the tilt-adjustable model marked down to $1,368 ($231 off) &#8212;&#160;its lowest price in several months. The 27-inch 5K monitor looks incredible, and has a built-in six-speaker audio system that impressed us in our tests. Its three microphone array and Apple&#8217;s optional voice [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not ready to say goodbye to Taylor Swift's The Eras Tour? You can live it one last time on Disney+ very soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/not-ready-to-say-goodbye-to-taylor-swifts-the-eras-tour-you-can-live-it-one-last-time-on-disney-very-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Vz5KZuTTXKhNxfhDWcabC7</guid>
      <description>Disney+ is coming in hot with two new Taylor Swift projects for diehards to stream this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These automatic doors are a glimpse of the new &#8216;intelligent&#8217; home era</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457860/these-automatic-doors-are-a-glimpse-of-the-new-intelligent-home-era</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457860/these-automatic-doors-are-a-glimpse-of-the-new-intelligent-home-era</guid>
      <description>The startup Doma is creating automatic doors and windows that could turn a house into a &#8216;living system.&#8217;
The automatic door has been reinvented. The home-focused tech startup Doma just announced its first product line: a set of residential doors capable of opening and closing automatically at the sight of an approaching homeowner. Packed with sensors, motors, and facial recognition technology, Doma Intelligent Doors bring automatic functionality and programmable controls to a home&#8217;s front door&#8212;all without clunky and unsightly equipment....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk says DOGE was &#8216;somewhat successful&#8217; and he wouldn&#8217;t do it again</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458246/elon-musk-doge-somewhat-successful-wouldnt-do-it-again</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458246/elon-musk-doge-somewhat-successful-wouldnt-do-it-again</guid>
      <description>Musk was speaking as a guest on the &#8216;Katie Miller Podcast.&#8217; 
Mega billionaire&#160;Elon Musk, in a friendly interview with his aide and conservative influencer Katie Miller, said his efforts leading the&#160;Department of Government Efficiency&#160;were only &#8220;somewhat successful&#8221; and he would not do it over again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;&#233;diteur vid&#233;o de Google Photos &#233;tait basique, il devient enfin utilisable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/google-apps/2905763_lediteur-video-de-google-photos-etait-basique-il-devient-enfin-utilisable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/google-apps/2905763_lediteur-video-de-google-photos-etait-basique-il-devient-enfin-utilisable</guid>
      <description>
C'est la fin du montage vid&#233;o basique chez Google. L'application Google Photos d&#233;ploie une refonte massive de ses outils d'&#233;dition. Google a d&#233;ploy&#233; une interface pens&#233;e pour le tactile, des mod&#232;les intelligents et une gestion du son digne de ce nom. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers tricked ChatGPT, Grok and Google into helping them install malware</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/hackers-tricked-chatgpt-grok-and-google-into-helping-them-install-malware-185711492.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">850dce1b-1d30-4561-98d5-9bffd28989c5</guid>
      <description>Ever since reporting earlier this year on how easy it is to trick an agentic browser, I've been following the intersections between modern AI and old-school scams. Now, there's a new convergence on the horizon: hackers are apparently using AI prompts to seed Google search results with dangerous commands. When executed by unknowing users, these commands prompt computers to give the hackers the access they need to install malware.
The warning comes by way of a recent report from detection-and-response firm Huntress. Here's how it works. First, the threat actor has a conversation with an AI assis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube TV to launch genre-based subscription plans in 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/youtube-tv-to-launch-genre-based-subscription-plans-in-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074820</guid>
      <description>The new packages will give consumers more flexibility over the content that they want to pay for. YouTube notes that users will still get access to popular features like&#160;unlimited DVR, multiview, key plays, and fantasy view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 essential stretches you should be doing every day, according to an expert</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/5-essential-stretches-you-should-be-doing-every-day-according-to-an-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZeKPkJbcEknNiLPtVMRgnj</guid>
      <description>Tight hips, sore shoulders or a stiff back don't have to be a daily reality. These expert-approved, no-fuss moves will help you boost mobility, reduce pain and smooth out any sign of &#8216;tech neck&#8217;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FrandroidOffreMoi des lunettes AR ultra pratiques de Xreal</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/lunettes-intelligentes/2905697_frandroidoffremoi-des-lunettes-ar-ultra-pratiques-de-xreal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/lunettes-intelligentes/2905697_frandroidoffremoi-des-lunettes-ar-ultra-pratiques-de-xreal</guid>
      <description>
Jour 10 du calendrier de l'Avent de Frandroid et il est temps de vous pr&#233;senter les lunettes Xreal One Pro (et un module Xreal Eye) qui sont &#224; gagner via notre concours.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta might charge for a future AI model</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841809/meta-avocado-ai-model-charge-open-source-mark-zuckerberg</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T13:46:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841809</guid>
      <description>Meta's next AI model could mark a change in its "open source" AI strategy that Mark Zuckerberg had called "the path forward." Currently, the company is working on a new AI model, code-named Avocado, that it might charge for access to, Bloomberg reports. Last year, Meta launched its open source (depending on who you ask, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Vital NASA Mars Orbiter Has Gone Dark</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-vital-nasa-mars-orbiter-has-gone-dark-2000697867</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697867</guid>
      <description>MAVEN has circled Mars for more than a decade, exploring the planet and relaying data from robots on the surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Outbreak Nears Grim Milestone as Hundreds Quarantine in South Carolina</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/u-s-measles-outbreak-nears-grim-milestone-as-hundreds-quarantine-in-south-carolina-2000697900</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697900</guid>
      <description>What happens when your country's public health system is run by anti-vaccine activists?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 rumored Samsung Galaxy S26 upgrades &#8211; from chipset surprises to magnetic charging</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/5-rumored-samsung-galaxy-s26-upgrades-from-chipset-surprises-to-magnetic-charging</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9sKoDLfPCLRWYhFwdX27si</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy S26 line is expected to debut in early 2026 &#8211; here are the biggest rumored upgrades we've heard so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette batterie Anker (20 000 mAh et 87 W) &#224; -30% est la solution ultime pour ne jamais tomber en panne</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2905385_cette-batterie-anker-20-000-mah-et-87-w-a-30-est-la-solution-ultime-pour-ne-jamais-tomber-en-panne</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2905385_cette-batterie-anker-20-000-mah-et-87-w-a-30-est-la-solution-ultime-pour-ne-jamais-tomber-en-panne</guid>
      <description>
Les batteries externes sont r&#233;put&#233;es pour &#234;tre des accessoires pratiques et salvateurs pour celles et ceux &#224; court de batterie sur leur smartphone. En ce moment, celle d'Anker avec une capacit&#233; de 20 000 mAh et une puissance de 87 W est propos&#233;e avec 30 % de r&#233;duction.&#160;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit is testing verification badges</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/reddit-is-testing-verification-badges/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074785</guid>
      <description>Verified users will actually be notable figures, not just people who paid for the checkmark.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
