<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:55:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AI models that simulate internal debate dramatically improve accuracy on complex tasks</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/ai-models-that-simulate-internal-debate-dramatically-improve-accuracy-on</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ZOpQtqzcdkyNR2LXBbvmu</guid>
      <description>A new study by Google suggests that advanced reasoning models achieve high performance by simulating multi-agent-like debates involving diverse perspectives, personality traits, and domain expertise.Their experiments demonstrate that this internal debate, which they dub &#8220;society of thought,&#8221; significantly improves model performance in complex reasoning and planning tasks. The researchers found that leading reasoning models such as DeepSeek-R1 and QwQ-32B, which are trained via reinforcement learning (RL), inherently develop this ability to engage in society of thought conversations without exp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music publishers sue Anthropic for $3 billion over &#8216;flagrant piracy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/music-publishers-sue-anthropic-for-3-billion-over-flagrant-piracy-185459358.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b36a85f5-9da9-43ed-a659-a3e7e91afb88</guid>
      <description>A group of music publishers led by Concord Music Group and Universal Music Group are suing Anthropic, according to a report by Reuters. The suit accuses the AI company of illegally downloading more than 20,000 copyrighted songs, including sheet music, lyrics and compositions.
These songs were then allegedly fed into the chatbot Claude for training purposes. There are some iconic tunes named by Universal in the suit, including tracks by The Rolling Stones, Neil Diamond and Elton John, among many others. Concord is an independent publisher that handles artists like Common, Killer Mike and Korn.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Favorite Open Earbuds Are $60 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/anker-soundcore-aeroclip-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697b97a22ba10bfd0b8ed14d</guid>
      <description>The Anker Soundcore Aeroclip boast great sound without cutting you off from the outside world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything is gambling now: the latest news on prediction markets like Polymarket and Kalshi</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868238/prediction-markets-polymarket-kalshi-robinhood</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T13:42:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=868238</guid>
      <description>Prediction markets will let you bet on just about anything, from how many tweets Elon Musk will post this week to the next president of the United States, with predictions sometimes showing shockingly (or suspiciously) spot-on accuracy. Polymarket&#8217;s CEO Shayne Copland has even claimed that prediction markets are &#8220;the most accurate thing we have as [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google's Project Genie lets you generate your own interactive worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/googles-project-genie-lets-you-generate-your-own-interactive-worlds-183646186.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f96776b3-9f86-4da3-a49e-ab792ecdecfc</guid>
      <description>This past summer, Google DeepMind debuted Genie 3. It&#8217;s what&#8217;s known as a world world, an AI system capable of generating images and reacting as the user moves through the environment the software is simulating. At the time, DeepMind positioned Genie 3 as a tool for training AI agents. Now, it&#8217;s making the model available to people outside of Google to try with Project Genie. To start, you&#8217;ll need Google&#8217;s $250 per month AI Ultra plan to check out Project Genie. You&#8217;ll also need to live in the US and be 18 years or older. At launch, Project Genie offers three different modes of interaction: Wo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top antivirus hacked to push out a malicious update - find out if you're affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/top-antivirus-hacked-to-push-out-a-malicious-update-find-out-if-youre-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">G2zkXwL53gbroCAY4DAGbW</guid>
      <description>Popular antivirus program eScan was used as a malware launchpad, deploying a backdoor to a small subset of users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple ach&#232;te pour 2 milliards une IA qui lit sur les visages</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/apple-achete-pour-2-milliards-une-ia-qui-lit-sur-les-visages.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323375</guid>
      <description>Contrairement &#224; d'autres grandes entreprises de la tech, Apple s'abstient de d&#233;penser sans compter pour acqu&#233;rir des soci&#233;t&#233;s. Mais il arrive de temps en temps que la firme &#224; la pomme signe des ch&#232;ques qui d&#233;passent le milliard de dollars pour s'offrir des technologies et des talents indispensables &#224; ses projets. C'est le cas aujourd'hui avec Q.AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Garmin Venu X1 is back down to its lowest-ever price, with 25% shaved off Garmin's slimmest smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/the-garmin-venu-x1-is-back-down-to-its-lowest-ever-price-with-25-percent-shaved-off-garmins-slimmest-smartwatch</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KXRmxifkwTnvcaV7i8zBEJ</guid>
      <description>Save a fat $200 on a slim Garmin Venu X1 &#8212; at this price, I'd get it over an Apple Watch Ultra 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major baby food company recalls &#8216;crawler snacks&#8217; nationwide. Watch out for these products</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91483255/major-baby-food-company-recalls-crawler-snacks-nationwide-watch-out-for-these-products</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T18:10:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91483255/major-baby-food-company-recalls-crawler-snacks-nationwide-watch-out-for-these-products</guid>
      <description>The cookie-like snacks are being yanked from shelves after it was discovered that they may contain soft plastic or pieces of paper. Here&#8217;s what to know.
Virginia-based Gerber Products Company is voluntarily recalling limited batches of Gerber Arrowroot Biscuits, a cookie-like snack meant for children 10 months or older. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Computer History Museum&#8217;s New Online Portal Is a Nerd&#8217;s Dream Come True</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-computer-history-museums-new-online-portal-is-a-nerds-dream-come-true-2000715455</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715455</guid>
      <description>It's the next best thing to an IRL visit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Pretends It&#8217;s a Military Force. Its Tactics Would Get Real Soldiers Killed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-pretends-its-a-military-force-its-tactics-would-get-real-soldiers-killed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69783a35fc0e68ec73ab4bea</guid>
      <description>WIRED asked an active military officer to break down immigration enforcement actions in Minneapolis and elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It&#8217;s an awesome robot. It looks like a human. People could be easily confused that it&#8217;s a human' &#8212; Tesla exec on why Optimus 3 is a game changer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/its-an-awesome-robot-it-looks-like-a-human-people-could-be-easily-confused-that-its-a-human-tesla-exec-on-why-optimus-3-is-a-game-changer</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27M57y96LeVkeVw7AGJUDX</guid>
      <description>Tesla makes big shift to focus on AI and robotics, promising a very human-like Optimus 3 by March &#8212; but what does that really mean?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#8217;re not alone in feeling unprepared for the AI boom</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480132/youre-not-alone-in-feeling-unprepared-for-the-ai-boom</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T18:01:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480132/youre-not-alone-in-feeling-unprepared-for-the-ai-boom</guid>
      <description>Even Dario Amodei, the co-founder and CEO of Anthropic, has been shaken by the increasing power of AI tools.
Journalist Ira Glass, who hosts the NPR show &#8220;This American Life,&#8221; is not a computer scientist. He doesn&#8217;t work at Google, Apple, or Nvidia. But he does have a great ear for useful phrases, and in 2024, he organized an entire episode around one that might resonate with anyone who feels blindsided by the pace of AI development: &#8220;Unprepared for what has already happened.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Absolute Batman&#8217; Is the Batman We Deserve in 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/absolute-batman-scott-snyder-nick-dragotta-dc-comics-2000714980</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714980</guid>
      <description>Now is the perfect time to dive into Scott Snyder and Nick Dragotta's generational DC Comics run in 'Absolute Batman.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napster&#8217;s back &#8212; and its new AI-first app wants you to help create the music, not just listen to it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/napsters-back-and-its-new-ai-first-app-wants-you-to-help-create-the-music-not-just-listen-to-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">y3kAERE78idymR462GRS5J</guid>
      <description>Napster is back and this time as an AI-powered music platform betting that the future of audio is co-creation, not passive listening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infostealers added Clawdbot to their target lists before most security teams knew it was running</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/security/clawdbot-exploits-48-hours-what-broke</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7zyuBaekbIiptJa4NpmVJg</guid>
      <description>Clawdbot's MCP implementation has no mandatory authentication, allows prompt injection, and grants shell access by design. Monday's VentureBeat article documented these architectural flaws. By Wednesday, security researchers had validated all three attack surfaces and found new ones.Commodity infostealers are already exploiting this. RedLine, Lumma, and Vidar added the AI agent to their target lists before most security teams knew it was running in their environments. Shruti Gandhi, general partner at Array VC, reported 7,922 attack attempts on her firm's Clawdbot instance.The reporting prompt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une &#171; tour &#187; de panneaux solaires va enfin alimenter une base lunaire</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/exploration-tour-panneaux-solaires-va-enfin-alimenter-base-lunaire-w2t8-130539/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/exploration-tour-panneaux-solaires-va-enfin-alimenter-base-lunaire-w2t8-130539/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Pour r&#233;pondre aux enjeux &#233;nerg&#233;tiques croissants des missions lunaires, la Nasa s'associe &#224; Astrobotic pour d&#233;velopper le VSAT-XL (Extra Large Vertical Solar Array Technology). Con&#231;u pour le p&#244;le sud de la Lune, ce syst&#232;me de panneaux solaires promet de r&#233;volutionner la production d'&#233;nergie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, start time, where to stream and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-start-time-where-to-stream-and-more-175759610.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

Drake Maye and the New England Patriots face Sam Darnold and the Seattle Seahawks at Super Bowl LX, which will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA this year. For those of you who don't have your calendars blocked off already, the game is on February 8, with kickoff scheduled for 6:30 p.m. ET.&#160;
Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the championship game will be broadcast on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. (Oh, and in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo robotaxis are now giving rides to and from San Francisco International Airport</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/29/waymo-sfo-airport-robotaxis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087816</guid>
      <description>Waymo's SFO win comes as the company faces criticism and concerns about safety in some of the cities it operates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Fire TV offers all you need if you want a basic 4K TV for under $300</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/this-fire-tv-offers-all-you-need-if-you-want-a-basic-4k-tv-for-under-usd300</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pn4TmbMfmXWX8wHv6NY2tG</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#8217;s 4K Fire TV hits an all-time low price</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maingear's latest retro gaming desktop takes you back to the Quake era</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/maingears-latest-retro-gaming-desktop-takes-you-back-to-the-quake-era-174958445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fbc11cf-f0e2-42ee-a70d-45393ba50331</guid>
      <description>Maingear is back with another nostalgia-fueled gaming PC. The Retro98 may look like it's made for playing Quake while you wait for The Phantom Menace trailer to drop. But on the inside, the beige box is powerful enough to slay today's most demanding AAA games. "You're not going to find this PC at your local Radio Shack," Maingear promises.If you're at least middle-aged, the Retro98's exterior is instantly familiar. The hand-built tower includes an LED fan-speed display, a working turbo button and a power-lockout key. Sticking with the nostalgic motif, its front I/O is hidden behind the Maingea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Working on Social Media Network That Could Require Creepy Eye Scans: Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-working-on-social-media-network-that-could-require-creepy-eye-scans-report-2000715588</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715588</guid>
      <description>Signing up for the bot-free platform will reportedly require submitting some biometric data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify has a group messaging feature now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/spotify-has-a-group-messaging-feature-now-173734450.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20844f9b-b9cf-4b21-a2cf-399cfdcb579f</guid>
      <description>Spotify is adding group chats to the messaging service it premiered last year. In an addendum to the original blog post introducing Messages, the company announced that users can initiate chats with up to 10 of their friends to share the podcasts, playlists and songs they are listening to.
The in-app messaging feature, which was released last August, works to keep users on the app instead of navigating to another platform to share content with friends. Since its introduction, Spotify has added functionality bit by bit. Earlier this month, the company added the ability to share what you're list...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify&amp;#8217;s new group chats share music with everyone in your circle</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/870288/spotify-group-chats-direct-messaging-expansion</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T12:36:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870288</guid>
      <description>Spotify is expanding its in-app messaging feature with group chats. Now you can add up to 10 friends and family members to your discussion about your new favorite song, podcast, or audiobook, as reported earlier by TechCrunch. The music streaming platform launched direct messaging last August, allowing you to share what you're listening to without [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I reclaimed 5+ hours a week &#8212; my 12 essential productivity tools of 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/shop/pro/how-i-reclaimed-5-hours-a-week-my-12-essential-productivity-tools</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffwuy3FK5fmXoZg64VhRA9</guid>
      <description>Spare time feels like a luxury in 2026, I used these productivity tools to reclaim hours every week. Now I'm not sure what to do with that time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graines, capteurs, plats fran&#231;ais : le contenu surprenant des bagages de Sophie Adenot pour la Station spatiale</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sophie-adenot-graines-capteurs-plats-francais-contenu-surprenant-bagages-sophie-adenot-station-spatiale-130273/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:29:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sophie-adenot-graines-capteurs-plats-francais-contenu-surprenant-bagages-sophie-adenot-station-spatiale-130273/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Que met-on dans sa valise quand on part huit mois dans l&#8217;espace ? Pour sa toute premi&#232;re mission &#224; bord de l&#8217;ISS, Sophie Adenot, premi&#232;re femme astronaute fran&#231;aise depuis Claudie Haigner&#233;, n&#8217;emportera pas seulement des effets personnels. Graines &#224; faire germer, capteurs m&#233;dicaux, exp&#233;riences de...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I built marshmallow castles in Google&#8217;s new AI world generator</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/29/i-built-marshmallow-castles-in-googles-new-ai-world-generator-project-genie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087840</guid>
      <description>Starting Thursday, Google AI Ultra subscribers in the U.S. can play around with Project Genie, which is powered by a combination of Google&#8217;s latest world model Genie 3, its image generation model Nano Banana Pro, and Gemini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Most Distant Galaxy Ever Seen Barely Makes Any Sense</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-age-of-the-most-distant-galaxy-ever-seen-barely-makes-any-sense-2000715503</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715503</guid>
      <description>The light from MoM-z14 galaxy has been traveling through space for about 13.5 billion years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les SSD vont co&#251;ter bien plus cher : cette promo Amazon est probablement la meilleure &#224; saisir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2960523_les-ssd-vont-couter-bien-plus-cher-cette-promo-amazon-est-probablement-la-meilleure-a-saisir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2960523_les-ssd-vont-couter-bien-plus-cher-cette-promo-amazon-est-probablement-la-meilleure-a-saisir</guid>
      <description>
&#192; 80 euros seulement, ce SSD Transcend MTS820S au format M.2 s&#8217;impose comme une&#160;belle&#160;opportunit&#233; pour doper un PC portable sans se ruiner. Une promotion d&#8217;autant plus int&#233;ressante que les SSD font partie des prochains composants touch&#233;s par la p&#233;nurie, ce qui laisse pr&#233;sager une remont&#233;e des prix dans les mois &#224; venir.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung veut remplacer le papier avec cet &#233;cran en plancton</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2960595_samsung-veut-remplacer-le-papier-avec-cet-ecran-en-plancton</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2960595_samsung-veut-remplacer-le-papier-avec-cet-ecran-en-plancton</guid>
      <description>
Samsung vient de pr&#233;senter un produit pour le moins insolite : un &#233;cran Color E-Paper de 13 pouces. Sa particularit&#233; ? Il abandonne le plastique traditionnel pour une bio-r&#233;sine issue du phytoplancton.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This AI startup wants to be your virtual &#8216;computer for business&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482690/adapt-ai-cloud-systems</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T17:18:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482690/adapt-ai-cloud-systems</guid>
      <description>Adapt&#8217;s&#160;AI can pull data from a wide range of cloud systems, writing code to crunch numbers and automate tedious tasks.&#160;
A startup called&#160;Adapt&#160;is betting that it can be an AI hub connecting other software tools to help answer questions and get things done.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forfait Free 2&#8364; : l&#8217;option illimit&#233;e devient enfin la norme (et c&#8217;est gratuit)</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/forfait-free-2e-loption-illimitee-devient-enfin-la-norme-et-cest-gratuit.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323292</guid>
      <description>Free Mobile revoit sa copie pour son offre historique. Le forfait 2&#8364; int&#232;gre d&#233;sormais par d&#233;faut l'option booster 1 Go et les appels illimit&#233;s, sans surco&#251;t. Une modernisation n&#233;cessaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAM is the new gold &#8211; why Costco is pulling memory from display PCs to halt a shoplifting surge</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/ram-is-the-new-gold-why-costco-is-pulling-memory-from-display-pcs-to-halt-a-shoplifting-surge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hus7mhXdmgFXvmeH9iyEMo</guid>
      <description>It used to be GPUs that might be shoplifted from display PCs on retailer shelves &#8211; now it's high-end RAM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 Is About to Be a Blockbuster Year for Smart Glasses</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/2026-is-about-to-be-a-blockbuster-year-for-smart-glasses-2000715511</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715511</guid>
      <description>Heated competition, legal drama, and the future of tech on the line? Start writing the movie now, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An inventory boomerang just hit the housing market</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91483441/housing-market-inventory-boomerang-just-hit</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T17:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91483441/housing-market-inventory-boomerang-just-hit</guid>
      <description>Last year&#8217;s 10-year high in delistings is turning into a relistings jump. Here&#8217;s what that means for homebuyers.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to dial down the AI slop on platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91483260/ai-content-slop-pinterest-tiktok-deezer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T17:10:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91483260/ai-content-slop-pinterest-tiktok-deezer</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s a guide on using app settings and tools to minimize the amount of AI content you see.
AI&#160;slop&#160;seems to be everywhere. Low-quality digital content made with artificial intelligence has flooded our feeds, screens and speakers. Is there anything we can do about it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Moltbot AI assistant just spreads malware - so AI fans, watch out for scams</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/fake-moltbot-ai-assistant-just-spreads-malware-so-ai-fans-watch-out-for-scams</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6zemN2xqba5n8zwohqAxi5</guid>
      <description>Crooks are impersonating popular Moltbot AI assistant to deploy trojan malware, so be on your guard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heated Rivalry fleece is coming &#8212; we all begged for Canada to release the fleece and theyre delivering</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-29-heated-rivalry-fleece</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00fg9JWA2sAvbqjK7S6lMr9</guid>
      <description>Sign up for alerts on the official 'Heated Rivalry' fleece coming soon from Province of Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it finally happening? Ubisoft appears to respond to new Assassin's Creed: Black Flag remake leak with everyone's favorite GTA meme</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/is-it-finally-happening-ubisoft-appears-to-respond-to-new-assassins-creed-black-flag-remake-leak-with-everyones-favorite-gta-meme</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DLvZhHXXvfxaWbsFgde8rn</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft has finally acknowledged the ongoing Assassin's Creed: Black Flag remake rumors with a GTA meme after another leak appeared online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 genius Amazon tech finds under $40 that will make everyday life easier &#8212; shop deals starting at just $7.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/15-genius-amazon-tech-finds-under-usd40-that-will-make-everyday-life-easier-shop-deals-starting-at-just-usd7-99</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fXxXkm9BzZATcqopwSHtRc</guid>
      <description>I'm rounding up my 15 favorite cheap tech gadgets from Amazon that will make your everyday life easier without breaking the bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop paying full price for Photoshop: Adobe slashes Creative Cloud Pro subscriptions by 40% for your first year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/stop-paying-full-price-for-photoshop-adobe-slashes-creative-cloud-pro-subscriptions-by-40-percent-for-your-first-year</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RdjfwjWY2VMBCGsuy5ooSj</guid>
      <description>If you're a creator, these Adobe deals are worth definitely checking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Inception&#8217; and &#8216;The Incredibles&#8217; Among 2025&#8217;s National Film Registry Inductees</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/national-film-registry-library-of-congress-inception-the-thing-2000715469</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715469</guid>
      <description>The Library of Congress deemed 'Inception', the original 'Karate Kid', and 'The Thing' worth preserving for their 'cultural, historic, or aesthetic importance.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI Toy Exposed 50,000 Logs of Its Chats With Kids to Anyone With a Gmail Account</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/an-ai-toy-exposed-50000-logs-of-its-chats-with-kids-to-anyone-with-a-gmail-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6978fda85780318e8dc1728c</guid>
      <description>AI chat toy company Bondu left its web console almost entirely unprotected. Researchers who accessed it found nearly all the conversations children had with the company&#8217;s stuffed animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of developers think gen AI is bad for the gaming industry</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/869386/ai-game-development-gdc-survey</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869386</guid>
      <description>While generative AI is being adopted at various levels of game development, a new survey suggests that developers increasingly think the technology is bad for the industry. According to the most recent survey from the Game Developers Conference, 52 percent of respondents said that gen AI is having a "negative" impact on the games industry, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s AI helped me make bad Nintendo knockoffs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869726/google-ai-project-genie-3-world-model-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869726</guid>
      <description>This week, a new generative AI tool from Google let me create bad knockoffs of 3D Nintendo worlds. Check out my version of something like Super Mario 64: I didn't like Metroid Prime 4: Beyond, but it's better than my version of a Metroid Prime experience: Or how about my take on The Legend of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is working to rebuild trust in Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/870045/microsoft-windows-11-issues-rebuilding-trust-notepad</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870045</guid>
      <description>Windows is in a weird spot. In its 40-year history, the operating system has weathered its fair share of missteps, but Windows 11 is testing the patience of its users in new ways. Persistent bugs, performance issues, intrusive prompts, ads, and bloatware have eroded the core Windows experience. Early system requirement decisions have also damaged [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo is finally starting passenger trips at SFO &#8212;&#160;but not to the terminals</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/870102/waymo-sfo-passenger-trip-approval-airport</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870102</guid>
      <description>Waymo has finally broken through its SFO logjam. The company announced today that it will start offering robotaxi rides to a select group of passengers traveling to and from the San Francisco International Airport, a major step in Waymo's effort to increase its footprint in the Bay Area. The company plans on gradually growing the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI face swapping video could be a bonanza for scammers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482342/ai-face-swapping-tim-cook-trump-minneapolis-pretti-altman</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482342/ai-face-swapping-tim-cook-trump-minneapolis-pretti-altman</guid>
      <description>A new class of video generation tools could fool phishing victims, especially the elderly, into divulging information or sending money.&#160;
Welcome to AI Decoded, Fast Company&#8217;s weekly newsletter that breaks down the most important news in the world of AI. I&#8217;m Mark Sullivan, a senior writer at Fast Company,covering emerging tech, AI, and tech policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big Starbucks Rewards overhaul is coming. What it means for your stars</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91483407/a-big-starbucks-rewards-overhaul-is-coming-what-it-means-for-your-stars</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-29T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91483407/a-big-starbucks-rewards-overhaul-is-coming-what-it-means-for-your-stars</guid>
      <description>The coffee chain is reintroducing three loyalty tiers and new perks as part of its turnaround strategy.
Coffee giant Starbucks just announced its rewards program is about to get a major overhaul.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une sym&#233;trie trop parfaite pour &#234;tre naturelle ? Ce cercle g&#233;ant d&#233;range la science</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-symetrie-trop-parfaite-etre-naturelle-ce-cercle-geant-derange-science-w2t8-130536/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-symetrie-trop-parfaite-etre-naturelle-ce-cercle-geant-derange-science-w2t8-130536/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Cet objet vient d&#8217;&#234;tre d&#233;couvert dans les donn&#233;es de&#160;l&#8217;Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder (Askap). Et sa forme presque parfaitement sph&#233;rique d&#233;route les astronomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelle est la meilleure voiture Tesla &#224; choisir en 2026&#8201;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-survoltes/guides-dachat-voitures/1333657_quelle-est-la-meilleure-tesla-a-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-survoltes/guides-dachat-voitures/1333657_quelle-est-la-meilleure-tesla-a-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Si la marque Tesla vous attire, mais que vous avez du mal &#224; vous y retrouver entre les diff&#233;rentes versions disponibles, ce guide est fait pour vous. D&#233;couvrez les diff&#233;rents v&#233;hicules de la gamme pour y voir plus clair et d&#233;terminer quelle Tesla choisir.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver : les 50 meilleures offres &#224; ne surtout pas rater</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_les-meilleures-offres-tombent-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-voici-le-top-25</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_les-meilleures-offres-tombent-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-voici-le-top-25</guid>
      <description>
Il ne faut pas se le cacher, la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes est souvent le moment o&#249; l'on trouve les meilleures offres, car les e-commer&#231;ants comme Amazon, Fnac, Darty ou encore Boulanger veulent &#233;couler les derniers stocks. Avec cet article, vous serez s&#251;rs de ne manquer aucun deal Tech int&#233;ressant. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shit&#8217;s Getting Real: NASA Aims for Artemis 2 Fueling Test on Saturday</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/shits-getting-real-nasa-aims-for-artemis-2-fueling-test-on-saturday-2000715590</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715590</guid>
      <description>The agency has bumped up the wet dress rehearsal to increase its chances of launching within the February window, but could an Arctic blast interfere?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
