<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:38:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi est de retour avec ses &#233;couteurs sans fil en promo &#224; moins de 10 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2352522_xiaomi-est-de-retour-avec-ses-ecouteurs-sans-fil-en-promo-a-moins-de-10-euros</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2352522_xiaomi-est-de-retour-avec-ses-ecouteurs-sans-fil-en-promo-a-moins-de-10-euros</guid>
      <description>
Xiaomi propose des produits audio de qualit&#233;, avec m&#234;me des r&#233;f&#233;rences &#224; petit prix, comme les Redmi Buds 6 Play. Un mod&#232;le sans pr&#233;tention qui offre tout de m&#234;me de bonnes performances et qui co&#251;te seulement 9,99 euros sur le site officiel de la marque. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enfin un bouclier anti-ondes qui marche sur les fr&#233;quences Wi-Fi et 5G &#224; 99,97 %</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/2919521_enfin-un-bouclier-anti-ondes-qui-marche-sur-les-frequences-wi-fi-et-5g-a-9997</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/2919521_enfin-un-bouclier-anti-ondes-qui-marche-sur-les-frequences-wi-fi-et-5g-a-9997</guid>
      <description>
Vous voyez ces autocollants &#171; anti-ondes &#187; vendus une fortune sur Internet qui ne servent strictement &#224; rien ? C'est ironique, car la science vient de produire l'exact oppos&#233;. Des chercheurs ont mis au point un film transparent capable de bloquer 99,97 % des rayonnements. Sauf que lui, il repose sur de la vraie physique, pas sur de la magie quantique.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's iOS 26.3 will introduce proximity pairing to third-party devices in the EU</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/apples-ios-263-will-introduce-proximity-pairing-to-third-party-devices-in-the-eu-133037696.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aae1a62-b390-4355-a79a-87e2749999c1</guid>
      <description>Apple is making it a little easier to use third-party devices with iPhones in order to comply with Europe's Digital Market Act (DMA), MacRumors reported. For iOS 26.3, Apple's devices will support third-party proximity pairing and notifications in Europe only, according to the latest beta notes. That will make it a bit easier to connect devices like Sony headphones or receive notifications from an iPhone on Wear OS smartwatches &#8212; provided manufacturers support the new feature.&#160;
"The DMA creates new opportunities for developers to bring to market innovative products and services in Europe," an ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI broke the smart home in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/845958/ai-smart-home-broken</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845958</guid>
      <description>This morning, I asked my Alexa-enabled Bosch coffee machine to make me a coffee. Instead of running my routine, it told me it couldn't do that. Ever since I upgraded to Alexa Plus, Amazon's generative-AI-powered voice assistant, it has failed to reliably run my coffee routine, coming up with a different excuse almost every time [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All I want for Christmas is NOT a scam &#8211; Surfshark shares some tips to avoid digital threats during the festive season</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/all-i-want-for-christmas-is-not-a-scam-surfshark-shares-some-tips-to-avoid-digital-threats-during-the-festive-season</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">L5smQH7hvcD3gE5KrjNwm6</guid>
      <description>Scammers don't go on holiday for Christmas, quite the opposite. This is why Surfshark shares a mini guide to help you protect your digital assets during the festive season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les drones fabriqu&#233;s en Chine ne pourront plus &#234;tre vendus aux &#201;tats-Unis</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/les-drones-fabriques-en-chine-ne-pourront-plus-etre-vendus-aux-etats-unis.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316766</guid>
      <description>Apr&#232;s les semi-conducteurs, les drones ? Ces appareils strat&#233;giques, tr&#232;s utilis&#233;s outre Atlantique, et en majorit&#233; fabriqu&#233;s en Chine, viennent de faire l'objet d'une nouvelle interdiction de vente aux &#201;tats-Unis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Technics earbuds are the best I&#8217;ve tried &#8211; and they&#8217;re cheaper than ever before</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/these-technics-earbuds-are-the-best-ive-tried-and-theyre-cheaper-than-ever-before</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YuJdUQJWTG4Ax3fxCiwDhD</guid>
      <description>This is the best price I've ever seen on these sensational Technics earbuds &#8211; and, trust me, they&#8217;re worth every cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware attack on Romanian water agency hits over a thousand systems</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/ransomware-attack-on-romanian-water-agency-hits-over-a-thousand-systems</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hWAvY22wEnmzCW9NY8fcMZ</guid>
      <description>An unknown threat actor wreaked some serious havoc but operations are continuing unabated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 preview provides more details on how AI agents will work &#8211; but this remains a controversial path for Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/windows-11-preview-provides-more-details-on-how-ai-agents-will-work-but-this-remains-a-controversial-path-for-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R4BSjeeKnyCxrqM4T5dwMh</guid>
      <description>We know more about how AI agents will work thanks to the latest Windows 11 preview &#8211; but not everyone's happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faut-il vraiment conserver les lois de Newton pour expliquer les galaxies avec de la mati&#232;re noire ? Partie II</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-faut-il-vraiment-conserver-lois-newton-expliquer-galaxies-matiere-noire-partie-ii-128117/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-faut-il-vraiment-conserver-lois-newton-expliquer-galaxies-matiere-noire-partie-ii-128117/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Depuis presque 40 ans, les astrophysiciens d&#233;battent pour savoir si l'on doit introduire de nouvelles particules, celles de la fameuse mati&#232;re noire, ou au contraire modifier la physique de Newton pour expliquer les observations concernant les galaxies, les amas de galaxies et la plus vieille...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godzilla Has Descended Upon Haneda Airport</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/godzilla-statue-haneda-airport-2000702771</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702771</guid>
      <description>The previously teased 40-meter-long, 9-meter-tall statue of Godzilla has begun gracing/delightfully terrorizing Haneda's main international terminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts cards to give this holiday season: Amazon, Apple, Best Buy and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-gifts-cards-to-give-this-holiday-season-amazon-apple-best-buy-and-others-110032592.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb96c933-efa4-4ca0-a9b6-2c7e09e5110a</guid>
      <description>This late in the game, it&#8217;s not possible to ship gifts to friends and family and have them arrive before the holidays. But that&#8217;s ok because it&#8217;s never been easier to give a digital gift that will arrive basically whenever you want it to. If you&#8217;re looking for more creative digital gift ideas, we&#8217;ve got you covered. But right now, you may just be looking for the best gift card ideas that you can buy online and digitally send to the people you love. We&#8217;ve got you covered: these are the best gift cards to send as last-minute gifts this year.
Best gift cards to give for the holidays













...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laptop Buying Guide (2025): How to Choose the Right PC (Step-by-Step Guide)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-buy-the-right-laptop-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">602fdcf4ff6e0ab6e8be9319</guid>
      <description>Shopping for a laptop can be infuriating. Here&#8217;s how to sift through the acronyms, storage options, and extra features to find the best one for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The year the government broke</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/845838/2025-year-end-government-doge</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845838</guid>
      <description>The first crack showed right before Inauguration Day. The year before, Congress had overwhelmingly passed a bill banning TikTok unless it broke ties with its Chinese parent company. The Supreme Court unanimously upheld it, and it was clear what needed to happen next: either the president could give TikTok another 90 days to complete a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 was the year Xbox died</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/2025-was-the-year-xbox-died-130000467.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c62c8801-94a4-4e20-9f88-79ae7035ca71</guid>
      <description>Want to see a dead body? I present to you the Xbox. After a subdued launch at the height of the COVID pandemic in 2020, the Xbox Series X quickly lost the fight against the PlayStation 5. Microsoft simply couldn't deliver enough compelling games, despite some huge acquisitions, while Sony leaned on its goodwill from the PS4 era and a handful of desirable exclusives. As prices rose due to supply chain issues and the Trump administration's volatile tariff scheme, there was even less of a reason to get an Xbox (even the cheaper Series S). When I re-reviewed the Series X last year, it was clear th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon sells an MSI 27-inch monitor for &#163;69 &#8212; brand new Pro display has speakers and even a free HDMI cable</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amazon-sells-an-msi-27-inch-monitor-for-gbp69-brand-new-pro-display-has-speakers-and-even-a-free-hdmi-cable</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GjasNtz7kHrSaC9C7jHZDn</guid>
      <description>You can buy a brand new MSI 27-inch monitor for &#163;69 on Amazon right now with built-in speakers and a free HDMI cable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple fined $116 million over app privacy prompts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849528/apple-italy-antitrust-fine-att-app-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T07:46:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849528</guid>
      <description>Apple has been fined more than &#8364;98 million (about $116 million) by Italy's antitrust regulator over the "excessively burdensome" privacy rules it imposes on third-party apps. The Italian Competition Authority (AGCM) says that Apple abused its dominant app store market position by burdening developers with "disproportionate" terms around data collection that exceed privacy law requirements, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How solopreneurs can break free from a corporate mindset</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462663/how-solopreneurs-can-break-free-from-corporate-mindset</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T12:37:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462663/how-solopreneurs-can-break-free-from-corporate-mindset</guid>
      <description>The secrets to achieving the autonomy you were after in the first place.
You quit the 9-to-5 to have more control over your time. You wanted flexibility, autonomy, and the freedom to structure your days around your life instead of someone else&#8217;s schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Someone&#8217;s made a USB-C version of the iPod Classic, complete with clickwheel &#8212; and it&#8217;s extremely cheap</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/portable-media-players/someones-made-a-usb-c-version-of-the-ipod-classic-complete-with-clickwheel-and-its-extremely-cheap</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uCRM9XX7tuTpiKdn78snLC</guid>
      <description>This budget MP3 player is an Apple lawsuit waiting to happen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Everything we're expecting from tech's biggest conference in January</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-everything-were-expecting-from-techs-biggest-conference-in-january-120000106.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2645ab40-20b1-4cf0-bdcf-9e9656c79061</guid>
      <description>As we hurtle towards the end of the year, the shadow of CES hovers on the horizon. Tech&#8217;s biggest annual conference is starting in just under two weeks, and we already know some of the products and announcements that could be in store. The CES 2026 show floor is officially open from January 6 through 9, but the fun kicks off with events on Sunday January 4 and a host of press conferences on Monday. As always, product demos, announcements and networking will be happening at the Las Vegas Convention Center and other hotels all over the city. As usual, Engadget will be covering the event in-perso...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huawei Band 10 : ce bracelet connect&#233; abordable de 2025 chute d&#233;j&#224; sous les 30 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2919299_huawei-band-10-ce-bracelet-connecte-abordable-de-2025-chute-deja-sous-les-30-e</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2919299_huawei-band-10-ce-bracelet-connecte-abordable-de-2025-chute-deja-sous-les-30-e</guid>
      <description>
Gr&#226;ce &#224; ses cent modes d'entra&#238;nement, le Huawei Band 10 pourra vous accompagner lors de toutes vos s&#233;ances de sport. Vendu &#224; 49,99 euros lors de sa sortie, il passe &#224; 29,99 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre chez Amazon
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battlefield 6 fans are furious after spotting apparent AI 'slop' for sale in the game's store</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/battlefield-6-fans-are-furious-after-spotting-apparent-ai-slop-for-sale-in-the-games-store</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8NPjKy36DEVKXK6yLXG7rH</guid>
      <description>Battlefield 6 players are accusing EA of selling alleged AI-generated content in the game's store, despite the VP general manager at DICE previously stating that the game wouldn't feature any generative AI content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordProtect adds fraud monitoring tool to help protect users from scams</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/nordprotect-adds-fraud-monitoring-tool-to-help-protect-users-from-scams</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8BYeosWW9AMxogE3rnX6ki</guid>
      <description>NordProtect has been upgraded from "sufficient" to "outstanding," but new tools remain only available to US customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Morning After: The best games of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/the-morning-after-engadget-newsletter-121545111.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48bbbf33-92ac-4979-98a2-f1d7bbfff693</guid>
      <description>As many of us hunker down for the holidays, you might want to tackle some of the best games we&#8217;ve seen this year: the long-time-coming Silksong, the critically acclaimed (and sumptuous) Expedition 33 and the bizarre world of Baby Steps.
Engadget
Not to mention the Switch 2, which is slowly building out its own exclusive library with Metroid Prime 4 and Donkey Kong Bananza. Rare for me, this year, I&#8217;ve played many of the new games we&#8217;ve picked. Brag. I&#8217;d recommend both Dispatch and Blue Prince &#8212; I still haven&#8217;t completed the latter, but, yes, I&#8217;ve unlocked the secret elevator.
And if you don&#8217;t ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed the Oppo Find X9 Pro, and it&#8217;s the maximized flagship for Android lovers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/oppo-phones/oppo-find-x9-pro-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">quwQWWu5AQSE2QtPbqhCTf</guid>
      <description>The Oppo Find X9 Pro is a maxed-out pro camera phone that will happily wear its inspirations on its sleeve if it means delivering a fantastic flagship experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to set up an Apple Watch for a child</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/how-to-set-up-an-apple-watch-for-a-child-120051230.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">046928ca-a8c5-4525-af35-7734680aa389</guid>
      <description>Giving a child an Apple Watch can offer extra peace of mind and tools that promote independence in a controlled way. Apple&#8217;s Family Setup feature makes it possible for a kid to use an Apple Watch without owning an iPhone, and the feature set has expanded thanks to recent watchOS updates. It supports communication controls, location tools, Schooltime limits and privacy protections that allow a parent or guardian to manage how the device is used throughout the day.
The setup process begins with creating or signing in with a child&#8217;s Apple ID. It continues with adding them to your Family Sharing g...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Five Nights at Freddy&#8217;s 2&#8217; Director Emma Tammi Explains How Abby Anchors the Sequel</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/five-nights-at-freddys-2-director-emma-tammi-explains-how-abby-anchors-the-sequel-2000702738</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702738</guid>
      <description>Young actor Piper Rubio gets a special focus in the hit horror video game adaptation, which you can now rent or buy on digital platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mint Mobile&#8217;s MINTernet Powered by T-Mobile at $30/Month Is Now a Budget 5G Home Internet Option</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mint-mobiles-minternet-powered-by-t-mobile-at-30-month-is-now-a-budget-5g-home-internet-option-2000702393</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702393</guid>
      <description>The folks who brought you unlimited 5G data on the world's largest cellular network are at it again, this time with huge savings on premium, unlimited home internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iBuyPower RDY Slate 9MP R01 Gaming PC Review: Great Value</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/review/ibuypower-rdy-slate-9mp-r01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6927228e710160abd3899e2e</guid>
      <description>iBuyPower&#8217;s prebuilt gaming desktop tries some new tricks but comes with a few flaws.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
