<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:24:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>You can&#8217;t trust your eyes to tell you what&#8217;s real anymore, says the head of Instagram</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852124/adam-mosseri-ai-images-video-instagram</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T17:54:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852124</guid>
      <description>Instagram boss Adam Mosseri is closing out 2025 with a 20-images-deep dive into what a new era of "infinite synthetic content" means as it all becomes harder and harder to distinguish from reality, and the old, more personal Instagram feed that he says has been "dead" for years. Last year, The Verge's Sarah Jeong wrote [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 reasons why this Samsung vacuum is my #1 home gadget of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/5-reasons-why-this-samsung-vacuum-is-my-1-home-gadget-of-the-year</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GZajgxeTHyVKiNFBS54gcW</guid>
      <description>Beautiful and functional &#8211; what more could you want from a vacuum?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porsche recalls over 173,000 vehicles over rearview camera image</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468144/porsche-recall-173000-vehicles-rearview-camera-image</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468144/porsche-recall-173000-vehicles-rearview-camera-image</guid>
      <description>Porsche dealers will update the driver assistance software, free of charge.
Porsche is recalling 173,538 vehicles in the U.S. as the rearview camera image may not display when the vehicle is placed in reverse, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build safe danger and make teams come alive</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457680/safe-danger-teams-come-alive</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457680/safe-danger-teams-come-alive</guid>
      <description>Safe Danger creates the space for everyone to engage.
Below, Ben Swire shares five key insights from his new book,&#160;Safe Danger: An Unexpected Method for Sparking Connection, Finding Purpose, and Inspiring Innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the dollar closes out a dismal year, here&#8217;s what to expect in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468141/dollar-dismal-year-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468141/dollar-dismal-year-2025</guid>
      <description>Longer-term views for dollar weakness notwithstanding, a near-term rebound for the dollar is not to be ruled out, investors cautioned.
A dismal year for the U.S. dollar is ending with signs of stabilization, but many investors believe the currency&#8217;s decline will resume next year as global growth picks up and the Fed eases further.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
