<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:34:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A surprise God of War prequel is out on the PS5 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/878375/god-of-war-sons-of-sparta-trilogy-sony-playstation-ps5-release-date-trailer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T18:30:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878375</guid>
      <description>To close out its February 2026 State of Play presentation, Sony revealed God of War Sons of Sparta, a new prequel 2D side scroller in the God of War franchise, and announced that it's out right now on PlayStation 5. "God of War Sons of Sparta is a 2D action platformer with a canon story [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saturn&#8217;s Rings Came From a Two-Moon Collision About 100 Million Years Ago, Study Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/saturns-rings-came-from-a-two-moon-collision-about-100-million-years-ago-study-says-2000721450</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721450</guid>
      <description>The collision could also be responsible for Saturn&#8217;s iconic rings, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid disappointing earnings, Pinterest claims it sees more searches than ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/amid-disappointing-earnings-pinterest-claims-it-sees-more-searches-than-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092700</guid>
      <description>Pinterest's stock tumbles after an earnings miss, with higher-than-expected usage its only bright spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PS Plus Game Catalog additions for February include Marvel&#8217;s Spider-Man 2</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/the-ps-plus-game-catalog-additions-for-february-include-marvels-spider-man-2-232459779.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">094dc353-2489-4c98-a413-3603f46cb004</guid>
      <description>During its State of Play livestream on Thursday, Sony revealed the first PlayStation Plus Game Catalog addition for February and it's a doozy. Marvel&#8217;s Spider-Man 2 will finally websling its way onto the Game Catalog on February 17.
Marvel&#8217;s Spider-Man 2 was released in October 2023, and Insomniac's third Spidey game is the the best of the bunch. You can play as both Peter Parker and his prot&#233;g&#233; Miles Morales. Each Spidey has his own skill tree and moveset to master.
Traversing New York (with a lot more of it explorable than in previous entries) has never felt better thanks to the addition of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM&#160;will hire your entry-level talent in the age of AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/ibm-will-hire-your-entry-level-talent-in-the-age-of-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092703</guid>
      <description>IBM plans to triple its entry-level hiring in the U.S. in 2026 but these jobs will have different tasks than in previous years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Asus Zenbook S 16 Is $500 Off and Has Never Been This Cheap</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/asus-zenbook-s-16-presidents-day-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698e405339d1817ca4f084ac</guid>
      <description>The Asus Zenbook S 16 was a favorite of ours last year, but the price was always too high. Now it has dropped to $1,000, and it&#8217;s a total steal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian was saved by software in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/rivian-was-saved-by-software-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092681</guid>
      <description>The company's annual revenue was boosted by its technology joint venture with Volkswagen Group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Metal Gear Solid remaster collection arrives this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/the-next-metal-gear-solid-remaster-collection-arrives-this-summer-231711005.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75c02b9d-44f4-499f-a569-55d5c6904ac9</guid>
      <description>Volume two of the Metal Gear Solid: Master Collection will arrive on August 27, publisher Konami announced today during Sony&#8217;s latest State of Play presentation. The bundle will feature 2008&#8217;s Metal Gear Solid 4: Guns of the Patriots, the HD remaster of 2010&#8217;s Metal Gear Solid: Peace Walker and a selection of bonus content, including Metal Gear: Ghost Babel, which was originally released for Game Boy Color in 2000. All told, that&#8217;s a smaller selection of games than Konami made available with Vol. 1 of the Master Collection, but Metal Gear fans will be excited nonetheless, if only for the fact ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Widely panned' is an understatement! Intel kills pay-as-you-go hardware upgrades, 15 years after the infamous Intel Upgrade Service scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/widely-panned-is-an-understatement-intel-zaps-on-pay-as-you-go-hardware-upgrades-15-years-after-the-infamous-intel-upgrade-service-scheme</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">N3Mnn2UMxARuABRLpvXNQM</guid>
      <description>Intel has quietly abandoned its pay-to-unlock silicon strategy after enterprises rejected fees for features already built into processors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Store is finally releasing BDX droids figures &#8212; and they look fantastic</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/disney-store-is-finally-releasing-bdx-droids-figures-and-they-look-fantastic</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XumNCBDBVRQhRUhSR7KqwG</guid>
      <description>Plus, talking figures and RC speeders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your First Look at Hasbro&#8217;s &#8216;Mandalorian and Grogu&#8217; Figures Is Here (Exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hasbro-mandalorian-and-grogu-black-series-star-wars-2000721261</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721261</guid>
      <description>We might not have seen much from the movie itself yet, but would it be 'Star Wars' if we didn't get some hints through some toys?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring cancels its partnership with Flock Safety after surveillance backlash</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/878447/ring-flock-partnership-canceled</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878447</guid>
      <description>Following intense backlash to its partnership with Flock Safety, a surveillance technology company that works with law enforcement agencies, Ring has announced it is canceling the integration. In a statement published on Ring's blog and provided to The Verge ahead of publication, the company said: "Following a comprehensive review, we determined the planned Flock Safety [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New to JRPGs? I've reviewed tons of them, and these are the six PS5 games I'd get started with</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/new-to-jrpgs-ive-reviewed-tons-of-them-and-these-are-the-six-ps5-games-id-get-started-with</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UcqPTYQFp7NrbZFsydJndP</guid>
      <description>I'm a JRPG devotee, and I always recommend these six PS5 games to new players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I cannot think of a single meaningful downside:' I tested Wharfedale's new Diamond 12.1i stereo speakers, and they're as good as things get for this price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/speakers/wharfedale-diamond-12-1i-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xAvw9P4RbdeuqBiEkoPVwg</guid>
      <description>Wharfedale finally refreshes its great Diamond 12 series of stereo speakers, and they're nearly flawless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: Hasbro&#8217;s Star Wars: The Vintage Collection reveal is headlined by an epic deluxe Mandalorian &amp; Grogu figure that keeps the clan of two together</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/exclusive-hasbros-star-wars-the-vintage-collection-reveal-is-headlined-by-an-epic-deluxe-mandalorian-and-grogu-figure-that-keeps-the-clan-of-two-together</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eP6sjAoLNeUEEhkAcGeoqS</guid>
      <description>TechRadar exclusively reveals Hasbro&#8217;s new Star Wars: The Vintage Collection wave inspired by The Mandalorian &amp; Grogu, including a deluxe Mandalorian &amp; Grogu figure, Imperial Remnant AT-RT and troopers, and IG-11 ahead of the film's 2026 premiere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next great American innovation is in the trades</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491707/the-next-great-american-innovation-is-in-the-trades</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T23:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491707/the-next-great-american-innovation-is-in-the-trades</guid>
      <description>The education system and savings plans are slowly catching up to meet these needs.
For decades, America has told a singular story about success, suggesting that the only acceptable path to success is a four-year degree. Any other trajectory was treated as a detour. Fortunately, that story is changing with new, acceptable ways to achieve success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first Control Resonant gameplay trailer shows Dylan defying physics in a sideways NYC</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/the-first-control-resonant-gameplay-trailer-shows-dylan-defying-physics-in-a-sideways-nyc-224746545.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e197c7e-d06c-4f9f-a31a-48035c425e19</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s been less than three months since we got our first look at Control Resonant, the sequel to Remedy&#8217;s mind-bending, third-person adventure that introduced us to Jesse Faden and the Federal Bureau of Control. At today&#8217;s State of Play event, we got to see the first extended bit of gameplay from Control Resonant &#8212; and the combat looks as inspired as ever, though the setting is completely new.As we learned in December, the next Control games doesn&#8217;t focus on Jesse Faden; instead, you&#8217;ll primarily play as her brother Dylan who Jesse was trying to find for much of the first game. Dylan&#8217;s out in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mina the Hollower resurfaces with a spring 2026 release window</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/mina-the-hollower-resurfaces-with-a-spring-2026-release-window-224327165.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5920e580-738c-4dc5-a4c5-384704637c73</guid>
      <description>Sony&#8217;s first State of Play stream of the year included an update on Mina the Hollower, the latest title from Shovel Knight studio Yacht Club Games. It&#8217;s now slated to arrive sometime this spring. The developer initially planned to release the retro-style action-adventure platformer on Halloween last year, but delayed it to &#8220;to apply some final polish and balancing to make the game truly shine.&#8221;While Mina the Hollower didn&#8217;t make its original Halloween release date, at least the new demo, which will be available for a limited time, is getting a eerily timed debut. It&#8217;ll hit PS5 tomorrow i.e. Fr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kena: Scars of Kosmora is coming out later this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/kena-scars-of-kosmora-is-coming-out-later-this-year-224006963.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0dba442f-eff6-4e06-aec9-42b83fbf0611</guid>
      <description>When it launched in 2021, Kena: Bridge of Spirits was an early example of the graphical power of the PS5 thanks to its Pixar-adjacent animation and over-the-top effects. Based on a surprise trailer at Sony's latest State of Play, it seems like its sequel, Kena: Scars of Kosmora, could up the ante when it launches later this year.Scars of Kosmora follows spirit guide Kena to a mysterious island called Kosmora, where a powerful spirit breaks her staff and forces her to embrace a new style of spirit guiding (and presumably a collection of new game mechanics). Like the first game, Scars of Kosmora...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost of Yotei's multiplayer expansion arrives March 10</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/ghost-of-yoteis-multiplayer-expansion-arrives-march-10-223842684.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ce9de5a-901c-47b7-a57e-76d9c130e66d</guid>
      <description>Ghost of Yotei&#8217;s forthcoming Legends multiplayer expansion will arrive early next month, Sony announced today during its latest State of Play presentation. As in Ghost of Tsushima, you&#8217;ll be able to play the mode with up to three other people online. Players can each choose from one of four classes &#8212; samurai, archer, mercenary and shinobi &#8212; who excel in different combat scenarios. All four classes can wield a katana and bow, but then they also have access to special weapons and skills. For example,  the samurai can wield the odachi, giving them a sweeping move set against groups of enemies.  Y...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Uncanny Valley&#8217;: ICE&#8217;s Secret Expansion Plans, Palantir Workers&#8217; Ethical Concerns, and AI Assistants</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-ice-expansion-palantir-workers-ethical-concerns-openclaw-ai-assistants/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698ba3e7357c15b942accd54</guid>
      <description>In this episode of Uncanny Valley, our hosts dive into WIRED&#8217;s scoop about a secret Trump administration campaign extending right into your backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bafflingly, over half of Aussie households have said 'no thanks' to NBN Co's speedy new tiers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/wi-fi-broadband/bafflingly-over-half-of-aussie-households-have-said-no-thanks-to-nbn-cos-speedy-new-tiers</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XfZNvTmS8ZfqXVj489JoAN</guid>
      <description>Despite NBN Co making it easier than ever to upgrade to a fast NBN plan, it seems millions of Australians have yet to jump on the bandwagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk needed a new vision for SpaceX and xAI. He landed on Moonbase Alpha.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/musk-needed-a-new-vision-for-spacex-and-xai-he-landed-on-moonbase-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092509</guid>
      <description>"I really want to see a mass driver on the moon that is shooting AI satellites into deep space."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI President Defends Trump Donations, Refuses to Comment on ICE</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-president-defends-trump-donations-refuses-to-comment-on-ice-2000721451</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721451</guid>
      <description>Are you just an apolitical defender of AI if you give money to fascists?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Puts 21-Year-Old Spacecraft on Pause to Keep It From Crashing Into Earth</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-puts-21-year-old-spacecraft-on-pause-to-keep-it-from-crashing-into-earth-2000721058</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721058</guid>
      <description>A rescue mission could reach the gamma-ray observatory this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Scarlet&#8217; Is a Ravishing Vision Undercut by a Glib &#8216;Hamlet&#8217; Reimagining</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scarlet-is-a-ravishing-vision-undercut-by-a-glib-hamlet-reimagining-2000720766</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720766</guid>
      <description>Mamoru Hosoda&#8217;s medieval, isekai-adjacent epic about a princess&#8217;s brutal quest for revenge is now playing in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iRobot takeover is complete &#8211; but it looks like the Roomba brand is clinging on to its US roots</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/the-irobot-takeover-is-complete-but-it-looks-like-the-roomba-brand-is-clinging-on-to-its-us-roots</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">heEhdzpLRTgght49LQnAFe</guid>
      <description>Roomba's parent brand might have a new Chinese owner, but it's still a 'US-based global consumer robotics company'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Tiny Comet Pulled Off a First-of-Its-Kind Spin Flip</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-tiny-comet-pulled-off-a-first-of-its-kind-spin-flip-2000721172</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721172</guid>
      <description>A fresh analysis of Comet 41P/Tuttle-Giacobini-Kres&#225;k observations suggests it abruptly reversed its spin after its last Earth flyby&#8212;an extreme and unprecedented change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation State of Play February 2026: all the news and trailers</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/877875/playstation-state-of-play-february-2026-ps5-news-trailers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=877875</guid>
      <description>Strap in, because the next PlayStation event is going to be a long one. Sony&#8217;s latest State of Play &#8212; a showcase event for upcoming PS5 games &#8212; kicks off on February 12th at 5PM ET and it&#8217;ll last more than an hour. We don&#8217;t know what exactly will be shown. Sony says that the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursor claims more than 30,000 Nvidia engineers commit 3x more code and make coding 'a lot more fun than it used to be', but is it too good to be true?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/cursor-claims-more-than-30-000-nvidia-engineers-commit-3x-more-code-and-make-coding-a-lot-more-fun-than-it-used-to-be-but-is-it-too-good-to-be-true</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nyNWC3cHzKqpR76Zivt6JF</guid>
      <description>Cursor claims Nvidia engineers produce three times more code using AI tools, yet industry observers remain skeptical about the quality and stability of the code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic has vowed to pay for electricity price hikes from its data centers. Its plan is short on details</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91492080/anthropic-has-vowed-to-pay-for-electricity-price-hikes-from-its-data-centers-its-plan-is-short-on-details</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T21:40:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91492080/anthropic-has-vowed-to-pay-for-electricity-price-hikes-from-its-data-centers-its-plan-is-short-on-details</guid>
      <description>The Claude AI chatbot maker has joined a growing crop of tech companies that are promising to cover the rising costs of their power needs. 
If you live near an AI data center, you may already be seeing higher electricity bills. But if that data center is for Anthropic, the AI company now says it will cover the price hikes consumers face.&#160;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
