<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:38:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon wants swarms of voice-controlled AI drones, and is offering a $100 million prize as a reward &#8212; and Elon Musk's SpaceX is taking pole position</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-pentagon-wants-swarms-of-voice-controlled-ai-drones-and-is-offering-a-usd100-million-prize-as-a-reward-and-elon-musks-spacex-is-taking-pole-position</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iLnKp6cVdA9wJXnvKcciDD</guid>
      <description>The Pentagon has launched a $100 million contest to develop voice-controlled autonomous drone swarms amid unresolved technical challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read new Microsoft gaming CEO Asha Sharma&amp;#8217;s memo on the future of Xbox</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/882326/read-microsoft-gaming-ceo-asha-sharma-first-memo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:30:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882326</guid>
      <description>Microsoft gaming boss Phil Spencer has just announced he's leaving the company after 12 years leading Xbox and nearly 40 at Microsoft in total. His replacement: Asha Sharma, formerly head of development for Microsoft's AI enterprise teams. Before that, she was COO of Instacart for three years, and spent four at Meta in charge of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Xbox chief Phil Spencer&#8217;s memo about leaving Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/882340/xbox-phil-spencer-microsoft-retirement-memo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:30:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882340</guid>
      <description>Xbox chief Phil Spencer has just announced in an internal memo that he's leaving Microsoft after 38 years. In a memo entitled "A new chapter for Microsoft Gaming," Spencer reveals to Xbox employees that he made the decision to retire from Microsoft last fall. He also reveals Xbox president Sarah Bond is leaving Microsoft, triggering [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox chief Phil Spencer is leaving Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/882241/microsoft-phil-spencer-xbox-leaving-retirement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:30:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882241</guid>
      <description>Xbox chief Phil Spencer is leaving Microsoft after nearly 40 years at the software giant. Xbox president Sarah Bond is also leaving Microsoft, in what is a major shakeup to the management of Xbox and Microsoft's gaming efforts. Asha Sharma, currently president of CoreAI product, is taking over as CEO of Microsoft Gaming. Microsoft CEO [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Bond is leaving Xbox</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/882281/xbox-sarah-bond-leaving-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:29:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882281</guid>
      <description>Sarah Bond, the president of COO and Xbox, is leaving the organization, along with CEO of Microsoft Gaming Phil Spencer. Her departure is being announced at the same time as Spencer's, with Asha Sharma moving into the EVP and CEO of Gaming role and Matt Booty being promoted to EVP and chief content officer. Microsoft [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read &#8216;Claymore,&#8217; Manga&#8217;s Best-Kept Dark Fantasy Secret</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/read-claymore-mangas-best-kept-dark-fantasy-secret-2000724567</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724567</guid>
      <description>A PSA to experience Norihiro Yagi&#8217;s gatekept series before the live&#8209;action adaptation breaches containment and has its fandom sweating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is making coal plants even dirtier as AI demands more energy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/882288/trump-ai-data-center-power-plant-pollution-mercury-mats</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:18:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882288</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration just tossed out Biden-era restrictions on mercury and other toxic pollutants from power plants. It's repealing Mercury and Air Toxics Standards (MATS) just as electricity demand in the US ticks up with the buildout of new AI data centers. Those standards are particularly impactful when it comes to pollution from coal plants [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web scraper sued by Google claims Google is the one scraping the web</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/882300/serpapi-google-lawsuit-web-scraper-motion-to-dismiss</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:06:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882300</guid>
      <description>SerpApi, a company that offers tools to scrape content on the web, is fighting back against Google's copyright lawsuit that accuses it of vacuuming up search results "at an astonishing scale." In a motion to dismiss filed on Friday, SerpApi argues that Google doesn't hold a copyright on its search results, alleging that the engine [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Wants a Single Search Engine to Flag Faces and Fingerprints Across Agencies</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/dhs-wants-a-single-search-engine-to-flag-faces-and-fingerprints-across-agencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69977cb46682b7d0faefb42e</guid>
      <description>Homeland Security aims to combine its face and fingerprint systems into one big biometric platform&#8212;after dismantling centralized privacy reviews and key limits on face recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite being designed to 'connect and just work', it turns out IKEA's new smart home sensors actually have some specific, confusing hub requirements</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/despite-being-designed-to-connect-and-just-work-it-turns-out-ikeas-new-smart-home-sensors-actually-have-some-specific-confusing-hub-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wUjABjYNnKPvc6pYSzW4dj</guid>
      <description>Those temptingly cheap sensors aren't quite such a bargain if you have to buy IKEA's own $109 / &#163;60 hub to make them work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can save $30 on Sony&#8217;s DualSense Edge controller by buying refurbished</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/815676/sony-playstation-dualsense-edge-controller-refurbished-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T14:55:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=815676</guid>
      <description>If the PlayStation 5 is your console of choice &#8212;&#160;and you&#8217;re not satisfied with the DualSense gamepad it comes with &#8212; the DualSense Edge may be what you&#8217;re looking for. Luckily, if its high asking price of $199 was keeping you away, Sony is now offering the white and black controller via the PlayStation Direct [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America is at risk of becoming an automotive backwater</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/882194/america-auto-backwater-ev-loss-detroit-trump-emissions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T14:52:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882194</guid>
      <description>For decades, America's auto industry was the envy of the world, driven by mass production, the rise of Detroit's Big Three automakers, and the iconic stylings of the 1950s and '60s. Then, through a series of blunders and missteps, things started to unravel. There was the fuel crisis of the 1970s, which led to an [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Reportedly Pins the Blame for AI-Caused Outage on Humans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-reportedly-pins-the-blame-for-ai-caused-outage-on-humans-2000724681</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724681</guid>
      <description>Allegedly, the coding assistant decided to &#8220;delete and recreate the environment&#8221; that was causing problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CDC Has a Leadership Crisis</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-cdc-has-a-leadership-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699786e93a099f5ddd9e73ff</guid>
      <description>A 2023 law championed by Republicans requires the CDC have a director confirmed by the Senate. For months, though, it's had only acting directors&#8212;and the White House won't say when that will change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s iOS 26.4 arrives in public beta with AI music playlists, video podcasts, and more</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/apples-ios-26-4-arrives-in-public-beta-with-ai-music-playlists-video-podcasts-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095036</guid>
      <description>Several updates are introduced in iOS 26.4, including an AI-powered playlist-generation feature in Apple Music, support for video content in the Podcasts app, end-to-end encryption (E2EE) for RCS messages, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I get a tariff refund from DHL, UPS, or FedEx after the Supreme Court struck down Trump&#8217;s tariffs?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496215/tariff-refunds-dhl-ups-fedex-will-you-get-one-after-supreme-court-trump-tariffs-ruling</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496215/tariff-refunds-dhl-ups-fedex-will-you-get-one-after-supreme-court-trump-tariffs-ruling</guid>
      <description>Consumers likely have many questions about what happens to the $230 billion in tariff revenue collected by the U.S. government last year.
The Supreme Court struck down President Trump&#8217;s sweeping tariffs on Friday, ruling that he overstepped his authority in imposing them on global imports.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC calls on broadcasters to air &#8216;pro-America content&#8217; for the country&#8217;s&#160;250th anniversary</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/882250/fcc-brendan-carr-pro-america-content-250-anniversary</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T14:29:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882250</guid>
      <description>Federal Communications Commission Chair Brendan Carr is urging broadcasters to air "patriotic, pro-America content" in celebration of the US's 250th anniversary. The initiative, called the "Pledge America Campaign," encourages broadcasters to run public service announcements, short segments, or specials to promote "civic education, inspiring local stories, and American history." Carr says broadcasters can "voluntarily choose [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InScope nabs $14.5M to solve the pain of financial reporting</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/inscope-nabs-14-5m-to-solve-the-pain-of-financial-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095072</guid>
      <description>The startup, founded by accountants who worked at Flexport, Miro, Hopin and Thrive Global, automates the difficulties of prepping financial statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wunmi Mosaku on the Most Surprising Moments in &#8216;Sinners&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wunmi-mosaku-sinners-best-scene-2000724670</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724670</guid>
      <description>The Oscar nominee praises the 'perfect script' that still brought unexpected moments to the screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, Gravity Made These Space Snowmen. No, It&#8217;s Not That Simple</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/yes-gravity-made-these-space-snowmen-no-its-not-that-simple-2000724528</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724528</guid>
      <description>Astronomers had decent guesses about how these peanut-shaped asteroids formed but couldn&#8217;t get the physics to work&#8212;until now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s Dusty Texas Town Needs Some Law and Order</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musks-dusty-texas-town-needs-some-law-and-order-2000724611</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724611</guid>
      <description>Starbase, Texas, has grown to over 580 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla still has to pay $243 million over fatal Autopilot crash, judge rules</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496204/tesla-still-has-to-pay-243-million-over-fatal-autopilot-crash-judge-rules</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T19:10:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496204/tesla-still-has-to-pay-243-million-over-fatal-autopilot-crash-judge-rules</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s EV maker had attempted to overturn a verdict that held it partially liable for an accident involving a Model S, but that ruling has now been upheld.
A federal judge has ruled that Tesla is still required to pay $243 million over a 2019 crash involving a Tesla equipped with Autopilot, despite the company&#8217;s efforts to overturn the verdict.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Mainz 05 vs. Hamburger SV online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/mainz-hamburger-bundesliga-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02If4gw82oIEx9dYlLbvM4a</guid>
      <description>How to watch Bundesliga for free. Watch Mainz 05 vs. Hamburger SV in the Bundesliga for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whether you use it or not, better public transit makes your commute better</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91493803/whether-you-use-it-or-not-better-public-transit-makes-your-commute-better</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91493803/whether-you-use-it-or-not-better-public-transit-makes-your-commute-better</guid>
      <description>The knock-on effects of subways, buses, and trains.
You&#8217;re stuck in traffic again, late for work, watching brake lights stretch to the horizon. According to the most recent data in the U.S. (2024), here are some of the ways traffic jams are lowering the quality of life:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Might Be Making a Smart Speaker That No One Asked for</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-might-be-making-a-smart-speaker-that-no-one-asked-for-2000724650</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724650</guid>
      <description>Rejoice: a smart speaker that can... identify objects on a table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tunic publisher claims TikTok ran 'racist, sexist' AI ads for one of its games without its knowledge</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/tunic-publisher-claims-tiktok-ran-racist-sexist-ai-ads-for-one-of-its-games-without-its-knowledge-185303395.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0324d1a0-8b72-414b-a395-ce9bc3d22dc2</guid>
      <description>Indie publisher and developer Finji has accused TikTok of using generative AI to alter the ads for its games on the platform without its knowledge or permission. Finji, which published indie darlings like Night in the Woods&#160;and Tunic, said it only became aware of the seemingly modified ads after being alerted to them by followers of its official TikTok account.
As reported by IGN, Finji alleges that one ad that went out on the platform was modified so it displayed a "racist, sexualized" representation of a character from one of its games. While it does advertise on TikTok, it told IGN that it ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Not Just Pugs&#8212;New Study IDs the Dog Breeds at High Risk of Breathing Issues</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/its-not-just-pugs-new-study-ids-the-dog-breeds-at-high-risk-of-breathing-issues-2000724473</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724473</guid>
      <description>Bulldogs and pugs are far from the only dogs frequently suffering from breathing problems, new research shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 7 vs OnePlus Open&#160;: comment choisir le meilleur smartphone pliant au format fold&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/versus/2761133_samsung-galaxy-z-fold-7-vs-oneplus-open-comment-choisir-le-meilleur-smartphone-pliant-au-format-fold</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/versus/2761133_samsung-galaxy-z-fold-7-vs-oneplus-open-comment-choisir-le-meilleur-smartphone-pliant-au-format-fold</guid>
      <description>
Samsung reste le leader incontest&#233; du march&#233; des smartphones pliants, mais cela ne devrait pas occulter qu'il existe bel et bien une concurrence. Le OnePlus Open peut-il se d&#233;fendre contre le dernier-n&#233; du g&#233;ant sud-cor&#233;en&#160;?
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
