<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:29:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google dans le viseur d&#8217;une enqu&#234;te de l&#8217;UE : l&#8217;utilisation de vos donn&#233;es pour Gemini jug&#233;e ill&#233;gale ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2903699_google-dans-le-viseur-dune-enquete-de-lue-lutilisation-de-vos-donnees-pour-gemini-jugee-illegale</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2903699_google-dans-le-viseur-dune-enquete-de-lue-lutilisation-de-vos-donnees-pour-gemini-jugee-illegale</guid>
      <description>
La Commission europ&#233;enne ouvre une enqu&#234;te pour abus de position dominante de Google concernant l'utilisation par le g&#233;ant des donn&#233;es pour son IA.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique (VAE) choisir en d&#233;cembre 2025 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-survoltes/guides-dachat-velos-electriques/917361_guide-achat-choisir-meilleurs-velos-electriques-vae</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-survoltes/guides-dachat-velos-electriques/917361_guide-achat-choisir-meilleurs-velos-electriques-vae</guid>
      <description>
Difficile de s'y retrouver dans la jungle des v&#233;los &#233;lectriques (VAE). Pour vous aider &#224; choisir celui qu'il vous faut, nous avons test&#233; et s&#233;lectionn&#233; les meilleurs v&#233;los &#233;lectriques du march&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our favorite Anker MagSafe power bank is 34 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/our-favorite-anker-magsafe-power-bank-is-34-percent-off-right-now-151039224.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09ea5372-026a-46a7-9896-17bd53529054</guid>
      <description>Holiday travel is almost upon us and, while it likely won't be something out of a Richard Curtis film, there are ways to make it easier. You can raid our list of best travel gifts for 2025 and pick up our favorite MagSafe power bank: Anker's MagGo 10,000mAh Power Bank.
Even better, the Anker MagGo power bank is currently on sale for $60, down from $90. This 34 percent discount brings the power bank to only $5 more than its all-time low price. We're big fans of Anker's MagGo power bank &#8212; one of the first and best Qi2-certified products available. You can get about 1.7 iPhone 15 charges out of i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda has shadow dropped Skyrim Anniversary Edition on Nintendo Switch 2, proving the 14-year-old game can never have too many ports</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/bethesda-has-shadowdropped-the-nintendo-switch-2-version-of-skyrim-anniversary-edition-proving-the-14-year-old-game-can-never-have-too-many-ports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cHRtQRzyFQKDkkmci5owbL</guid>
      <description>Bethesda Game Studios has today announced that The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim Anniversary Editionis now available on Nintendo Switch 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic and Accenture sign multi-year AI&#160;strategic partnership</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/anthropic-and-accenture-sign-multi-year-ai-strategic-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074124</guid>
      <description>The two companies are launching the Accenture Anthropic Business Group to bring Anthropic's AI to Accenture's employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;IA &#171;&#160;Avocado&#160;&#187;, un pari &#224; plusieurs milliards de Mark Zuckerberg qui doit sauver Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/lia-avocado-le-pari-a-plusieurs-milliards-de-mark-zuckerberg-qui-doit-sauver-meta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314578</guid>
      <description>Llama va-t-il rejoindre le cimeti&#232;re des marottes &#233;ph&#233;m&#232;res (et tr&#232;s co&#251;teuses) de Mark Zuckerberg ? Le mod&#232;le de langage d&#233;velopp&#233; par Meta, tout comme l&#8217;initiative des mondes virtuels, n&#8217;est plus en odeur de saintet&#233; suite au changement de strat&#233;gie, un de plus, du grand patron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of coding has a vibe problem: balancing creativity with control</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-future-of-coding-has-a-vibe-problem-balancing-creativity-with-control</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RY7oaErwLCCae6QNCsSSMh</guid>
      <description>With AI and developers collaborating side-by-side, the future of coding is set for a profound shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling for gift ideas? Get a handy Tile Bluetooth tracker for its lowest-ever price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/struggling-for-gift-ideas-get-a-handy-tile-bluetooth-tracker-for-its-lowest-ever-price</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jyDT8KvhBSvym2r9Pph7AN</guid>
      <description>Tile Bluetooth trackers are now down to $14.99 at Amazon and are a good choice for an excellent gift idea or a cheap stocking stuffer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify&#8217;s music videos feature arrives in the US and Canada</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840308/spotify-music-videos-beta-us-canada</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T10:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840308</guid>
      <description>Spotify is launching its beta music videos feature to Premium subscribers in the US and Canada today, over a year after it rolled out to Premium users in other regions. If you have a Spotify Premium subscription, you should now begin seeing an option to "Switch to video" on some tracks on the iOS, Android, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify finally brings music videos to the US</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/spotify-finally-brings-music-videos-to-the-us-150037974.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a17d6cb0-bba1-46c9-b2ee-601431581ca3</guid>
      <description>Spotify is finally letting the United States join its music video party. Music Videos have started rolling out in beta today to Premium users across the US and Canada, offering not only official artist videos but also new formats like live performances and covers.
Music Videos first arrived last year in 11 countries, but the United States wasn't one of them. The reason for that was simple &#8212; Spotify simply didn't have the rights. However, last month the streaming service struck a deal with the National Music Publishers' Association (NMPA) that included new provisions for video content, paving t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble Is Making a Smart Ring for Saving All Your Fleeting Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pebble-index-01-smart-ring-microphone-saving-your-thoughts-2000697194</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697194</guid>
      <description>The smart ring is called the Index 01 and it's very hackable and customizable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble Index: Everything You Need to Know About the $75 Smart Ring</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/pebble-index-ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693709c5532eea46faabbf94</guid>
      <description>You can speak into the Pebble Index to have it remember things or set reminders, timers, and tasks. No cloud processing, no subscription, and best of all, no charging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Pebble gadget is the Index 01, a ring with a microphone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/840352/pebble-index-smart-ring-launch-price</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840352</guid>
      <description>Eric Migicovsky, the founder of Pebble and the person leading its recent comeback, is very much in the business of making gadgets for himself. And he seems extremely into the one on his finger: It's called the Pebble Index 01 (but we'll just call it Index), and it's a $75 ring meant to be worn [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexa Plus can automatically buy stuff when the price drops</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840579/amazon-alexa-plus-shopping-features-automatic-purchase</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840579</guid>
      <description>Amazon is launching Alexa Plus shopping features that make it easier to track your orders and avoid missing out on deals. The AI-powered Alexa Plus assistant - like Amazon's Rufus chatbot - can proactively track products to tell you when they've dropped to a specific price, and automatically purchase them when they fall below the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble&#8217;s founder introduces a $75 AI smart ring for recording brief notes with a press of a button</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/pebbles-founder-introduces-a-75-ai-smart-ring-for-recording-brief-notes-with-a-press-of-a-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073797</guid>
      <description>After rebooting the Pebble smartwatch, founder Eric Migicovsky is expanding his company's device lineup with a new smart wearable: an AI-powered smart ring known as Index 01. Named for the finger where the ring is meant to be worn, the new $75 ring is not meant to be a competitor to the always-on, always-listening AI devices, like the AI pendant Friend, but instead offers a way to record quick notes and reminders with a press of a button on the ring's side.

AI only comes into play via the open source, speech-to-text, and AI models that run locally on your smartphone, via the open source Pebbl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify launches music videos in the U.S. and Canada for Premium subscribers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/spotify-launches-music-videos-in-the-u-s-and-canada-for-premium-subscribers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073901</guid>
      <description>Spotify will let you switch between music videos and audio at any time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble is reinventing voice assistants and smart rings in one device &#8212; meet the Pebble Index 01</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/pebble-is-reinventing-voice-assistants-and-smart-rings-in-one-device-meet-the-pebble-index-01</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ru4rbRBgi3YjsVzjRUoKq8</guid>
      <description>Pebble is taking the most useful aspects of a voice assistant, and putting it into a smart ring that has nothing to do with health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Wednesday, December 10 (game #913)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-10-december-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GnMLq7TDT4MCdYbLkzFi4K</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Wednesday, December 10 (game #1416)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-10-december-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">THbUH8yjFPVxLcQPyMz3cT</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Wednesday, December 10 (game #647)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-10-december-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">s9AmnUqB5duD3FvKEHHLQ4</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify steps up its plan to be the new MTV &#8212; music videos are rolling out whether you want them or not</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/spotify/spotify-steps-up-its-plan-to-be-the-new-mtv-music-videos-are-rolling-out-whether-you-want-them-or-not</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">thvTLvfobeX7KpdGSeY4PT</guid>
      <description>After nearly two years, music videos are coming to Spotify in the US and Canada, but is it what users actually want?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is rolling out new shopping features for Alexa+, because of course it is</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazon-is-rolling-out-new-shopping-features-for-alexa-because-of-course-it-is-150000355.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31d5cac6-a2f5-4724-8eda-5a91621d7f6f</guid>
      <description>Congrats to any budding Nostradamus out there who peered into the future to boldly predict that Amazon would bring more shopping features to Alexa+ sooner rather than later. A gold star for you. Yes, it hasn't taken too long for Amazon to weave more features into the generative AI-powered version of Alexa that are designed to get you to buy more stuff.Shopping features were part of the original Alexa from the jump, of course, but Amazon is doing some interesting things with the latest iteration. For instance, the company is rolling out a new price tracking feature. Tell it the product you want...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairbuds XL 2025, le casque modulaire qui se d&#233;monte mais pas face &#224; la concurrence</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fairphone/2903667_fairbuds-xl-2025-le-casque-modulaire-qui-se-demonte-mais-pas-face-a-la-concurrence</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fairphone/2903667_fairbuds-xl-2025-le-casque-modulaire-qui-se-demonte-mais-pas-face-a-la-concurrence</guid>
      <description>
Fairphone lance une nouvelle version de son casque circum-aural Fairbuds XL, qui reprend la philosophie modulaire du mod&#232;le de 2023 tout en corrigeant plusieurs points faibles, notamment sur le plan audio et du confort.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford taps Renault for help building cheap EVs in Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840632/ford-renault-cheap-ev-europe</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T09:59:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840632</guid>
      <description>Ford is teaming up with France's Renault to design and produce affordable electric vehicles for the European market, with the goal of turning around the Blue Oval's struggling business on the continent. The move comes as cheap Chinese-made EVs have flooded Europe, snatching away market share from long-established players. Ford will use Renault's Ampere platform [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google extends free repairs to cover known Pixel 9 Pro and Pro Fold issues</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840622/google-pixel-9-pro-xl-display-issues-repair-program-fold-extended-warranty</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T09:57:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840622</guid>
      <description>Google announced a new "extended repair program" for the Pixel 9 Pro and Pixel 9 Pro XL smartphones yesterday after it confirmed display issues with a "limited number" of devices, as spotted by 9to5Google. The company is doing the same for the Pixel 9 Pro Fold, although Google didn't specify what's wrong with it other [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De 2 000 &#224; 560 000 satellites : la Nasa s&#8217;inqui&#232;te des cons&#233;quences en cha&#238;ne dans l&#8217;espace et l&#8217;atmosph&#232;re</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/satellite-2-000-560-000-satellites-nasa-inquiete-consequences-chaine-espace-atmosphere-128219/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:49:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/satellite-2-000-560-000-satellites-nasa-inquiete-consequences-chaine-espace-atmosphere-128219/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>En seulement cinq ans, le nombre de satellites en orbite basse autour de la Terre a presque &#233;t&#233; multipli&#233; par dix. C&#8217;est une bonne nouvelle du point de vue des services qu&#8217;ils nous rendent. Mais des scientifiques commencent &#224; s&#8217;inqui&#233;ter des cons&#233;quences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas authorities have made multiple arrests in an NVIDIA GPU smuggling operation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/texas-authorities-have-made-multiple-arrests-in-an-nvidia-gpu-smuggling-operation-144749526.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d7c98a6-07a2-4295-b85f-fe1ba4e9d649</guid>
      <description>The Southern District of Texas announced the seizure of more than $50 million in NVIDIA GPUs bound for China in violation of US export laws. Authorities arrested two businessmen, one of them the owner of a Houston company, accused of smuggling the chips used to train and run AI models.
&#8220;Operation Gatekeeper has exposed a sophisticated smuggling network that threatens our Nation&#8217;s security by funneling cutting-edge AI technology to those who would use it against American interests,&#8221; said US Attorney Nicholas J. Ganjei. The investigation had been ongoing since at least last year and centers on t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec 350&#8364; de moins, ce puissant laptop 2-en-1 (&#233;cran OLED 2,8K 120 Hz, Ultra 7 et 32 Go RAM) est le deal parfait pour No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2903217_avec-350e-de-moins-ce-puissant-laptop-2-en-1-ecran-oled-28k-120-hz-ultra-7-et-32-go-ram-est-le-deal-parfait-pour-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2903217_avec-350e-de-moins-ce-puissant-laptop-2-en-1-ecran-oled-28k-120-hz-ultra-7-et-32-go-ram-est-le-deal-parfait-pour-noel</guid>
      <description>
Avec le Lenovo Yoga 7i 2-en-1 vous avez un laptop hybride polyvalent et puissant avec sa puce Ultra 7. Il d&#233;ploie une configuration solide et voit son prix passer de 1 299 euros &#224; 999 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vergecast 2025 year in review</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/840661/tech-stories-2025-ai-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T09:45:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840661</guid>
      <description>When we look back on 2025, at least in tech, we'll remember it mostly as a year about AI. We had a race between OpenAI, Google, Anthropic, and others to build the best model for the most things. Nvidia became the most valuable company in the world, data centers started to spring up everywhere, and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral AI surfs vibe coding tailwinds with new coding models</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/mistral-ai-surfs-vibe-coding-tailwinds-with-new-coding-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074070</guid>
      <description>French AI startup Mistral today launched Devstral 2, a new generation of its AI model designed for coding, as the company seeks to catch up to bigger AI labs like Anthropic and other coding-focused LLMs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt injection attacks might 'never be properly mitigated' UK NCSC warns</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/prompt-injection-attacks-might-never-be-properly-mitigated-uk-ncsc-warns</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">k2LAhAxyCWXUJb2Dr6jprC</guid>
      <description>Prompt injection and SQL injection are two entirely different beasts, with the former being more of a "confusable deputy".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Legion Pro Rollable leak reveals the world&#8217;s first ultrawide OLED gaming laptop &#8211; and I can&#8217;t wait to try it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/lenovo-legion-pro-rollable-leak-reveals-the-worlds-first-ultrawide-oled-gaming-laptop-and-i-cant-wait-to-try-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HsUYh4u3ZP5vpra4mL4Xm6</guid>
      <description>A leaked render depicts Lenovo's new gaming laptop, which is a clear attempt at providing a portable ultrawide gaming experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures cam&#233;ras de s&#233;curit&#233; connect&#233;es pour l&#8217;int&#233;rieur en 2025&#8201;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guide-objets-connectes/1181025_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-cameras-de-surveillance-connectees-pour-linterieur-en-2022</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guide-objets-connectes/1181025_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-cameras-de-surveillance-connectees-pour-linterieur-en-2022</guid>
      <description>
Envie de garder un &#339;il sur votre domicile&#8201;? Nous avons fait le tri pour vous et s&#233;lectionn&#233; les meilleures cam&#233;ras de s&#233;curit&#233; connect&#233;es pour l'int&#233;rieur !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How an Iconic &#8216;Five Nights at Freddy&#8217;s 2&#8217; Sound Got Its Spooky Origins</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/five-nights-at-freddys-2-kellen-goff-interview-foxy-2000696973</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696973</guid>
      <description>The voice of Foxy and Toy Freddy, Kellen Goff, talks about contributing a small but iconic part of 'Five Nights at Freddy's' cinematic soundscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Peloton Instructor Jess King Needs to Survive the Day</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/jess-king-wellness-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692f0f05023a10659d928c0d</guid>
      <description>Peloton star, DJ, and mom Jess King shares the wellness gear that fuels her nonstop hustle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best thing I bought this year: the Remarkable Paper Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/837877/remarkable-paper-pro-type-folio-marker-plus-favorite</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T09:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=837877</guid>
      <description>About a year ago, we said you probably don&#8217;t need the Remarkable Paper Pro. The e-ink device is equal parts outrageous and luxurious; it&#8217;s not ideal for consuming books, and the screen can sometimes feel painfully slow. Then there&#8217;s the starting price, which is, quite frankly, ludicrous at $629 (up from $579 thanks to US-induced [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;&#233;cran des Pixel 10 a un gros probl&#232;me depuis la derni&#232;re mise &#224; jour d&#8217;Android 16</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2903503_lecran-des-pixel-10-a-un-gros-probleme-depuis-la-derniere-mise-a-jour-dandroid-16</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2903503_lecran-des-pixel-10-a-un-gros-probleme-depuis-la-derniere-mise-a-jour-dandroid-16</guid>
      <description>
Les Pixel de Google ont &#233;t&#233; mis &#224; jour d&#233;but d&#233;cembre et globalement, les retours sont positifs. Sauf ceux des utilisateurs touch&#233;s par ce bug p&#233;nible.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architects are embracing this ancient building technique to combat climate change&#8212;and soulless design</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453541/architects-embracing-rammed-earth-designs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T14:18:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453541/architects-embracing-rammed-earth-designs</guid>
      <description>Rammed earth buildings have been around for thousands of years. Now, they&#8217;re having a modern moment.  
In the English countryside, a new project has emerged from the landscape&#8212;quite literally. Rammed Earth House, a residential estate by London-based Tuckey Design Studio, combines renovated brick buildings with new rammed earth structures, harnessing the clay soil of the very land it sits on. &#8220;The material is already under your feet, and it doesn&#8217;t come with all the carbon baggage that other [building] materials come with,&#8221; says studio founder Jonathan Tuckey.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qobuz teams up with indie music mag Drowned in Sound to produce 6 months of artist-first podcasts &#8212; and I can&#8217;t wait to tune in</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/audio-streaming/qobuz-teams-up-with-indie-music-mag-drowned-in-sound-to-produce-6-months-of-artist-first-podcasts-and-i-cant-wait-to-tune-in</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cHrqPnwjZvbWfmv4t2KDrc</guid>
      <description>Qobuz's Drowned in Sound collab will bring 6 months of artist-first podcasts to discerning music-lovers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn wants every user to be verified</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/linkedin-wants-every-user-to-be-verified</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GnosnzDtSiSVJHCiSxA5p8</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn hits 100 million verified accounts on its platform, but the goal is to verify everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook et Instagram&#160;: bient&#244;t moins de publicit&#233;s cibl&#233;es pour les Europ&#233;ens</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/facebook-et-instagram-bientot-moins-de-publicites-ciblees-pour-les-europeens.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314546</guid>
      <description>Les utilisateurs de Facebook et d&#8217;Instagram auront bient&#244;t acc&#232;s &#224; un nouveau r&#233;glage leur permettant de r&#233;duire le nombre de publicit&#233;s cibl&#233;es pr&#233;sentes dans ces applications. L&#8217;arriv&#233;e de cette nouvelle option est pr&#233;vue pour le mois de janvier. C'est la cons&#233;quence d&#8217;une amende inflig&#233;e &#224; Meta au printemps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundpeats H3 Review: Triple-Driver Wireless Earbuds</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/review/soundpeats-h3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6936fe2d886f1ed371a4e2ed</guid>
      <description>You don&#8217;t need to be an audiophile to appreciate how great these buds sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now text photos directly to Aura&amp;#8217;s digital picture frames</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840142/aura-text-to-frame-digital-picture-frame-share-photos</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840142</guid>
      <description>It's now easier for friends and family who aren't tech savvy or are struggling with app fatigue to share images via your Aura digital photo frame. As the name of the new "text to frame" feature implies, photos can now be shared to an Aura frame through a text message, and they will be automatically [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech's biggest losers of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/techs-biggest-losers-of-2025-140000419.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b0860e7-62ad-4fa7-bfb7-174993be8262</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s the end of another year, so it&#8217;s time for the Engadget staff to compile a list of the year&#8217;s biggest losers. We scour over articles from the previous 12 months to determine the people, companies, products and trends that made our lives worse over the course of the year. Some selections may be so pervasive they actually make our list of biggest winners. But, for the most part, we&#8217;re confident you&#8217;ll share in our collective rage over the biggest losers of 2025.OpenAIOpenAI CEO Sam Altman delivers a speech with video at the SK AI Summit 2025 at COEX in Seoul, South Korea on November 3, 2025 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this once-trendy DTC sneaker pioneer is pivoting to women&#8217;s vitamins</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453653/allbirds-maha-womens-health-biologica</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T14:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453653/allbirds-maha-womens-health-biologica</guid>
      <description>Joey Zwillinger explains what he learned from the Allbirds experience
After Joey Zwillinger stepped down as CEO of Allbirds in March 2024, he took three months off&#8212;mainly because his wife Liz said she&#8217;d divorce him if he jumped into another venture. He had run the sustainable shoe company for 10 years while the couple raised their three young children. &#8220;It took a real toll on the family,&#8221; Liz says. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Xbox controller I hold dearest is at a simply ridiculously low price right now at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-xbox-controller-i-hold-dearest-is-at-a-simply-ridiculously-low-price-right-now-at-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">USm8K4rXMxFDRyLFyVVHqZ</guid>
      <description>For the love of game pads, please buy my favorite Xbox controller ever at this ridiculously low price that has to be a mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nouveau record mondial : pourquoi les futures voitures &#233;lectriques chinoises seront encore plus difficiles &#224; plier</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/chery/2903437_nouveau-record-mondial-pourquoi-les-futures-voitures-electriques-chinoises-seront-encore-plus-difficiles-a-plier</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/chery/2903437_nouveau-record-mondial-pourquoi-les-futures-voitures-electriques-chinoises-seront-encore-plus-difficiles-a-plier</guid>
      <description>
Le constructeur chinois Chery et le sid&#233;rurgiste HBIS viennent d'annoncer un sacr&#233; pas en avant concernant la s&#233;curit&#233; des voitures. Leur nouvel acier thermoform&#233; affiche une r&#233;sistance impressionnante, d&#233;passant le record mondial d&#233;tenu jusqu'ici par Xiaomi et sa voiture &#233;lectriqu. Mais quels sont les avantages concrets pour l'utilisateur ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce smartphone fin en promo &#224; moins de 300 &#8364; sur Amazon a tout pour plaire, mais les stocks sont tr&#232;s limit&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2873693_ce-smartphone-fin-en-promo-a-moins-de-300-sur-amazon-a-tout-pour-plaire-mais-les-stocks-sont-tres-limites</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2873693_ce-smartphone-fin-en-promo-a-moins-de-300-sur-amazon-a-tout-pour-plaire-mais-les-stocks-sont-tres-limites</guid>
      <description>
Si vous cherchez un bon smartphone au form factor fin, le Motorola Edge pourrait &#234;tre le candidat id&#233;al. Surtout avec cette r&#233;duction sur Amazon qui le fait passer de 499 euros &#224; 299 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empromptu raises $2M pre-seed to help enterprises build AI apps</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/empromptu-raises-2m-pre-seed-to-help-enterprises-build-ai-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074061</guid>
      <description>Empromptu claims all a user has to do is tell the platform's AI chatbot what they want &#8212; like a new HTML or JavaScript app &#8212; and the AI will go ahead and build it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WNBA star Paige Bueckers launches good-for-you snack Ragerz with Chris Paul&#8217;s brand Good Eat&#8217;n</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456902/wnba-star-paige-bueckers-launches-good-for-you-snack-ragerz-with-chris-pauls-brand-good-eatn</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T13:50:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456902/wnba-star-paige-bueckers-launches-good-for-you-snack-ragerz-with-chris-pauls-brand-good-eatn</guid>
      <description>The partnership marks the first time that a WNBA star has taken an equity stake in a food brand founded by an NBA player.
If you&#8217;re searching for a new snack that&#8217;s heavy on flavor but manages to skip the unhealthy additives, you&#8217;re in luck. There&#8217;s a new one called Ragerz from Good Eat&#8217;n, NBA star Chris Paul&#8217;s snack brand, in partnership with the WNBA&#8217;s Paige Bueckers. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under-16s social media ban lands in Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/under-16s-social-media-ban-lands-in-australia</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ifiDWvfbYiuWAd6yRMgeY</guid>
      <description>Australian teens are now locked out of the most popular social media apps. Here's how the platforms are complying with the new rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Fortnite's most hated weapons is making a comeback this week in OG</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/one-of-fortnites-most-hated-weapons-is-making-a-comeback-this-week-in-og</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iLTqE7sJmRKdjZPEuxgeen</guid>
      <description>Epic Games has confirmed that the overpowered Infinity Blade will return in Fortnite OG this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Je n&#8217;ai pas l&#8217;intention de partir de sit&#244;t&#160;&#187;&#160;: l&#8217;architecte des puces Apple silicon est l&#224; pour rester, une excellente nouvelle pour vos futurs Mac</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2903407_je-nai-pas-lintention-de-partir-de-sitot-larchitecte-des-puces-apple-silicon-est-la-pour-rester-une-excellente-nouvelle-pour-vos-futurs-mac</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2903407_je-nai-pas-lintention-de-partir-de-sitot-larchitecte-des-puces-apple-silicon-est-la-pour-rester-une-excellente-nouvelle-pour-vos-futurs-mac</guid>
      <description>
Retournement de situation chez Apple. Johny Srouji, l'architecte des puces Apple Silicon, resterait au sein de la firme de Cupertino. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU opens antitrust investigation into Google's AI practices</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/eu-opens-antitrust-investigation-into-googles-ai-practices-133015762.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6e52ef0-5839-4023-bcaf-de2217f0011c</guid>
      <description>Google is no stranger to scrutiny from government bodies such as the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC) the UK Competition and Markets Authority (CMA), and the European Commission. Now it can add another probe to its list: The European Commission has opened an antitrust investigation into the company surrounding the content used for its AI tools. Namely, the Commission is looking into two things, starting with whether Google used web publisher's content for its AI Overview and AI Mode services &#8212; without "appropriate compensation" or the option to "refuse" the use of their materials.&#160;
"The Commi...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
