<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:19:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The new Ultraloq smart lock uses both your face and your palm to let you in</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853844/ultraloq-ces-smart-lock-face-palm-reading</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T21:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853844</guid>
      <description>Xthings is rolling into CES with a bunch of new gear, including two new smart locks and a few smart security cameras. It's definitely the Ultraloq Bolt Sense that's the most intriguing of the bunch, however. It's a relatively compact smart deadbolt that combines facial recognition with palm vein authentication for touch-free access, without resorting [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PartyStudio is a wireless MIDI speaker with 128 built-in instrument sounds</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/partystudio-is-a-wireless-midi-speaker-with-128-built-in-instrument-sounds-015511003.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3973703-dfd1-4679-8cea-037bd84e3ff0</guid>
      <description>There are a slew of keyboards and apps that help people learn how to play the piano, but a small company called PopuMusic is showing off an intriguing set of products at CES to make the process easier.  PartyKeys and PartyStudio are a 36-key MIDI keyboard and MIDI / Bluetooth speaker that pair together in seamless fashion. The PartyStudio is particularly interesting because it has a built-in library of 128 instrument tones and more than 50 different drum machine patterns. Naturally, it works with the PartyKeys, but any MIDI keyboard can connect to it and use those sounds. The PartyStudio and P...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea&#8217;s new $4 USB-C charger is cheaper than Apple&#8217;s and Anker&#8217;s</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854333/ikea-sjoss-20w-usb-c-wall-charger</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T20:54:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854333</guid>
      <description>Ikea has released the most affordable version of its Sj&#246;ss USB-C chargers yet. Following an $8 30W version that launched in 2024 and a $35 65W option that debuted earlier this year, the new 20W Sj&#246;ss is now available online and through many of Ikea's physical US stores for just $3.99. That's considerably cheaper than [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchBot turned up to CES with an AI wearable that records everything you say</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/switchbot-turned-up-to-ces-with-an-ai-wearable-that-records-everything-you-say-014959824.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2c50e8c-3159-4138-802c-d954fcab9790</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;ve all fantasied about sprawling on an embroidered chaise lounge while our amanuensis faithfully typed out everything we said. SwitchBot turned up to CES with something that does a similar job, but without the romance of the amanuensis, the typewriter or the chaise lounge. Instead, it&#8217;s launching the AI MindClip, a wearable microphone which records and transcribes every noise to come from your mouth.&#160;The company isn&#8217;t alone, with many others turning up to CES this year offering devices to log your thoughts through the day. But SwitchBot does hope to distinguish itself from the crowd with an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockin's everlasting vein-recognizing smart lock doorbell cam combo is peak CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/lockins-everlasting-vein-recognizing-smart-lock-doorbell-cam-combo-is-peak-ces-013431113.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d083620-c6a8-4a4f-816f-14fee8df123a</guid>
      <description>Smart locks have a notable inconvenience: running out of power. Lockin, maker of vein-recognition locks, debuted its newest model on the CES floor. It charges wirelessly via an optical infrared beam with a four-meter range.  A small device, connected to a standard outlet inside the house, shoots a beam at the lock, which has a small receptor panel that turns the light into power, sort of like a plug-in sun beaming at a tiny solar array.  The tech carries certifications from two independent organizations, and won&#8217;t harm eyeballs or bodies that get in the way of the beam (though if the beam is i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: What to expect from tech's big January conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-what-to-expect-from-techs-big-january-conference-120000956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2645ab40-20b1-4cf0-bdcf-9e9656c79061</guid>
      <description>The pre-show events are already up and running at CES 2026 &#8212; the tech world&#8217;s biggest annual conference &#8212; and the news is already flowing. While the CES show floor doesn't officially open until Tuesday, January 6, Las Vegas is already abuzz with various pre-show events, including the CES Unveiled mini show and Samsung's First Look press conference, scheduled for late Sunday. Nearly all day Monday will be comprised of more press conferences from the likes of LG, Intel, NVIDIA and Sony. And that doesn't include the product demos, announcements and networking that will be happening at the Las Veg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xreal updates its entry-level personal cinema glasses at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/xreal-updates-its-entry-level-personal-cinema-glasses-at-ces-140000544.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e74752e-36c5-4418-b7b5-90ed4a774f24</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been on the fence about trying the sort of &#8220;AR glasses&#8221; that, until recently, were called &#8220;personal cinemas,&#8221; then check this out. Xreal has turned up to CES 2026 with an updated version of its entry level Xreal One glasses, first launched at the end of 2024. The new model, dubbed the 1S (yes, with a numeral rather than the word) gets marginally better specs and $50 knocked from the asking price.
If you&#8217;re unfamiliar, One is a wearable spatial display that connects over USB-C to any compatible device including smartphones, tablets, laptops and consoles. It has two teeny-tiny displays...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Withings' updated Body Scan scale tracks 60 different biomarkers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/withings-updated-body-scan-scale-tracks-60-different-biomarkers-010000703.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e782b9c-3d7d-4663-9aed-934412a42d22</guid>
      <description>Back in 2023, Withings launched Body Scan, a super-premium scale with the sort of tech found in a high-end gym or low-end clinic. It had a six-lead ECG, offered segmented body composition and could monitor your nerve health, among other things. Now the company has rocked up at CES 2026 in Las Vegas with a second-generation model that adds in tests for hypertension and cellular health. Withings hopes the new model will give you even more data you can use to fight against chronic illnesses brought on by our decadent modern lifestyle.
The first generation Body Scan checked 40 biomarkers, while th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Withings thinks of its latest smart scale as a &#8216;longevity station&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/850005/ces-2026-withings-body-scan-2-smart-scale-longevity-tech-health</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850005</guid>
      <description>Withings is back at CES 2026 with another smart scale: the $599.95 Body Scan 2. This time, it's got an even tighter focus on cardiovascular and metabolic health. The Body Scan 2 contains eight electrodes on the scale itself, as well as an additional four electrodes within a retractable handle. This is similar to the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shure MV88 USB-C stereo mic mounts directly to your phone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852938/shure-mv88-usb-c-stereo-mic-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852938</guid>
      <description>Shure is updating its MV88 microphone for the modern age by adding a USB-C connector for mounting directly to your smartphone. The original MV88, released in 2015, had a Lightning connector, but obviously that's not practically useful anymore. The MV88+ added USB, but relied on a cable and didn't mount directly to a phone or [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB is the next big thing in OLED gaming monitors</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854183/oled-gaming-monitors-rgb-stripe-lg-samsung-display-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854183</guid>
      <description>New OLED gaming monitors from top companies coming out this year should look clearer and crisper. LG Display and Samsung Display, which typically provide the actual panels used in gaming monitors, are finally lining up the colors of their subpixels in vertical RGB stripes - remember when we used to worry about Pentile OLED displays? [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shure debuts a USB-C version of its MV88 microphone at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/shure-debuts-a-usb-c-version-of-its-mv88-microphone-at-ces-2026-010000294.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acf91d25-1756-49b1-a3cd-317766d2a36c</guid>
      <description>Shure&#8217;s original MV88 microphone (no, not the + version) was a convenient snap-on option for iPhone users. Since Apple ditched the port for USB-C, the audio accessory became obsolete for newer handsets. At CES 2026, the company debuted a revised version of the mic, swapping the Lightning connection for USB-C, which also adds compatibility for Android users and a host of other devices. The best part is the updated MV88 is available now, and it&#8217;s priced at $159. 
If you missed the 2015 version, the MV88 is a compact stereo condenser microphone that simply snaps onto a phone, tablet or one of you...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Withings Body Scan 2 : cette balance connect&#233;e r&#233;alise votre bilan de sant&#233; complet avec 60 biomarqueurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/withings/2923133_withings-body-scan-2-cette-balance-connectee-realise-votre-bilan-de-sante-complet-avec-60-biomarqueurs</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/withings/2923133_withings-body-scan-2-cette-balance-connectee-realise-votre-bilan-de-sante-complet-avec-60-biomarqueurs</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES de Las Vegas, Withings a d&#233;voil&#233; sa nouvelle Withings Body Scan 2. Plus qu'une balance, elle se pr&#233;sente comme une &#171; station de sant&#233; connect&#233;e &#187; capable d'analyser plus de 60 biomarqueurs, du poids &#224; la rigidit&#233; art&#233;rielle. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narwal's first mattress vacuum heats, taps, UV-blasts and sucks up all the ick living in your bed</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/narwals-first-mattress-vacuum-heats-taps-uv-blasts-and-sucks-up-all-the-ick-living-in-your-bed-004929304.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2119e83-0d92-4e83-a189-642a59aa508c</guid>
      <description>Narwal brought new cleaning robots with it to CES this year, including the Narwal Flow 2,  it&#8217;s latest flagship robo mop-vac, and the Narwal U50, an automatic mattress vac designed for &#8220;deep mite removal.&#8221; While I&#8217;d hoped the latter vac was an automatic crawler that could navigate your mattress top, the U50 is a handheld device. Still, no one likes to think about what filters down into their mattress as they sleep &#8212; and there are lots of opinions on how and why to remove those dead skin cells, dust, oils and the mites that arrive to dine on those things. Narwal&#8217;s mattress vacuum cleaner not on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At CES, Belkin launches a new charging case for the Switch 2 with a screen for checking battery life</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/belkin-charging-case-for-the-switch-2-ces-2026-screen-for-checking-battery-life-170029146.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e64ca9d-4aa1-4b0b-a542-4f6b332e9944</guid>
      <description>Belkin just introduced the appropriately-named Charging Case Pro for Nintendo Switch 2 at CES 2026. This is a high-end charging case specifically designed for Nintendo's latest console.
The 10,000mAh power bank delivers up to 30W of fast charging, which is a decent enough metric. I'm more excited, however, about the bells and whistles. The Charging Case Pro boasts an LCD screen on the exterior, making it easy to keep track of remaining battery life. It also doubles as a tabletop stand, which is always nice. The built-in Switch 2 stand is better than what we got with the first Switch, but it's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Samsung 'First Look' CES 2026 presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/how-to-watch-the-samsung-first-look-ces-2026-presentation-190027420.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99e05139-49a3-486e-a22a-1ec128284043</guid>
      <description>NurPhoto via Getty Images
Are you ready for CES 2026? While the show floor doesn't open until Tuesday, things are effectively kicking off this evening with the first big press event of the show. Samsung is taking the stage to set the agenda for the new year and share an overview of its latest and greatest advances.&#160;
Instead of its longtime midday Monday press conference, the Korean giant will take the lead of the show with a Sunday night presentation. Over the past few weeks, Samsung has been dropping press releases left and right, so we know at least some of what to expect in Vegas this year....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
