<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:59:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok ban: all the news on the app&#8217;s shutdown and return in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T20:30:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/655/tiktok-ban-us-news</guid>
      <description>After briefly going dark in the US to comply with the divest-or-ban law targeting ByteDance that went into effect on January 19th, TikTok quickly came back online. It eventually reappeared in the App Store and Google Play as negotiations between the US and China continued, and Donald Trump continued to sign extensions directing officials not [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 13 hours, Dispatch has given me hope that the tell-your-own adventure genre of video games will see a renaissance era</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/dispatch-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WzGa9RuQcwC3BkoDY5XTRm</guid>
      <description>A heartfelt story told within a mature, superhero workplace comedy, Dispatch has managed to find itself in my top games of the year. My review explores its lovable characters and gorgeous art style to soak up over the course of eight episodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok&#8217;s long-awaited US sale may finally be happening, according to new reports</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/tiktoks-long-awaited-us-sale-may-finally-be-happening-according-to-new-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gWr3DZY5bM9oscM8QNZC9f</guid>
      <description>TikTok&#8217;s long-running US ownership saga may be nearing a resolution, with reports suggesting its US operations could shift from ByteDance to a new American-led joint venture as early as January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok agrees to deal to cede control of US business to American investor group</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/tiktok-agrees-to-deal-to-cede-control-of-u-s-business-to-american-investor-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077634</guid>
      <description>The deal closes a long-running drama in which U.S. authorities have sought to compel ByteDance to divest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok signs deal to sell its U.S. operations after years of uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tiktok-signs-us-sale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03AdOUp1ApuZPQ5m913Hd4L</guid>
      <description>TikTok&#8217;s long-running saga of a U.S. ban may be coming to an end after the company signed a deal to sell its American operations to a new joint venture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Awards 2025: How to watch</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tiktok-awards-2025-how-to-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06UTYI6fW2A44dM8GG8OVUH</guid>
      <description>It should not prove difficult to watch the TikTok Awards. All you need is the TikTok app and/or a free Tubi account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Rai Rai Rai&#8217; Is a Pastiche of Manga Greats Rolled Into a Cutesy Kaiju Package</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rai-rai-rai-is-a-pastiche-of-manga-greats-rolled-into-a-cutesy-kaiju-package-2000701470</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701470</guid>
      <description>We need you to understand why we need you to join the fight to keep this manga going.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Now You See Me franchise at home: The newest movie is now streaming</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/how-to-watch-now-you-see-me</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07J44Lp9JvKO7XayVkrSJ5A</guid>
      <description>Find out how to watch 'Now You See Me,' 'Now You See Me 2,' and 'Now You See Me: Now You Don't' online &#8212; including where each movie is streaming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's TikTok deal is another step closer to finally actually happening</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/trumps-tiktok-deal-is-another-step-closer-to-finally-actually-happening-001813404.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ccc84bb-09a9-492d-89a7-fa195ff1b297</guid>
      <description>Remember back in September when President Donald Trump signed an executive order that seemingly finalized some of the terms of a deal to spin off TikTok's US business? Three months later, that same deal is apparently one step closer to being official.According to Bloomberg, TikTok CEO Shou Chew told employees that TikTok and ByteDance had signed off the agreement for control of TikTok's US business. It sounds like terms of the deal are roughly the same as what Trump announced earlier this year. A group of US investors, including Oracle, Silver Lake and MGX will control a majority of the new en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Awards 2025: Live updates from the red carpet and beyond</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/tiktok-awards-2025-live-updates-winners</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05vSACwBvCM0fVYa2zD7U44</guid>
      <description>Creators take center stage as TikTok turns its For You Page into a live awards show &#8212; follow along for real-time updates all night.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
