<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:23:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>My business travel essential goes everywhere with me - and it probably isn't what you'd expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/my-business-travel-essential-goes-everywhere-with-me-and-it-probably-isnt-what-youd-expect</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Gx5H2L8GoG5FqR8ijQHoki</guid>
      <description>The Skysper foldable backpack may not be the peak of human ingenuity, but I've found it to be an absolute essential for business travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus vies for fastest mini PC ever with Panther Lake NUC 16 Pro &#8212; B390 GPU inside the Core Ultra X9 388H impresses but won't beat the 8060S</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/asus-vies-for-fastest-mini-pc-ever-with-panther-lake-nuc-16-pro-b390-gpu-inside-the-core-ultra-x9-388h-impresses-but-wont-beat-the-8060s</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gEyYpKjn6b7FYBKhx5s4n</guid>
      <description>The Panther Lake based Asus NUC 16 Pro blends strong integrated graphics with leading AI performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s on your desk, Stevie Bonifield?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/850479/desk-pc-keyboard-razer-kobo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850479</guid>
      <description>Stevie Bonifield is a news writer here at The Verge and, they say, &#8220;I cover a little bit of just about everything, from the FCC to AI shopping tools to Linux.&#8221; Before joining our news team, they wrote weekend news for PC Gamer and did reviews, news, features, and guides for Laptop Mag, along with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Playdate gets its Monument Valley</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/859675/diora-review-playdate-monument-valley</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859675</guid>
      <description>Diora might be the most ambitious game I've played on the Playdate. It's all about perspective: You turn the handheld's crank to rotate your viewpoint of the bite-size 3D landscapes, which lets you peek around corners to find solutions to various puzzles. On a device with a 1-bit, black-and-white display, the miniature worlds feel miraculous, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Wildcard Round 2026 Free Streams: How to Watch Rams vs Panthers, Packers vs Bears From Anywhere in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/nfl-wildcard-round-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iciH8RXCMG6HNbmWnZNqJL</guid>
      <description>Saturday sees the first of six Wildcard games this postseason and here's how you can watch NFL Wildcard Round 2026 games for free and from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From rollable screens to a new AI tabletop companion - 5 of the best new Lenovo releases we saw at CES to boost your office...and one coming soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/from-rollable-screens-to-a-new-ai-tabletop-companion-5-of-the-best-new-lenovo-releases-we-saw-at-ces-to-boost-your-office-and-one-coming-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXwsQ7PrarPSStds2q2kNS</guid>
      <description>Rollable screens, sensor hubs, and the most powerful ThinkPads ever - we go hands-on with Lenovo's top CES 2026 products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to change location with a VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-change-location-with-a-vpn-140000339.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b143258-aaec-4e80-aceb-3402b72d930e</guid>
      <description>Chances are that you're here because you've heard a virtual private network (VPN) can change your virtual location, and want to know what that means. If you know already, head over to my best VPN list to learn which services I recommend for changing your location. But if you're clueless, read on.Whenever any device connects to the internet &#8212; whether it's a laptop, a phone or a smart Lego brick &#8212; it's assigned a unique IP address that other devices can use to identify it. Think of the name you give the barista at a coffee shop, except instead of a hot beverage, you&#8217;re being served websites and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Je suis mont&#233; &#224; bord de la Zeekr 7GT : pourquoi cette voiture &#233;lectrique qui recharge en 13 minutes m&#8217;a mis une claque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/zeekr/2937733_je-suis-monte-a-bord-de-la-zeekr-7gt-pourquoi-jai-hate-quelle-arrive-en-france</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/zeekr/2937733_je-suis-monte-a-bord-de-la-zeekr-7gt-pourquoi-jai-hate-quelle-arrive-en-france</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s des mois d'attente, la Zeekr 7GT arrive enfin en Europe. Cette voiture &#233;lectrique promet un style spectaculaire, des technologies dernier cri, une recharge ultra-rapide... et elle sera bient&#244;t vendue en France. Voici mes premi&#232;res impressions.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World&#8217;s Oceans Soaked Up Record-Breaking Heat for the 9th Straight Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-worlds-oceans-soaked-up-record-breaking-heat-for-the-9th-straight-year-2000708348</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708348</guid>
      <description>The global ocean heat content increased yet again in 2025, further raising the risk of catastrophic storms, seal level rise, and coral bleaching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CES 2026 stuff I might actually buy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859808/ces-2026-best-gadgets-installer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859808</guid>
      <description>Hi, friends! Welcome to Installer No. 111, your guide to the best and Verge-iest stuff in the world. (If you're new here, welcome, hope you had a wonderful holiday season, and also you can read all the old editions at the Installer homepage.) This week, I've been reading about gerrymandering and watch conventions and John [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A charity speedrunning event has turned into a perfect showcase for smaller games</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/859891/awesome-games-done-quick-2026-indie-games-small-saga</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859891</guid>
      <description>Games Done Quick, the biannual charity speedrunning event currently going on right now, not only helps organizations like the Prevent Cancer Foundation and Doctors Without Borders - it helps indie games get noticed, too. Indie game developers face an incredible uphill battle not only getting their projects funded, completed, and launched, but discovered as well. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branded entertainment will just be entertainment in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462980/branded-entertainment-will-just-be-entertainment-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462980/branded-entertainment-will-just-be-entertainment-in-2026</guid>
      <description>What marketers need to know to win in the new battle for attention, as Instagram heads to TV and Hollywood wants their money.
We&#8217;ve had branded entertainment since Procter &amp; Gamble invented soap operas back in the 1930s. But today, brands are forced to diversify the ways in which they gain and hold our attention. It&#8217;s no longer as viable or effective to depend on traditional paid media tools.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette mini borne d&#8217;arcade avec 45 jeux perd plus de 40 % de son prix chez Amazon pour les soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936511_cette-mini-borne-darcade-avec-45-jeux-perd-plus-de-40-de-son-prix-chez-amazon-pour-les-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936511_cette-mini-borne-darcade-avec-45-jeux-perd-plus-de-40-de-son-prix-chez-amazon-pour-les-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Entre un design qui tient dans la main et 45 jeux disponibles, cette mini borne d'arcade de la marque Unico pourra vous assurer de longues heures de jeu. Amazon profite des soldes d'hiver pour retirer 41 % de son prix et la faire passer &#224; 59,49 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Deals for New Year&#8217;s Resolutions: Sleep, Fitness, and More (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-years-resolution-deals-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69612e3b4169e08c999c69d5</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re hitting the gym or tracking your schedule, these discounts on WIRED-approved gear can help.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
