<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:25:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>5 reasons why this Samsung vacuum is my #1 home gadget of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/5-reasons-why-this-samsung-vacuum-is-my-1-home-gadget-of-the-year</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GZajgxeTHyVKiNFBS54gcW</guid>
      <description>Beautiful and functional &#8211; what more could you want from a vacuum?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build safe danger and make teams come alive</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457680/safe-danger-teams-come-alive</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457680/safe-danger-teams-come-alive</guid>
      <description>Safe Danger creates the space for everyone to engage.
Below, Ben Swire shares five key insights from his new book,&#160;Safe Danger: An Unexpected Method for Sparking Connection, Finding Purpose, and Inspiring Innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the dollar closes out a dismal year, here&#8217;s what to expect in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468141/dollar-dismal-year-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468141/dollar-dismal-year-2025</guid>
      <description>Longer-term views for dollar weakness notwithstanding, a near-term rebound for the dollar is not to be ruled out, investors cautioned.
A dismal year for the U.S. dollar is ending with signs of stabilization, but many investors believe the currency&#8217;s decline will resume next year as global growth picks up and the Fed eases further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term mortgage rate drops to lowest level of 2025 at 6.15%</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468137/long-term-mortgage-rate-drops-lowest-level-2025-homebuyers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468137/long-term-mortgage-rate-drops-lowest-level-2025-homebuyers</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s the lowest average long-term mortgage rate since October 3, 2024.
The average rate on a 30-year U.S. mortgage fell to its lowest level of 2025 this week, an encouraging sign for prospective home buyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street slides on the final day of 2025 to close out a record year</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468133/wall-street-slides-final-day-2025-record-year</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468133/wall-street-slides-final-day-2025-record-year</guid>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500, which set 39 record highs in 2025, is up about 17%&#160;for the year, it&#8217;s third straight double-digit annual gain.
U.S. stocks are slipping in afternoon trading Wednesday as Wall Street closes out a banner year for markets driven by both optimism and uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 good things that happened in 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/2025-good-things</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">059g7uMW78H836JMruDpDa6</guid>
      <description>This year had its share of negative news, but here's our selection of the good, positive, upbeat and uplifting stories you may be craving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims drop to one-month low to cap a tough year for job market</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468130/jobless-claims-one-month-low-bumpy-year-job-market</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468130/jobless-claims-one-month-low-bumpy-year-job-market</guid>
      <description>Claims have been volatile in recent weeks amid challenges in adjusting the data for seasonal fluctuations ahead of the holiday season.
Americans filed the fewest new jobless claims in a month last week, and while the number of unemployed workers collecting relief payments has eased from recent highs, there is little indication of a break from the weak hiring environment that settled in over the course of President Donald Trump&#8216;s first year back at the White House....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram chief: AI is so ubiquitous 'it will be more practical to fingerprint real media than fake media'</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/instagram-chief-ai-is-so-ubiquitous-it-will-be-more-practical-to-fingerprint-real-media-than-fake-media-202620080.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f349227-b021-4270-a8fc-3fa8bea3d692</guid>
      <description>It's no secret that AI-generated content took over our social media feeds in 2025. Now, Instagram's top exec Adam Mosseri has made it clear that he expects AI content to overtake non-AI imagery and the significant implications that shift has for its creators and photographers.Mosseri shared the thoughts in a lengthy post about the broader trends he expects to shape Instagram in 2026. And he offered a notably candid assessment on how AI is upending the platform. "Everything that made creators matter&#8212;the ability to be real, to connect, to have a voice that couldn&#8217;t be faked&#8212;is now suddenly acces...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
