<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:23:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AI models are starting to crack high-level math problems</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/ai-models-are-starting-to-crack-high-level-math-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082724</guid>
      <description>Since the release of GPT 5.2, AI tools have become inescapable in high-level mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla just switched to a Netflix-style subscription model for Full Self-Driving &#8211; here's why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/dash-cams/tesla-just-switched-to-a-netflix-style-subscription-model-for-full-self-driving-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">trvah5Jocpry5dsdtgD3aZ</guid>
      <description>Musk moves self-driving technology to subscription model only as of February 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackstone, General Atlantic-backed Liftoff Mobile files for IPO</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/blackstone-general-atlantic-backed-liftoff-mobile-files-for-ipo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082643</guid>
      <description>The company offers a platform that helps mobile app developers market their wares and has an army of bankers working on its IPO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI&#8217;s Hacking Skills Are Approaching an &#8216;Inflection Point&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-models-hacking-inflection-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965470bbf96e65096dda90d</guid>
      <description>AI models are getting so good at finding vulnerabilities that some experts say the tech industry might need to rethink how software is built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digg launches its new Reddit rival to the public</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/digg-launches-its-new-reddit-rival-to-the-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082570</guid>
      <description>Digg, a reboot of an earlier social news site, is now relaunching as a Reddit competitor focused on communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose&#8217;s first-gen QC Ultra headphones have returned to their best price to date</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/861286/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-headphones-steam-detective-fest-sale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:56:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861286</guid>
      <description>This year&#8217;s CES introduced a bevy of unique headphones, including Fender&#8217;s first set and a pair that roll up to become a Bluetooth speaker when you want to share your music with friends. However, despite the interesting advancements, we doubt any of them will dethrone our favorite pair for travel: the Bose QuietComfort Ultra Headphones. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s first original podcasts star Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861971/netflix-original-podcasts-pete-davidson-michael-irvin</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:56:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861971</guid>
      <description>Netflix is launching its first pair of original video podcasts, hosted by Saturday Night Live alum Pete Davidson and NFL commentator and former star Michael Irvin. While The Pete Davidson Show makes its debut on January 30th, you can find Irvin's The White House on the streaming service on January 19th. The two shows will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon Outage Knocks Out US Mobile Service, Including Some 911 Calls</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/verizon-outage-knocks-out-us-mobile-service-including-some-911-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967dbfa585d9a70fc535833</guid>
      <description>A major Verizon outage appeared to impact customers across the United States starting around noon ET on Wednesday. Calls to Verizon customers from other carriers may also be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network appears to be having technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Verizon customers on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even the network provider&#8217;s own status page is struggling to load during the outage.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started growing around 12PM ET and now number in the hundreds of thousands...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon&#8217;s wireless network is down for many people nationwide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861956/verizon-is-down-outage-cell-wireless-service-sos-mode</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:44:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861956</guid>
      <description>The first big outage of 2026 is here, as Verizon customers across the US, including several of our phones, complain that service has been spotty or nonexistent starting at around noon ET, with phones switching to SOS Mode and being unable to connect. This cell service outage follows a "software issue" that cut off service [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Gemini&#8217;s &#8216;Personal Intelligence&#8217; Pulls from Your Search and YouTube History</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-geminis-personal-intelligence-pulls-from-your-search-and-youtube-history-2000710312</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710312</guid>
      <description>Personalization that is maybe a bit too personal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Trends Explore page gets new Gemini capabilities</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/googles-trends-explore-page-gets-new-gemini-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082705</guid>
      <description>The Trends Explore page for users to analyze search interest just got a major upgrade. It now uses Gemini to identify and compare relevant trends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPEngine buys major WordPress agency in drive to add more enterprise customers faster</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/wpengine-buys-major-wordpress-agency-in-drive-to-add-more-enterprise-customers-faster</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7DsBDEExqPC7Mrf4TyB2un</guid>
      <description>WP Engine acquires Big Bite, ending its agency role and integrating engineers internally to expand WordPress products for publishers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 30 Most Anticipated Films of 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/most-anticipated-movies-2026-ranked-2000708402</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708402</guid>
      <description>Here are the sci-fi, fantasy, horror, animated, and superhero movies we're most excited about coming out this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's new Cowork tool offers Claude coding help to non-experts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/anthropics-new-cowork-tool-offers-claude-coding-help-to-non-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vmYiuq5re8ogYbWViMo2ph</guid>
      <description>Cowork will make plans and execute tasks just like a colleague, so all you have to do is tell it what you want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A critical climate trend just reversed&#8212;driven by crypto and data centers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474856/climate-change-trend-just-reversed-ai-data-centers-crypto-mining-coal-pushed-us-greenhouse-gas-emissions-up</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474856/climate-change-trend-just-reversed-ai-data-centers-crypto-mining-coal-pushed-us-greenhouse-gas-emissions-up</guid>
      <description>After two years in decline, the United States&#8217; greenhouse gas emissions grew more than its economy in 2025.
After two years of declines, United States greenhouse gas emissions increased in 2025&#8212;a change driven by increased electricity use, due in part to data centers and cryptocurrency mining, as well as cold winter temperatures that meant homes required more heating....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini is winning</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/861863/google-gemini-ai-race-winner</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:16:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861863</guid>
      <description>If you want to win in AI - and I mean win in the biggest, most lucrative, most shape-the-world-in-your-image kind of way - you have to do a bunch of hard things simultaneously. You need to have a model that is unquestionably one of the best on the market. You need the nearly infinite resources [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoFundMe Campaign for Autoworker Who Got the Middle Finger From Trump Hits $340,000</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gofundme-campaign-for-autoworker-who-got-the-middle-finger-from-trump-hits-340000-2000710238</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710238</guid>
      <description>The autoworker called the president a "pedophile protector," a reference to his suppression of the Epstein files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus Game Catalog additions for January include Resident Evil Village and Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/ps-plus-game-catalog-additions-for-january-include-resident-evil-village-and-like-a-dragon-infinite-wealth-181501574.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b08ae624-21a4-4141-b0bf-3e32e5c6ca56</guid>
      <description>Sony just announced January's Game Catalog additions for PS Plus subscribers and it's a fantastic lineup. All of these titles will be ready to play on January 20.

First up, there's Resident Evil Village. This is a direct sequel to 2017&#8217;s Resident Evil 7: Biohazard. It's a full game with plenty of jump scares and an engrossing narrative. It's set in a spooky village, thus the name, and a nearby castle. This shouldn't disappoint fans of the franchise and will be available for both PS4 and PS5.

Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth is a 2024 sequel to Yakuza: Like a Dragon. It was a massive hit upon r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Why your phone says SOS, what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-outage-phone-sos-what-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b3BjNJgL2nDXUlVE7I4JU</guid>
      <description>There appears to be a major Verizon outage. Here's what to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He could just turn it off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/he-could-just-turn-it-off-180209551.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d0e43da-f59d-4728-986e-a3a7a9681a7c</guid>
      <description>Generative AI, we are repeatedly told, is a transformative and complicated technology. So complicated that its own creators are unable to explain why it acts the way it does, and so transformative that we'd be fools to stand in the way of progress. Even when progress resembles a machine for undressing strangers without their consent on an unprecedented scale, as has been the case of late with Elon Musk's Grok chatbot.&#160;
UK Prime Minister Kier Starmer seems to have so fully bought into the grand lie of the AI bubble that he was willing to announce:
"I have been informed this morning that X is ac...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to turn off a VPN on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-turn-off-a-vpn-on-iphone-180000533.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7934a72d-401b-46dd-b5d3-718c51489445</guid>
      <description>Look, virtual private networks are great &#8212; I wouldn't have made a list of the best VPNs if I didn't recommend using them. But being able to control your own technology is also important. A VPN can provide protection and peace of mind when used properly, but you may not want it active on your phone all the time.For example: Are your Google search results suddenly in German? That&#8217;s one example of what can happen if you leave your virtual location set to Berlin or Vienna. Or maybe a VPN you installed for work or to watch a single tennis match is persistently trying to keep itself active.The point...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les iPhone 17 ont tout &#233;cras&#233;, mais la victoire d&#8217;Apple me laisse un go&#251;t &#233;trange</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/editoid/2942513_les-iphone-17-ont-tout-ecrase-mais-la-victoire-dapple-me-laisse-un-gout-etrange</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/editoid/2942513_les-iphone-17-ont-tout-ecrase-mais-la-victoire-dapple-me-laisse-un-gout-etrange</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu ce carton ? Apple est num&#233;ro 1 mondial en volume et en valeur pour la troisi&#232;me ann&#233;e cons&#233;cutive. Mais personnellement, cette domination totale me laisse un arri&#232;re-go&#251;t amer.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon has our favorite tech gadgets on sale &#8212; here are 19 deals that I recommend on cheap TVs, headphones, smartwatches, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/amazon-has-our-favorite-tech-gadgets-on-sale-here-are-19-deals-that-i-recommend-on-cheap-tvs-headphones-smartwatches-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pzcFupmzNWHiCXrY6sTLTZ</guid>
      <description>Amazon's winter clearance sale has discounts on our favorite tech gadgets, and I've rounded up the 19 best deals that I recommend from Apple, JBL, Fitbit, and Sony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidentally deleted treasured photos? We have just the service for you - and it's on sale right now this New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/accidentally-deleted-treasured-photos-we-have-just-the-service-for-you-and-its-on-sale-right-now-this-new-year</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RjNWhpENVBRxoEeRaqvAWV</guid>
      <description>Stellar Photo Recovery is our top rated service - and it's up to &#163;80 off!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Atlantic, Penske, and Vox Media have all sued Google for antitrust violations</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861897/atlantic-penske-vox-google-ad-tech-antitrust-lawsuits</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T12:47:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861897</guid>
      <description>Lawsuits seeking damages from Google's illegal ad tech monopoly are piling up following the Justice Department's successful antitrust case. Vox Media, The Verge's parent company, is the latest in a wave of media companies that have filed suit against Google, seeking to be reimbursed for the monopoly profits the tech company allegedly made at publishers' [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X hasn&amp;#8217;t really stopped Grok AI from undressing women in the UK</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861894/grok-still-undressing-in-uk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T12:47:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861894</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's X is trying to stop people using its AI chatbot Grok to undress women amid intensifying outrage and legal scrutiny over the deluge of nonconsensual sexual deepfakes flooding the site. It's not trying very hard: it took us less than a minute to get around its latest attempt to rein in the chatbot. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get three months of Audible for only $3</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-three-months-of-audible-for-only-3-193859098.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>Have a hankering for some audiobooks? Audible is holding one heck of a sale right now, giving users three months of access for $3. That's a dollar per month. This is something of a winter tradition for the Amazon-owned platform and the promotion ends on January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated titles. Think of it like N...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The viral Kodak Charmera is the worst camera I&#8217;ve ever used &#8211; but it&#8217;s so bad and so retro, that I actually love it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/compact-cameras/the-viral-kodak-charmera-is-the-worst-camera-ive-ever-used-but-its-so-bad-and-so-retro-that-i-actually-love-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Titn5eWygNBqWWWPVry8Qb</guid>
      <description>Kodak, the prominent producer of cheap compact cameras, goes even smaller and cheaper with the Charmera keychain camera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Proves It Still Has the Best Software for Better-Looking Games</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nvidia-proves-it-still-has-the-best-software-for-better-looking-games-2000710251</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710251</guid>
      <description>While 6x frame gen won&#8217;t be here until spring, better AI upscaling is more than welcome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>En solde &#224; -50 %, le Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 est toujours une r&#233;f&#233;rence en mati&#232;re de smartphone pliable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2943063_en-solde-a-50-le-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-6-est-toujours-une-reference-en-matiere-de-smartphone-pliable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2943063_en-solde-a-50-le-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-6-est-toujours-une-reference-en-matiere-de-smartphone-pliable</guid>
      <description>
Samsung est toujours un mod&#232;le en mati&#232;re de smartphone pliable et ce Galaxy Z Flip 6 ne fait pas exception. Chez Carrefour, vous pourrez le retrouver pour 559,99 euros au lieu de 1 199,99 euros si vous choisissez l'option de livraison.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major US healthcare breach exposes data on 145,000 patients - Central Maine Healthcare reveals all</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/major-us-healthcare-breach-exposes-data-on-145-000-patients-central-maine-healthcare-reveals-all</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fT2TyKbHJn9VoQNWsp5c7n</guid>
      <description>Names, health insurance information, and SSNs were all exposed in a breach which lasted for more than two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These PSVR 2 demos and game trials are must-plays if you recently picked up Sony's latest VR headset</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/these-psvr-2-demos-and-game-trials-are-must-plays-if-you-recently-picked-up-sonys-latest-vr-headset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Q49HYiWaayjZgUQ52Z5K5n</guid>
      <description>PSVR 2 free demos are mostly offered via PS Plus Premium, though they're well worth checking out. Here's five game trials and demos to get you started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Auto : pourquoi un bug majeur rend Google Assistant inutilisable pour de nombreux conducteurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/2943193_android-auto-pourquoi-un-bug-majeur-rend-google-assistant-inutilisable-pour-de-nombreux-conducteurs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/2943193_android-auto-pourquoi-un-bug-majeur-rend-google-assistant-inutilisable-pour-de-nombreux-conducteurs</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez remarqu&#233; ? Depuis quelques semaines, votre voiture semble &#234;tre devenue sourde. Vous demandez un itin&#233;raire, et Google Assistant vous r&#233;pond ce fatidique "Je n'ai pas compris". Ce n'est pas votre microphone qui d&#233;raille, c'est Google qui g&#232;re (tr&#232;s) mal sa transition vers Gemini. Et franchement, &#231;a commence &#224; bien faire.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flamb&#233;e de la RAM&#160;: le patron de Nothing annonce des hausses de prix pour ses smartphones</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/flambee-de-la-ram-le-patron-de-nothing-annonce-des-hausses-de-prix-pour-ses-smartphones.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320152</guid>
      <description>2026 sera l'ann&#233;e o&#249; la course &#224; l'&#233;chalote des caract&#233;ristiques techniques prendra fin, ass&#232;ne Carl Pei, le fondateur et patron de Nothing. Et pour cause : les composants comme la m&#233;moire vont co&#251;ter si cher que les constructeurs (en dehors du tr&#232;s haut de gamme) devront se contenter de peu tout en offrant quand m&#234;me &#224; leurs utilisateurs des nouveaut&#233;s qui tirent le march&#233; vers le haut....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK digital ID plans will no longer be mandatory</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861890/uk-backpeddles-mandatory-digital-id-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T12:36:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861890</guid>
      <description>The United Kingdom has walked back plans to make its upcoming digital ID scheme a mandatory requirement for working adults. While the UK government remains "committed to mandatory digital right-to-work checks," an unspecified government spokesperson told The Times, digital ID will now be optional when the initiative is introduced sometime in 2029. The national digital [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon is down, with many users seeing 'SOS' &#8211; here's everything we know about this outage</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/verizon-outage-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">w5FfiYa27ckqf9uyidVpzF</guid>
      <description>Verizon is experiencing issues as of midday on January 14, 2026, with many users reporting no service and seeing an SOS icon instead of bars. TechRadar is following this story and has reached out to Verizon for more information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;In AI models, the real bottleneck isn&#8217;t computing power &#8212; it&#8217;s memory&#8217;: Phison CEO on 244TB SSDs, PLC NAND, why high-bandwidth flash isn&#8217;t a good idea, and why CSP profit goes hand in hand with storage capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/in-ai-models-the-real-bottleneck-isnt-computing-power-its-memory-phison-ceo-on-244tb-ssds-plc-nand-why-high-bandwidth-flash-isnt-a-good-idea-and-why-csp-profit-goes-hand-in-hand-with-storage-capacity</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcmQFjwbXzjcz3PJYrBXDA</guid>
      <description>Phison CEO tells us about 244TB SSDs, PLC NAND, and why High Bandwidth Flash is not a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 6 Apple apps just got hit by a subscription bombshell &#8211;but users say there&#8217;s an even bigger crime</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/these-6-apple-apps-just-got-hit-by-a-subscription-bombshell-but-users-say-theres-an-even-bigger-crime</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">r9PSuXBExExK9ob2jSixMn</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s Creator Studio subscription locks features behind a paywall and comes with some unpopular new icons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lovehoney has tons of V-Day goodies on sale: Get 50% off vibrators, lingerie, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-lovehoney-valentines-day-sale-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043ce0SfpcyXmTCq7Rp9A84</guid>
      <description>Save up to 70% at Lovehoney's Valentine's Day sale. Get clitoral suction toys for $43, lingerie under $25, and a free gift on orders over $89.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy&#8217;s Edge Will Soon Cover All Eras of &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/galaxys-edge-will-soon-cover-all-eras-of-star-wars-2000710279</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710279</guid>
      <description>Disney's 'Star Wars' land is moving on from its original setting during the Sequel Trilogy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Finally Figured Out How Some People Get Drunk Without Drinking</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-finally-figured-out-how-some-people-get-drunk-without-drinking-2000710220</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710220</guid>
      <description>Gut microbes can make people drunk without booze. Scientists now know which ones to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Incroyablement mauvais&#160;&#187; : le patron de GOG d&#233;truit Windows et encense Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2943179_incroyablement-mauvais-le-patron-de-gog-detruit-windows-et-encense-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2943179_incroyablement-mauvais-le-patron-de-gog-detruit-windows-et-encense-linux</guid>
      <description>
Vous trouvez que Windows 11 devient une usine &#224; gaz publicitaire ? Vous n'&#234;tes pas seul. Le propri&#233;taire de GOG vient de tirer &#224; boulets rouges sur l'OS de Microsoft, qu'il a personnellement abandonn&#233; pour&#8230; un Mac. Mais la vraie info est ailleurs : GOG pr&#233;pare sa riposte sur Linux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dream-team combo: The new Rubiks Cube Tetris Brainteaser joins two of the best classic games</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/rubiks-cube-tetris-brainteaster</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04omS24IA2rY04PvvcYhqdW</guid>
      <description>The new Rubik's Cube Tetris Brainteaser is on sale at Target and Amazon, combining the two classic games into one.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
