<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:32:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enfin un vrai chatbot pour Siri&#160;? Apple le lancerait cet automne</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/enfin-un-vrai-chatbot-pour-siri-apple-le-lancerait-cet-automne.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321715</guid>
      <description>Des ann&#233;es apr&#232;s ses principaux rivaux, Apple lancerait finalement son propre chatbot. Il remplacerait l'interface textuelle actuelle de Siri et permettrait de discuter de tout et de rien, sans oublier de nombreuses autres fonctions in&#233;dites pour l'assistant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's smarter, long-promised AI-powered Siri might be arriving in a few months, according to a new report</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/apple-intelligence/apples-smarter-long-promised-ai-powered-siri-might-be-arriving-in-a-few-months-according-to-a-new-report</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zD9rwFjf4MJgVAMSGBCzA3</guid>
      <description>According to a new report from Bloomberg, Apple might ship the AI-powered Siri, first teased in June 2024, which is way more personal, in a few months with iOS 26.4 and Gemini under Apple's Foundational Models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Floppy disks are the best storage media ever invented' - dad modder creates an ingenious TV control system that lets toddler select shows with the iconic storage device</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/floppy-disks-are-the-best-storage-media-ever-invented-dad-modder-creates-an-ingenious-tv-control-system-that-lets-toddler-select-shows-with-the-iconic-storage-device</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Dme6DyRAjcEzgJk4ogs8KF</guid>
      <description>Floppy disks have become a physical TV selector, letting toddlers choose shows simply while avoiding menus, ads, and complex television interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marshall's new Heddon hub adds multi-room audio to speakers with Auracast</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/marshalls-new-heddon-hub-adds-multi-room-audio-to-speakers-with-auracast-210500811.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50db7c1b-a753-43cd-8e92-4ba129abc454</guid>
      <description>Marshall plans to add seamless multi-room audio to its Bluetooth speakers via a newly announced music streaming hub called Heddon. The $300 hub makes it possible to connect and synchronize multiple older Marshall speakers together, not unlike Sonos' audio devices.Rather than use Wi-Fi to get multiple speakers playing the same audio, though, the Marshall Heddon uses Auracast. The hub connects to services like Spotify Connect or Tidal over Wi-Fi, or other devices through Google Cast and AirPlay, and then shares that audio over Auracast to the Marshall Acton III, Stanmore III and Wobrun III speak...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;It: Welcome to Derry&#8217; Season 2 Is All But Confirmed</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/it-welcome-to-derry-season-2-is-all-but-confirmed-2000699507</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699507</guid>
      <description>Fans have been waiting for official word on whether HBO's Stephen King adaptation from co-creators Andy Muschietti, Barbara Muschietti, and Jason Fuchs will return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is reportedly overhauling Siri to be an AI chatbot</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/apple-is-reportedly-overhauling-siri-to-be-an-ai-chatbot-205303818.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03530a8f-d58d-49e6-b038-e3c218d634cf</guid>
      <description>Apple has been spinning its wheels for many months over its approach to artificial intelligence, but a strategy finally appears to be emerging for the company. Bloomberg's Mark Gurman reported today that Apple's long-awaited Siri overhaul will allegedly involve transforming the voice assistant into an AI chatbot, internally called Campos.&#160;Sources have reportedly told Gurman that Apple chatbot will completely replace the current Siri interface in favor of a more interactive model similar to those used by OpenAI's ChatGPT and Google's Gemini. He also cited sources who claimed that while Apple ha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Pirates of the Caribbean&#8217; Director Has a Theory on Why Visual FX Suck So Much Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-director-has-a-theory-on-why-visual-fx-suck-so-much-now-2000712660</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712660</guid>
      <description>Gore Verbinski says the software behind modern blockbusters may be the real problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#8217;d Be Surprised How Few Companies Are Behind Half the World&#8217;s CO2 Emissions</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youd-be-surprised-how-few-companies-are-behind-half-the-worlds-co2-emissions-2000712658</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712658</guid>
      <description>Fortunately, emissions data is increasingly being used to hold these companies accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A massive Microsoft Surface sale is underway at Amazon and Best Buy &#8212; score 'the best Surface ever' for its lowest-ever price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows-laptops/a-massive-microsoft-surface-sale-is-underway-at-amazon-and-best-buy-score-the-best-surface-ever-for-its-lowest-ever-price</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ke6587cdELrSgYSxzTpUW</guid>
      <description>Several Microsoft Surface devices are on sale at record-low prices, and even with new models rumoured to be announced soon, these are well worth buying if you want a great value laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is reportedly developing a wearable AI pin</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/apple-is-reportedly-developing-a-wearable-ai-pin-204705065.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3512fe01-96f9-404d-bb5c-4712d6f3dcc9</guid>
      <description>Apple will reportedly try to succeed where Humane failed (miserably). On Wednesday, The Information reported that the iPhone maker is working on an AI pin. The wearable is said to resemble a slightly thicker AirTag and include multiple cameras, a speaker, microphones, and wireless charging.The report coincides with another from Bloomberg that claims that Apple will revamp Siri as a ChatGPT-style chatbot. When combined with the recent announcement that Google's Gemini will power Siri AI, it looks like the company is finally making a more defined play for a piece of the generative AI pie. On the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Apple does about-face on Siri chatbot &#8212; and it might compete directly with ChatGPT and Google</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/report-apple-does-about-face-on-siri-chatbot-and-it-might-compete-directly-with-chatgpt-and-google</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vdo6maNvMamVuvdBgfL35J</guid>
      <description>Is Apple building an entirely new Siri Chatbot? One rumor says that's the new plan, even if it's the opposite of what Apple execs once told us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple pourrait lancer un badge connect&#233; de la taille d&#8217;un AirTag</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/apple-pourrait-lancer-un-badge-connecte-de-la-taille-dun-airtag.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321713</guid>
      <description>Et si Humane avait eu raison avant tout le monde ? Le badge connect&#233; de la d&#233;funte start-up, l'Ai Pin, a &#233;t&#233; un &#233;chec retentissant. Mais l'id&#233;e en elle-m&#234;me pourrait &#234;tre reprise par d'autres&#8230; et pourquoi pas Apple ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new LinkedIn phishing scam is targeting executives online - make sure you don't fall for this</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-new-linkedin-phishing-scam-is-targeting-executives-online-make-sure-you-dont-fall-for-this</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SSYLKuXXnasgrxfcGH823H</guid>
      <description>A little bit of Python, a little bit of DLL sideloading, and a little bit of fake jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps for boycotting American products surge to the top of the Danish App Store</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/21/apps-for-boycotting-american-products-surge-to-the-top-of-the-danish-app-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084674</guid>
      <description>The boost in downloads comes as Danish consumers have been organizing a grassroots boycott of American-made products, which also included canceling their U.S. vacations and ditching their subscriptions to U.S.-based streaming services, like Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s new Claude &#8216;constitution&#8217;: be helpful and honest, and don&#8217;t destroy humanity</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/865185/anthropic-claude-constitution-soul-doc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T15:36:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865185</guid>
      <description>Anthropic is overhauling Claude's so-called "soul doc." The new missive is a 57-page document titled "Claude's Constitution," which details "Anthropic's intentions for the model's values and behavior," aimed not at outside readers but the model itself. The document is designed to spell out Claude's "ethical character" and "core identity," including how it should balance conflicting [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 Grammy Awards: Who&#8217;s performing, how to watch, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478718/2026-grammys-bad-bunny-kendrick-lamar-lady-gaga</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T20:35:38</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478718/2026-grammys-bad-bunny-kendrick-lamar-lady-gaga</guid>
      <description>The main show will air live on CBS beginning at 8 p.m. Eastern on Feb. 1 as well as several streaming platforms.
The 68th annual Grammy Awards will take place Feb. 1 at the Crypto.com Arena in Los Angeles. This year marks a return to normalcy after&#160;the 2025 award show&#160;was altered to focus on supporting relief efforts following the&#160;devastating Los Angeles-area wildfires....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irony alert: Hallucinated citations found in papers from NeurIPS, the prestigious AI conference</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/21/irony-alert-hallucinated-citations-found-in-papers-from-neurips-the-prestigious-ai-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084660</guid>
      <description>Research from startup GPTZero points to the impossible problem prestigious conferences face in the age of AI slop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Type of Mattress Is Right for You? (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/mattress-types-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68370b036baf5303ef22995a</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s how to pick the best mattress for your sleep needs, straight from a professional mattress tester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland is turning the MAGA hat into a protest symbol</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477693/greenland-maga-hat-protest-symbol</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477693/greenland-maga-hat-protest-symbol</guid>
      <description>Parody versions of President Trump&#8217;s red hat have become an emblem of the movement against his proposed Greenland takeover.
On January 17, Copenhagen resident Jesper Rabe T&#248;nnesen woke up, packed his cargo bike with 300 red hats, and trekked over to his city&#8217;s U.S. embassy, where thousands of citizens were gathering in the street to protest President Trump&#8217;s proposed takeover of Greenland. By the end of the weekend, those hats had become the dominant symbol of the dissenting movement....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineer at Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI Departs After Spilling the Beans in Podcast Interview</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/engineer-at-elon-musks-xai-departs-after-spilling-the-beans-in-podcast-interview-2000712569</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712569</guid>
      <description>Interesting timing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is turning Siri into an AI bot that&amp;#8217;s more like ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865172/apple-siri-ai-chatbot-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T15:26:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865172</guid>
      <description>Apple is planning a big Siri overhaul that will transform the voice assistant into an AI chatbot built directly into its iPhone and Mac, according to Bloomberg reporter Mark Gurman. The update is reportedly coming later this year and will replace the existing Siri interface, allowing users to interact with the assistant by both typing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Cour f&#233;d&#233;rale annule l&#8217;ordonnance de fermeture de TikTok Canada</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-21/la-cour-federale-annule-l-ordonnance-de-fermeture-de-tiktok-canada.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:13:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc4484ae3e103e4cb98675271093992b</guid>
      <description>La Cour f&#233;d&#233;rale a annul&#233; mercredi une ordonnance du gouvernement exigeant que TikTok cesse ses activit&#233;s au Canada. Cette d&#233;cision signifie que le g&#233;ant des m&#233;dias sociaux peut continuer &#224; exploiter ses bureaux au pays pendant que le gouvernement f&#233;d&#233;ral proc&#232;de &#224; un nouvel examen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You&#8217;re Not Watching &#8216;Frieren,&#8217; You&#8217;re Missing Out on the Best Fantasy Anime in Ages</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/if-youre-not-watching-frieren-youre-missing-out-on-the-best-fantasy-anime-in-ages-2000712509</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712509</guid>
      <description>The second season of 'Frieren: Beyond Journey's End' is poised to be a quintessential must-watch anime in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Roku streaming stick feature gets you a free add-on to help improve connectivity and performance</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/hidden-roku-streaming-stick-feature-gets-you-a-free-add-on-to-help-improve-connectivity-and-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4HsjoThGJEy94Adu2gHLe</guid>
      <description>Roku streaming stick users can claim a free HDMI extender. Here's how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most people now can't separate AI videos from reality, new Runway study reveals &#8211; not even its co-founder</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/most-people-now-cant-separate-ai-videos-from-reality-new-runway-study-reveals-not-even-its-co-founder</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">C3ZVhhWzm9mcQngsk6DgHj</guid>
      <description>Runway's latest AI video generator model shows that you may as well flip a coin when deciding if something is AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is human-centric design and why does it matter?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478642/what-is-human-centric-design-and-why-does-it-matter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478642/what-is-human-centric-design-and-why-does-it-matter</guid>
      <description>Often dismissed as a &#8216;soft&#8217; discipline, it&#8217;s actually the most practical route to value creation 
We have a growing problem making our institutions work for humans. Across society, and especially in business, humans are increasingly treated as resources to be squeezed rather than as individuals to be served. Employees become &#8220;human capital&#8221; to be optimized; customers become &#8220;users&#8221; to be converted or upsold. This tendency predates AI, but AI threatens to accelerate it dramatically&#8212;automating the depersonalization, scaling the indifference, and introducing another layer of abstraction that sepa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 Sundance Film Festival: Everything you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478705/2026-sundance-film-festival-everything-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478705/2026-sundance-film-festival-everything-you-need-to-know</guid>
      <description>The festival runs from Thursday, Jan. 22 through Sunday, Feb. 1. 
The 42nd&#160;Sundance Film Festival&#160;kicks off this week in Park City, Utah. It will be the last edition in its longtime home and the first without its founder Robert Redford, who&#160;died in September&#160;at age 89.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI romance is not a bug</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477856/ai-romance-is-not-a-bug</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T19:57:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477856/ai-romance-is-not-a-bug</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s Big Tech&#8217;s most dangerous feature.
OpenAI, Meta, and Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI are not accidentally drifting into romance and sex. They are deliberately inviting it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Pediatricians Say You&#8217;re Thinking Way Too Much About Screen Time Limits</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/american-pediatricians-say-youre-thinking-way-too-much-about-screen-time-limits-2000712512</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712512</guid>
      <description>Good news: There are other things to worry about.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
