<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:28:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Before &#8216;Avengers&#8217;, Simu Liu&#8217;s Brain Has Been Hacked in &#8216;The Copenhagen Test&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/simu-liu-copenhagen-test-peacock-melissa-barrera-2000696895</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696895</guid>
      <description>It's not 'Doomsday' or 'Shang Chi 2,' but Liu will soon kick ass on a a Peacock sci-fi show with Melissa Barrera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Global plans cautious venture  future with a new $2.2B fund</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/tiger-global-plans-cautious-venture-future-with-a-new-2-2b-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073794</guid>
      <description>Tiger's last fund did well with investmetments in OpenAI, Waymo and Databricks. But it warns investors that AI valuations are already 'elevated.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even Minor Video Call Glitches Could Cost You a Job&#8212;or Your Freedom</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/even-minor-video-call-glitches-could-cost-you-a-job-or-your-freedom-2000696578</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696578</guid>
      <description>Researchers found that minor connection issues during face-to-face video calls negatively impacted interpersonal judgments, with significant implications in contexts such as telehealth visits, remote interviews, and virtual parole hearings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une r&#233;volution est en cours : l&#8217;IA red&#233;finit en profondeur la mani&#232;re dont nous observons l&#8217;Univers</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-revolution-cours-ia-redefinit-profondeur-maniere-nous-observons-univers-127675/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:07:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-revolution-cours-ia-redefinit-profondeur-maniere-nous-observons-univers-127675/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Franck Marchis est un astronome et plan&#233;tologue franco-am&#233;ricain travaillant &#224; l'Institut Seti. Il y a plusieurs d&#233;cennies, il avait pr&#233;vu l'essor de l'optique adaptative qui a depuis transform&#233; l'astronomie. Il pr&#233;dit aujourd'hui une nouvelle transformation mais en raison des d&#233;veloppements de...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android XR chief on the moment he realized &#8212; 'Things have changed. This is very different. This is very new. It's very powerful.'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/android-xr-head-on-the-ecosystem-we-think-that-this-is-actually-a-very-early-space-and-the-history-is-not-yet-written-for-it</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JT6sb8besrERkNutzRBhQ9</guid>
      <description>What's the future of Android XR? We spoke to Juston Payne, Google's Senior Director of Product Management for XR, to find out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They can build a hospital in a weekend': Nvidia CEO warns about China's big AI advantages &#8212; as report reveals it now has 30% of global AI usage</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/they-can-build-a-hospital-in-a-weekend-nvidia-ceo-warns-about-chinas-big-ai-advantages-as-report-reveals-it-now-has-30-percent-of-global-ai-usage</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rMeuCXUZ4VTM3TzPdhx7vi</guid>
      <description>Nvidia's CEO has again warned about China's swift progress and potential to move ahead in the AI race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The safest intersection on Earth (and why half the infrastructure profession hates it)</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91448151/roundabouts-safest-intersection-infrastructure-profession-hate</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91448151/roundabouts-safest-intersection-infrastructure-profession-hate</guid>
      <description>Traffic Engineering Inc. is wrong on many topics, but it&#8217;s absolutely right on this one.
Planner vs. Engineer is a well-known professional rivalry in the infrastructure world. The arguments are sometimes friendly, sometimes hostile, sometimes about important issues, sometimes insignificant. I&#8217;m in a peculiar spot because of my career as a &#8220;plangineer.&#8221; My parents helped me buy a civil engineering degree, but several years into my career, I bought the certified planning certificate. I know the two camps very well.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the new, influencer-stacked Pentagon press corps</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456633/pentagon-hegseth-influencer-loomer-higby</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456633/pentagon-hegseth-influencer-loomer-higby</guid>
      <description>&#8220;The Fake News is OUT &#8230; LifeSiteNews is IN.&#8221;
The new Pentagon press corps gathered last week for their first in-person briefing. That&#8217;s since almost all credentialed reporters from traditional media companies surrendered their passes in October to protest new Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth&#8217;s strict media policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's how Google is laying the foundation for our mixed reality future</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/heres-how-google-is-laying-the-foundation-for-our-mixed-reality-future-180000716.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">721b1f85-0f59-46bb-9f5b-7e2bab08822d</guid>
      <description>Today, during the XR edition of The Android Show, Google showed off a bunch of updates and new features headed to its mixed reality OS. And while most of the news was aimed at developers, I got a chance to demo some of the platform's expanded capabilities on a range of hardware including Samsung's Galaxy XR headset, two different reference designs and an early version of Xreal's Project Aura smart glasses and I came away rather impressed. So here's a rundown of what I saw and how it will impact the rapidly growing ecosystem of head-mounted displays.First up was one of Google's reference design...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmental groups call for halt to new data center construction</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/environmental-groups-call-for-halt-to-new-data-center-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073869</guid>
      <description>More than 230 organizations signed a public letter urging members of Congress to take action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok announces shared feed and collections features</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/tiktok-announces-shared-feed-and-collections-features-193857725.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cc61204-4a18-410c-ba62-5998daf518cd</guid>
      <description>TikTok just announced a couple of updates that that should make the app a bit more social. There's something called Shared Feed, which is exactly what it sounds like. It's a feed that friends and family can watch together, though at different times.&#160;
This feed is shared via direct messaging and pulls up relevant content to everyone involved in the chat. TikTok says this is a "new way to discover content together." It consists of a daily curated selection of 15 videos that are generated by TikTok activity.
These feeds are shared via invitation and the participants can leave the chat at any time...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount makes a $108 billion hostile takeover bid for Warner Bros. Discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/paramount-makes-a-108-billion-hostile-takeover-bid-for-warner-bros-discovery-152248473.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">889cb4f3-09c4-4ef3-b35d-213e37d0dc9a</guid>
      <description>Paramount has been none too pleased about Netflix striking an $82.7 billion deal to buy much of Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD). Now, Paramount is making a hostile takeover bid for WBD. It's making its pitch directly to WBD shareholders with an all-cash offer of $30 per share that expires on January 8.Late last week, the WBD board unanimously accepted Netflix's offer of $27.75 per share. That breaks down to $23.25 per share in cash and another $4.50 per share in Netflix stock. Netflix's overall bid is valued at $82.7 billion, while Paramount's totals $108.4 billion. There's a key difference when ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I review 4K Blu-rays for a living &#8212; these 5 new discs are so good, they've entered my TV testing rotation</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/i-review-4k-blu-rays-for-a-living-these-5-new-discs-are-so-good-theyve-entered-my-tv-testing-rotation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z66MVKDdJBsukp52p5zGWg</guid>
      <description>As a TV reviewer, it's good to update the 4K Blu-rays I use for testing. These 5 discs are the latest additions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These vintage-inspired string lights are here to fix the &#8216;blue&#8217; Christmas problem</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91454622/tru-tone-christmas-lights-vintage-christmas-decor</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91454622/tru-tone-christmas-lights-vintage-christmas-decor</guid>
      <description>Over the past few years, Christmas has become increasingly white, blue, and sterile. Tru-Tone is here to fix that.
For many who grew up visiting older relatives during the holidays, memories of childhood Christmas are swathed in a warm glow that feels like the calling card of the season: a combination of colorful bulbs, lit candles, and soft lamplight. In recent years, though, it feels like the holiday season has traded its cozy tones for a much cooler, even sterile color palette. As it turns out, that&#8217;s not just a quirk of our rosy collective memory....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why deep expertise is the secret to success for today&#8217;s entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91454854/entrepreneurs-deep-domain-expertise-secret-success</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91454854/entrepreneurs-deep-domain-expertise-secret-success</guid>
      <description>Your niche is your moat.
When Steve Jobs and Steve Wozniak built Apple in a garage, the incumbents they were up against were slow-moving hardware companies. When Jeff Bezos started Amazon, Barnes &amp; Noble wasn&#8217;t pouring billions into machine learning or cloud infrastructure. This doesn&#8217;t mean that it was easy for these entrepreneurs to change the face of whole industries. It was not. But it was at least possible. Back then, giants could be out-innovated because they were bureaucratic, cautious, and often blind to the potential of what the upstart start-ups were building....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Rivian's Autonomy and AI day and what to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/how-to-watch-rivians-autonomy-and-ai-day-and-what-to-expect-192838410.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e118d317-3aa5-4bd3-b64d-45914be2520f</guid>
      <description>Rivian is about to give the public and its investors another taste of its future with an event focused on autonomy and AI on December 11. The company's Autonomy and AI day starts at 12PM ET. You can watch the event via the Rivian website. We'll be liveblogging the Autonomy and AI day right here on Engadget, so we'll be recapping the major news as it happens and sharing our reactions.&#160;As for what to expect, the name of the event clearly indicates that Rivian will be talking about autonomous operation of its vehicles. RivianTrackr speculates, quite reasonably, that the company will share more ab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Code is coming to Slack, and that&#8217;s a bigger deal than it sounds</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/claude-code-is-coming-to-slack-and-thats-a-bigger-deal-than-it-sounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073830</guid>
      <description>Anthropic launches Claude Code in Slack, letting developers delegate coding tasks from chat threads. It's part of a shift toward AI-embedded collaboration that could reshape software workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Series 11 just got a big $100 discount ahead of the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/840161/apple-watch-series-11-holiday-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T14:17:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840161</guid>
      <description>We thought Black Friday and Cyber Monday would bring the lowest prices of the year, but apparently not. Right now, you can snag Apple&#8217;s Watch Series 11 in the 42mm configuration with GPS for a new all-time low of $299 ($100 off) at Amazon, Walmart, and Best Buy. That beats the $70 discount we saw [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount just trumped Netflix's Warner Bros deal, but I don't see how this will be good news for any of us</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-just-trumped-netflixs-warner-bros-deal-but-i-dont-see-how-this-will-be-good-news-for-any-of-us</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">u8H5xEJjeZurbGvCAedvW3</guid>
      <description>Just when you thought the Netflix plan to acquire Warner Bros. was all but a done deal, Paramount swoops in, and things just got very interesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National cybercrime network operating for 14 years dismantled in Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/national-cybercrime-network-operating-for-14-years-dismantled-in-indonesia</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ysdxEmfSKFXFNYYvaegmMG</guid>
      <description>A large network of domains, malware, and stolen credentials, has been making rounds for 14 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ron DeSantis Proposes AI Bill of Rights as Trump Says He&#8217;ll Kill State AI Laws</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ron-desantis-proposes-ai-bill-of-rights-as-trump-says-hell-kill-state-ai-laws-2000696828</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696828</guid>
      <description>A MAGA rift?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic is bringing Claude Code to Slack</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839817/anthropic-claude-code-slack-integration</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T14:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839817</guid>
      <description>Slack users can now access Anthropic's Claude Code directly in Slack by tagging Claude on coding-related messages and threads. The new feature is launching today in beta as a research preview. When Claude is tagged, it will now automatically scan the message to see if it's a coding task and, if so, route it to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The War Between the Land and the Sea&#8217; Is Off to a Soggy Start</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/war-between-the-land-and-the-sea-premiere-recap-review-doctor-who-disney-2000696766</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696766</guid>
      <description>The real war in the new 'Doctor Who' spinoff isn't between the Sea Devils and humanity, but between the show's bold ideas and a wildly uneven tone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICEBlock Sues Trump Admin Over Pressuring Apple for App Store Removal</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iceblock-sues-white-house-over-pressuring-apple-for-app-store-removal-2000696820</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696820</guid>
      <description>ICEBlock developer Joshua Aaron claims that the removal is a suppression of free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&#8217;s trade surplus tops $1 trillion for the first time&#8212;even with Trump&#8217;s tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456580/china-trade-surplus-trillion-trump-tariffs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456580/china-trade-surplus-trillion-trump-tariffs</guid>
      <description>With exports still going strong, economists generally expect China to meet its target of around 5% annual growth for this year.
China&#8217;s exports rebounded in November after an unexpected contraction the previous month, pushing its trade surplus past $1 trillion for the first time, according to data released Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X shuts down EU ad account after historic fine</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/elon-musk-x-shuts-down-eu-ad-account-after-fine-over-exploit</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02Lq3m4sHRA5BVScChuICkz</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's X has escalated its feud with the EU by banning its ad account on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All you need to know about the increasingly complex sale of Warner Bros. Discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456603/warner-brothers-discovery-netflix-paramount-david-ellison-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:50:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456603/warner-brothers-discovery-netflix-paramount-david-ellison-trump</guid>
      <description>A rundown of the deal, how it will be funded, and whether it stands a chance of clearing regulatory review.
The long battle over control of Warner Bros. Discovery took another turn Monday when Paramount Skydance announced a hostile bid for the entertainment giant, following Warner&#8217;s acceptance of a competing offer from Netflix last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta will let Facebook and Instagram users in the EU share less data</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-will-let-facebook-and-instagram-users-in-the-eu-share-less-data-183535897.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28146827-8691-41f3-b999-1d94cad68df3</guid>
      <description>Meta will soon allow Facebook and Instagram users in the European Union to choose to share less data and see less personalized ads on the platform, the European Commission announced. The change will begin to roll out in January, according to the regulator.&#160;"This is the first time that such a choice is offered on Meta's social networks," the commission said in a statement. "Meta will give users the effective choice between: consenting to share all their data and seeing fully personalised advertising, and opting to share less personal data for an experience with more limited personalised adverti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon retire 40 % de son prix &#224; ce chargeur 2-en-1 compatible MagSafe et Qi2</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2902491_amazon-retire-40-de-son-prix-a-ce-chargeur-2-en-1-compatible-magsafe-et-qi2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2902491_amazon-retire-40-de-son-prix-a-ce-chargeur-2-en-1-compatible-magsafe-et-qi2</guid>
      <description>
Ugreen propose de nombreux accessoires pour t&#233;l&#233;phone, et quelques produits qui sortent du lot comme ce chargeur &#224; induction 2-en-1 certifi&#233; Qi2 et MagSafe dont le prix passe de 39 euros &#224; 23 euros seulement sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s next gaming laptop may have a rollable OLED screen that stretches ultrawide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/840124/lenovo-rollable-legion-pro-gaming-laptop-rumor</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T13:33:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840124</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has already demonstrated its ability to put rollable OLEDs into laptops by graduating last year from demo concept models to shipping the ThinkBook Plus Gen 6, an actual device you can buy. It has a built-in mechanism that expands the screen vertically to give you more screen real estate for typing and scrolling. However, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s Optimus Robot Collapses in a Hilariously Suspicious Way</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musks-optimus-robot-collapses-in-a-hilariously-suspicious-way-2000696760</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696760</guid>
      <description>Musk says he's going to make 1 million robots per year by 2030.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s ugly, it&#8217;s beautiful, it&#8217;s how you know a game might be a classic</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/840080/square-enix-hd2d-games-octopath-dragon-quest</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840080</guid>
      <description>At their biggest and most expensive, video games all sort of look the same. The reason often comes down to simple economics: More resources means more costs that need to be recouped, and historically the way publishers have done that is by being comically risk-averse. Hence the glut of semi-realistic rocky wastelands that look like [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service drops free admission for MLK Day, Juneteenth, and adds Trump&#8217;s birthday</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456576/national-parks-free-admission-mlk-day-juneteenth-trump-birthday</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456576/national-parks-free-admission-mlk-day-juneteenth-trump-birthday</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration&#8217;s national parks cut free admission on two of the nation&#8217;s most prominent civil rights holidays.
The&#160;National Park Service&#160;will offer free admission to U.S. residents on President Donald Trump&#8216;s birthday next year &#8212; which also happens to be Flag Day &#8212; but is eliminating the benefit for Martin Luther King Jr. Day and Juneteenth....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
