<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:39:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic reportedly raising $10B at $350B valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/anthropic-reportedly-raising-10b-at-350b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080816</guid>
      <description>Anthropic is reportedly in talks to raise $10 billion at a $350 billion valuation, marking its third mega-round in a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&amp;#8217;s smart shopping cart for Whole Foods gets bigger, lighter, and adds tap-to-pay</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/857811/amazon-redesigned-dash-cart-whole-foods-fresh-launch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T13:36:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857811</guid>
      <description>Amazon is launching a revamped version of its smart shopping cart, which it plans to bring to dozens of Whole Foods locations by the end of this year, according to an announcement on Wednesday. The new Dash Cart features a "more responsive" item scanner that's now located next to the built-in display, along with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft is shutting down a studio 16 days after it unionized</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ubisoft-is-shutting-down-a-studio-16-days-after-it-unionized-183000983.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">701fb660-b898-4ce5-81ed-fc627db09153</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft is closing a Canadian studio just over two weeks after it unionized. In a dizzying claim, the company told GamesIndustry.biz that the closure of Ubisoft Halifax was part of "company-wide actions to streamline operations" and unrelated to the unionization.On December 22, Ubisoft Halifax announced that 61 of its workers had joined the Game &amp; Media Workers Guild of Canada. At the time, the studio's lead programmer, Jon Huffman, told CTV News that 73.8 percent of employees voted in favor of unionizing. Ominously in hindsight, he had described the decision as a "huge relief." The studio was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fujifilm&#8217;s new instant camera captures video with vintage effects</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857798/fujifilm-instax-mini-evo-cinema-printer-instant-camera-video-effects</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T13:29:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857798</guid>
      <description>Fujifilm is expanding its hybrid instant camera line with the new Instax Mini Evo Cinema that adds the ability to capture video clips up to 15 seconds long. The Mini Evo Cinema also features a unique design inspired by the vintage Fujica Single-8 8mm film camera that Fujifilm introduced in 1965. It will be released [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some of our favorite 4K UHD Blu-rays are three for $33 at Amazon right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/857061/amazon-4k-uhd-blu-ray-promo-genki-moonbase-charger-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T13:26:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857061</guid>
      <description>The holidays &#8212; and the copious amounts of binge-watching that come with them &#8212; are very much behind us at this point, but that doesn&#8217;t mean there won&#8217;t be time to catch up on the movies from last year (and beyond) you might have missed. Thankfully, Amazon has brought back one of the better promos [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG's CLOiD robot can fold laundry and serve food&#8230; very slowly</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/lgs-cloid-robot-can-fold-laundry-and-serve-food-very-slowly-181902306.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b19d77b-0da1-44f6-a5a3-79d6dbc2b933</guid>
      <description>When LG announced that it would demo a laundry-folding, chore-doing robot at CES 2026, I was immediately intrigued. For years, I've wandered the Las Vegas Convention Center halls and wondered when someone might create a robot that can tackle the mundane but useful tasks I despise like folding laundry. With CLOiD (pronounced like "Floyd"), LG has proven that this is theoretically possible, but probably not likely to happen any time soon.&#160;I went to the company's CES booth to watch its demonstration of CLOiD's abilities, which also include serving food, fetching objects and fitness coaching. Duri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikon's affordable travel zoom looks like a no-brainer for full-frame first timers &#8211; here's what it can do</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-lenses/nikons-affordable-travel-zoom-looks-like-a-no-brainer-for-full-frame-first-timers-heres-what-it-can-do</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eH86jaPVjjUGFiqXXVCjRR</guid>
      <description>Nikon has unveiled the Nikkor Z 24-105mm f/4-7.1 zoom lens for full-frame cameras, and it's available as a kit with the new Nikon Z5 II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown off a wide ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Fans Have Built an Elaborate Delusion Around a Secret &#8216;True&#8217; Finale</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-5-conformity-gate-finale-2000706857</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706857</guid>
      <description>Nicknamed 'Conformity Gate,' the conspiracy theory rabbit hole goes deep but ultimately leads nowhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skylight debuts Calendar 2 to keep your family organized</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/skylight-debuts-calendar-2-to-keep-your-family-organized/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080778</guid>
      <description>Skylight, known for its digital picture frame, has a new digital product that puts software and AI at the center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell admits consumers don&#8217;t care about AI PCs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/857723/dell-consumers-ai-pcs-comments</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T12:57:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857723</guid>
      <description>Dell has revealed that consumers aren't buying PCs for AI features right now. In an interview with PC Gamer ahead of CES, Dell has made it clear its 2026 products aren't all about being AI-first, and it's moving beyond being "all about" AI PCs. "We're very focused on delivering upon the AI capabilities of a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr&#8217;s Food Pyramid Announcement Interrupted by His Quacking Ringtone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rfk-jrs-food-pyramid-announcement-interrupted-by-his-quacking-ringtone-2000706856</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706856</guid>
      <description>It was a little on the nose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grosse panne chez Logitech : pourquoi vos p&#233;riph&#233;riques Mac plantent et comment r&#233;gler le probl&#232;me</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/logitech/2934135_grosse-panne-chez-logitech-pourquoi-vos-peripheriques-mac-plantent-et-comment-regler-le-probleme</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/logitech/2934135_grosse-panne-chez-logitech-pourquoi-vos-peripheriques-mac-plantent-et-comment-regler-le-probleme</guid>
      <description>
Depuis hier, les utilisateurs de p&#233;riph&#233;riques Logitech sur macOS font face &#224; un blocage complet des logiciels de configuration de la marque. Une mise &#224; jour corrective vient d'&#234;tre d&#233;ploy&#233;e pour r&#233;tablir la connexion avec vos souris et claviers.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Classroom&#8217;s new tool uses Gemini to transform lessons into podcast episodes</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/google-classrooms-new-tool-uses-gemini-to-transform-lessons-into-podcast-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080706</guid>
      <description>Google Classroom now offers a Gemini-powered tool that generates podcast-style audio lessons for teachers to deepen engagement with students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's how to claim a refund up to $52 from Amazon for its Prime settlement &#8211; and how to check if you're eligible for one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/heres-how-to-claim-a-refund-up-to-usd52-from-amazon-for-its-prime-settlement-and-how-to-check-if-youre-eligible-for-one</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wqfSPBXb43bFsFfMMrsQg7</guid>
      <description>The total FTC settlement will total $2.5 billion, so here's how to get your share of the pie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway launches two more e-bikes at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/segway-launches-two-more-e-bikes-at-ces-130000152.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6228cc32-3766-4468-b41d-98a5e95f02c7</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m no psychologist, but I get a sense Segway turned up to CES 2026 with something to prove after last year. Certainly, it&#8217;s gone out of its way to prove its micromobility bona fides with the press, who perhaps were a bit too sniffy that scooter people were launching an e-bike. This year, Segway&#8217;s not just launching two more mainstream e-bikes, but an electric dirt bike, all of which are crammed with the sort of tech that might just make everyone halt their sniffiness.First up, there&#8217;s the Myon, a chunky step-through with a decent-sized pannier rack for folks who want to go far and carry a bit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xgimi&#8217;s New AI-First Smart Glasses Will Come in Three Tiers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xgimis-new-ai-first-smart-glasses-will-come-in-three-tiers-2000706628</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706628</guid>
      <description>All three feature multiple AI assistants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI Just Raised $20 Billion While Grok Churns Out Sexual Deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musks-xai-just-raised-20-billion-while-grok-churns-out-sexual-deepfakes-2000706818</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706818</guid>
      <description>During a a recent review, Grok generated thousands of sexually suggestive AI images per hour, according to a deepfake researcher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These robotic sneakers gave me a surprising boost at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/these-robotic-sneakers-gave-me-a-surprising-boost-at-ces-174500005.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ce0ddbf-0818-4432-b3ec-f438e0f720b8</guid>
      <description>I'll admit that I've always kind of taken walking for granted. Other than a knee injury more than a decade ago, my ability to walk long distances has largely been limited only by my own choices. That's not the case for everyone, though. And robotics company Dephy has created a pair of robotic sneakers, called the Sidekick, that are meant to help people who want to walk more than their bodies might otherwise be capable of.The system consists of two parts: an ankle-worn exoskeleton and a special pair of sneakers that attach to it. The exoskeleton hooks onto the back of the shoe and is secured wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify now lets you share what you&#8217;re listening to in real time via chat</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/spotify-now-lets-you-share-what-youre-listening-to-in-real-time-via-chat-173749120.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c37a3494-4eff-4449-9cef-275caf70f48a</guid>
      <description>Spotify is rolling out more social features to keep people on the platform. It's adding a new tool to its messaging platform that lets users see what their friends and family members are listening to in real time.
Once activated, a user's listening activity will be displayed at the top of the chat. The other person in the chat can tap the bar to play a particular track, save it or react with an emoji. People can also, of course, comment directly to either praise or rag on the song selection.
There's another little addition to Spotify's messaging system. Users will now be able to invite chat pa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#160;: apr&#232;s Windows 11, la Legion Go 2 arrive aussi sous SteamOS</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/lenovo-apres-windows-11-la-legion-go-2-arrive-aussi-sous-steamos.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318689</guid>
      <description>Lenovo ne veut pas enfermer ses consoles portables dans le carcan d'un seul syst&#232;me d'exploitation. Histoire de ne pas faire de jaloux (et de s'am&#233;nager une porte de sortie au cas o&#249;), le constructeur mise aussi bien sur Windows 11 que sur SteamOS &#8212; ce dernier va ainsi &#233;quiper la Legion Go 2, mod&#232;le le plus haut de gamme au catalogue qui tourne uniquement sur Windows pour le moment....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hisense, une gamme compl&#232;te de TV RGB MiniLED en 2026, mais aussi des TV LCD Mini LED et Direct LED, tous les d&#233;tails</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hisense/2934057_hisense-une-gamme-complete-de-tv-rgb-miniled-en-2026-mais-aussi-des-tv-lcd-mini-led-et-direct-led-tous-les-details</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hisense/2934057_hisense-une-gamme-complete-de-tv-rgb-miniled-en-2026-mais-aussi-des-tv-lcd-mini-led-et-direct-led-tous-les-details</guid>
      <description>
C&#8217;&#233;tait &#233;cris, Hisense a profit&#233; du CES 2026 pour pr&#233;senter plusieurs s&#233;ries de t&#233;l&#233;viseurs utilisant sa nouvelle technologie de r&#233;tro&#233;clairage RGB MiniLED. En plus, la marque devrait proposer d&#8217;autres gammes de TV embarquant une dalle Mini LED, plus classiques, mais pas inint&#233;ressantes.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Nasa sauv&#233;e par le Congr&#232;s, mais contrainte de renoncer &#224; un r&#234;ve martien</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-nasa-sauvee-congres-mais-contrainte-renoncer-reve-martien-129892/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:33:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-nasa-sauvee-congres-mais-contrainte-renoncer-reve-martien-129892/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Apr&#232;s des mois de grandes d&#233;clarations et de menaces de la part de Donald Trump, la plupart des vell&#233;it&#233;s du pr&#233;sident am&#233;ricain ont finalement &#233;t&#233; mises de c&#244;t&#233;, et la Nasa s'en sort quasiment indemne&#8230; M&#234;me si quelques ajustements sont de mise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s the first anniversary of the L.A. wildfires. Why have less than a dozen homes been rebuilt since then?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470621/first-anniversary-l-a-wildfires-less-dozen-homes-rebuilt-since-then</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T17:31:57</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470621/first-anniversary-l-a-wildfires-less-dozen-homes-rebuilt-since-then</guid>
      <description>The Palisades and Eaton fires tore through the Los Angeles area on Jan. 7, 2025, killing 31 people and destroying nearly 13,000 properties. 
On the first anniversary of the most destructive wildfires in the L.A. area, the scant home construction projects stand out among the still mostly flattened landscapes.Fewer than a dozen homes have been rebuilt in Los Angeles County since Jan. 7, 2025, when the Palisades and Eaton fires erupted, killing 31 people and destroying about 13,000 homes and other residential properties.For those who had insurance, it&#8217;s often not enough to cover the costs of cons...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tin Can phones have been overwhelmed since Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470295/tin-can-phones-network-issues-christmas</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470295/tin-can-phones-network-issues-christmas</guid>
      <description>The company says&#160;it&#8217;s&#160;working to fix a network&#160;issue&#160;and&#160;that&#160;paying customers&#160;won&#8217;t&#160;be charged until the devices&#160;are reliable once more.&#160;
The&#160;Tin Can phone&#160;is designed to be a simple and screen-free way for children to connect with friends and family. But since Christmas morning, when many families unwrapped and installed the retro, landline-style phones, network issues have left many users unable to make or receive calls.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 tech you can already buy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/856494/ces-2026-tech-you-can-already-buy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T12:27:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856494</guid>
      <description>News coming out of CES 2026 might be slowing down, but as of Wednesday we still have writers on the ground, zipping around from hotel suite to Las Vegas convention center to try everything that matters. We've published well over 100 articles, and there's plenty of more content to come, including reviews of stuff we [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA's first CES appearance included a $6 Matter smart bulb</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/ikeas-first-ces-appearance-included-a-6-matter-smart-bulb-172623474.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39c98f7d-37cf-4932-97e8-3c0d15f76bc7</guid>
      <description>I know IKEA is all about small, efficient spaces, but their meeting room inside the Venetian during the company&#8217;s first-ever CES was the same size as my (not large) living room. Plenty of people were as excited as I was to see what the Swedish designers brought with them to the show and the room was thick with humans. A bowl full of BEL&#214;NING bars helped ease my mounting claustrophobia and I was able to check out the new smart home lineup. Like most things IKEA, the 21 Matter-compatible smart home devices are simple, sleek and silly affordable. They include a $6 smart bulb, an $8 smart plug, a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best hi-fi kit we saw at CES 2026: an iconic turntable updated, Edifier's first eARC active speakers, and much more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/hi-fi/the-best-hi-fi-kit-we-saw-at-ces-2026-an-iconic-turntable-updated-edifiers-first-earc-active-speakers-and-much-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hqR6PN95Pg8PL6jp2Wd2NU</guid>
      <description>Cambridge's first ever bookshelf stereo speakers, portable Fender Bluetooth options and Victrola's, er, soundbase (yes really).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#192; moins de 700 &#8364;, ce pack avec un Samsung Galaxy S25 et une powerbank 10 000 mAh est l&#8217;un des meilleurs deals des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933763_a-moins-de-700-e-ce-pack-avec-un-samsung-galaxy-s25-et-une-powerbank-10-000-mah-est-lun-des-meilleurs-deals-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933763_a-moins-de-700-e-ce-pack-avec-un-samsung-galaxy-s25-et-une-powerbank-10-000-mah-est-lun-des-meilleurs-deals-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Si vous attendiez les soldes d'hiver pour changer de smartphone, laissez-nous vous dire que vous avez bien fait : si vous &#234;tes team Samsung, sachez que le Galaxy S25 se trouve actuellement aux c&#244;t&#233;s d'une batterie externe de 10 000 mAh dans un pack &#224; 699 euros au lieu de 949,99 euros chez Boulanger.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do I Have the &#8216;Super Flu&#8217;? Here&#8217;s What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/do-i-have-the-super-flu-heres-what-you-need-to-know-2000706754</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706754</guid>
      <description>Subclade K is causing plenty of misery this winter. Here's what to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers poison their own data when stolen by an AI to ruin results</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/researchers-poison-their-own-data-when-stolen-by-an-ai-to-ruin-results</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BYWnSwmhxNMWXoybkg8PL9</guid>
      <description>Poisoned knowledge graphs can make the LLM hallucinate, rendering it useless to the thieves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell New Year sale slashes up to $500 off laptops &#8212; here are the 5 best deals from $299.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/dell-new-year-sale-slashes-up-to-usd500-off-laptops-here-are-the-5-best-deals-from-usd299-99</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qfsBqsaVFMx27XtLejrrA</guid>
      <description>Dell's New Year sale features some big savings of up to $500 on its latest and top-rated laptops, so I've searched through and picked out the five best deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 7 weirdest gadgets we&#8217;ve seen at CES 2026 &#8211; from a musical popsicle to headphones with eyes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/the-7-weirdest-gadgets-weve-seen-at-ces-2026-from-a-musical-popsicle-to-headphones-with-eyes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dZAcSnG8Z88wmm5qD3258i</guid>
      <description>There have been some wild tech announcements at CES 2026. Here are 7 of the craziest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp : vous pouvez d&#233;sormais transformer n&#8217;importe quel texte en sticker, voici comment</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/meta/2933975_whatsapp-vous-pouvez-desormais-transformer-nimporte-quel-texte-en-sticker-voici-comment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/meta/2933975_whatsapp-vous-pouvez-desormais-transformer-nimporte-quel-texte-en-sticker-voici-comment</guid>
      <description>
WhatsApp am&#233;liore les discussions de groupes avec de nouvelles fonctionnalit&#233;s pour les stickers, les membres et les &#233;v&#233;nements. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burnley vs Man Utd Free Streams: How to Watch Premier League 2025-26 From Anywhere in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/burnley-vs-manchester-united-premier-league-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">U9MJQFqHUifzJWKs6zVMCA</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Burnley vs Man Utd live streams online and from anywhere, as Darren Fletcher takes charge of the Red Devils for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This IKEA speaker is tiny, insanely cheap, and I want 100 of them</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/this-ikea-speaker-is-tiny-insanely-cheap-and-i-want-100-of-them</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zfPfFtQ73ocwvuwKGQJTyh</guid>
      <description>IKEA's moved on from Sonos, but now it has its own line of adorable and cheap speakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khadas Mind&#160;: le PC modulaire qui veut enterrer votre laptop (mais &#224; quel prix&#160;?)</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/khadas-mind-le-pc-modulaire-qui-veut-enterrer-votre-laptop-mais-a-quel-prix.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318650</guid>
      <description>Au CES 2026, Khadas tente de bousculer l'informatique mobile avec son Mind Pro sous Intel Panther Lake. Si la promesse de la modularit&#233; fait r&#234;ver, la r&#233;alit&#233; d'un &#233;cosyst&#232;me ferm&#233; et co&#251;teux pourrait bien refroidir les ardeurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Bitchat Sees Downloads Spike in Uganda Over Internet Shutdown Worries</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jack-dorseys-bitchat-sees-downloads-spike-in-uganda-over-internet-shutdown-worries-2000706828</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706828</guid>
      <description>Ugandans have good reason to believe there will be a blackout soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia : voici comment bien configurer le DLSS 4.5 pour la meilleure qualit&#233; d&#8217;image selon votre carte graphique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2933735_presets-l-m-ou-k-voici-comment-bien-configurer-le-dlss-4-5-selon-votre-carte-graphique-nvidia</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2933735_presets-l-m-ou-k-voici-comment-bien-configurer-le-dlss-4-5-selon-votre-carte-graphique-nvidia</guid>
      <description>
Le DLSS 4.5 promet une qualit&#233; d'image sup&#233;rieure pour tous les possesseurs de cartes graphiques RTX, mais tous les joueurs ne seront pas log&#233;s &#224; la m&#234;me enseigne. On fait le point sur les diff&#233;rents r&#233;glages conseill&#233;s pour cette nouvelle version.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung says RAM costs will likely lead to price hikes soon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/samsung-says-ram-costs-will-likely-lead-to-price-hikes-soon-170653524.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f8e3b16-3c55-45ce-9a8e-daa7f15c25ee</guid>
      <description>Samsung says AI data center-fueled RAM scarcity could raise the company's prices. Wonjin Lee, Samsung's global marketing leader, sounded the alarm in an interview with Bloomberg on Tuesday at CES 2026.  As recently as early December, Samsung told Reuters that it was monitoring the market but wouldn't comment on pricing. So, the change of tune can be seen as a deliberate signal to soften the ground ahead of an official announcement."There's going to be issues around semiconductor supplies, and it's going to affect everyone," Samsung&#8217;s Lee said. "Prices are going up even as we speak. Obviously, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Heated Rivalry&#8217; Mystique Reference Is More Than Just a Movie Gag</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/heated-rivalry-rose-mystique-reference-xmen-lgbtq-2000706335</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706335</guid>
      <description>The gay hockey romance sensation has a brief nod to Canada's superhero moviemaking history&#8212;one that has a wonderfully queer comics legacy behind it, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: How auto and tech companies are turning cars into companions</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470644/ces-2026-cars-companions-nvidia-bosch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T17:02:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470644/ces-2026-cars-companions-nvidia-bosch</guid>
      <description>Experts say the push toward a more personalized driving experience is intensifying questions about how much driver data is being collected.
In a vision of the near future shared at CES, a girl slides into the back seat of her parents&#8217; car and the cabin instantly comes alive. The vehicle recognizes her, knows it&#8217;s her birthday and cues up her favorite song without a word spoken....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;Or&#233;al&#8217;s new LED face masks address all my issues with this category</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857164/ces-2026-hands-on-loreal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T12:01:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857164</guid>
      <description>I hate when friends and family ask me which LED face mask to buy. That's because LED face masks are another prime example of the wild wellness west. There's compelling science behind using red and infrared light therapy to address skin concerns, particularly wrinkles. However, wellness influencers have taken that concept and absolutely ran away [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can RGB mini-LED dethrone OLED? Here&#8217;s what it needs to do</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/can-rgb-mini-led-dethrone-oled-heres-what-it-needs-to-do</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hiygijhoo9cftdcr6iW3hX</guid>
      <description>RGB mini-LED is taking the TV world by storm, but it needs to improve in one key area if it's going to rival OLED.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures trottinettes &#233;lectriques en 2026&#8201;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-survoltes/guides-dachat-trottinettes-electriques/617520_quelle-trottinette-electrique-acheter</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-survoltes/guides-dachat-trottinettes-electriques/617520_quelle-trottinette-electrique-acheter</guid>
      <description>
Les trottinettes &#233;lectriques sont partout dans nos villes. Seulement voil&#224;, le march&#233; est satur&#233; de r&#233;f&#233;rences qui s'adressent &#224; diff&#233;rentes personnes. Quelles sont les meilleures trottinettes &#233;lectriques ? Voici notre comparatif.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caterpillar taps Nvidia to bring AI to its&#160;construction equipment</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/caterpillar-taps-nvidia-to-bring-ai-to-its-construction-equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080675</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar is piloting Cat AI, a system of AI agents in one of its excavators built on Nvidia's physical AI platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurry! ESET's holiday discount ends soon &#8211; save up to 33% off antivirus plans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hurry-esets-holiday-discount-ends-soon-save-up-to-33-percent-off-antivirus-plans</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32me7GSbyho936KGQmfrdm</guid>
      <description>ESET Essentials, Premium, and Ultimate are discounted by up to 33% off - but hurry, the deal ends soon!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nosh is an AI cooking robot for the meal prep crowd</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/nosh-is-an-ai-cooking-robot-for-the-meal-prep-crowd-170000610.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c86704d7-ce3f-4a9f-a105-8d846d2f6baf</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m fascinated by AI cooking robots which, as far as I&#8217;m concerned, automate the one fun bit of cooking. Sadly, it&#8217;s far easier to make something that can stir a pan of ingredients as they cook compared to building something that would successfully peel a carrot. Nosh is the latest unit to use CES to announce itself to the world, gearing up for its launch in the next few months. Like its many rivals, you load ingredients into the unit and then Nosh will assemble them for you. Unlike its many rivals, you can have more than one ingredient tray, opening up the possibility that you could prep mult...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan begins blocking unregistered VPN apps &#8211; and this popular service is among the casualties</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/pakistan-begins-blocking-unregistered-vpn-apps-and-this-popular-service-is-among-the-casualties</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QjjP7PJLBaYdgLFNx37RaL</guid>
      <description>Proton confirms its apps have been blocked since December 22. Here's what you can do to evade restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Just Sampled 1.4-Billion-Year-Old Air&#8212;and It&#8217;s Not What They Expected</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/researchers-just-sampled-1-4-billion-year-old-air-and-its-not-what-they-expected-2000706812</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706812</guid>
      <description>A "boring" time period may not have been so boring after all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony Honda Mobility Still Needs to Deliver Its Game-Filled Afeela 1 EV, but Here&#8217;s a New Concept Car</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-honda-mobility-still-needs-to-deliver-its-game-filled-afeela-1-ev-but-heres-a-new-concept-car-2000706776</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706776</guid>
      <description>Sony Honda Mobility introduced the Afeela Prototype 2026 at CES as a larger crossover EV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify vous laisse voir ce qu&#8217;&#233;coutent vos amis en temps r&#233;el</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/spotify-vous-laisse-voir-ce-quecoutent-vos-amis-en-temps-reel.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318676</guid>
      <description>La plate-forme de musique en streaming introduit une nouvelle fonction &#171; Activit&#233; d&#8217;&#233;coute &#187; pour vous permettre de voir et de partager en temps r&#233;el ce que vous &#233;coutez avec vos amis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Virginia teen safety law sparks privacy debate and fresh legal challenges</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/new-virginia-teen-safety-law-sparks-privacy-debate-and-fresh-legal-challenges</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yUK4tXKt4avP5hEB5E5s2d</guid>
      <description>The amendment to the VCDPA places strict limits on data collection and usage hours for minors, but privacy advocates warn that age verification could put data at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 CES gadgets you can buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/17-ces-gadgets-you-can-buy-right-now-164325644.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">486c0883-fd9d-4677-b8fe-ca2db36c7354</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is in full swing, but you don&#8217;t have to wait months to get your hands on everything announced in Las Vegas this year. A surprising number of products are already up for pre-order, if not outright available to buy today, from new chargers and docks to projectors, keyboards and smart home gear. CES is still a showcase for concepts and big promises, but these are the gadgets that have real pricing and an order button ready right now. Check out all of the CES 2026 gadgets you can buy right now below.


































This article originally appeared on Engadget at https:/...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker unveils a new lineup of chargers, docks and accessories at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/anker-unveils-a-new-lineup-of-chargers-docks-and-accessories-at-ces-2026-160021025.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a59925-1c86-46f9-b8b4-44c46f9069f6</guid>
      <description>Anker, one of the leaders in third-party chargers, has unveiled a new portfolio of "smart" chargers and docks at CES 2026. The company says the lineup adds improved visual interfaces, faster Qi2 wireless charging and "upgraded ecosystems" for the latest line of iPhone models.
First up is the Anker Nano Charger with smart display, which features a tiny screen, 180-degree foldable prongs and provides up to 45W of power. The plug can identify the exact iPhone model connected and then deliver the right amount of power for your phone. Anker says the Nano uses three-stage power delivery and a "Care ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 d&#233;marrent aujourd&#8217;hui ! Voici les 12 meilleures offres sur les smartphones Apple, Samsung et Xiaomi</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-soldes-dhiver-2026-demarrent-aujourdhui-voici-les-meilleures-offres-sur-les-smartphones-apple-samsung-et-xiaomi</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-soldes-dhiver-2026-demarrent-aujourdhui-voici-les-meilleures-offres-sur-les-smartphones-apple-samsung-et-xiaomi</guid>
      <description>
Du 7 janvier au 3 f&#233;vrier, les soldes d'hiver promettent de faire de bonnes affaires dans la tech, particuli&#232;rement aupr&#232;s des e-commer&#231;ants fran&#231;ais. C'est par exemple l'occasion de mettre la main sur un smartphone que le P&#232;re No&#235;l aurait oubli&#233; de d&#233;poser au pied du sapin.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony&amp;#8217;s new &amp;#8216;Hyperpop&amp;#8217; PS5 covers are bursting with RGB color</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857603/sony-ps5-covers-controller-hyperpop-color-accessories</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T11:40:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857603</guid>
      <description>Sony's first PlayStation announcement of 2026 is all about color. The new Hyperpop Collection includes colorful neon console covers and controllers that really add a pop of color to a PS5. Sadly, if you own a PS5 Pro then you won't be able to enjoy the RGB in your living room fun. There are three [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
