<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:46:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini can now generate a 30-second approximation of what real music sounds like</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/gemini-can-now-generate-a-30-second-approximation-of-what-real-music-sounds-like-204445903.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b1ea506-6d38-4bad-a73b-b9c8fa1f2d13</guid>
      <description>Google has announced that using its newly incorporated Lyria 3 model, Gemini users will be able to generate 30-second music tracks based on a prompt, or remix an existing track to their liking. The new model builds on Gemini's pre-existing ability to generate text, images and video, and will also be available in YouTube's "Dream Track" feature, where it can be used to generate detailed backing tracks for Shorts.Like some other music generation tools, prompting Gemini doesn't require a lot of detail to produce serviceable results. Google's example prompt is "a comical R&amp;B slow jam about a sock ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital excellence can yield exceptional in-person experiences</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494891/digital-excellence-can-yield-exceptional-in-person-experiences</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T20:22:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494891/digital-excellence-can-yield-exceptional-in-person-experiences</guid>
      <description>The future belongs to brands that master both digital innovation and human connection. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s not just you &#8212; LinkedIn is being flooded by awful AI-generated posts, and tech workers are particularly bad at it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/its-not-just-you-linkedin-is-being-flooded-by-awful-ai-generated-posts-and-tech-workers-are-particularly-bad-at-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">j6nekSHyCLQXMuebhWoakM</guid>
      <description>Mid-level and senior professionals are driving AI adoption on LinkedIn, responding to pressure for visibility, efficiency, and consistent industry updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg testifies at social media addiction trial</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494858/mark-zuckerberg-trial-testimony-instagram</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T20:15:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494858/mark-zuckerberg-trial-testimony-instagram</guid>
      <description>Zuckerberg mostly stuck to his talking points, referencing his goal of building a platform that is valuable to users.
Mark Zuckerberg&#160;and opposing lawyers dueled in a Los Angeles courtroom on Wednesday, where the Meta CEO answered questions about young people&#8217;s use of Instagram, his congressional testimony, and internal advice he&#8217;s received about being &#8220;authentic&#8221; and not &#8220;robotic.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This powerful and lightweight Dyson vacuum is now a massive $300 off at Walmart</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/this-powerful-and-lightweight-dyson-vacuum-is-now-a-massive-usd300-off-at-walmart</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oR4ujzdK8PpMVjYwCgpTmH</guid>
      <description>The Dyson V9 is an ideal entry to the Dyson vacuum world, especially now it's on sale at 50% off at Walmart &#8212; here's why I think it's a good purchase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayer proposes $7.25 billion Roundup settlement as Supreme Court case looms</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494736/bayer-proposes-7-25-billion-roundup-settlement-as-supreme-court-case-looms</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T20:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494736/bayer-proposes-7-25-billion-roundup-settlement-as-supreme-court-case-looms</guid>
      <description>The proposed agreement comes as the Supreme Court prepares to weigh whether federal pesticide approval blocks state-level failure-to-warn claims.
A new $7.25 billion settlement between Bayer and a group of cancer patients could wrap up a huge wave of lawsuits against the company over allegations that it didn&#8217;t warn consumers about cancer risks associated with the weedkiller Roundup....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best AirPods deals you can get right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21302051/best-apple-airpods-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T15:00:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21302051/best-apple-airpods-deals</guid>
      <description>If you know where to look, you can often score deals on Apple&#8217;s ever-expanding AirPods lineup. Both the AirPods Max and AirPods 4 (with and without ANC) now consistently receive discounts, as do the newer AirPods Pro 3. And while more recent shopping events like Black Friday and Cyber Monday delivered some of the steepest [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Game of Thrones&#8217; Prequel Play Is Officially Happening</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-game-of-thrones-prequel-play-is-officially-happening-2000723637</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723637</guid>
      <description>'Game of Thrones: The Mad King,' set over 15 years before the HBO series and featuring many familiar characters, premieres at the Royal Shakespeare Company this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It&#8217;s not too far-fetched to believe that companies like Discord could share this data with state or federal agencies - in the US or elsewhere - for their benefit' &#8212; users overload yet another Discord alternative's servers as they flee ID checks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/software/its-not-too-far-fetched-to-believe-that-companies-like-discord-could-share-this-data-with-state-or-federal-agencies-in-the-us-or-elsewhere-for-their-benefit-users-overload-yet-another-discord-alternatives-servers-as-they-flee-id-checks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UZmKL4MTbCHFuv57TZYhyV</guid>
      <description>Discord&#8217;s age verification backlash continues as fleeing users overload the servers of yet another platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Jwiki&#8217; is Wikipedia for all things Epstein files</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494601/jwiki-new-tool-designed-to-keep-track-of-everyone-implicated-in-the-epstein-files</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494601/jwiki-new-tool-designed-to-keep-track-of-everyone-implicated-in-the-epstein-files</guid>
      <description>This Wikipedia-style tool is holding the rich and powerful to account.
On February 2, wellness influencer Peter Attia stepped down from his role as chief science officer at the protein company David. On February 12, Goldman Sachs&#8217; top lawyer Kathryn Ruemmler announced her resignation from the company. And on February 13, Hollywood agent Casey Wasserman revealed that he would sell his talent agency.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chase bank is opening 160 branches in over 30 states, including in rural areas. Here&#8217;s where the new locations will be</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494634/chase-to-open-new-banks-branches-2026-states-cities-locations-full-list</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494634/chase-to-open-new-banks-branches-2026-states-cities-locations-full-list</guid>
      <description>The move continues a years-long expansion strategy. The bank will also renovate nearly 600 branches this year.
JPMorganChase said Wednesday it plans to open more than 160 new bank branches in over three dozen states&#8212;and renovate nearly 600 more&#8212;as part of a nationwide, multibillion-dollar push for more affordable financial services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#8217;s Glass Chip Holds Terabytes of Data for 10,000 Years</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsofts-glass-chip-holds-terabytes-of-data-for-10000-years-2000723455</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723455</guid>
      <description>"This will change the way we think about keeping data and archival preservation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,2 million d&#8217;IBAN fran&#231;ais dans la nature : la France est victime d&#8217;un piratage historique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/securite-applications/2982353_12-million-diban-francais-dans-la-nature-la-france-est-victime-dun-piratage-historique</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/securite-applications/2982353_12-million-diban-francais-dans-la-nature-la-france-est-victime-dun-piratage-historique</guid>
      <description>
C'est du jamais vu. La Direction G&#233;n&#233;rale des Finances publiques (DGFiP) annonce qu'une faille a permis une intrusion sur sa base de donn&#233;es. 1,2 million de comptes sont concern&#233;s avec des donn&#233;es tr&#232;s pr&#233;cieuses, notamment l'IBAN.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Defense Company Made AI Agents That Blow Things Up</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-lab-scout-ai-is-using-ai-agents-to-blow-things-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698607fb8d12f90caa650ff8</guid>
      <description>Scout AI is using technology borrowed from the AI industry to power lethal weapons&#8212;and recently demonstrated its explosive potential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save on Gaming Earbuds Perfect for Playing on Switch or ROG Xbox Ally</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/arctis-gamebuds-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6995fa21caaeddcb590eee02</guid>
      <description>While it may sound unorthodox, these earbuds make a great companion for your Switch 2 or other portable console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec Claude Sonnet 4.6, Anthropic met du premium dans son IA gratuite</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2981715_avec-claude-sonnet-4-6-anthropic-met-du-premium-dans-son-ia-gratuite</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2981715_avec-claude-sonnet-4-6-anthropic-met-du-premium-dans-son-ia-gratuite</guid>
      <description>
Anthropic met &#224; jour son mod&#232;le d'intelligence Claude Sonnet, qui passe de la version 4.5 &#224; 4.6. Ne vous laissez pas berner par ce petit 0,1 de plus, beaucoup de choses ont chang&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Boys Talk &#8216;Retribution&#8217; as CEOs Kiss the Ring at Their Crypto Event</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-boys-talk-retribution-as-ceos-kiss-the-ring-at-their-crypto-event-2000723430</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723430</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump Jr. insists his father is "not involved."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#8217;s Deal With Meta Signals a New Era in Computing Power</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/nvidias-deal-with-meta-signals-a-new-era-in-computing-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6995c8515366fbe3869b6b5b</guid>
      <description>The days of tech giants buying up discrete chips are over. AI companies now need GPUs, CPUs, and everything in between.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polestar aims to shake off EV doldrums with 4 new models in 3 years</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/880808/polestar-four-new-models-ev-europe</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T14:21:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880808</guid>
      <description>Polestar says it will release four new electric models over the next three years, including a new SUV and a revamped version of its Polestar 2 sedan. The Swedish automaker, which is owned by China's Geely, said it will start delivering its Polestar 5 grand tourer to customers this summer, followed by a new long-roof [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huawei Watch GT 6, Forfait 5G 120 Go et iPhone 16e : les 3 promos tech &#224; ne pas manquer ce mercredi 18 f&#233;vrier 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2981987_huawei-watch-gt-6-prixtel-oxygene-et-iphone-16e-les-3-promos-tech-a-ne-pas-manquer-ce-mercredi-18-fevrier-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2981987_huawei-watch-gt-6-prixtel-oxygene-et-iphone-16e-les-3-promos-tech-a-ne-pas-manquer-ce-mercredi-18-fevrier-2026</guid>
      <description>
En ce mercredi 18 f&#233;vrier 2026, les bons plans continuent de pleuvoir sur la tech.  
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;humanit&#233; vient de d&#233;couvrir le plus lointain &#171; gigalaser &#187; cosmique !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-humanite-vient-decouvrir-plus-lointain-gigalaser-cosmique-131395/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:07:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-humanite-vient-decouvrir-plus-lointain-gigalaser-cosmique-131395/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>L'effet maser, le fr&#232;re de l'effet laser, ne se produit pas que dans des petits dispositifs sur Terre, on le rencontre aussi dans certaines r&#233;gions des galaxies et aussi &#224; l'&#233;chelle d'une galaxie enti&#232;re. On parle alors de m&#233;gamaser. Le plus lointain et le plus brillant connu&#160;&#224; ce jour vient...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeatGeek and Spotify team up to offer concert ticket sales inside the music platform</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/18/seatgeek-and-spotify-team-up-to-offer-concert-ticket-sales-inside-the-music-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094088</guid>
      <description>SeatGeek announced on Wednesday a new integration with Spotify, bringing a seamless ticket-buying experience for Spotify users.&#160; Now, when Spotify users browse an artist&#8217;s page or upcoming tour dates, they will see ticket links powered by SeatGeek for concerts at these participating venues, allowing for a streamlined purchase process. Currently, the integration is available for [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberpunk platformer Replaced has once again been delayed</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/cyberpunk-platformer-replaced-has-once-again-been-delayed-190621246.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">714e2acb-e64c-4a96-a7b7-eb9cdf3dff20</guid>
      <description>The long-awaited cyberpunk platformer Replaced just got hit with a short delay. The pixel-art game was supposed to come out on March 12, but will now be released on April 14. That's just a month, which isn't that big of a deal considering this game has been on our radar for five years.
Why the delay? Developer Sad Cat Studios notes that the game is "technically finished" but the team needs a few more weeks for polish. The company says it wants the day-one release to be "polished, stable and true to the vision" of the original concept. This is something to be commended, in my opinion, given the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Margot Robbie&#8217;s hot take on filmmaking goes viral as critics slam her latest movie, &#8216;Wuthering Heights&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494740/margot-robbie-wuthering-heights-hot-take-on-filmmaking-goes-viral-as-critics-slam-her-latest-movie</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494740/margot-robbie-wuthering-heights-hot-take-on-filmmaking-goes-viral-as-critics-slam-her-latest-movie</guid>
      <description>In a recent panel discussion, the A-list actress suggested movies aren&#8217;t just about the art form.
Emerald Fennell&#8217;s Wuthering Heights is a love-it-or-hate-it kind of film&#8212;and for the most part, critics are falling in the &#8220;hate it&#8221; camp.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici deux manettes pour am&#233;liorer l&#8217;ergonomie la Switch 2 en mode console portable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2981203_voici-deux-manettes-pour-ameliorer-lergonomie-la-switch-2-en-mode-console-portable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2981203_voici-deux-manettes-pour-ameliorer-lergonomie-la-switch-2-en-mode-console-portable</guid>
      <description>
Parmi les accessoires autour de la Nintendo Switch 2, plusieurs projets Kickstarter fourmillent. L'Abxylute N6 et N9C sont deux mod&#232;les de manettes au format &#171; dock &#187; pour la console de Nintendo. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 87 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-87-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056484.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>The Winter Olympics have been a blast so far, and there are still four days left. It's the perfect time to get ahold of a virtual private network (VPN) and check out how the games are broadcast in other countries&#8212; all while improving your cybersecurity. By  connecting to a VPN every time you get online, you can keep your activity hidden from your ISP and anyone to whom it may sell that data, while streaming sports and TV from across the globe.
We strongly recommend using a VPN, but shopping for one takes some care. If you jump on the very first deal you see, you might get stuck with a substand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to overcome guilt as a woman and beat unreasonable expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91493007/how-to-overcome-guilt-as-a-woman-and-beat-unreasonable-expectations</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T18:54:19</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91493007/how-to-overcome-guilt-as-a-woman-and-beat-unreasonable-expectations</guid>
      <description>We have been socialized to feel guilty.
Below, Jennifer Reid shares five key insights from her new book,&#160;Guilt Free: Reclaiming Your Life From Unreasonable Expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A &#8216;Spider-Man: Brand New Day&#8217; Book Just Accidentally Told Us What the Film Is About</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-spider-man-brand-new-day-book-just-accidentially-told-us-what-the-film-is-about-2000723535</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723535</guid>
      <description>We have yet to see a trailer for the Tom Holland Marvel sequel, but we now have an official synopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#201;couteurs &#224; clip d&#8217;oreille : quand le confort prend le pas sur le son</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/audio/ecouteurs-true-wireless/2981313_ecouteurs-a-clip-doreille-quand-le-confort-prend-le-pas-sur-le-son</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/audio/ecouteurs-true-wireless/2981313_ecouteurs-a-clip-doreille-quand-le-confort-prend-le-pas-sur-le-son</guid>
      <description>
Rester &#224; l&#8217;&#233;coute du monde sans renoncer &#224; la musique, voil&#224; la promesse des &#233;couteurs ouverts &#224; clip d&#8217;oreille qui se multiplient ces derniers mois. Apr&#232;s plusieurs tests, une &#233;vidence s&#8217;impose : ces produits sont d&#8217;abord des outils de confort et de s&#233;curit&#233;, bien plus que des instruments de haute fid&#233;lit&#233;. On fait le point.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
