<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:22:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The wild, intense rise and fall of Flappy Bird</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/853824/flappy-bird-game-version-history</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T09:10:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853824</guid>
      <description>Flappy Bird was almost preposterously simple. If you ever played the game, even once, you surely remember how it worked, but here's a summary just in case. You were a bird. Your job was to fly, left to right, for as long as possible without crashing into the green Mario-ish pipes coming from both the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xreal&#8217;s Neo is the best-looking mobile dock for AR glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/846376/xreal-neo-specs-switch-2-battery-dock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846376</guid>
      <description>When the Nintendo Switch 2 launched in June, AR glasses brand Viture beat Xreal to the punch with its own multi-port battery pack that doubles as a portable video dock for the new console. After several months, Xreal answered with the Neo, a 10,000mAh (38.7Wh) battery pack with DisplayPort Alt video-out. It sure is one [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narwal&#8217;s Flow 2 robovac might help you find that earring you lost</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850787/narwal-flow-2-robovac-ai-object-recognition-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850787</guid>
      <description>Narwal's successor to its edge-mopping Flow robovac is here, and it sports a refreshed design along with a new cleaning mode that can scan your floor to tag valuables that you may have dropped, like jewelry, your phone, a key, wallet, and more. When the Flow 2 detects one of these items, the robovac will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseus&#8217; new desktop dock includes a Qi2 25W charger</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/850811/baseus-rd1-pro-desktop-dock-qi2-25w</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850811</guid>
      <description>Chinese accessory brand Baseus has launched a new desktop dock for CES 2026 with an exhaustive array of ports and power options, including a magnetic Qi2 25W charging pad that flips up from the dock's top. Baseus calls the Spacemate RD1 Pro a 15-in-1 docking station, though there might be some double counting to get [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xreal&#8217;s entry-level AR glasses get a spec bump and 3D conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852821/xreal-1s-ces-hands-on-ar-glasses-wearables</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852821</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Xreal announced an upgraded, slightly more affordable version of its entry-level AR glasses: the $449 Xreal 1S. And this time, you can also convert 2D videos to 3D without any extra apps, software, or proprietary players. At a glance, the Xreal 1S don't look much different from the Xreal One or One [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This startup brought WALL-E to life and will also sell you WALL-E&amp;#8217;s weird cousin</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852956/zeroth-wall-e-robot-w1-m1-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852956</guid>
      <description>An AI robotics startup called Zeroth is turning WALL-E into a real-life robot companion. Though the WALL-E version with the Disney-licensed design is currently only on sale in China, Zeroth is launching what looks like an off-brand version of the beloved bot in the US for $5,599. The bot, called the W1, doesn't feature WALL-E's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Xreal 1S glasses put a big virtual screen in front of your face, and I'm loving the simplicity and pure entertainment value</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/the-xreal-1s-glasses-put-a-big-virtual-screen-in-front-of-your-face-and-im-loving-the-simplicity-and-pure-entertainment-value</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YCd3kDGhsscXrq2wpz4evZ</guid>
      <description>The Xreal  1S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 33 most exciting new movies of 2026: TechRadar's top picks that are coming to the big screen, Netflix, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/most-exciting-new-movies-of-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WbWy8tDgZPBRGX4oxidD44</guid>
      <description>2026 looks like it's going to be another great year of new movies &#8211; here are our top choices for the weeks and months to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra leaks tip colors, camera and S Pen changes &#8212; here are all the details</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/new-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-leaks-tip-colors-camera-and-s-pen-changes-here-are-all-the-details</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gtnCJt6WZbqBEtXstwkUZA</guid>
      <description>We've got some more advance information on the premium flagship from Samsung that's due in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xreal updates its entry-level personal cinema glasses at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/xreal-updates-its-entry-level-personal-cinema-glasses-at-ces-140000544.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e74752e-36c5-4418-b7b5-90ed4a774f24</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been on the fence about trying the sort of &#8220;AR glasses&#8221; that, until recently, were called &#8220;personal cinemas,&#8221; then check this out. Xreal has turned up to CES 2026 with an updated version of its entry level Xreal One glasses, first launched at the end of 2024. The new model, dubbed the 1S (yes, with a numeral rather than the word) gets marginally better specs and $50 knocked from the asking price.
If you&#8217;re unfamiliar, One is a wearable spatial display that connects over USB-C to any compatible device including smartphones, tablets, laptops and consoles. It has two teeny-tiny displays...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magn&#233;tom&#232;tre quantique : l'ESA et SBQuantum &#224; l'avant-garde de l'observation de la Terre</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/champ-magnetique-magnetometre-quantique-esa-sbquantum-avant-garde-observation-terre-129576/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:03:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/champ-magnetique-magnetometre-quantique-esa-sbquantum-avant-garde-observation-terre-129576/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Dans le cadre de son programme d'observation de la Terre, FutureEO, l'Agence spatiale europ&#233;enne&#160;a conclu un partenariat strat&#233;gique avec l'entreprise canadienne SBQuantum pour concevoir un prototype de capteur magn&#233;tom&#232;tre quantique. Ce capteur, dot&#233; de performances avanc&#233;es, a pour ambition de...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Intel CES 2026 launch event</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-intel-ces-2026-launch-event-130040089.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f580535b-fd7f-4472-8749-2372604b977f</guid>
      <description>SOPA Images via Getty Images
We're just hours away from the start of CES 2026, and with that comes Intel's launch event. The chip giant is expected to provide more details on its AI PC initiative and the new processors powering it: The Core Ultra Series 3 CPUs (aka Panther Lake) are made using an 18A process &#8212; that's 18 angstroms, or just under 2nm &#8212; and designed for high-end laptops and gaming devices.
For Intel, the stakes at CES are higher than ever. In the past 12 months, both NVIDIA and the US government acquired ownership stakes in the company, helping nearly double the stock price by th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackery&#8217;s solar-powered Gazebo is a good DIY idea</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852600/jackerys-solar-powered-gazebo-is-a-good-diy-idea</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852600</guid>
      <description>Jackery, the home battery company, is back at CES with a solar-powered Gazebo it swears you'll be able to buy in the second half of the year, starting in California. With an expected price of between $12,000 and $15,000 before adding any battery storage, you might want to save a few bucks and build one [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govee&#8217;s latest smart lights can make your ceiling more interesting</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853006/govee-sky-ceiling-light-ultra-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853006</guid>
      <description>Govee is known for putting lights in every corner of your room: in your bulb sockets, in the corner for a little multicolored bias lighting, and even behind the TV with its scene-matching LED strips. And it has some curious announcements at CES 2026 that tackle a new part of the room: the ceiling. Govee [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Ject's new premium turntable promises "analogue excellence" &#8212; but it's from its more beginner-friendly range</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/pro-jects-new-premium-turntable-promises-analogue-excellence-but-its-from-its-more-beginner-friendly-range</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ifSNAtJKpmdAWUsD3bmxc3</guid>
      <description>The Pro-Ject Debut Reference 10 is another beautiful turntable from the Austrian audiophiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govee's CES lineup includes a ceiling lamp that simulates skylights</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/govees-ces-lineup-includes-a-ceiling-lamp-that-simulates-skylights-130000611.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">527287b3-fafc-44ae-aaf7-ec32c5bde8d6</guid>
      <description>Govee, which makes some of the more unique and interesting smart lighting products, has a new batch at CES 2026. That includes two ceiling lights (one of which simulates a skylight) and a floor lamp that supports trillions of colors.Govee describes the new Ceiling Light Ultra as "the industry's first ceiling light designed as a true creative canvas." It uses 616 individually controlled LEDs (the highest in its class, according to Govee) to provide that level of detail. Using the Govee app, you can design visuals for it "with up to eight distinct layers of motion, color and shapes."Govee Ceilin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test de l&#8217;Amazfit Active Max : une montre de sport accessible, avec 25 jours d&#8217;autonomie et un &#233;cran lumineux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazfit/2913655_test-de-lamazfit-active-max-une-montre-de-sport-accessible-avec-25-jours-dautonomie-et-un-ecran-lumineux</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazfit/2913655_test-de-lamazfit-active-max-une-montre-de-sport-accessible-avec-25-jours-dautonomie-et-un-ecran-lumineux</guid>
      <description>
Avec l'Active Max, Amazfit propose non seulement une montre de sport accessible, mais aussi un mod&#232;le avec plusieurs semaines d'autonomie malgr&#233; un &#233;cran Amoled lumineux. Voici son test complet. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Best Electrolyte Powders (2026): Tasty and Effective</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-electrolyte-powders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68389a28f6eefaac10ea087a</guid>
      <description>Get those lost minerals back with the help of our top picks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
