<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:28:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo is following up Alarmo with a weird Talking Flower in March</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/865618/nintendo-talking-flower-preorder-super-mario-wonder</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:17:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865618</guid>
      <description>After sharing a brief look at its new Talking Flower during a Nintendo Direct showcase last September that generated more questions than answers, Nintendo has finally revealed more details about what the interactive toy actually does and how much it costs. It shares some functionality with Nintendo's Alarmo alarm clock, but the Talking Flower seems [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL made a pair of AI-powered practice amps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/jbl-made-a-pair-of-ai-powered-practice-amps-221000631.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2a5cbfe-8d8c-4131-b0b7-d3db14c557cc</guid>
      <description>JBL is trying its hand at something new, with a pair of AI-powered practice amps. The BandBox Solo and BandBox Trio include an onboard Stem AI that purportedly lets you separate or remove vocals and instruments from any music streamed over Bluetooth. So, say you're a young guitarist learning &#8220;Stairway to Heaven&#8221; (as one does). At least in theory, you could use the speaker to remove Jimmy Page's part and hone your chops with the rest of the band.The $250 BandBox Solo, designed for individual musicians, has a single guitar / mic input. And the $600 BandBox Trio, better for bands, supports up to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legislators Push to Make Companies Tell Customers When Their Products Will Die</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/legislators-push-to-make-companies-tell-customers-when-their-products-will-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69712224cad1b20bf41c64d0</guid>
      <description>A pair of bills in Massachusetts would require manufacturers to tell consumers when their connected gadgets are going dark. It should be a boon for cybersecurity as connected devices grow obsolete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vimeo lays off &#8216;large portion&#8217; of staff after Bending Spoons buyout</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866238/vimeo-layoffs-bending-spoons-acquisition</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:02:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866238</guid>
      <description>Vimeo is laying off employees around the globe just months after the Italian software company Bending Spoons acquired the platform for $1.38 billion, as reported earlier by Business Insider. Even though it's not clear how many people were laid off, Dave Brown, Vimeo's former brand VP, says in a post on LinkedIn that "a large [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Coogler on &#8216;Sinners&#8217; Making Oscar History&#8212;Especially for Horror Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ryan-coogler-on-sinners-making-oscar-history-especially-for-horror-movies-2000713063</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713063</guid>
      <description>The period vampire thriller scored a record-breaking 16 nominations, including Best Picture and Best Director.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telly has only delivered 35,000 of its free televisions with always-on ads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/telly-has-only-delivered-35000-of-its-free-televisions-with-always-on-ads-215033698.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c48e4be-853c-4c3a-9a66-c18965764ade</guid>
      <description>Telly appeared on the home theater scene in 2023 with an unusual proposition. Its business model revolves around giving customers free dual-screen televisions where the lower screen shows non-stop advertisements. At the time, the start-up&#8217;s execs projected that Telly would ship its first 500,000 screens that summer. However, Janko Roettgers of Lowpass reported that Telly only had 35,000 sets in people's homes at the end of the third quarter of 2025. The figure appears to come from a quarterly investor update, but Telly didn't provide Roettgers with any comment on the report.Personally, I don't...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic and Google have a secret $800 million Unreal Engine and services deal</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/866140/epic-google-fortnite-android-unreal-deal-antitrust-settlement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T16:47:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866140</guid>
      <description>A judge is questioning whether Epic Games and Google are settling their long-running antitrust fight partly because of a previously unannounced partnership involving the Unreal Engine, Fortnite, and Android. In a hearing in San Francisco today, the court revealed that Epic and Google have struck a new deal that apparently includes "joint product development, joint [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are AI agents ready for the workplace? A new benchmark raises doubts.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/are-ai-agents-ready-for-the-workplace-a-new-benchmark-raises-doubts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085277</guid>
      <description>New research looks at how leading AI models hold up doing actual white-collar work tasks, drawn from consulting, investment banking, and law. Most models failed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#8217;s Artemis 2 Is Sending Some Legendary Artifacts Around the Moon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/artemis-2-is-sending-some-legendary-artifacts-around-the-moon-2000713150</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713150</guid>
      <description>The Artemis 2 astronauts&#8212;and the historical keepsakes they&#8217;re bringing with them&#8212;will travel farther from Earth than any have gone before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Exactly the opposite of what AI and mission-critical workloads require": Dell VP says recycling enterprise SSDs to save costs could result in catastrophic data loss</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/exactly-the-opposite-of-what-ai-and-mission-critical-workloads-require-dell-vp-says-recycling-enterprise-ssds-to-save-costs-could-result-in-catastrophic-data-loss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UALxaPj5tAxySw9vKUcwb3</guid>
      <description>Dell warns reusing worn enterprise SSDs because of flash shortages increases failure risks for AI and mission-critical storage environments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ChatGPT ends up in childrens toys</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/chatgpt-ai-toys</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01zxekSq8hzseXOtl6G4tNt</guid>
      <description>A ChatGPT-enabled teddy bear got spicy. Then U.S. senators started paying attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 hit by outage, preventing access to emails and files</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/microsoft-365-hit-by-outage-preventing-access-to-emails-and-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085280</guid>
      <description>An hours-long outage is preventing Microsoft's enterprise customers from accessing their inboxes, files, and video meetings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Markey questions OpenAI about &#8216;deceptive advertising&#8217; in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865854/senator-ed-markey-ai-companies-chatbots-advertising</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T16:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865854</guid>
      <description>Sen. Ed Markey (D-MA) is pressing OpenAI about its move to bring ads to ChatGPT, and is asking several other companies whether they have similar plans. In letters to the CEOs of OpenAI, Anthropic, Google, Meta, Microsoft, Snap, and xAI, Markey writes that embedding ads into AI chatbots "raises significant concerns for consumer protection, privacy, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla is finally doing unsupervised robotaxi rides</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/866165/tesla-robotaxi-unsupervised-austin-texas-safety-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T16:23:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866165</guid>
      <description>Tesla is finally doing unsupervised robotaxi trips in Austin, Texas, according to a video posted on X. Elon Musk reposted the video, congratulating Tesla's AI team for the milestone. For months, Tesla's robotaxis in Austin and San Francisco have included safety monitors with access to a kill switch in case of emergency - a fallback [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Evidence Melts the Stonehenge Glacier Theory</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-evidence-melts-the-stonehenge-glacier-theory-2000713126</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713126</guid>
      <description>It seems like glaciers weren't helpful in the construction of the famous prehistoric monument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious FTX Exec Caroline Ellison Is Out of Federal Custody</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/notorious-ftx-exec-caroline-ellison-is-out-of-federal-custody-2000713133</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713133</guid>
      <description>SBF's ex-girlfriend was released early after cooperating in the FTX fraud case. Is anyone hiring?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patagonia takes drag queen Pattie Gonia to court in trademark infringement lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479616/patagonia-files-lawsuit-against-pattie-gonia-drag-queen-trademark-infringement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T21:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479616/patagonia-files-lawsuit-against-pattie-gonia-drag-queen-trademark-infringement</guid>
      <description>The outdoor apparel company says it&#8217;s suing the drag queen and environmentalist for $1 in damages to &#8216;protect the brand.&#8217;
Patagonia, the outdoor apparel company, is suing Pattie Gonia, the drag queen and environmentalist, for trademark infringement&#8212;a move the company says is necessary to &#8220;protect the brand [it has] spent the last 50 years building.&#8221;&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Cool Details We Spotted in the &#8216;Maul&#8212;Shadow Lord&#8217; Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-maul-shadow-lord-trailer-breakdown-2000713065</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713065</guid>
      <description>Our first proper look at Darth Maul's new animated series brings some interesting ties to other areas of the 'Star Wars' galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Garmin kept accidentally calling people in the shower &#8212; here's the simple fix</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-trackers/my-garmin-kept-accidentally-calling-people-in-the-shower-heres-the-simple-fix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86XE5fDWYeqgYg2btuyDNU</guid>
      <description>My Garmin watch has a life of its own in the shower &#8212; here's how to set up a touchscreen locking hot key.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Good luck, the rest of you&#8217;: Volvo taunts Ford and Volkswagen and says it's overcome 'painful' software issues with new EX60</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/good-luck-the-rest-of-you-volvo-taunts-ford-and-volkswagen-and-says-its-overcome-painful-software-issues-with-new-ex60</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NPBASEWFZvWryK7LFrx7BR</guid>
      <description>Volvo unveils the upcoming EX60 electric SUV, which it claims is a game changer. But it still has a huge task on its hands to make customers forget about the EX90 software debacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Sure Made Lots of Predictions at Davos</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-sure-made-lots-of-predictions-at-davos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697256adfad3dcdb3fa877e9</guid>
      <description>Humanoid robots, space travel, the science of aging&#8212;Musk weighed in on all of it at this week&#8217;s World Economic Forum. But his predictions rarely work out the way he says they will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 and Outlook are down for many &#8211; here's everything we know about issues affecting the apps, as a disruption is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/microsoft-outlook-365-outage-january-22-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TdGHkE25WjzLirHS4oh76D</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has confirmed an issue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Ellison extends deadline for Warner Bros. Discovery takeover offer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/david-ellison-extends-deadline-for-warner-bros-discovery-takeover-offer-204752313.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9a88ff9-8c85-4305-a835-21506b4531ac</guid>
      <description>Paramount Skydance CEO David Ellison is apparently still hopeful that investors will approve his $108.4 billion hostile takeover of Warner Bros. Discovery. Paramount Skydance announced Thursday that it's extending its all-cash offer to acquire the storied studio, and giving investors until February 20, 2026 to accept. The company's previous offer expired on January 21, but with a lawsuit in the works and a revised Netflix deal to compete with, Paramount Skydance wants to stay in the conversation.Netflix and Warner Bros. Discovery originally announced their $82.7 billion acquisition agreement i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's biggest memory rival has a clever plan to make SSDs bigger (but not cheaper) &#8212; split-cell 5-bit flash sounds like RAID-0 on hard drives, but for SSD</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/samsungs-biggest-ssd-rival-has-a-clever-plan-to-make-ssd-bigger-but-not-cheaper-split-cell-5-bit-flash-sounds-like-raid-0-on-hard-drives-but-for-ssd</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zgdHLELu8u2F6M6FqiUnaH</guid>
      <description>SK Hynix introduces split-cell 5-bit NAND flash that increases SSD capacity, improves speed, and extends endurance without increasing costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring says it&amp;#8217;s not giving ICE access to its cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866003/ring-ice-camera-access-flock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T15:30:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866003</guid>
      <description>Ring's partnership with Flock is sparking renewed online backlash this week, with influencers calling for people to smash their Ring cameras and claiming the company is part of the surveillance state amid heightened concerns over ICE actions. Flock is an AI-powered surveillance camera company that has reportedly allowed government agencies - including ICE - to [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We had to do a lot of technological work that was sort of unprecedented ... which was really challenging and exciting,' Crossplay producer on the effort to bring The New York Times' first two-player game to life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/we-had-to-do-a-lot-of-technological-work-that-was-sort-of-unprecedented-which-was-really-challenging-and-exciting-crossplay-producer-on-the-effort-to-bring-the-new-york-times-first-two-player-game-to-life</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xvXwNrUjsYr7xKQGNW2obE</guid>
      <description>TechRadar speaks with New York Times Senior Producer Jeff Petriello about the origins of the newly launched Crossplay, its hidden easter eggs, and what&#8217;s next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have your say: do you actually use Apple Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/have-your-say-do-you-actually-use-apple-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qV3vD8VSZvhkMa9iqd3Jn8</guid>
      <description>Apple Intelligence hasn't won over a lot of TechRadar, but let me know if you use it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
