<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:39:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Trends Explore page gets new Gemini capabilities</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/googles-trends-explore-page-gets-new-gemini-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082705</guid>
      <description>The Trends Explore page for users to analyze search interest  just got a major upgrade. It now uses Gemini to identify and compare relevant trends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPEngine buys major WordPress agency in drive to add more enterprise customers faster</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/wpengine-buys-major-wordpress-agency-in-drive-to-add-more-enterprise-customers-faster</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7DsBDEExqPC7Mrf4TyB2un</guid>
      <description>WP Engine acquires Big Bite, ending its agency role and integrating engineers internally to expand WordPress products for publishers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 30 Most Anticipated Films of 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/most-anticipated-movies-2026-ranked-2000708402</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708402</guid>
      <description>Here are the sci-fi, fantasy, horror, animated, and superhero movies we're most excited about coming out this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network appears to be having technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Users on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even Verizon&#8217;s own network status page is struggling to load.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started growing around 12PM ET and now number in the hundreds of thousands.We are aware of an issue impacting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's new Cowork tool offers Claude coding help to non-experts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/anthropics-new-cowork-tool-offers-claude-coding-help-to-non-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vmYiuq5re8ogYbWViMo2ph</guid>
      <description>Cowork will make plans and execute tasks just like a colleague, so all you have to do is tell it what you want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini is winning</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/861863/google-gemini-ai-race-winner</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:16:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861863</guid>
      <description>If you want to win in AI - and I mean win in the biggest, most lucrative, most shape-the-world-in-your-image kind of way - you have to do a bunch of hard things simultaneously. You need to have a model that is unquestionably one of the best on the market. You need the nearly infinite resources [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoFundMe Campaign for Autoworker Who Got the Middle Finger From Trump Hits $340,000</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gofundme-campaign-for-autoworker-who-got-the-middle-finger-from-trump-hits-340000-2000710238</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710238</guid>
      <description>The autoworker called the president a "pedophile protector," a reference to his suppression of the Epstein files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus Game Catalog additions for January include Resident Evil Village and Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/ps-plus-game-catalog-additions-for-january-include-resident-evil-village-and-like-a-dragon-infinite-wealth-181501574.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b08ae624-21a4-4141-b0bf-3e32e5c6ca56</guid>
      <description>Sony just announced January's Game Catalog additions for PS Plus subscribers and it's a fantastic lineup. All of these titles will be ready to play on January 20.

First up, there's Resident Evil Village. This is a direct sequel to 2017&#8217;s Resident Evil 7: Biohazard. It's a full game with plenty of jump scares and an engrossing narrative. It's set in a spooky village, thus the name, and a nearby castle. This shouldn't disappoint fans of the franchise and will be available for both PS4 and PS5.

Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth is a 2024 sequel to Yakuza: Like a Dragon. It was a massive hit upon r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Why your phone says SOS, what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-outage-phone-sos-what-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b3BjNJgL2nDXUlVE7I4JU</guid>
      <description>There appears to be a major Verizon outage. Here's what to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He could just turn it off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/he-could-just-turn-it-off-180209551.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d0e43da-f59d-4728-986e-a3a7a9681a7c</guid>
      <description>Generative AI, we are repeatedly told, is a transformative and complicated technology. So complicated that its own creators are unable to explain why it acts the way it does, and so transformative that we'd be fools to stand in the way of progress. Even when progress resembles a machine for undressing strangers without their consent on an unprecedented scale, as has been the case of late with Elon Musk's Grok chatbot.&#160;
UK Prime Minister Kier Starmer seems to have so fully bought into the grand lie of the AI bubble that he was willing to announce:
"I have been informed this morning that X is ac...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to turn off a VPN on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-turn-off-a-vpn-on-iphone-180000533.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7934a72d-401b-46dd-b5d3-718c51489445</guid>
      <description>Look, virtual private networks are great &#8212; I wouldn't have made a list of the best VPNs if I didn't recommend using them. But being able to control your own technology is also important. A VPN can provide protection and peace of mind when used properly, but you may not want it active on your phone all the time.For example: Are your Google search results suddenly in German? That&#8217;s one example of what can happen if you leave your virtual location set to Berlin or Vienna. Or maybe a VPN you installed for work or to watch a single tennis match is persistently trying to keep itself active.The point...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les iPhone 17 ont tout &#233;cras&#233;, mais la victoire d&#8217;Apple me laisse un go&#251;t &#233;trange</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/editoid/2942513_les-iphone-17-ont-tout-ecrase-mais-la-victoire-dapple-me-laisse-un-gout-etrange</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/editoid/2942513_les-iphone-17-ont-tout-ecrase-mais-la-victoire-dapple-me-laisse-un-gout-etrange</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu ce carton ? Apple est num&#233;ro 1 mondial en volume et en valeur pour la troisi&#232;me ann&#233;e cons&#233;cutive. Mais personnellement, cette domination totale me laisse un arri&#232;re-go&#251;t amer.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon has our favorite tech gadgets on sale &#8212; here are 19 deals that I recommend on cheap TVs, headphones, smartwatches, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/amazon-has-our-favorite-tech-gadgets-on-sale-here-are-19-deals-that-i-recommend-on-cheap-tvs-headphones-smartwatches-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pzcFupmzNWHiCXrY6sTLTZ</guid>
      <description>Amazon's winter clearance sale has discounts on our favorite tech gadgets, and I've rounded up the 19 best deals that I recommend from Apple, JBL, Fitbit, and Sony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidentally deleted treasured photos? We have just the service for you - and it's on sale right now this New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/accidentally-deleted-treasured-photos-we-have-just-the-service-for-you-and-its-on-sale-right-now-this-new-year</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RjNWhpENVBRxoEeRaqvAWV</guid>
      <description>Stellar Photo Recovery is our top rated service - and it's up to &#163;80 off!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Atlantic, Penske, and Vox Media have all sued Google for antitrust violations</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861897/atlantic-penske-vox-google-ad-tech-antitrust-lawsuits</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T12:47:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861897</guid>
      <description>Lawsuits seeking damages from Google's illegal ad tech monopoly are piling up following the Justice Department's successful antitrust case. Vox Media, The Verge's parent company, is the latest in a wave of media companies that have filed suit against Google, seeking to be reimbursed for the monopoly profits the tech company allegedly made at publishers' [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X hasn&amp;#8217;t really stopped Grok AI from undressing women in the UK</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861894/grok-still-undressing-in-uk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T12:47:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861894</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's X is trying to stop people using its AI chatbot Grok to undress women amid intensifying outrage and legal scrutiny over the deluge of nonconsensual sexual deepfakes flooding the site. It's not trying very hard: it took us less than a minute to get around its latest attempt to rein in the chatbot. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get three months of Audible for only $3</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-three-months-of-audible-for-only-3-193859098.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>Have a hankering for some audiobooks? Audible is holding one heck of a sale right now, giving users three months of access for $3. That's a dollar per month. This is something of a winter tradition for the Amazon-owned platform and the promotion ends on January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated titles. Think of it like N...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The viral Kodak Charmera is the worst camera I&#8217;ve ever used &#8211; but it&#8217;s so bad and so retro, that I actually love it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/compact-cameras/the-viral-kodak-charmera-is-the-worst-camera-ive-ever-used-but-its-so-bad-and-so-retro-that-i-actually-love-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Titn5eWygNBqWWWPVry8Qb</guid>
      <description>Kodak, the prominent producer of cheap compact cameras, goes even smaller and cheaper with the Charmera keychain camera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Proves It Still Has the Best Software for Better-Looking Games</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nvidia-proves-it-still-has-the-best-software-for-better-looking-games-2000710251</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710251</guid>
      <description>While 6x frame gen won&#8217;t be here until spring, better AI upscaling is more than welcome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>En solde &#224; -50 %, le Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 6 est toujours une r&#233;f&#233;rence en mati&#232;re de smartphone pliable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2943063_en-solde-a-50-le-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-6-est-toujours-une-reference-en-matiere-de-smartphone-pliable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2943063_en-solde-a-50-le-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-6-est-toujours-une-reference-en-matiere-de-smartphone-pliable</guid>
      <description>
Samsung est toujours un mod&#232;le en mati&#232;re de smartphone pliable et ce Galaxy Z Flip 6 ne fait pas exception. Chez Carrefour, vous pourrez le retrouver pour 559,99 euros au lieu de 1 199,99 euros si vous choisissez l'option de livraison.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major US healthcare breach exposes data on 145,000 patients - Central Maine Healthcare reveals all</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/major-us-healthcare-breach-exposes-data-on-145-000-patients-central-maine-healthcare-reveals-all</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fT2TyKbHJn9VoQNWsp5c7n</guid>
      <description>Names, health insurance information, and SSNs were all exposed in a breach which lasted for more than two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These PSVR 2 demos and game trials are must-plays if you recently picked up Sony's latest VR headset</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/these-psvr-2-demos-and-game-trials-are-must-plays-if-you-recently-picked-up-sonys-latest-vr-headset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Q49HYiWaayjZgUQ52Z5K5n</guid>
      <description>PSVR 2 free demos are mostly offered via PS Plus Premium, though they're well worth checking out. Here's five game trials and demos to get you started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Auto : pourquoi un bug majeur rend Google Assistant inutilisable pour de nombreux conducteurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/2943193_android-auto-pourquoi-un-bug-majeur-rend-google-assistant-inutilisable-pour-de-nombreux-conducteurs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/2943193_android-auto-pourquoi-un-bug-majeur-rend-google-assistant-inutilisable-pour-de-nombreux-conducteurs</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez remarqu&#233; ? Depuis quelques semaines, votre voiture semble &#234;tre devenue sourde. Vous demandez un itin&#233;raire, et Google Assistant vous r&#233;pond ce fatidique "Je n'ai pas compris". Ce n'est pas votre microphone qui d&#233;raille, c'est Google qui g&#232;re (tr&#232;s) mal sa transition vers Gemini. Et franchement, &#231;a commence &#224; bien faire.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flamb&#233;e de la RAM&#160;: le patron de Nothing annonce des hausses de prix pour ses smartphones</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/flambee-de-la-ram-le-patron-de-nothing-annonce-des-hausses-de-prix-pour-ses-smartphones.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320152</guid>
      <description>2026 sera l'ann&#233;e o&#249; la course &#224; l'&#233;chalote des caract&#233;ristiques techniques prendra fin, ass&#232;ne Carl Pei, le fondateur et patron de Nothing. Et pour cause : les composants comme la m&#233;moire vont co&#251;ter si cher que les constructeurs (en dehors du tr&#232;s haut de gamme) devront se contenter de peu tout en offrant quand m&#234;me &#224; leurs utilisateurs des nouveaut&#233;s qui tirent le march&#233; vers le haut....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK digital ID plans will no longer be mandatory</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861890/uk-backpeddles-mandatory-digital-id-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T12:36:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861890</guid>
      <description>The United Kingdom has walked back plans to make its upcoming digital ID scheme a mandatory requirement for working adults. While the UK government remains "committed to mandatory digital right-to-work checks," an unspecified government spokesperson told The Times, digital ID will now be optional when the initiative is introduced sometime in 2029. The national digital [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon is down, with many users seeing 'SOS' &#8211; here's everything we know about this outage</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/verizon-outage-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">w5FfiYa27ckqf9uyidVpzF</guid>
      <description>Verizon is experiencing issues as of midday on January 14, 2026, with many users reporting no service and seeing an SOS icon instead of bars. TechRadar is following this story and has reached out to Verizon for more information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;In AI models, the real bottleneck isn&#8217;t computing power &#8212; it&#8217;s memory&#8217;: Phison CEO on 244TB SSDs, PLC NAND, why high-bandwidth flash isn&#8217;t a good idea, and why CSP profit goes hand in hand with storage capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/in-ai-models-the-real-bottleneck-isnt-computing-power-its-memory-phison-ceo-on-244tb-ssds-plc-nand-why-high-bandwidth-flash-isnt-a-good-idea-and-why-csp-profit-goes-hand-in-hand-with-storage-capacity</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcmQFjwbXzjcz3PJYrBXDA</guid>
      <description>Phison CEO tells us about 244TB SSDs, PLC NAND, and why High Bandwidth Flash is not a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 6 Apple apps just got hit by a subscription bombshell &#8211;but users say there&#8217;s an even bigger crime</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/these-6-apple-apps-just-got-hit-by-a-subscription-bombshell-but-users-say-theres-an-even-bigger-crime</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">r9PSuXBExExK9ob2jSixMn</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s Creator Studio subscription locks features behind a paywall and comes with some unpopular new icons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lovehoney has tons of V-Day goodies on sale: Get 50% off vibrators, lingerie, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-lovehoney-valentines-day-sale-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043ce0SfpcyXmTCq7Rp9A84</guid>
      <description>Save up to 70% at Lovehoney's Valentine's Day sale. Get clitoral suction toys for $43, lingerie under $25, and a free gift on orders over $89.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy&#8217;s Edge Will Soon Cover All Eras of &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/galaxys-edge-will-soon-cover-all-eras-of-star-wars-2000710279</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710279</guid>
      <description>Disney's 'Star Wars' land is moving on from its original setting during the Sequel Trilogy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Finally Figured Out How Some People Get Drunk Without Drinking</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-finally-figured-out-how-some-people-get-drunk-without-drinking-2000710220</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710220</guid>
      <description>Gut microbes can make people drunk without booze. Scientists now know which ones to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Incroyablement mauvais&#160;&#187; : le patron de GOG d&#233;truit Windows et encense Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2943179_incroyablement-mauvais-le-patron-de-gog-detruit-windows-et-encense-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2943179_incroyablement-mauvais-le-patron-de-gog-detruit-windows-et-encense-linux</guid>
      <description>
Vous trouvez que Windows 11 devient une usine &#224; gaz publicitaire ? Vous n'&#234;tes pas seul. Le propri&#233;taire de GOG vient de tirer &#224; boulets rouges sur l'OS de Microsoft, qu'il a personnellement abandonn&#233; pour&#8230; un Mac. Mais la vraie info est ailleurs : GOG pr&#233;pare sa riposte sur Linux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dream-team combo: The new Rubiks Cube Tetris Brainteaser joins two of the best classic games</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/rubiks-cube-tetris-brainteaster</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04omS24IA2rY04PvvcYhqdW</guid>
      <description>The new Rubik's Cube Tetris Brainteaser is on sale at Target and Amazon, combining the two classic games into one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am literally not in it&#8230;but I could be in it.' Kat Dennings says she's 'in Marvel&#8217;s system' so she can't rule out an appearance in Avengers: Doomsday</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/i-am-literally-not-in-it-but-i-could-be-in-it-kat-dennings-says-shes-in-marvels-system-so-she-cant-rule-out-an-appearance-in-avengers-doomsday</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pVbuUdGTbmhyoybtTh4as8</guid>
      <description>&#8216;They could put me in anything they want at this point&#8217;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Next Smart Glasses May Have Actually Learned Something From the Glasshole Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/googles-next-smart-glasses-may-have-actually-learned-something-from-the-glasshole-days-2000710198</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710198</guid>
      <description>If Reddit leaks are anything to go off of, Google Glass 2.0 might have learned a thing or two about privacy and distraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snag the Razer Basilisk V3 Pro gaming mouse near its lowest price ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-razer-basilisk-v3-pro-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00IrbOHfhPKkzeGAwgjsjvO</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 14, get the Razer Basilisk V3 Pro gaming mouse near its lowest price ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Issues Arrest Warrant for OnePlus CEO in Crackdown on Tech Talent Poaching</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/taiwan-issues-arrest-warrant-for-oneplus-ceo-in-crackdown-on-tech-talent-poaching-2000710236</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710236</guid>
      <description>Prosecutors allege Pete Lau recruited dozens of Taiwanese engineers without proper government approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch Heated Rivalry for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/theres-a-sneaky-way-to-watch-heated-rivalry-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CoUWhGDHGTEgg3weSEUcsm</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch YouTube ad-free from anywhere in the world, without coughing up for a Premium subscription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver : voici les offres immanquables de la deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque sur Amazon, Fnac, Darty&#8230;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-offres-immanquables-deuxieme-demarque-amazon-fnac-darty-etc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-offres-immanquables-deuxieme-demarque-amazon-fnac-darty-etc</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver ont commenc&#233; la semaine derni&#232;re et nous voici d&#233;j&#224; &#224; la deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque ! Au programme : encore plus d'offres pour des produits Tech &#224; prix cass&#233;s, que ce soient les smartphones, les tablettes, les t&#233;l&#233;viseurs 4K, et surtout les ordinateurs portables, gaming ou de bureautique. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandcamp takes a stand against AI music, banning it from the platform</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/bandcamp-takes-a-stand-against-ai-music-banning-it-from-the-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082593</guid>
      <description>"We want musicians to keep making music, and for fans to have confidence that the music they find on Bandcamp was created by humans," the company said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers hijack LinkedIn comments to spread malware - here's what to look out for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-hijack-linkedin-comments-to-spread-malware-heres-what-to-look-out-for</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">m6vPCcxjkaBwSauA4ND6PC</guid>
      <description>As if AI-generated content wasn't enough, phishing has now made it into LinkedIn comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#8217;t Believe Where Scientists Found a 14,400-Year-Old Woolly Rhino Genome</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-wont-believe-where-scientists-found-a-14400-year-old-woolly-rhino-genome-2000710184</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710184</guid>
      <description>The stomach of an Ice Age puppy is shedding new light onto the woolly rhinoceros and what&#8212;or what didn't&#8212;cause these horned giants to die out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skipping this exercise at the gym could be bad for your brain</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474508/skipping-this-exercise-at-the-gym-could-be-bad-for-your-brain</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474508/skipping-this-exercise-at-the-gym-could-be-bad-for-your-brain</guid>
      <description>Getting swole is great. But cognitive function also improves when you work a certain muscle group.
&#8220;Never skip leg day&#8221; sounds like something a swole gym bro with killer quads might harp on about. But doctors also sing the praises of lunges and split bench squats, and not for the reason you might think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Nigeria vs. Morocco online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nigeria-morocco-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05Y5zf6YzUtErL0WWBURTBz</guid>
      <description>How to watch Africa Cup of Nations for free. Live stream Nigeria vs. Morocco in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le PlayStation Plus commence tr&#232;s fort 2026 avec Resident Evil, Yakuza et Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2943085_le-playstation-plus-commence-tres-fort-2026-avec-resident-evil-yakuza-et-exit-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2943085_le-playstation-plus-commence-tres-fort-2026-avec-resident-evil-yakuza-et-exit-8</guid>
      <description>
Voici la premi&#232;re s&#233;lection de jeux &#224; int&#233;grer le catalogue du PlayStation Plus Extra et Premium en 2026. Plusieurs gros titres font leur arriv&#233;e dans le catalogue comme Resident Evil Village, Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth et Expeditions: A MudRunner Game.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia : le DLSS 4.5 arrive sur toutes les cartes RTX avec une option qui change tout</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2942925_nvidia-le-dlss-4-5-arrive-sur-toutes-les-cartes-rtx-avec-une-option-qui-change-tout</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2942925_nvidia-le-dlss-4-5-arrive-sur-toutes-les-cartes-rtx-avec-une-option-qui-change-tout</guid>
      <description>
Nvidia officialise le lancement du DLSS 4.5 pour toutes les cartes graphiques GeForce RTX et en profite pour rendre bien plus pratique son application en jeu.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP Omen Max 16 review: a powerhouse gaming laptop at a compelling price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/hp-omen-max-16</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DNm2N8uMGPEH9FHK9bdNjZ</guid>
      <description>The HP Omen Max 16 is a powerful gaming laptop that offers excellent performance for a very competitive price - but the design is dated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The LG C6 is LG's mid-range OLED TV for 2026 &#8211; here's everything we know so far about one of this year's most anticipated TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-lg-c6-is-lgs-mid-range-oled-tv-for-2026-heres-everything-we-know-so-far-about-one-of-this-years-most-anticipated-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37QMmKqkkY5375zWp7wH8W</guid>
      <description>Here's all the information we have about the LG C6, as revealed at CES 2026, including its two variations and LG's new processor and AI features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euphoria Season 3 trailer: Rues on the run, Jules is a sugar baby, and Im worried</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/euphoria-season-3-trailer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">019PNuKkeYSswGIvVwNlWMX</guid>
      <description>"Euphoria" Season 3 premieres April 12 on HBO. The series, which stars Zendaya, picks up after a five-year time jump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first-gen Bose QuietComfort Ultra headphones are $150 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-first-gen-bose-quietcomfort-ultra-headphones-are-150-off-right-now-164826329.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0e52277-834b-45d3-97d6-f9aebb452d38</guid>
      <description>The first-generation Bose QuietComfort Ultra headphones are on sale right now for $280, marked down from $430. That 35 percent savings is an even steeper discount than we saw last year Black Friday.


In our review of the first-generation Ultras, we gave them a score of 86 out of 100, noting their best-in-class active noise cancellation (ANC) and comfort. Bose improved its stock tuning for these headphones, which we could immediately tell sounded warmer and clearer. Bose has typically lagged behind the likes of Sony and Sennheiser in raw sound quality, but the first-generation QuietComfort Ult...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priyanka Chopra Jonas and Karl Urban's new Prime Video movie The Bluff gets a swashbuckling first trailer &#8212; and February looks like it'll be a pirate's life for me</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/amazon-prime-video/priyanka-chopra-jonas-and-karl-urbans-new-prime-video-movie-the-bluff-gets-a-swashbuckling-first-trailer-and-february-looks-like-itll-be-a-pirates-life-for-me</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">U6xAvPFyPGhwxhcndQYkU4</guid>
      <description>Amazon has released the first trailer for its new, violent pirate movie The Bluff ahead of its late February debut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Police Used Microsoft Copilot for Faulty Report That Led to Ban on Soccer Team Fans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/british-police-used-microsoft-copilot-for-faulty-report-that-led-to-ban-on-soccer-team-fans-2000710201</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710201</guid>
      <description>Microsoft's AI assistant hallucinated a soccer match.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&#8217;s trade surplus soared to a record $1.2 trillion in 2025, despite Trump&#8217;s tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474737/chinas-trade-surplus-soars-record-1-2-trillion-despite-trumps-tariffs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T16:43:59</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474737/chinas-trade-surplus-soars-record-1-2-trillion-despite-trumps-tariffs</guid>
      <description>This past November, China&#8217;s trade surplus topped the $1 trillion mark for the first time, ever.  
China&#8217;s trade surplus surged to a record of almost $1.2 trillion in 2025, the government said Wednesday, as exports to other countries made up for slowing shipments to the U.S. under President Donald Trump&#8217;s onslaught of higher tariffs.China&#8217;s exports rose 5.5% for the whole of last year to $3.77 trillion, customs data showed, as Chinese automakers and other manufacturers expanded into markets across the globe. Imports flatlined at $2.58 trillion. The 2024 trade surplus was over $992 billion.In De...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit, Strava and Nike Training Club are the most data-hungry fitness apps according to a new report &#8212; here are 5 ways to protect your privacy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-apps/fitbit-strava-and-nike-training-club-are-the-most-data-hungry-fitness-apps-according-to-a-new-report-here-are-4-ways-to-protect-your-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">t9WcirxFs97Kd4wDAKbn9V</guid>
      <description>Surfshark analyzed 16 different fitness apps, and ranked them by most to least data collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chez SFR, r&#233;silier l&#8217;abonnement internet co&#251;tera d&#233;sormais plus cher, sans exception</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/chez-sfr-resilier-labonnement-internet-coutera-desormais-plus-cher-sans-exception.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320139</guid>
      <description>Mauvaise surprise pour les clients internet de SFR : d&#233;sormais, tout le monde est assujetti &#224; des frais de r&#233;siliation de 59&#160;&#8364;. Jusqu'&#224; pr&#233;sent, tous ceux qui avaient souscrit avant avril 2025 b&#233;n&#233;ficiaient d'une ristourne de 10&#160;&#8364;, mais c'est bien termin&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates-backed Type One Energy raises $87M ahead of $250M Series B</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/bill-gates-backed-type-one-energy-raises-87m-ahead-of-250m-series-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082610</guid>
      <description>Type One Energy has raised more than $160 million from investors to date. The new funding will help the company further refine its stellarator technology.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
