<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:36:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google Just Stuffed a Bunch of New AI Into Your Gmail</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-just-stuffed-a-bunch-of-new-ai-into-your-gmail-2000707529</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707529</guid>
      <description>Heard you like inboxes. Well, you're getting an "AI Inbox" in your inbox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour les geeks un peu nostalgiques, la console SNK Neo Geo Mini Japonaise avec 40 jeux est sold&#233;e &#224; -40%</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935719_pour-les-geeks-un-peu-nostalgiques-la-console-snk-neo-geo-mini-japonaise-avec-40-jeux-est-soldee-a-40</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935719_pour-les-geeks-un-peu-nostalgiques-la-console-snk-neo-geo-mini-japonaise-avec-40-jeux-est-soldee-a-40</guid>
      <description>
La nostalgie a le vent en poupe et les constructeurs le savent : c'est pourquoi vous retrouvez la SNK Neo Geo Mini Japonaise au format bartop sur le march&#233;. En plus, elle est &#224; 59,49 euros au lieu de 99,99 euros sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ s&#8217;essaie &#224; la vid&#233;o verticale pour retenir ses abonn&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/disney-sessaie-a-la-video-verticale-pour-retenir-ses-abonnes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318916</guid>
      <description>Disney+ n'est pas all&#233; chercher tr&#232;s loin sa prochaine nouveaut&#233; : le service de streaming va en effet proposer des vid&#233;os au format vertical histoire de faire mousser l'engagement des abonn&#233;s. Comme chez TikTok, Instagram, ou encore&#8230; Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV makers are taking AI too far</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/858463/tv-too-much-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T11:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858463</guid>
      <description>This is Lowpass by Janko Roettgers, a newsletter on the ever-evolving intersection of tech and entertainment, syndicated just for The Verge subscribers once a week. Every year, TV makers flock to CES in Las Vegas to show off bigger, brighter, and better-looking displays. And every year, the same companies also use the show to throw [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon frappe fort pour le d&#233;but des soldes d&#8217;hiver : les 10 deals Tech &#224; retenir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-frappe-fort-pour-le-debut-des-soldes-dhiver-les-10-deals-tech-a-retenir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-frappe-fort-pour-le-debut-des-soldes-dhiver-les-10-deals-tech-a-retenir</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver viennent de d&#233;buter, et si Amazon n'indique pas clairement sa participation &#224; l'&#233;v&#233;nement, de nombreux produits Tech se trouvent &#224; prix cass&#233;s chez le g&#233;ant du e-commerce. L&#8217;occasion parfaite de s&#8217;&#233;quiper malin pour bien d&#233;marrer l'ann&#233;e 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the tech and gadgets announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/all-the-tech-and-gadgets-announced-at-ces-2026-130124023.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown off a wide ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who needs Black Friday? The AirPods Pro 3 plummet to a record-low price again</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/who-needs-black-friday-the-airpods-pro-3-plummet-to-a-record-low-price-again</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sHvBtRcZ3SYUejHTWGAxrX</guid>
      <description>The Apple AirPods Pro 3 have dropped back to their lowest-ever price of $199.99 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US withdraws from internet freedom bodies it deems "wasteful, ineffective and harmful"</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/us-withdraws-from-internet-freedom-bodies-it-deems-wasteful-ineffective-and-harmful</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9wGjiPDN6yWhfXqx9LsnFh</guid>
      <description>President Trump has signed an executive order withdrawing the country from key international internet freedom organizations, including the Freedom Online Coalition and Global Forum on Cyber Expertise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s lawsuit against OpenAI will face a jury in March</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/elon-musks-lawsuit-against-openai-will-face-a-jury-in-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081167</guid>
      <description>District Judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers said there was evidence suggesting OpenAI&#8217;s leaders made assurances that its original nonprofit structure would be maintained. The case will go to trial in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Galaxy Watch 8 is TechRadar's best smartwatch of 2025 &#8212; and it's $70 off at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/the-galaxy-watch-8-is-techradars-best-smartwatch-of-2025-and-its-usd70-off-at-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">S2qJi66kEN5k5tipzcBjVY</guid>
      <description>Samsung's Galaxy Watch 8 is our best smartwatch of the year, and Amazon has a $70 discount right now, bringing the price down to $279.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Code 2.1.0 arrives with smoother workflows and smarter agents</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/claude-code-2-1-0-arrives-with-smoother-workflows-and-smarter-agents</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51oDu6ZOjdvfl5Wl57vbxD</guid>
      <description>Anthropic has released Claude Code v2.1.0, a notable update to its "vibe coding" development environment for autonomously building software, spinning up AI agents, and completing a wide range of computer tasks, according to Head of Claude Code Boris Cherny in a post on X last night.The release introduces improvements across agent lifecycle control, skill development, session portability, and multilingual output &#8212; all bundled in a dense package of 1,096 commits. It comes amid a growing wave of praise for Claude Code from software developers and startup founders on X, as they increasingly use th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's New Year gaming laptop deals offer up to $650 off RTX 5060 and RTX 5070 models this week</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/best-buys-new-year-gaming-laptop-deals-offer-up-to-usd650-off-rtx-5060-and-rtx-5070-models-this-week</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Acd8chynXyPbTXCxZEaVMd</guid>
      <description>Don't miss Best Buy's excellent New Year sale if you're on the lookout for a seriously cheap premium gaming laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruxelles et Londres se penchent sur Grok apr&#232;s la g&#233;n&#233;ration d&#8217;images sexuelles, y compris d&#8217;enfants</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/bruxelles-et-londres-se-penchent-sur-grok-apres-la-generation-dimages-sexuelles-y-compris-denfants.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318886</guid>
      <description>Les ennuis s'accumulent pour Grok, xAI, X/Twitter et Elon Musk. La facilit&#233; avec laquelle le bot IA g&#233;n&#232;re et diffuse des images sexuellement explicites, y compris d'enfants, provoque la mobilisation de la Commission europ&#233;enne et du r&#233;gulateur britannique.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Cruise Helped Shoot a Lightsaber Duel for &#8216;Star Wars: Starfighter&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-starfighter-tom-cruise-lightsaber-duel-2000707547</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707547</guid>
      <description>An unlikely source gives us an intriguing new detail about Shawn Levy's new 'Star Wars' movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honor steps up to the big leagues with the Magic 8 Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/854163/honor-magic-8-pro-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854163</guid>
      <description>I have a simple gut check I use when reviewing phones, especially ones that rely on their cameras as a selling point: how often do I wish I had another phone with me instead? These days, it's mostly the Vivo X300 Pro I miss when I'm testing something else, a phone whose camera remains unmatched. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this the world&#8217;s first solid-state battery?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/858514/is-this-the-worlds-first-solid-state-battery</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858514</guid>
      <description>CES is a land of bold announcements of amazing, innovative products and technologies that will revolutionize the world, often set for release in two years' time. Twenty-four months seems to be about the right hype window: close enough to generate excitement and investment, but far enough that everyone forgets about your promises before that deadline [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Hunting Party season 2 &#8212; stream online from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/the-hunting-party-season-2</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6p7mYteaSc77reQ4ARM3xN</guid>
      <description>NBC&#8217;s manhunt thriller returns as Bex Henderson&#8217;s team pursues the fugitives of 'The Pit'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holographic AI is going to happen. But this bizarre &#8216;friend in a jar&#8217; is not it</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470610/razer-holographic-ai-project-ava</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470610/razer-holographic-ai-project-ava</guid>
      <description>Humans want to personify AI. Razer&#8217;s new &#8216;holographic&#8217; companion is a crude step toward that future.
Gaming peripheral company Razer is betting that people want AI holograms. So much so that it introduce a perplexing new product at CES 2026 that early critics have dubbed a &#8220;friend in a bottle.&#8221; Project AVA, is a small glass cylinder that features a 5.5-inch animated desk buddy that can interact with you, coach you, or offer gaming advice on demand&#8212;all powered by xAI&#8217;s Grok....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail&#8217;s new inbox is the ultimate gateway drug to AI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470945/gmail-new-ai-inbox-gateway-drug-to-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470945/gmail-new-ai-inbox-gateway-drug-to-ai</guid>
      <description>The world&#8217;s largest email service just initiated step one in a larger plan to secure Google as your favorite AI platform.
Gmail was always a gateway drug for the greater Google ecosystem. When it launched in 2004, Gmail stood out by offering then-wild amounts of storage for free. Despite few updates to its design in two decades, it now boasts 2.5 billion users and is the largest email service in the world....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo is bringing its cute My Mario collection to the US next month</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858587/nintendo-my-mario-apparal-toys-book-mobile-app</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T10:59:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858587</guid>
      <description>After exclusively launching in Japan last August, Nintendo has announced its My Mario product line will be available in the US starting next month. That includes the interactive Hello, Mario! app featuring an interactive 3D version of Mario's head that reacts to being poked, tugged, and flung around the screen. The app will be available [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger brade un tas de produit Tech durant les soldes d&#8217;hiver : voici le TOP 15 des deals &#224; saisir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-degaine-de-belles-offres-pour-les-soldes-dhiver-les-10-offres-qui-meritent-votre-argent</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-degaine-de-belles-offres-pour-les-soldes-dhiver-les-10-offres-qui-meritent-votre-argent</guid>
      <description>
Pour le lancement des soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026, Boulanger propose de fortes remises sur de nombreux produits Tech. L&#8217;enseigne d&#233;gaine ses meilleures offres pour faire de bonnes affaires pour ce d&#233;but d'ann&#233;e 2026. Nous avons fait le tri pour vous !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce rover de la Nasa vient d&#8217;envoyer l&#8217;une des plus belles images jamais prises sur Mars</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/espace-ce-rover-nasa-vient-envoyer-plus-belles-images-jamais-prises-mars-129932/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:57:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/espace-ce-rover-nasa-vient-envoyer-plus-belles-images-jamais-prises-mars-129932/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Depuis les flancs du mont Sharp, sur Mars, le rover Curiosity a captur&#233; un panorama saisissant o&#249; les lumi&#232;res du matin et de l&#8217;apr&#232;s-midi se r&#233;pondent. Derri&#232;re ces couleurs se cache un paysage cl&#233; pour comprendre l&#8217;histoire de l&#8217;eau sur la Plan&#232;te rouge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft could reveal its OEM Xbox PC this year according to 'credible rumors'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/xbox/microsoft-could-reveal-its-oem-xbox-pc-this-year-according-to-credible-rumors</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zC3EXMznBtGaQEgZ3BjovZ</guid>
      <description>A new report from Windows Central claims that Microsoft could unveil the first look at its new Xbox hardware this year, which would include an OEM "Xbox" PC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remplacer la RAM ou le SSD de son PC portable : en 2026, la r&#233;parabilit&#233; fait son grand retour sur PC</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2935271_a-linverse-dapple-ces-geants-du-pc-rendent-enfin-leurs-ordinateurs-totalement-reparables</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2935271_a-linverse-dapple-ces-geants-du-pc-rendent-enfin-leurs-ordinateurs-totalement-reparables</guid>
      <description>
Une tendance se d&#233;gage des constructeurs de PC au CES 2026 : la r&#233;parabilit&#233; devient le nouvel argument de vente des g&#233;ants de l&#8217;informatique. Entre le programme "Space Frame" de Lenovo et la mue des Dell XPS, le PC portable de demain ne se jette plus : il se r&#233;pare. Mais &#224; quel prix ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell unveils a massive 52-inch 6K ultrawide curved monitor at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/dell-unveils-a-massive-52-inch-6k-ultrawide-curved-monitor-at-ces-2026-140024842.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f50d6f99-01f1-45ee-9af4-32825a117ff2</guid>
      <description>PC and gaming monitors are among the CES 2026 announcements, and Dell may just have one of the most impressive. The company launched an ultrawide, curved 52-inch 6K monitor at the show this year, a productivity behemoth designed for stock traders, engineers and other professionals. Dell claims the UltraSharp 52 Thunderbolt Hub Monitor is the first 52-incher to market that&#8217;s also ultrawide, curved and supports 6K resolution (but with that many qualifiers almost anything can be a world first).Given Dell&#8217;s experience in the monitor realm, this could be a dream display for professionals who handle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-powered health gadgets at CES 2026 are concerning experts. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471109/ai-powered-health-gadgets-ces-2026-are-concerning-experts-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T15:53:39</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471109/ai-powered-health-gadgets-ces-2026-are-concerning-experts-heres-why</guid>
      <description>During the show in Las Vegas, the FDA announced that it will ease regulations on wellness products such as heart monitors.
Health tech gadgets displayed at the annual CES trade show make a lot of promises. A smart scale promoted a healthier lifestyle by scanning your feet to track your heart health, and an egg-shaped hormone tracker uses AI to help you figure out the best time to conceive.Tech and health experts, however, question the accuracy of products like these and warn of data privacy issues &#8212; especially as the federal government eases up on regulation.The Food and Drug Administration an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best sleep tech doesn&#8217;t cancel noise</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471256/the-best-sleep-tech-doesnt-cancel-noise</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T15:52:03</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471256/the-best-sleep-tech-doesnt-cancel-noise</guid>
      <description>Follow the science to understand how passive noise blocking and noise-masking audio create a truly restful environment.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch MrBeast make celebrities fight it out for $1 million</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/mrbeast-celebrities-1-million-charity-competition</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04I98Z2pnessFiyHdWpTXfc</guid>
      <description>MrBeast had 30 celebs fight it out for $1 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level up your listening with these bmani ANC Headphones for $100 off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-8-bmani-anc-headphones-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ncHsXczxHYzR9KO8eEJXa</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 8, get $100 off the bmani ANC Headphones at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini d&#233;barque dans Gmail : c&#8217;est la fin de votre bo&#238;te de r&#233;ception telle que vous la connaissiez</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2935759_gemini-debarque-dans-gmail-decouvrez-les-trois-nouvelles-fonctions-secretes-de-votre-future-boite-de-reception</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2935759_gemini-debarque-dans-gmail-decouvrez-les-trois-nouvelles-fonctions-secretes-de-votre-future-boite-de-reception</guid>
      <description>
Google int&#232;gre plus profond&#233;ment Gemini &#224; Gmail pour faire de votre bo&#238;te de r&#233;ception un v&#233;ritable assistant personnel. On fait le point sur les trois fonctionnalit&#233;s majeures qui font changer votre fa&#231;on d'utiliser Gmail.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long unskippable ads will reportedly be illegal in one country next month</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/unskippable-ads-illegal-vietnam-5-second-limit</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03CGjen9JnYZiolDWzdj3DE</guid>
      <description>There's one country reportedly taking a stand against the scourge of unskippable ads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The gaming monitors that caught our eye at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-gaming-monitors-that-caught-our-eye-at-ces-2026-130000433.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">956bf7a1-2d74-4ed3-9241-ef90d36cecbf</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 has been a big event for screens of all sizes: TVs, laptops and everything in between. New PC monitors are among the CES announcements, with several companies are using the trade show as an opportunity to update their gaming monitor lineups. Some companies are showing off expanded OLED panels with improved refresh rates, brightness and color production, while others are showing off weirder ideas like a glasses-free 3D monitor. The collection below are some of our favorite gaming monitors that have already been announced:&#160;LG UltraGear GX7LG's latest QHD OLED gaming monitor is its brigh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Xbox Developer Direct showcase is on January 22</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/the-next-xbox-developer-direct-showcase-is-on-january-22-154444166.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e715b5-a7b4-4148-b536-e664adf053a9</guid>
      <description>Xbox will kick off the fourth installment of its Developer Direct event on January 22 at 1PM ET. As usual, we'll get a glimpse at what the upcoming year has in store along with news, new gameplay footage and more directly from the teams behind this year's slate of games.
It's officially Developer_Direct season!Join us on January 22 at 10am PT for an exclusive look at&#160;Fable, Forza Horizon 6, and Beast of Reincarnation: https://t.co/FvFUT7RzVZ | #DeveloperDirect pic.twitter.com/GMRpVDxucs&#8212; Xbox (@Xbox) January 8, 2026

In a blog post announcing the event, Xbox Wire Editor-in-Chief Jon Skrebels s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions I want to ask Trisha Paytas about her potential Congressional run</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/trisha-paytas-congressional-run-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00jbjGmMzt1K9NdtwUzsqHr</guid>
      <description>Influencer and podcaster Trisha Paytas teased a Congressional run on TikTok. We have some questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first Joy-Con 2 color variant is coming soon, but don't expect any big revisions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-first-joy-con-2-color-variant-is-coming-soon-but-dont-expect-any-big-revisions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22anVuF7kyLPGvy9VrSqhH</guid>
      <description>You can pre-order the first alternate Joy-Con 2 color variants now, but there are no big hardware revisions here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fnac et Darty se montrent bien g&#233;n&#233;reux lors des soldes : les 20 deals qui valent le coup</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-cassent-les-prix-pour-les-soldes-dhiver-2026-les-meilleures-offres-tech-a-ne-pas-rater</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-cassent-les-prix-pour-les-soldes-dhiver-2026-les-meilleures-offres-tech-a-ne-pas-rater</guid>
      <description>
C'est le TOP d&#233;part des soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 &#8239;! De quoi faire de belles &#233;conomies sur les produits Tech g&#233;n&#233;ralement vendus &#224; prix fort. Fnac et Darty affichent d&#233;j&#224; de fortes r&#233;ductions : d&#233;couvrez les meilleures offres pour bien commencer l&#8217;ann&#233;e&#8239;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ecovacs Deebot T50 Omni robot vacuum and mop is down to its best price ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-8-ecovacs-deebot-t50-omni-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05TajsS4akSS7f3LkiGZLE6</guid>
      <description>The Ecovacs Deebot T50 Omni robot vacuum and mop is down to $449 at Amazon. That's over 30% off and its best price on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer a r&#233;pondu &#224; l&#8217;une de mes obsessions : les noms indigestes de produits</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/acer/2935677_acer-a-repondu-a-lune-de-mes-obsessions-les-noms-indigestes-de-produits</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/acer/2935677_acer-a-repondu-a-lune-de-mes-obsessions-les-noms-indigestes-de-produits</guid>
      <description>
Les noms des &#233;crans de PC sont souvent incompr&#233;hensibles. Acer travaille sur le sujet.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cdiscount se d&#233;marque en multipliant les codes promos pour les soldes : le TOP 10 des offres &#224; retenir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933945_cdiscount-se-demarque-en-multipliant-les-codes-promos-pour-les-soldes-le-top-10-des-offres-a-retenir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933945_cdiscount-se-demarque-en-multipliant-les-codes-promos-pour-les-soldes-le-top-10-des-offres-a-retenir</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver sont aussi chez Cdiscount, et c&#8217;est le moment id&#233;al pour craquer sur un nouveau produit Tech sans se ruiner. En plus des remises d&#233;j&#224; g&#233;n&#233;reuses, l&#8217;e-commer&#231;ant ajoute deux codes promo exclusifs pour faire encore baisser la note. On vous a s&#233;lectionn&#233; les meilleures offres &#224; ne surtout pas manquer.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, Lego, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adieu la panne de batterie : pour 310 euros, ce smartphone muscl&#233; promet 2 jours d&#8217;autonomie</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2935673_adieu-la-panne-de-batterie-pour-310-euros-ce-smartphone-muscle-promet-2-jours-dautonomie</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2935673_adieu-la-panne-de-batterie-pour-310-euros-ce-smartphone-muscle-promet-2-jours-dautonomie</guid>
      <description>
Le Poco M8 Pro 5G vient d'&#234;tre annonc&#233; et il ne fait pas dans la demi-mesure. Avec sa batterie monstrueuse de 6 500 mAh et son &#233;cran 1,5K, il veut mettre tout le monde d'accord sur le milieu de gamme.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Votre Pixel 10 est instable apr&#232;s cette mise &#224; jour ? Pas de panique, voici la solution</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2935501_votre-pixel-10-est-instable-apres-cette-mise-a-jour-pas-de-panique-voici-la-solution</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2935501_votre-pixel-10-est-instable-apres-cette-mise-a-jour-pas-de-panique-voici-la-solution</guid>
      <description>
Il semble que la derni&#232;re mise &#224; jour en apparence anodine propos&#233;e sur Android pose des soucis &#224; certains mod&#232;les de Pixel 10.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neige et verglas&#160;: cette ville peut &#171;&#160;fermer les routes en un clic&#160;&#187; sur Waze pour vous sauver</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/neige-et-verglas-cette-ville-peut-fermer-les-routes-en-un-clic-sur-waze-pour-vous-sauver.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318880</guid>
      <description>Pour &#233;viter le chaos de la neige, la ville d'Orsay a une arme secr&#232;te. Gr&#226;ce &#224; un partenariat avec Waze, la mairie peut fermer virtuellement des rues et guider les automobilistes vers des refuges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most popular games are getting harder and harder to usurp</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/858127/top-five-most-played-games-xbox-ps5-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T10:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858127</guid>
      <description>It's harder than ever for a new video game to crack the top of the most-played list. According to the Circana Player Engagement Tracker and video game market analyst Mat Piscatella, in 2025, the top five most-played games on PS5 and Xbox&#8230; were the same in 2024. And they likely won't be changing anytime soon. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI factories are the foundation for enterprise-scale AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ai-factories-are-the-foundation-for-enterprise-scale-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LwaL58NTVUj9tyMrJNg3jW</guid>
      <description>The next phase of AI growth will be driven by the maturity of the underlying infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozempic Quitters Pay a Heavy Price, Research Shows</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ozempic-quitters-pay-a-heavy-price-research-shows-2000707510</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707510</guid>
      <description>People taking an obesity drug typically regain weight, a new review finds, often even quicker than people who lose weight through lifestyle changes alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roblox rolls out mandatory age verification for chat features globally</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/roblox-rolls-out-mandatory-age-verification-for-chat-features-globally</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">L4qemzQmSDAi8ocKxJB2ZD</guid>
      <description>If you want to chat on Roblox, get your ID ready. The platform is expanding mandatory age verification globally, raising new questions about data privacy and user safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $325 on the DJI Osmo Pocket 3 Creator Combo &#8212; the best price ever on a vlogging camera</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-8-dji-osmo-pocket-3-creator-combo-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00M10YSdPgWk5ou96oB5r5f</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 8, get the DJI Osmo Pocket 3 vlogging camera for just $654. That saves you over $300 on the device, bringing it down to its lowest price ever. Plus, this combo includes a wireless mic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google set to reduce the Android source code releases to just twice a year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/google-set-to-reduce-the-android-source-code-releases-to-just-twice-a-year</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CLtEeHkcwycZx9LT4EBH88</guid>
      <description>Google will only publish AOSP source code 2x/year, not 4x/year - no changes to actual OS development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your data&#8217;s where, exactly? SMEs and data sovereignty</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/your-datas-where-exactly-smes-and-data-sovereignty</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q5Fqex7FmDcbmvK32ctRyb</guid>
      <description>Where does your SME data really live? Sovereignty, resilience, and contracts now demand precise, provable answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecovacs' new launch nearly made me cry during my CES booth tour</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/ecovacs-new-launch-nearly-made-me-cry-during-my-ces-booth-tour</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wxvjCYJWMGS79iSufWrrfE</guid>
      <description>I made a new friend, and I'm going to take him home in my suitcase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Momoa and Dave Bautista's new Prime Video movie The Wrecking Crew gets an explosive first trailer &#8212; and it looks like big, dumb fun</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/amazon-prime-video/jason-momoa-and-dave-bautistas-new-prime-video-movie-the-wrecking-crew-gets-an-explosive-first-trailer-and-it-looks-like-big-dumb-fun</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NS4Vw4SotzoLiN3Xo63wmX</guid>
      <description>The Wrecking Crew will see Jason Momoa and Dave Bautista team up to fight the Yakuza in Prime Video's latest film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Luck, Have Fun, Dont Die trailer: Sam Rockwell recruits a wacky team to save the world</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/good-luck-have-fun-dont-die-trailer-gore-verbinski</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00CwYJiK12HQ492R5bd1QKX</guid>
      <description>Gore Verbinski's "Good Luck, Have Fun, Don't Die" stars Sam Rockwell as a man on a mission to save the future. Trailer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Play&#160;: LEGO promet de ne pas tourner le dos aux briques classiques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/smart-play-lego-promet-de-ne-pas-tourner-le-dos-aux-briques-classiques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318869</guid>
      <description>Malgr&#233; l'annonce de la plateforme Smart Play, LEGO n'a pas l'intention d'abandonner ce qui fait son succ&#232;s depuis des d&#233;cennies : la bonne vieille briquette en plastique. La nouvelle offre interactive &#171;&#160;son et lumi&#232;re &#187;&#160;est compl&#233;mentaire, affirme le g&#233;ant danois du jouet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can score a refurbished Sonos Arc SL soundbar for just $320</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/858486/sonos-arc-sl-microsd-express-apple-charger-google-pixel-fold-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T10:00:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858486</guid>
      <description>Woot has an excellent deal on refurbished Sonos Arc SL soundbars, the 2020 model that&#8217;s similar to the original Arc aside from not having any microphones. It debuted for $749, but you can get one with a one-year Sonos warranty for $319.99 while supplies last. If this discount doesn&#8217;t sell out quickly (which it may), [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Good Luck, Have Fun, Don&#8217;t Die&#8217; Trailer Teases a Wacky Tech Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/good-luck-have-fun-dont-die-trailer-sam-rockwell-gore-verbinski-2000707525</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707525</guid>
      <description>Sam Rockwell plays a laid back timetraveler who enlists a bunch of randos to save the world from our codependency of computers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures batteries externes (power bank) en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/410310_guide-achat-batterie-externe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/410310_guide-achat-batterie-externe</guid>
      <description>
&#192; la recherche d'une nouvelle batterie de voyage pour les vacances ou tout simplement pour d&#233;panner au quotidien ? Voici notre comparatif des meilleures batteries externes, classiques ou bien MagSafe, pour recharger votre smartphone ou encore vos &#233;couteurs sans fil.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Friday, January 9 (game #677)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-9-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WPYURK7r7sPAJE5BRmPNJe</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atl&#233;tico Madrid vs Real Madrid Free Streams: How to Watch Spanish Super Cup Semi-final 2025/26</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/atletico-madrid-vs-real-madrid-free-streams-how-to-watch-spanish-super-cup-semi-final-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fSNJqoiJrBCWMZJsqNFhce</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Atl&#233;tico Madrid vs Real Madrid live streams online, with Kylian Mbapp&#233; ruled out in Jeddah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Friday, January 9 (game #943)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-9-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PBE6SoDPwWtCoK93o78b3Q</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Friday, January 9 (game #1446)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-9-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LsSENdYKGH724trCDUw8a7</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Super Cup Final 2025/26 Live Streams: How to Watch PSG vs Marseille From Anywhere in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/french-super-cup-final-2025-26-psg-vs-marseille</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TYXfP4UW6NhuJqtPDGb7rP</guid>
      <description>How to watch 2025 French Super Cup Final live streams online, with Ousmane Dembele set to light up the PSG vs Marseille clash in Kuwait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Uncomfortable truths facing media and marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91466312/ces-2026-uncomfortable-truths-facing-media-and-marketing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T15:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91466312/ces-2026-uncomfortable-truths-facing-media-and-marketing</guid>
      <description>Why the brands that win in 2026 won&#8217;t be the loudest, but the most intentional 
As CES 2026 gets underway, Havas Media Network North America is publishing its 2026 Predictions Forecast, outlining the forces we believe will define the year ahead and separate brands that grow from those that fade. This perspective is drawn directly from that report and grounded in what leaders are seeing, discussing, and debating in Las Vegas this week.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus Rog Xbox Ally : cette console portable&#160;qui renferme un vrai PC revient en promotion pour les soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2890465_asus-rog-xbox-ally-cette-console-portable-qui-renferme-un-vrai-pc-revient-en-promotion-pour-les-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2890465_asus-rog-xbox-ally-cette-console-portable-qui-renferme-un-vrai-pc-revient-en-promotion-pour-les-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Bonne nouvelle pour ceux qui esp&#233;raient une baisse de prix durant les soldes sur la derni&#232;re console d&#8217;Asus, la ROG Xbox Ally : elle est d&#233;sormais propos&#233;e &#224; 529 euros au lieu de 599 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's massive winter sale is still live &#8212; up to 50% off Kindle, Fitbit, Ninja, and Shark</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/amazons-massive-winter-sale-is-still-live-up-to-50-percent-off-kindle-fitbit-ninja-and-shark</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VeMfsF35k3hJvZyiDHC3Jo</guid>
      <description>Amazon's 2026 winter sale is still live, and I'm rounding up my 25 top deal picks from Kindle, Apple, Fitbit, Shark, and Ninja, with prices starting at just $15.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI, age verification and censorship: how the VPN industry tackled 2025's biggest issues &#8211; and what it plans to do next</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/ai-age-verification-and-censorship-how-the-vpn-industry-tackled-2025s-biggest-issues-and-what-it-plans-to-do-next</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">thG2cghDEBJZp3hj4dGLqe</guid>
      <description>2025 was a "turning point" that proved challenging for even the top VPNs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PC market braces for an AI-driven storm</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858505/pc-market-ram-nand-ssd-gpu-pricing-notepad</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T09:51:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858505</guid>
      <description>The personal computer has remained surprisingly resilient to change over the past 15 years. Apple promised a "post-PC" era with the iPad in 2010 and failed to deliver one. Smartphones even overtook laptops as the most popular device to connect to the internet a decade ago, but millions of people still kept buying PCs every [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. is withdrawing from 66 international organizations, Trump memo reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471119/u-s-withdrawing-66-international-organizations-trump-memo-reveals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T14:48:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471119/u-s-withdrawing-66-international-organizations-trump-memo-reveals</guid>
      <description>The U.N. Framework Convention on Climate Change is part of the list of 35 non-U.N. groups and 31 U.N. entities.
U.S. President Donald Trump said on Wednesday that the United States would withdraw from dozens of international and U.N. entities, including a key climate treaty and a U.N. body that promotes gender equality and women&#8217;s empowerment, because they &#8220;operate contrary to U.S. national interests.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this VC thinks 2026 will be &#8216;the year of the consumer&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/why-this-vc-thinks-2026-will-be-the-year-of-the-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080933</guid>
      <description>AI adoption in enterprise is stalling as companies don't know where to start. Vanessa Larco of Premise VC thinks 2026 will be the year of the consumer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Discover Unusual Asteroid Spinning Faster Than Anything Its Size</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/astronomers-discover-unusual-asteroid-spinning-faster-than-anything-its-size-2000707371</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707371</guid>
      <description>Way out there in the asteroid belt is an object that's spinning so fast, scientists are surprised it hasn't flown apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#192; 230 euros, ce nouveau Poco M8 5G est aussi puissant qu&#8217;un Galaxy A36</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2935491_a-230-euros-ce-nouveau-poco-m8-5g-est-aussi-puissant-quun-galaxy-a36</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2935491_a-230-euros-ce-nouveau-poco-m8-5g-est-aussi-puissant-quun-galaxy-a36</guid>
      <description>
Avec son nouveau Poco M8 5G, la filiale de Xiaomi oublie le c&#244;t&#233; &#171; cheap &#187; pour proposer un &#233;cran AMOLED incurv&#233; et un design ultra fin. Le tout sans faire exploser le prix.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ and Netflix are reviving a failed streaming app&#8217;s short-form video dream</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/disney-and-netflix-are-reviving-a-failed-streaming-apps-short-form-video-dream</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZGbsTG4chab2ypazmas8BL</guid>
      <description>Want more short films and shows on Disney+? TikTok-style videos could be on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Il y aurait bien un nouvel appareil Xbox cette ann&#233;e, mais pas celui auquel vous pensez</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2935369_il-y-aurait-bien-un-nouvel-appareil-xbox-cette-annee-mais-pas-celui-auquel-vous-pensez</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2935369_il-y-aurait-bien-un-nouvel-appareil-xbox-cette-annee-mais-pas-celui-auquel-vous-pensez</guid>
      <description>
Alors que de nombreux joueurs attendent l'annonce de la Xbox nouvelle g&#233;n&#233;ration, Microsoft pourrait cr&#233;er la surprise avec un tout autre produit.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose is open-sourcing its old smart speakers instead of bricking them</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/858501/bose-soundtouch-smart-speakers-open-source</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T09:42:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858501</guid>
      <description>In a surprisingly user-friendly move, Bose has announced it will be open-sourcing the API documentation for its SoundTouch smart speakers, which were slated to lose official support on February 18th, as reported by Ars Technica. Bose has also moved that date back to May 6th, 2026. When cloud support ends, an update to the SoundTouch [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
