<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:36:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A $10K+ bounty is waiting for anyone who can unplug Ring doorbells from Amazon&amp;#8217;s cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881678/ring-doorbell-bounty-amazon-servers-fulu</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T17:32:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881678</guid>
      <description>With Ring facing fierce backlash over its Search Party feature, a new program is challenging developers to move Ring doorbell footage off of Amazon's cloud - and into users' own devices. The Fulu Foundation, the consumer advocacy group cofounded by YouTuber Louis Rossmann, is offering an initial bounty of $10,000 to anyone who can integrate [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI says ATM &#8216;jackpotting&#8217; attacks are on the rise, and netting hackers millions in stolen cash</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/fbi-says-atm-jackpotting-attacks-are-on-the-rise-and-netting-hackers-millions-in-stolen-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094673</guid>
      <description>The FBI says hacks that trick ATMs into spitting out cash on demand are rising, with hundreds of attacks in the past year alone netting hackers millions in stolen bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At a critical moment, Snap loses a top Specs exec</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/at-a-critical-moment-snap-loses-a-top-specs-exec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094590</guid>
      <description>As Snap readies the public release of its long-awaited VR glasses, one of the key executives on the project has left the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Gemini 3.1 Pro first impressions: a 'Deep Think Mini' with adjustable reasoning on demand</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/google-gemini-3-1-pro-first-impressions-a-deep-think-mini-with-adjustable</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1si2wDqrN919bVuxYh9ET6</guid>
      <description>For the past three months, Google's Gemini 3 Pro has held its ground as one of the most capable frontier models available. But in the fast-moving world of AI, three months is a lifetime &#8212; and competitors have not been standing still.Earlier today, Google released Gemini 3.1 Pro, an update that brings a key innovation to the company's workhorse power model: three levels of adjustable thinking that effectively turn it into a lightweight version of Google's specialized Deep Think reasoning system.The release marks the first time Google has issued a "point one" update to a Gemini model, signaling ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second and last chance for innovators to win scaling perks: Belden extends nomination window</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/second-and-last-chance-for-innovators-to-win-scaling-perks-belden-extends-nomination-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094631</guid>
      <description>Last day to nominate for the 2026 Joseph C. Belden Innovation Award has been extended through February 27. Don't miss your chance to win scaling perks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NASA Chief Blames Prior Leadership for Botched Starliner Mission</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-nasa-chief-blames-prior-leadership-for-botched-starliner-mission-2000724290</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724290</guid>
      <description>Jared Isaacman said the goal of maintaining multiple means of ISS access influenced decision-making when mission and crew safety should have been the top priority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I looted 36 Cyberpunk home office upgrades for jacking into work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/i-looted-36-cyberpunk-home-office-upgrades-for-jacking-into-work</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MMKHMqs6jmQiBfJiBXmaqM</guid>
      <description>From Tier 1 components to Tier 5++ gear for your home office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Claims Obama Leaked Classified Intel When He Said Aliens Are Real</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-are-aliens-real-obama-classified-intel-2000724273</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724273</guid>
      <description>Lara Trump recently claimed the president already has a speech prepared on UFOs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellebrite cut off Serbia citing abuse of its phone unlocking tools. Why not others?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/cellebrite-cut-off-serbia-citing-abuse-of-its-phone-unlocking-tools-why-not-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094602</guid>
      <description>Cellebrite, which makes phone unlocking and hacking tools, stopped sales to countries that allegedly abused its tools. But after new allegations in Jordan and Kenya, the company has changed its approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Green Arrow Is a Horror-Fueled Billionaire Killer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dc-comics-absolute-green-arrow-release-date-details-2000724195</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724195</guid>
      <description>DC's Absolute Universe expands with series following Green Arrow and Catwoman, plus the first-ever Absolute Universe event miniseries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It seems Microsoft just started work on Windows 11 27H2 &#8212; and this could be the update that saves the OS... or dooms it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/it-seems-microsoft-just-started-work-on-windows-11-27h2-and-this-could-be-the-update-that-saves-the-os-or-dooms-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pyGnYdYDnkTiEuXpaa7oF4</guid>
      <description>I just hope Microsoft delivers on the promises of greater stability and faster performance for the OS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A massive new EV study just dispelled the biggest myth about electric car batteries</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/a-massive-new-ev-survey-just-dispelled-the-biggest-myth-about-electric-car-batteries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EcvDfLbE2qw73aCnQqT9a9</guid>
      <description>The UK's largest EV Battery Performance Index proves that used car customers have little to fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Era of the $20,000 New Car Is Over</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-era-of-the-20000-new-car-is-over-2000724260</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724260</guid>
      <description>This is the first year no automaker is selling a new car for under $20,000 in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeywell CCTV cameras vulnerable to hijacking which allows hackers to crack passwords easily</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/honeywell-cctv-cameras-vulnerable-to-hijacking-which-allows-hackers-to-crack-passwords-easily</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CdaAoCaxxhcHGsHu5wXQwH</guid>
      <description>CISA tells Honeywell CCTV users to patch now - or risk hackers hijacking their devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best earbuds we&#8217;ve tested for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T16:33:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s hard to buy a bad pair of wireless earbuds these days, and with constant discounts and deals wherever you look, now is as good a time as any to splurge on the pair you&#8217;ve been eyeing. The market has come a long way since the early era of true wireless earbuds, when we had [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aphelion seems like a solid space adventure, but I need to see more before it really excites</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/aphelion-hands-on-preview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cxpWDqqWiFXhibnjXFo5Yh</guid>
      <description>Aphelion has decent platforming and a creepy alien foe, but I want to see more of its story before getting fully on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google says its AI systems helped deter Play Store malware in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/google-says-its-ai-systems-helped-deter-play-store-malware-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094561</guid>
      <description>Google said it prevented 1.75 million bad apps from going live on Google Play during 2025, a figure that's down from previous years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Price Crash Hasn&#8217;t Stopped One Company From Adding to Its $47 Billion Crypto Stash</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/bitcoins-price-crash-hasnt-stopped-one-company-from-adding-to-its-47-billion-crypto-stash-2000724252</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724252</guid>
      <description>How low can it go until it's too late? Well...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The chip shortage is now hitting employee bonuses &#8212; MediaTek worker rewards sliced as costs begin to bite hard</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/chip-shortage-is-now-hitting-employee-bonuses-mediatek-worker-rewards-sliced-as-costs-begin-to-bite-hard</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xnfMcqenDiCSzYoSZgMuC8</guid>
      <description>MediaTek reduced employee bonuses for H2 2025 amid RAM and storage shortages affecting smartphone chipset shipments and overall revenue performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood is freaking out over a viral AI video showing Brad Pitt and Tom Cruise fighting</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495560/hollywood-is-freaking-out-over-a-viral-ai-video-showing-brad-pitt-and-tom-cruise-fighting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T21:13:23</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495560/hollywood-is-freaking-out-over-a-viral-ai-video-showing-brad-pitt-and-tom-cruise-fighting</guid>
      <description>A clip made with ByteDance&#8217;s new Seedance tool racked up millions of views&#8212;and prompted warnings from studios over copyright infringement.
At first glance, it could be the trailer for a new Hollywood blockbuster starring Brad Pitt and Tom Cruise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why some United flyers will suddenly earn less for the same flights</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495455/why-some-united-flyers-will-suddenly-earn-less-for-the-same-flights</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T21:12:11</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495455/why-some-united-flyers-will-suddenly-earn-less-for-the-same-flights</guid>
      <description>United&#8217;s biggest MileagePlus overhaul in more than a decade rewards cardholders while cutting earnings for others, including many business travelers.
You may be loyal to United, but the airline really wants you to show your loyalty by carrying around a United MileagePlus credit card or debit card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI data center boom is fueling Redwood&#8217;s energy storage business</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/an-ai-data-center-boom-is-fueling-redwoods-energy-storage-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094559</guid>
      <description>Redwood Materials says its new energy storage business is the fastest growing unit within the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slay the Spire 2 will enter early access on March 5</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/slay-the-spire-2-will-enter-early-access-on-march-5-210338514.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">333a4dbb-1204-4e0a-a389-641eea962db8</guid>
      <description>Slay the Spire 2 will launch in early access next month. This sequel to the hugely popular 2019 roguelike deckbuilder hits early access on Steam beginning March 5, 2026. Along with releasing the teaser trailer above, developer Mega Crit shared some details about its goals for this phase ahead of the game's official release."Slay the Spire requires a lot of player feedback so we can balance content, add quality of life features, and make sure the game runs without issues," the developers explained. "Early Access is also a chance for us to test experimental features, try exotic designs, identify...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Time (Travel) to See &#8216;Nirvanna The Band The Show The Movie&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/make-time-travel-to-see-nirvanna-the-band-the-show-the-movie-2000722952</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722952</guid>
      <description>The new pop culture comedy starring Matt Johnson and Jay McCarrol is now in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested Sony's WF-1000XM6 against WF-1000XM5 to see whether the new flagship earbuds are worth it &#8212; and yes, I did find a winner</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/sony-wf-1000xm6-vs-wf-1000xm5-are-sonys-newest-flagship-earbuds-worth-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KsBFLMqMG6DWdwdG4py9jn</guid>
      <description>A deep dive suggests that the older model remains an excellent choice for the budget-conscious</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The legal fight that could force Apple to rethink iCloud design</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495492/the-legal-fight-that-could-force-apple-to-rethink-icloud-design</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495492/the-legal-fight-that-could-force-apple-to-rethink-icloud-design</guid>
      <description>West Virginia&#8217;s attorney general alleges Apple failed to prevent child sexual abuse material from being stored and shared through iOS and iCloud.
West Virginia&#8217;s attorney general filed a lawsuit against Apple on Thursday accusing the iPhone maker of knowingly allowing its software to be used for storing and sharing child sexual abuse material.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s VR metaverse is ditching VR</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881647/meta-vr-mobile-metaverse-horizon-worlds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T15:47:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881647</guid>
      <description>Meta, after laying off about 10 percent of its Reality Labs division, closing three VR studios, stopping new content for VR fitness app Supernatural, and discontinuing its metaverse for work, is announcing a major change for its Horizon Worlds metaverse platform. Instead of attempting to make the 3D social platform work for both VR and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why these startup CEOs don&#8217;t think AI will replace human roles</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/web-summit-qatar-read-ai-lucidya-notetakers-customer-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091415</guid>
      <description>The CEOs of Read AI and Lucidya told TechCrunch at Web Summit Qatar that they see AI tools replacing tasks, rather than workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump Jr.&#8217;s Private DC Club Has Mysterious Ties to an Ex-Cop With a Controversial Past</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/magas-secretive-members-only-club-is-partly-owned-by-an-ex-cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6996005c292f53dc4837a1fa</guid>
      <description>The Executive Branch has a reported membership list that includes&#160;Trumpworld elites like David Sacks. A WIRED review of corporate filings reveals an under-the-radar player: a notorious former DC police officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Staples Baddie&#8217; went viral. Here&#8217;s what the retailer is doing about its Gen Z employee&#8217;s internet fame</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495470/staples-baddie-gen-z-employee-what-the-retailer-is-doing-about-internet-fame</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495470/staples-baddie-gen-z-employee-what-the-retailer-is-doing-about-internet-fame</guid>
      <description>The company&#8217;s chief marketing officer weighs in on the breakout in-house influencer.
By now, the so-called &#8220;Staples Baddie&#8221; may have crossed your feed with her tutorials and informational videos exploring her workplace. TikTok creator @blivxx, known online as Oblivion, started getting attention in January for highlighting niche services and products offered at Staples....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
