<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:56:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This 'feature-stuffed pocket rocket' of a Garmin watch is at its lowest price ever &#8211; perfect timing for warmer spring runs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/this-feature-stuffed-pocket-rocket-of-a-garmin-watch-is-at-its-lowest-price-ever-perfect-timing-for-warmer-spring-runs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ummeGLVz8H3eq2RaoMdLoh</guid>
      <description>If you're a seasonal runner, the Garmin Vivoactive 6 is just what you need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk is getting serious about orbital data centers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/elon-musk-is-getting-serious-about-orbital-data-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089928</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re starting to see the idea of Musk-owned orbital AI data clusters cohere into an actual plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La PlayStation 5 devrait &#233;chapper &#224; une nouvelle augmentation de prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2968103_la-playstation-5-devrait-echapper-a-une-nouvelle-augmentation-de-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2968103_la-playstation-5-devrait-echapper-a-une-nouvelle-augmentation-de-prix</guid>
      <description>
Enfin une bonne nouvelle concernant la p&#233;nurie de m&#233;moire vive et de stockage. Sony aurait suffisamment fait de stocks pour &#233;viter d'augmenter le prix de la PS5.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CIA stops publishing The World Factbook</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-cia-stops-publishing-the-world-factbook-184419024.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f201e526-d149-44ce-b629-22e2f55b2bf7</guid>
      <description>The US Central Intelligence Agency is ending one of its popular services, The World Factbook. Over the decades, this reference has provided readers with information about different countries and communities around the world. The post from the CIA announcing the news didn't provide any information about why it will stop offering The World Factbook. The agency was subject to the same buyouts and job cuts that decimated much of the federal workforce in 2025, so maybe this type of public-facing tool is no longer a priority.&#160;This reference guide was first published in 1962 as The National Basic Int...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2026 Winter Olympics Will Have a Major Impact on the Region&#8217;s Snow</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/winter-olympics-2026-impacts-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69754fb4162ea64cf574981d</guid>
      <description>A recent report found that carbon emissions caused by the Milano Cortina Olympics could lead to the loss of 5.5 square kilometers of snowpack and millions of metric tons of glacial ice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapt&#233; aux t&#226;ches bureautiques, ce Lenovo IdeaPad Slim 3 avec Windows 11 Mode S chute sous les 200 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967833_adapte-aux-taches-bureautiques-ce-lenovo-ideapad-slim-3-avec-windows-11-chute-sous-les-200-e</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967833_adapte-aux-taches-bureautiques-ce-lenovo-ideapad-slim-3-avec-windows-11-chute-sous-les-200-e</guid>
      <description>
Le Lenovo IdeaPad Slim 3 est un laptop qui tend &#224; accomplir les principales t&#226;ches du quotidien gr&#226;ce &#224; son Windows 11 Mode S et son Intel Celeron. Chez Amazon, il perd 150 euros et tombe &#224; seulement 199,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof hosting providers renting cheap infrastructure to supply virtual machines to ransomware hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/bulletproof-hosting-providers-renting-cheap-infrastructure-to-supply-virtual-machines-to-ransomware-hackers</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K3FmWA2Eh9WJ8UwrwRTwTD</guid>
      <description>Most high-profile ransomware groups were using the same Russian-based infrastructure for years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the best laptop power banks available is cheaper than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/874509/anker-laptop-power-bank-google-pixel-watch-4-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:34:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874509</guid>
      <description>If you often travel with your gadgets, a fast, reliable portable battery like Anker&#8217;s Laptop Power Bank is a worthwhile purchase. Right now, you can buy the silver model at its all-time low price of $87.99 ($47 off) from Anker via Newegg when you apply promo code ENCF232 at checkout. Alternatively, the black color scheme [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to stream the 2026 Super Bowl for free: Patriots vs. Seahawks time, where to watch and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-stream-the-2026-super-bowl-for-free-patriots-vs-seahawks-time-where-to-watch-and-more-124512202.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b2b14-4380-47f2-9cb8-bd2dfe744915</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Super Bowl between the New England Patriots and the Seattle Seahawks will air on NBC this Sunday, Feb. 8. The game will also stream on Peacock. If you don't have NBC over the air and don't subscribe to Peacock, there are still ways to watch Super Bowl LX &#8212; and Bad Bunny's history-making halftime show &#8212; for free. Here's how to tune in.&#160;
How to watch Super Bowl LX free:




Date: Sunday, Feb. 8
Time: 6:30 p.m. ET
Location: Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.
TV channel: NBC, Telemundo
Streaming: Peacock, DirecTV, NFL+ and more
2026 Super Bowl game channel
Super Bowl LX will air on NBC...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA astronauts can now bring their phones with them on their mission to the moon</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/nasa-astronauts-can-now-bring-their-phones-with-them-on-their-mission-to-the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089951</guid>
      <description>Get ready for some selfies that are out of this world. Crew-12 is expected to head to the International Space Station next week, while the highly anticipated Artemis II mission -- which will bring humans around the moon for the first time since the 1960s -- was delayed until March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of the World's Largest Gay Dating App</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-how-people-in-china-learn-what-they-can-say-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69836bf7cb78795d1881df66</guid>
      <description>The new book The Wall Dancers explores the uneasy relationship between Chinese internet users and a government that is always watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested several cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:19:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Sure, it can take away from the slick design. But using a case relieves me of the worry that the console will accumulate tons of little scratches, or worse. I&#8217;ve tested several types of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl LX ads: all AI everything</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/874504/super-bowl-lx-ads-big-game</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:18:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=874504</guid>
      <description>Super Bowl LX is nearly here, with the Seattle Seahawks taking on the New England Patriots. While Bad Bunny will be the star of the halftime show, AI could be the star of the commercial breaks, much like crypto was a few years ago. Last year&#8217;s Super Bowl featured a Google Gemini ad that fumbled [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Notta Memo and ditched handwritten notes for searchable AI transcripts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/notta-memo-ai-voice-recorder-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8UA4j56bH6bKReJeJkdgPT</guid>
      <description>The Notta Memo is a compact AI voice recorder that attaches to the back of your mobile phone, recording audio and using AI to transcribe, summarise, and translate with the aid of the companion app, making it a far superior option than a notepad for meetings, lectures, and everyday note-taking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer Wants to Sell You a $1,337 Gaming Mouse</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/razer-wants-to-sell-you-a-1337-gaming-mouse-2000718577</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718577</guid>
      <description>Remember the 1999 Boomslang mouse? Now, you can once again fondle one of a limited set of 1,337.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI launches&#160;a way for enterprises to build and&#160;manage AI agents</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/openai-launches-a-way-for-enterprises-to-build-and-manage-ai-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090000</guid>
      <description>OpenAI launched Frontier, a new platform designed for enterprises to build and deploy agents while treating them like human employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Latest Apple Watch Is $100 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/apple-watch-11-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6984cf92681463fce33e7294</guid>
      <description>Upgrade to a full day of battery life and new health features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Switch 2-exclusive co-op adventure Orbitals launches this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/the-switch-2-exclusive-co-op-adventure-orbitals-launches-this-summer-180657892.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbea459b-85e0-454c-a217-fba2e400e3e1</guid>
      <description>Nintendo capped off today&#8217;s partner-focused Nintendo Direct with a flurry of Bethesda-related announcements, but arguably the most interesting game of the showcase appeared right at the start.
First announced at the beginning of the year, Orbitals is a two-player puzzle adventure game in which you and your co-op partner play as the intergalactic explorers Maki and Omura, on a mission to save their home in the stars from an incoming cosmic storm. Gameplay-wise, Orbitals looks like it&#8217;s at least partly inspired by the likes of It Takes Two&#160;and Split Fiction, but really what really stands out her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Tried Drilling Into Antarctica&#8217;s &#8216;Doomsday Glacier,&#8217; But the Ice Had Other Plans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-tried-drilling-into-the-doomsday-glacier-but-the-ice-had-other-plans-2000718421</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718421</guid>
      <description>A project that has been years in the making came to an early halt about 3,000 feet deep in the ice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Director of &#8216;Masters of the Universe&#8217; Promises It&#8217;ll Be Silly</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-director-of-masters-of-the-universe-promises-itll-be-silly-2000718567</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718567</guid>
      <description>'Bumblebee' director Travis Knight knows that He-Man and friends are a little goofy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who&#8217;s who and what&#8217;s what in TVs in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874138/tv-manufacturer-technology-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874138</guid>
      <description>Each TV company has its own distinct personality and direction. These change over the years, with new technological breakthroughs or at least new business deals. New aspirations shake up the natural order. This year, for example, nearly every company has decided to make and heavily promote RGB LED TVs. Some of them, like Hisense, seem [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude has been having a moment &#8212; can it keep it up?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/874308/anthropic-claude-code-opus-hype-moment</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874308</guid>
      <description>Boris Cherny gets recognized in public relatively often. At the bar, at the airport, and in generally any public space, people want to take selfies with the creator and head of Claude Code. For the last couple of months, Anthropic's Claude and its coding platform have been having a moment - on social media, in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic debuts new model with hopes to corner the market beyond coding</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/874440/anthropic-opus-4-6-new-model-claude</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874440</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's "smartest model" is getting a major boost, the company said in a blog post announcing Claude Opus 4.6. It called the new model a "direct upgrade" from its predecessor in a release, noting that it can better take on complex, multi-step tasks and get "much closer to production-ready quality on the first try than [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get two years of access to Proton VPN for 70 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-two-years-of-access-to-proton-vpn-for-70-percent-off-right-now-123000460.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dac4d6ed-e475-4c0c-80c0-7c390227395c</guid>
      <description>Proton VPN is offering a steep discount on its Proton VPN Plus subscription, with the two-year plan currently priced at $2.99 per month. You&#8217;ll pay $72 upfront for 24 months of service, which amounts to 70 percent off the usual monthly rate and brings the long-term cost well below what many premium VPNs typically charge.We&#8217;ve consistently been impressed by Proton VPN&#8217;s focus on privacy, its nonprofit ownership structure and the way it balances security features with strong real-world speeds. It&#8217;s a top pick in our best VPN guide, and this promotion also appears in our running list of the best ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Iger just left his Disney successor a disaster in the making</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486060/bob-iger-just-left-disney-successor-josh-damaro-disaster-in-the-making</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486060/bob-iger-just-left-disney-successor-josh-damaro-disaster-in-the-making</guid>
      <description>Iger doesn&#8217;t understand AI. That&#8217;s created a problem for new CEO Josh D&#8217;Amaro&#8212;and Disney itself.
Bob Iger doesn&#8217;t understand generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does your workplace look like this? If not, mothers may not want to work there</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487048/does-your-workplace-look-like-this-if-not-mothers-may-not-want-to-work-there</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487048/does-your-workplace-look-like-this-if-not-mothers-may-not-want-to-work-there</guid>
      <description>Even employers with generous parental leave benefits fail to fully address the unique transformation many working mothers are navigating when they return to work. 
In certain corners of corporate America, a generous parental leave policy has become a crucial tool for recruiting and retention. Many of the biggest tech employers have been leaders on this front, offering 16 to 20 weeks of leave, or even close to six months at companies like Google.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Novo Nordisk stock fell 7% after a telehealth startup&#8217;s announcement</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487685/why-novo-nordisk-stock-fell-7-after-a-telehealth-startups-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487685/why-novo-nordisk-stock-fell-7-after-a-telehealth-startups-announcement</guid>
      <description>Hims &amp; Hers will sell a compounded version of the new Wegovy pill for a fraction of the price, claiming a legal workaround to U.S. patent protection.
Novo Nordisk&#8217;s stock dove 7% on Thursday just after an announcement from a key competitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings drop to lowest level since 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487805/job-openings-december-labor-economy-ai-layoffs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487805/job-openings-december-labor-economy-ai-layoffs</guid>
      <description>December job openings were lower than economists had forecast.
U.S. job openings fell to the lowest level in more than five years, another sign that the American labor market remains sluggish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's Super Bowl TV sale is offering some of the best prices I've seen &#8212; here are 11 deals that I'm recommending to family and friends</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/best-buys-super-bowl-tv-sale-is-offering-some-of-the-best-prices-ive-seen-here-are-11-deals-that-im-recommending-to-family-and-friends</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HELrDb4wDEYG4NBVJmocbE</guid>
      <description>Best Buy's Super Bowl TV sale is ending soon, and I'm rounding up my 13 favorite deals that I'm recommending to family and friends on best-rated 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's Presidents' Day appliance sale starts early &#8212; here are the deals I'd buy for a premium kitchen upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/best-buys-presidents-day-appliance-sale-starts-early-here-are-the-deals-id-buy-for-a-premium-kitchen-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6isMmhd4UxSJokBwKyzHcM</guid>
      <description>The Best Buy Presidents' Day appliances sale is now underway with savings of up to 40%, free gift cards and package discounts all up for grabs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic releases Opus 4.6 with new &#8216;agent teams&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/anthropic-releases-opus-4-6-with-new-agent-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089523</guid>
      <description>The newest version of Anthropic's model is designed to broaden its appeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's Claude Opus 4.6 brings 1M token context and 'agent teams' to take on OpenAI's Codex</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/anthropics-claude-opus-4-6-brings-1m-token-context-and-agent-teams-to-take</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5G2L31NpyXiVRNJhniYN55</guid>
      <description>Anthropic on Thursday released Claude Opus 4.6, a major upgrade to its flagship artificial intelligence model that the company says plans more carefully, sustains longer autonomous workflows, and outperforms competitors including OpenAI's GPT-5.2 on key enterprise benchmarks &#8212; a release that arrives at a tumultuous moment for the AI industry and global software markets.The launch comes just three days after OpenAI released its own Codex desktop application in a direct challenge to Anthropic's Claude Code momentum, and amid a $285 billion rout in software and services stocks that investors attr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirDrop pour tous : Google veut ouvrir la fonction d&#8217;Apple &#224; d&#8217;autres smartphones Android</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2968025_airdrop-pour-tous-google-veut-ouvrir-la-fonction-dapple-a-dautres-smartphones-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2968025_airdrop-pour-tous-google-veut-ouvrir-la-fonction-dapple-a-dautres-smartphones-android</guid>
      <description>
Davantage de smartphones vont pouvoir go&#251;ter au partage de fichiers simplifi&#233; entre appareils gr&#226;ce &#224; Google.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab's comically oversized headphones are not an April Fool's Prank</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/jlabs-comically-oversized-headphones-are-not-an-april-fools-prank-174338833.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9588dd3-a71c-488b-8286-7ec134078a90</guid>
      <description>JLab just released a gigantic pair of headphones that doubles as a Bluetooth speaker. The Blue XL headphones are ridiculously oversized, making them headphones in name only. I don't even think Andre the Giant could've comfortably worn these suckers.
Unless you have a mythically large head, these are basically "headphone speakers." The idea is to drape them around your neck and stream tunes for all to hear. Though you could also pop them on a table or something. I prefer my Bluetooth speakers to be speaker-shaped, but maybe that's just me.
JLab
As for the internals, they feature 30W of power an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move over, Mac mini: Geekom A9 Max brings Ryzen AI power, 32GB RAM, and 2TB storage, all for under $1100</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/move-over-mac-mini-geekom-a9-max-brings-ryzen-ai-power-32gb-ram-and-2tb-storage-all-for-under-usd1100</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HD8LHTwV9PDzcJQNDA37uU</guid>
      <description>The Geekom A9 Max mini PC delivers serious AI-accelerated performance in a compact, upgradeable, office-ready design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI bot web traffic is closing in on human usage, experts warn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ai-bot-web-traffic-is-closing-in-on-human-usage-experts-warn</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wZMmAXRTzrUREiTnATcWM9</guid>
      <description>Human traffic is dwindling and CTR rates are dropping as the internet gears up to accept more AI bots than human users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA reportedly won't release new graphics cards this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/nvidia-reportedly-wont-release-new-graphics-cards-this-year-173002651.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc6f369-3de6-41c9-a5e2-6d2030643d23</guid>
      <description>With gaming becoming an ever-smaller part of NVIDIA's lucrative business, the company reportedly won't bother releasing new graphics cards this year. The Information reported on Thursday that NVIDIA has pushed back its plan to release an update to the RTX 50 line in 2026. This would be the first time in three decades that the company hasn't launched new gaming chips. The culprit? Why, AI, of course.AI demand has driven the current memory chip shortage, throwing the consumer electronics industry out of kilter. Many product prices are expected to rise (as if tariffs hadn't already done enough da...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondary sales shift from founder windfalls to employee-retention tools</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/secondary-sales-shift-from-founder-windfalls-to-employee-retention-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089746</guid>
      <description>AI startups like Clay and ElevenLabs are using early liquidity to keep their best talent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daring Theory Challenges the Black Hole&#8217;s Reign Over the Milky Way&#8217;s Core</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/daring-theory-challenges-the-black-holes-reign-over-the-milky-ways-core-2000718499</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718499</guid>
      <description>There is a lot we have yet to understand about the center of the Milky Way&#8212;could it be due to a mass of invisible dark matter?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark&#8217;s child care and parental leave policies erase 80% of the &#8216;motherhood penalty&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485320/denmarks-child-care-parental-leave-policies-erase-80-percent-motherhood-penalty</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T17:20:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485320/denmarks-child-care-parental-leave-policies-erase-80-percent-motherhood-penalty</guid>
      <description>Their government benefits do not fully offset earnings losses for Danish moms, but they help a lot.
For many women in the U.S. and around the world, motherhood comes with career costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta tests a standalone app for its AI-generated &#8216;Vibes&#8217; videos</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/meta-tests-a-standalone-app-for-its-ai-generated-vibes-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089950</guid>
      <description>Launched last September, Vibes lets you create and share short-form AI-generated videos and access a dedicated feed that displays AI videos from others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Dangbei Neo transforme n&#8217;importe quel salon en salle de cin&#233;ma pour pas cher avec cette remise de 50 %</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967741_le-dangbei-neo-transforme-nimporte-quel-salon-en-salle-de-cinema-pour-pas-cher-avec-cette-remise-de-50</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967741_le-dangbei-neo-transforme-nimporte-quel-salon-en-salle-de-cinema-pour-pas-cher-avec-cette-remise-de-50</guid>
      <description>
Le Dangbei Neo propose un design minimaliste et une image allant jusqu'&#224; 120 pouces en Full HD, parfaite pour animer une soir&#233;e entre amis ou seul(e) au fond de son lit. Chez Fnac-Darty, il tombe &#224; 209,99 euros au lieu de 399,99 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP Color LaserJet Pro 4201dw (4202dw) review: I love this laser printer&#8217;s rich black text, and hate the retro dial</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hp-color-laserjet-pro-4201dw-4202dw-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">r3wVPvdZ6QmNyYBLvMwbAX</guid>
      <description>Swift and crisp duplex printing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starlink pr&#233;parerait bien son propre smartphone</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/starlink-preparerait-bien-son-propre-smartphone.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324392</guid>
      <description>En attendant la cr&#233;ation d'un tr&#232;s hypoth&#233;tique r&#233;seau de centres de donn&#233;es dans l'espace pour l'IA, SpaceX et sa filiale Starlink pourraient lancer quelque chose de plus terre &#224; terre : un smartphone ! Les pi&#232;ces du puzzle se sont accumul&#233;es ces derniers temps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adafruit Warns New Ghost Gun Laws Could Have Unintended Consequences for 3D Printers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/adafruit-warns-new-ghost-gun-laws-could-have-unintended-consequences-for-3d-printers-2000718532</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718532</guid>
      <description>Bills in Washington and New York would require 3D printers to scan and block firearm blueprints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best tech gifts and cool gadgets for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/the-best-tech-gifts-and-cool-gadgets-for-2026-140052977.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50def0bc-316b-465e-845b-9469941205a6</guid>
      <description>It can be tough to find a good gift for tech obsessives. Since they keep up with the latest releases, they probably already have the new high-profile gadgets out there. Luckily, Engadget staffers keep their eyes peeled all year long for the truly unique stuff. We travel to CES, attend product launches, cover major and minor tech events &#8212; we also can&#8217;t help but buy ourselves any zany, clever, addictive or productive tech we happen to stumble across. In short, we&#8217;ve got some ideas about good gifts for tech nerds (which we are).
Best tech gifts and gadgets








































...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Just Threaded the Needle on a Near-Perfect Tribute to &#8216;Deep Space Nine&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-episode-5-recap-deep-space-nine-dax-sisko-jake-2000718134</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718134</guid>
      <description>'Series Acclimation Mil' puts a stellar spotlight on the unique position 'Starfleet Academy' finds itself in to reflect on the legacy of 'Star Trek.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The College Board Is Banning Students From Using Smart Glasses During the SATs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-college-board-is-banning-students-from-using-smart-glasses-during-the-sats-2000718422</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718422</guid>
      <description>Smart glasses are the ultimate cheating tool, and colleges know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s what Xbox is working on for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874303/microsoft-xbox-roadmap-2026-notepad</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874303</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has a big year ahead for Xbox as it marks its 25-year milestone. After the tough decision to release more Xbox games on rival consoles two years ago, 2026 is a chance to refocus on the platform and celebrate some of Xbox's biggest franchises. It's also an opportunity for Microsoft to define its vision [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Waymo is having a hard time time stopping for school buses</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/874385/waymo-school-bus-austin-safety-robotaxi</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874385</guid>
      <description>For years, Alphabet-owned Waymo has tried to set itself apart from other self-driving startups by emphasizing a culture of caution and safety. Now, just ahead of major planned rollouts across the country, it is facing a recurring failure in one of the most sensitive places imaginable: school zones. In December, the National Highway Traffic Safety [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Fusion finds a cheaper way to make its fusion reactor work</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/pacific-fusion-finds-a-cheaper-way-to-make-its-fusion-reactor-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089946</guid>
      <description>The fusion power startup recently completed some experiments at Sandia National Laboratory's Z Machine and shared the results exclusively with TechCrunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch Six Nations 2026 for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/rugby/sneaky-way-to-watch-six-nations-2026-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">shAKc6FvqRxsxha4PqoaCV</guid>
      <description>Here's a sneaky way to catch the Six Nations for free from anywhere in the world as rugby's biggest annual tournament returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to listen to Six Nations on BBC Radio 5 Live from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-listen/six-nations-bbc-radio-5-live-from-anywhere-in-the-world</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XGUTxqZXVjVUEgbGongSGh</guid>
      <description>Here's how to listen to the Six Nations rugby on BBC Radio 5 Live from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are VPNs legal?</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/are-vpns-legal-170000878.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad835619-3b83-4612-ac57-bb00c6eaf2c1</guid>
      <description>VPNs have a mixed reputation, primarily because you can use the technology to hide your location and identity on the internet. Even the best VPNs can be used to conceal crimes and make the perpetrators harder to track. Fortunately, most of the world's governments (at least for now) recognize that VPNs are just technology that can be used for good or ill.That means VPNs are legal in almost every country in the world. The countries that do restrict VPNs tend to be those where internet freedoms are already curtailed, like Russia, China, Iran and North Korea. There are distinct gradations between ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real reasons Elon Musk merged xAI and SpaceX</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486908/real-reasons-elon-musk-merged-xai-and-spacex</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486908/real-reasons-elon-musk-merged-xai-and-spacex</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s all about this sci-fi fantasy
Elon Musk just created the world&#8217;s most valuable private company. And he didn&#8217;t do it through rapid growth or a new product launch&#8202;&#8212;&#8202;at least not directly, anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic takes aim at chatbot ads&#8212;with its own Super Bowl ad</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487007/anthropic-super-bowl-ad-chatbots</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487007/anthropic-super-bowl-ad-chatbots</guid>
      <description>The company&#8217;s tongue-in-cheek spots spotlight concerns about advertising inside AI assistants and provoke a sharp response from OpenAI CEO Sam Altman.
Welcome to&#160;AI&#160;Decoded,&#160;Fast Company&#8217;s weekly newsletter that breaks down the most important news in the world of&#160;AI.&#160;You can sign&#160;up to receive this newsletter every week via email&#160;here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les clients payaient l&#8217;&#233;lectricit&#233; moins cher que son co&#251;t r&#233;el : EDF oblig&#233; d&#8217;augmenter les tarifs de l&#8217;option Tempo</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2967431_les-clients-payaient-lelectricite-moins-cher-que-son-cout-reel-edf-oblige-daugmenter-les-tarifs-de-loption-tempo</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2967431_les-clients-payaient-lelectricite-moins-cher-que-son-cout-reel-edf-oblige-daugmenter-les-tarifs-de-loption-tempo</guid>
      <description>
La f&#234;te est finie pour les abonn&#233;s &#224; l&#8217;option Tempo d&#8217;EDF. La Commission de r&#233;gulation de l&#8217;&#233;nergie (CRE) a revu les tarifs &#224; la hausse. Pour autant, l&#8217;offre conserve encore des atouts face aux autres propositions du march&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 8TB WD_Black SSD deal saves you over $1000 and actually pays for your 2026 tax prep</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-8tb-wd-black-ssd-deal-saves-you-over-usd1000-and-actually-pays-for-your-2026-tax-prep</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9NVPW5pghwHYDQKWBKNWMA</guid>
      <description>Newegg&#8217;s 8TB SSD deal cuts $1000+ off storage prices and quietly covers your tax filing too.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
