<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:25:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>New &#8216;CRASH Clock&#8217; Warns of 2.8-Day Window Before Likely Orbital Collision</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-crash-clock-warns-of-2-8-day-window-before-likely-orbital-collision-2000700374</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700374</guid>
      <description>The CRASH Clock is a new metric for measuring the risks of satellite congestion in low-Earth orbit. Its calculations are disturbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Defaults Free Users to Cheapest Model to Cut Back on Costs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-defaults-free-users-to-cheapest-model-to-cut-back-on-costs-2000700346</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700346</guid>
      <description>They're betting people won't notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X updates its terms, files countersuit to lay claim to the &#8216;Twitter&#8217; trademark after newcomer&#8217;s challenge</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/x-updates-its-terms-files-countersuit-to-lay-claim-to-the-twitter-trademark-after-newcomers-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076669</guid>
      <description>X's new terms of service say that no one can use the Twitter name, trademarks, logos and more without written consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Kingsley Also Can&#8217;t Believe He&#8217;s Starring in &#8216;Wonder Man&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ben-kingsley-wonder-man-marvel-trevor-2000700301</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700301</guid>
      <description>From 'Iron Man 3' to 'Shang-Chi' and now Disney+, the Oscar winner marvels at his Marvel longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Australia vs England: live stream 3rd Ashes Test for *FREE* from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/australia-vs-england-3rd-ashes-test-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">H2hDxrfP4DfodtmJxyDPj5</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch the 3rd Ashes Test at Adelaide from anywhere in the world as Australia and England battle in cricket&#8217;s most famous Test series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows Instacart may be charging some shoppers 20% more for the same product</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/study-shows-instacart-may-be-charging-some-shoppers-20-more-for-the-same-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076612</guid>
      <description>The delivery app has claimed that price testing is part of a longstanding practice in retail sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Replay 2025 is here to recap your PC gaming habits</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/steam-replay-2025-is-here-to-recap-your-pc-gaming-habits-205430951.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a6ef28b-843d-488a-a963-9b0b23d99c6b</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Tis the season for gift-giving, family feasts and companies turning their harvested user data into lighthearted recaps. Valve's take on the year-end rewind, Steam Replay, is now available. It follows similar offerings from Spotify, Apple Music, PlayStation and, increasingly, just about every service you use. Hell, even Uber and The New York Times somehow justified getting in on the action this year.This is the fourth edition of Valve&#8217;s wrap-up, which looks back on the titles you spent the most time with in 2025. You&#8217;ll find your top games, the number of titles you played, achievements unlocke...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The last Xbox update of 2025 includes a handy Wireless Headset upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/the-last-xbox-update-of-2025-includes-a-handy-wireless-headset-upgrade-204500386.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98bf3009-0025-4eb3-86f5-80ffdee3a4e2</guid>
      <description>As part of its last Xbox-focused software update of the year, Microsoft is improving the Bluetooth performance of the Xbox Wireless Headset to make it work even better with Windows 11. Microsoft released the latest Wireless Headset as an accessory for Xbox Series X/S and PC, but as of this update, Xbox Wireless Headset owners on Windows will now have a leg up on their console counterparts thanks to support for Bluetooth Low Energy (LE) Audio.Microsoft says that supporting Bluetooth LE Audio will let the headset offer lower latency audio, better battery life, richer stereo sound and the ability...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Games has a year-in-review thing now too</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nyt-games-has-a-year-in-review-thing-now-too-203000878.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d55947b4-c371-4675-b57c-98d16edec17f</guid>
      <description>The New York Times is getting in on the year-end roundup bandwagon. The publication's new Year in Games wraps up stats about which of its daily puzzles and brain-teasers readers played over the course of 2025. People can get their own personalized reports, or just look over the community stats for the Wordle, Connections, Spelling Bee and Strands games. The Year in Games reviews are available on the iOS and Android apps for The New York Times, as well as on a dedicated mobile web page.Annual analysis of all your activities has become a common feature for lots of services. Reports like Spotify ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking "5D memory crystal" storage could last until the end of the universe - but will it be able to hold all of your pet photos?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/groundbreaking-5d-memory-crystal-storage-could-last-until-the-end-of-the-universe-but-will-it-be-able-to-hold-all-of-your-pet-photos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rtMpR73hCFUQxufikVqTCQ</guid>
      <description>SPhotonix&#8217;s 5D memory crystal stores 360 TB per disc and lasts billions of years, designed for cold data in data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Streaming Bundles and Streaming Deals of December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-streaming-deals-and-streaming-bundles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">694074197656a254331c40ba</guid>
      <description>The best streaming deals right now are ad-free. Maybe the best streaming deals are always ad-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larian&#8217;s CEO says the studio isn&#8217;t &#8216;trimming down teams to replace them with AI&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845713/larian-ceo-divinity-ai-swen-vincke</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T15:15:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845713</guid>
      <description>The CEO of Baldur's Gate 3 studio Larian has inadvertently stirred up some controversy over the use of AI in the developer's next game. Based on an interview with Larian CEO Swen Vincke, Bloomberg reported that the studio uses AI tools for things like developing concept art and writing placeholder text. But following some initial [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sues five TV manufacturers over predatory ad-targeting spyware</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/texas-sues-five-tv-manufacturers-over-predatory-ad-targeting-spyware-201500248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3454b67-1222-4515-a718-38f90599dc47</guid>
      <description>Behold: Ken Paxton will now demonstrate that broken clocks are indeed right twice a day. The Texas Attorney General is notorious for, well, a very long list of reasons. But in this case, he at least appears to be doing consumers a solid: He sued five television companies for using ad-targeting spyware on their TVs.Texas sued Sony, Samsung, LG, Hisense and TCL for allegedly recording what viewers watch without their consent. The predatory technology, Automated Content Recognition (ACR), identifies the content being played on a device by matching short content fingerprints to a database.ACR is e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slate crosses 150,000 reservations despite waning EV truck enthusiasm</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/slate-crosses-150000-reservations-despite-waning-ev-truck-enthusiasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076618</guid>
      <description>It took Slate Auto about seven months to grow its customer list by 50%, but new reservations appear to be outpacing any cancelations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Burning Questions We Have After the &#8216;It: Welcome to Derry&#8217; Finale</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/7-burning-questions-we-have-after-the-it-welcome-to-derry-finale-2000699510</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699510</guid>
      <description>HBO&#8217;s Stephen King adaptation delivered plenty of Pennywise, but we have some lingering thoughts about what happened and what&#8217;s next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 Best Shows on Apple TV, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (December 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63cf1b483f042fa5827033d7</guid>
      <description>Down Cemetery Road, Pluribus, and The Morning Show are among the best shows on Apple TV this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump&#8217;s anti-DEI policies are hurting Black workers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460876/how-trumps-anti-dei-policies-are-hurting-black-workers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460876/how-trumps-anti-dei-policies-are-hurting-black-workers</guid>
      <description>If you want to understand how the DEI backlash is impacting workers, look no further than the Black unemployment rate. 
When the government shutdown came to an end last month, the much-delayed jobs report for September was finally released, revealing that the unemployment rate had inched up to 4.4%&#8212;the highest it had been in four years. Amid a tough job market and economic uncertainty, it&#8217;s little surprise that unemployment is on the rise again: In the latest jobs dispatch that was published today, unemployment had ticked up to 4.6% for the month of November.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These &#8216;historical tours&#8217; of modern offices capture just how banal work is</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461495/these-historical-tours-of-modern-offices-capture-just-how-banal-work-is</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461495/these-historical-tours-of-modern-offices-capture-just-how-banal-work-is</guid>
      <description>A viral TikTok series imagines how people in the future will talk about multiple monitors and &#8220;circling back by EOD.&#8221;
If you&#8217;ve ever been to a museum or on a school field trip, you may have had a tour guide walk you through a historical exhibit of 19th century households or of ancient Mesopotamian agricultural tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your TV is a &#8216;mass surveillance system&#8217; says Texas, and the state is suing LG, Samsung, Hisense, TCL, and more to stop it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/your-tv-is-a-mass-surveillance-system-says-texas-and-the-state-is-suing-lg-samsung-hisense-tcl-and-more-to-stop-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xdYav5qU5FRGZkEjMN7DyV</guid>
      <description>Texas's AG is suing Samsung, LG, TCL, Hisense, and Sony over their apparent use of ACR to deliver custom content and advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is letting creators make playable games with a Gemini 3 tool</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/youtube-is-letting-creators-make-playable-games-with-a-gemini-3-tool-195500318.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0365c187-d3d8-4a7f-9cfa-e50e11becd24</guid>
      <description>Google's at it again, once more insisting that AI is something people need or want more of in their lives. The latest move comes from YouTube Gaming, which announced an open beta for a project called Playables Builder. This allows select YouTube Creators to use a "prototype web app built using Gemini 3" to make bite-sized games, no coding required.&#160;YouTube is launching a closed Beta test for Playables Builder, a prototype web app built using Gemini 3 where users create games with short text, video or image prompts. we&#8217;ve partnered with YouTube Creators like @sambucha, @AyChristene, @goharsguid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sonos Arc Ultra is back down to its Black Friday price &#8212; don't miss out on this excellent Dolby Atmos soundbar deal</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/the-sonos-arc-ultra-is-back-down-to-its-black-friday-price-dont-miss-out-on-this-excellent-dolby-atmos-soundbar-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ayp6ozsfcHQHPYoY4KVcvN</guid>
      <description>Fancy upgrading your holiday movie soundtracks? There's a great deal on Sonos' superb Dolby Atmos soundbar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crunchyroll annual subscriptions are on sale for the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/crunchyroll-annual-subscriptions-are-on-sale-for-the-holidays-194345327.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4b4dd4d-8f13-4ef2-9537-58b9ba035b39</guid>
      <description>If you're looking for something to watch during a holiday break from work or school, you can't go wrong with anime, and right now you can sign-up for a year of Crunchyroll for as low as $65. Holiday discounts running through December 29 bring the anime streaming service's year-long Fan subscription from $80 down to $67 and its Mega Fan subscription from $120 down to $100. That's either $13 or $20 off access to one of the largest libraries of anime series and movies out there.
While both the Fan and Mega Fan plans are ad-free, you do get some different benefits depending on which you decide to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornhub cyberattack sees some Premium members data stolen - here's what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/pornhub-cyberattack-sees-some-premium-members-have-data-snatched</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zETBPQrSaov6TXTN7cypgX</guid>
      <description>ShinyHunters claims responsibility for the attack, saying they stole almost 100GB of sensitive Pornhub Premium user data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grindr Goes &#8216;AI-First&#8217; as It Strives to Be an &#8216;Everything App for the Gay Guy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/grindr-ai-first-era-everything-app-for-the-gay-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693c41e2199888f1c10473e1</guid>
      <description>After controlling shareholders failed to take Grindr private and controversies over data and the banning of the phrase &#8220;No Zionists,&#8221; Grindr&#8217;s CEO opens up about AI, privacy, and big expansion plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix will soon start airing video podcasts like The Breakfast Club</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/netflix-will-soon-start-airing-video-podcasts-like-the-breakfast-club-193112093.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">863ab051-7436-46a7-b15a-4539dbc82d73</guid>
      <description>Netflix has inked a deal with iHeartMedia to begin showing video podcasts, so the content will never, ever run out. The partnership covers new episodes from more than 15 popular podcasts, including The Breakfast Club, Dear Chelsea, My Favorite Murder and others. Customers will have access to video podcast episodes in early 2026.&#160;
In addition to new footage, the partnership includes a select library of archival episodes from each show. It's worth noting that YouTube already platforms video versions of many popular podcasts, including stuff like The Breakfast Club.
This follows a similar deal fr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold's best feature won't be its hardware &#8211; here's why I'm more excited for DeX</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-z-trifolds-best-feature-wont-be-its-hardware-heres-why-im-more-excited-for-dex</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VjpzcPyTo3SawWwXM2fCEJ</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold is due to merge the mobile and tablet experience like never before &#8211; and if Samsung plays its cards right, it could revolutionize on-the-go productivity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
