<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:43:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Native Instruments enters into insolvency proceedings, leaving its future uncertain</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/native-instruments-enters-into-insolvency-proceedings-leaving-its-future-uncertain-183206826.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e88ab674-b98f-4a2e-a8a5-67c23b02df61</guid>
      <description>Music hardware and software manufacturer Native Instruments has entered into preliminary insolvency proceedings, according to a report by Create Digital Music. This is the company behind iconic software like Massive, Traktor and Kontakt and hardware like Maschine+. Native Instruments also owns the brands iZotope, Brainworx and Plugin Alliance.
We don't have many specifics as to what this entails and what the future of the company will look like. We do know that an administrator has been appointed to handle restructuring and, potentially, to sell off existing assets. Native Instruments employs ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify says it paid out $11 billion in royalties in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869523/spotify-11-billion-in-royalties</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T13:22:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869523</guid>
      <description>Today, Spotify announced that it had paid out more than $11 billion to the music industry in 2025. It's an impressive-sounding number that's a full $1 billion more than it paid last year. And, according to Spotify, that accounts for roughly 30 percent of the entire recording industry's revenue. And, according to Spotify, that accounts [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Things We Liked, and 3 We Didn&#8217;t, About &#8216;Wonder Man&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/9-things-we-liked-and-3-we-didnt-about-wonder-man-2000713702</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713702</guid>
      <description>Yahya Abdul-Mateen II and Sir Ben Kingsley star in the new Marvel show, which is now on Disney+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed: SoundCloud data breach hit 29.8 million accounts - how to find out if you're affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/confirmed-soundcloud-data-breach-hit-29-8-million-accounts-how-to-find-out-if-youre-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SaXv27ps4f6vvHi3xDMmJU</guid>
      <description>HaveIBeenPwned confirms extent of the SoundCloud incident, allowing users to see if they're affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process Zero II will let you do a little processing, if you want</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/869354/halide-mark-iii-process-zero-update</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T13:01:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869354</guid>
      <description>Popular iPhone camera app Halide is debuting a major update today: Halide Mark III. It's been years in the making, and it'll be available as a "Public Preview," letting users get their hands on new features while design is finalized. This update includes the next iteration of the app's much-discussed Process Zero mode, adding HDR [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Unleashes AI in Chrome with &#8216;Auto Browse&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-unleashes-ai-in-chrome-with-auto-browse-2000714835</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714835</guid>
      <description>Google wants to do the browsing for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s New Chrome &#8216;Auto Browse&#8217; Agent Attempts to Roam the Web Without You</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-chrome-auto-browse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977bd968b3ddccd846ec307</guid>
      <description>Google&#8217;s latest addition to its Chrome browser puts generative AI behind the wheel and you in the passenger seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome takes on AI browsers with tighter Gemini integration, agentic features for autonomous tasks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/chrome-takes-on-ai-browsers-with-tighter-gemini-integration-agentic-features-for-autonomous-tasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086514</guid>
      <description>Google Chrome is adding Gemini in sidebar and is rolling out an agentic feature for AI Pro and Ultra users</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome gets its biggest upgrade in years &#8212; the new Gemini side panel puts AI agents, multitasking, and Nano Banana inside the browser</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chrome-gets-its-biggest-upgrade-in-years-the-new-gemini-side-panel-puts-ai-agents-multitasking-and-nano-banana-inside-the-browser</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V3LbgQHa77ehckmGZvk67</guid>
      <description>Google&#8217;s biggest Chrome update in years bakes Gemini AI agents, multitasking, and image editing directly into the browser, turning everyday web browsing into a hands-off experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested these quirky wireless earbuds that even let you play games on the charging case &#8212; and they cost less than &#163;40</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/groov-e-neo-buds-true-wireless-earbuds-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vjdpXpamNs7LBeHhfYMzs8</guid>
      <description>I tested the sub-&#163;40 wireless earbuds attempting to challenge JBL, but are they really up to the task?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Wonder Man directly set up a major storyline in Spider-Man: Brand New Day? The Marvel TV show's head writer has his say</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/does-wonder-man-directly-set-up-a-major-storyline-in-spider-man-brand-new-day-the-marvel-tv-shows-head-writer-has-his-say</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EKCZTyTKBJnsRrjQYpCpDn</guid>
      <description>Wonder Man's showrunner stopped short of confirming if the new Disney+ show will impact Spider-Man 4's story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google brings its Nano Banana image generator to Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-brings-its-nano-banana-image-generator-to-chrome-180000104.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b00cd63e-ecd1-4cbb-ac5b-1602200e7eea</guid>
      <description>Following its recent AI makeover of Gmail, Google is bringing more Gemini-powered tools to Chrome. Starting today, a host of new features are rolling out for the browser, with more to come over the next few months.&#160;The first of the new features is a sidebar. Available to all Gemini in Chrome users, the interface allows you to chat with Gemini and keep a conversation going across multiple tabs. Google suggests the sidebar is useful for multitaskers.&#160;"Our testers have been using it for all sorts of things: comparing options across too-many-tabs, summarizing product reviews across different sites...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tout savoir sur Kimi K2.5, le nouveau concurrent open source et &#171;&#160;gratuit&#160;&#187; qui se frotte &#224; Claude 4.5 et GPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2958953_tout-savoir-sur-kimi-k2-5-le-nouveau-concurrent-open-source-et-gratuit-qui-se-frotte-a-claude-4-5-et-gpt-5-2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2958953_tout-savoir-sur-kimi-k2-5-le-nouveau-concurrent-open-source-et-gratuit-qui-se-frotte-a-claude-4-5-et-gpt-5-2</guid>
      <description>
On nous promet souvent la r&#233;volution. Mais quand un mod&#232;le open source vient titiller Claude 4.5 Opus sur son propre terrain tout en g&#233;rant de la vid&#233;o native, on touche quelque chose d'int&#233;ressant. Voici Kimi K2.5 qui peut tourner en local.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple tells Patreon to move creators to in-app purchase for subscriptions by November</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/apple-tells-patreon-to-move-creators-to-in-app-purchase-for-subscriptions-by-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087258</guid>
      <description>Patreon isn&#8217;t happy about Apple&#8217;s new subscription billing mandate, arguing Apple&#8217;s shifting rules create uncertainty for creators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tag/ai-pro</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Y9GHv8UUn2fEdUZXVvDBqj</guid>
      <description>All TechRadar Pro stories tagged AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;You&#8217;ll rarely experience spy-movie stealth or the constant frustration of corporate geofences.&#8217; How 24 hours connected to a VPN changed my perspective on personal data security</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/youll-rarely-experience-spy-movie-stealth-or-the-constant-frustration-of-corporate-geofences-how-24-hours-connected-to-a-vpn-changed-my-perspective-on-personal-data-security</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aQFdZg5xXXMxxq2VMMBRr</guid>
      <description>I put the reality of using VPNs to the test, and the results weren't what I expected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The noise-canceling AirPods 4 are down to $120, one of their best prices yet</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/869428/apple-airpods-4-active-noise-cancellation-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T12:36:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869428</guid>
      <description>The AirPods Pro 3 may be on sale for $199 ($50 off), but that&#8217;s still a lot of money. If you want noise cancellation for less, fortunately you can buy the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation for $119 ($60 off) at Amazon and Walmart. That&#8217;s the cheapest they&#8217;ve been since the holidays, and only [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factify wants to move past PDFs and .docx by giving digital documents their own brain</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/factify-wants-to-move-past-pdfs-and-docx-by-giving-digital-documents-their</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3lhItsBSLENeR4Fgb9NAcE</guid>
      <description>Tel Aviv-based startup Factify emerged from stealth today with a $73 million seed round for an ambitious, yet quixotic mission: to bring digital documents beyond the standard formats most businesses use &#8212; .PDF, .docx, collaborative cloud files like Google Docs &#8212; and into the intelligence era.For Matan Gavish, Factify&#8217;s Founder and CEO, this isn't just a software upgrade&#8212;it is an inevitability he has been obsessed with for years."The PDF was developed when I was in elementary school," Gavish told VentureBeat. "The bedrock of the software ecosystem hasn't really evolved... someone has to redesig...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Ubisoft workers vote to strike</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ubisoft-173241918.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c70f746c-bf7f-40dc-a2f1-9447d44d0651</guid>
      <description>When deciding which video game to buy, "Is it fun?" is no longer the only consideration. Given the state of the industry, "Do I want to support this company?" is arguably more important. Take, for example, Ubisoft, where things seem to unravel more each day. After the floundering publisher floated even more layoffs this week, workers at its Paris headquarters said, "Enough is enough." They're now calling for a three-day strike.Unions representing Ubisoft employees plan to strike from February 10 to 12. "With management being stubbornly entrenched in its authoritarian ways, we are calling Ubiso...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Has a New Estimate for Europa&#8217;s Ice Shell, and Whoa Is It Ever Thick</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-has-a-new-estimate-for-europas-ice-shell-and-whoa-is-it-ever-thick-2000715015</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715015</guid>
      <description>Jupiter's fourth-largest moon is a main character in our search for other life-friendly places in our solar system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny startup Arcee AI built a 400B open source LLM from scratch to best Meta&#8217;s Llama</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tiny-startup-arcee-ai-built-a-400b-open-source-llm-from-scratch-to-best-metas-llama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086608</guid>
      <description>30-person startup Arcee AI has released a 400B model called Trinity, which it says is one of the biggest open source foundation models from a US company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve been using iPhones for years, and I always turn off this major iOS feature</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/ive-been-using-iphones-for-years-and-i-always-turn-off-this-major-ios-feature</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ex9AgESpirp9xydNf8xT5U</guid>
      <description>The iPhone's always-on display feature is potentially useful, but it also drains battery, and if you have an Apple Watch you probably don't need it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to cancel Windscribe and get your money back</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-cancel-windscribe-and-get-your-money-back-173000785.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9111484-53a9-4d3d-9f79-ec1f666bcb09</guid>
      <description>Windscribe isn't a VPN for everybody, and it's not trying to be. Despite its high-achieving free plan, it didn't quite make my list of the best VPNs, largely due to alienating interface choices and swingy download speeds. Its iconoclastic approach to everything from design to pricing to its online knowledge base will likely win some customers for life and turn others off.For those in the latter camp, I've written up this guide for cancelling Windscribe. Follow the instructions below to stop Windscribe from auto-renewing, cancel third-party subscriptions, delete your account altogether and get ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do virtues like being compassionate increase your well-being?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480129/do-virtues-like-being-compassionate-increase-your-well-being</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480129/do-virtues-like-being-compassionate-increase-your-well-being</guid>
      <description>The emerging science of virtue aims to find out.
Virtues such as compassion, patience, and self-control may be beneficial not only for others but also for oneself, according to new research my team and I published in the Journal of Personality in December 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I write about TV deals for a living &#8212; here&#8217;s what I&#8217;d buy to watch the Super Bowl LX</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/i-write-about-tv-deals-for-a-living-heres-what-id-buy-to-watch-the-super-bowl-lx</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CGpMwMPyQw2a5p2QBG6fdH</guid>
      <description>As TechRadar's TV deals expert, I'm listing my top 10 recommendations for watching the Super Bowl, including record-low prices on 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Should Probably Buy Wired Headphones Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-should-probably-buy-wired-headphones-now-2000714991</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714991</guid>
      <description>Sennheiser's new HD400U are cheap; they're cool; they're hi-fi. What more could you ask for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus en f&#233;vrier 2026 : voici les non pas trois, mais quatre jeux offerts aux abonn&#233;s du service !</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2958813_ps-plus-en-fevrier-2026-voici-les-non-pas-trois-mais-quatre-jeux-offerts-aux-abonnes-du-service</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2958813_ps-plus-en-fevrier-2026-voici-les-non-pas-trois-mais-quatre-jeux-offerts-aux-abonnes-du-service</guid>
      <description>
PlayStation vient de d&#233;voiler les quatre jeux qui seront offerts ce mois-ci aux abonn&#233;s du PS Plus. Au programme : de la boxe, de la plong&#233;e, un cousin de Metroid et des avions de chasse !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures cartes graphiques en 2026 ? Tests et s&#233;lection</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/815386_meilleures-cartes-graphiques</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/815386_meilleures-cartes-graphiques</guid>
      <description>
La carte graphique (GPU) est un &#233;l&#233;ment essentiel de tout bon PC gamer. Face &#224; un march&#233; en perp&#233;tuelle &#233;volution, avec des g&#233;n&#233;rations de GPU qui s&#8217;encha&#238;nent et des technologies qui progressent sans cesse, il peut &#234;tre difficile de s&#8217;y retrouver. Bienvenue sur notre guide s&#233;lectif qui vous aidera &#224; choisir la carte graphique la plus pertinente selon votre budget.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN two-year plans are up to 78 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-two-year-plans-are-up-to-78-percent-off-180602104.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $101 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.59 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There Can Only Be One First Look at the &#8216;Highlander&#8217; Reboot</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/there-can-only-be-one-first-look-at-the-highlander-reboot-2000715039</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715039</guid>
      <description>Henry Cavill is the new Connor MacLeod in Chad Stahelski and Amazon MGM's fresh take on the fantasy adventure film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napoli vs Chelsea Free Streams: How to watch Champions League 2025/26 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/napoli-vs-chelsea-free-streams-how-to-watch-champions-league-2025-26-online-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2WEs5LsFCJdHK9bQBZtbWN</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Napoli vs Chelsea in the 2025/26 Champions League with both sides in desperate need of three points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk reportedly wants a June SpaceX IPO to align with his birthday, the planets</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/elon-musk-reportedly-wants-a-june-spacex-ipo-to-align-with-his-birthday-the-planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087205</guid>
      <description>SpaceX eyes June for IPO to align with Musk's birthday and the planets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Not just censorship, it&#8217;s digital isolation:" Iran plans to cut ties with the global internet &#8212; and VPNs may not help this time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/not-just-censorship-its-digital-isolation-iran-plans-to-cut-ties-with-the-global-internet-and-vpns-may-not-help-this-time</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eyndRRX85amx5wGxGW3q3</guid>
      <description>After enforcing "one of the most severe blackouts in history," Iran is moving towards a permanent whitelisting system to better police the internet. Here's what is at stake for people in Iran, and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple lance aujourd&#8217;hui Creator Studio, pour cr&#233;er sur abonnement</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/apple-lance-aujourdhui-creator-studio-pour-creer-sur-abonnement.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323041</guid>
      <description>Les cr&#233;ateurs de tout poil ont d&#233;sormais &#224; leur disposition un nouvel abonnement pour couvrir tous leurs besoins ou presque. Le Creator Studio d'Apple regroupe sous une m&#234;me banni&#232;re tous les logiciels pro et bureautiques du constructeur, accompagn&#233;s de fonctions in&#233;dites g&#233;n&#233;r&#233;es par IA. Premi&#232;re d&#233;couverte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN service for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/best-vpn-130004396.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad91508b-bbe1-44e8-a716-02724cbca3ac</guid>
      <description>As frustrating as it is that governments and businesses are running roughshod over our online freedoms, at least we have plenty of good VPNs to keep us protected online. There are so many fast, intelligently designed, full-featured and affordable services on the market that the biggest problem is picking one. For any use case, you can bet at least two providers will be neck-and-neck for first place.
On the other hand, the VPN world is still the Wild West in some ways. It's easy enough to slap a cheap VPN together that the market is flooded with low-quality apps that put more money into adverti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer made a web app version of Synapse</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/razer-made-a-web-app-version-of-synapse-170715465.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09f81cc0-4cbf-49e0-8726-482006b2a3b2</guid>
      <description>Gaming peripheral company Razer has announced the beta release of Synapse Web, a browser-based version of its desktop software. The web app is intended for quick adjustments when away from home, such as LANs or tournaments, where downloading the full desktop version may not be possible or practical.
At launch, Synapse Web will only support the Razer Huntsman V3 Pro keyboards, though Razer says more devices will be added down the line. Using any Chromium-based browser, users can make quick changes to key settings, apply Chroma RGB quick effects and manage on-board profiles. These profiles can t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One UI 8.5 (Android 16) : Samsung ajoute enfin une fonctionnalit&#233; cl&#233; &#224; la Now Bar</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/one-ui-8-5-android-16-samsung-ajoute-enfin-une-fonctionnalite-cle-a-la-now-bar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323031</guid>
      <description>Introduite avec One UI 7 et les Galaxy S25, la Now Bar devait incarner la nouvelle mani&#232;re d&#8217;interagir avec son smartphone Samsung. Un an plus tard, elle s&#8217;enrichit enfin d&#8217;une fonction aussi simple qu&#8217;attendue : l&#8217;affichage des appels manqu&#233;s. Une &#233;volution modeste, mais symbolique, alors que la firme cor&#233;enne pr&#233;pare d&#233;j&#224; One UI 8.5 et les Galaxy S26, dans un contexte concurrentiel plus tendu que jamais....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Apple&#8217;s new Creator Studio Pro, AI is a tool to aid creation, not replace it</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/with-apples-new-creator-studio-pro-ai-is-a-tool-to-aid-creation-not-replace-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087197</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s Creator Studio Pro leverages AI to help creators with tedious tasks&#8212;like finding clips or building slides&#8212;without trying to do the work for them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best OLED TVs for all budgets, as reviewed by our experts.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-best-oled-tvs-for-all-budgets-as-reviewed-by-our-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vijPiUytHBa6yjCCwsa7Fh</guid>
      <description>With infinite contrast and phenomenal picture quality, the best OLED TVs will change how you experience your favorite movies and shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Police Department investigating Zoox collision with a parked car</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/san-francisco-police-department-investigating-zoox-collision-with-a-parked-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086198</guid>
      <description>The investigation is looking into a January 17 crash where a Zoox robotaxi hit the driver's-side door of a parked car, which Zoox said was "suddenly opened."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best projectors for all budgets, including portable and 4K projectors, all real-world tested by home theater experts.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/projectors/the-best-projectors-for-all-budgets-including-portable-and-4k-projectors-all-real-world-tested-by-home-theater-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7mSCGippZ9HUtm6JGtjF94</guid>
      <description>From long throw to ultra short throw and portable models, our guide will give you the big picture on the best 4K projectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's second-generation AirTag offers greater range but still doesn't have a keyring hole</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/apples-second-generation-airtag-offers-greater-range-but-still-doesnt-have-a-keyring-hole-150540407.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a69a787-277c-4401-8e22-7cb791d6eb0d</guid>
      <description>Apple has launched its next-generation AirTag for $29 and brought a slew of new features along with it. But, first, it's important to get this out of the way: The new AirTag still doesn't have a keyring hole, so you'll still need accessories like a case, holder or secure pocket.Once you get over that, the new Apple AirTag does offer some nice improvements. For starters, it's now powered by Apple's second-generation Ultra Wideband chip &#8212; the same one used in the iPhone 17 lineup and for the Apple Watch Ultra 3. It also uses Precision Finding to reach items up to 50 percent further away than the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAFTA vs the Oscars &#8211; I&#8217;m a serial movie-watcher, and there's a clear winner in these nominations lists</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/bafta-vs-the-oscars-im-a-serial-movie-watcher-and-theres-a-clear-winner-in-these-nominations-lists</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dGhQM7o96RXHukMH58nPGE</guid>
      <description>Chase Inifiniti and Odessa A'zion were snubbed at the Oscars, but their BAFTA nominations show which ceremony has better taste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roku just made a major tweak to its home screen &#8211; and not everyone is happy about it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/roku-just-made-a-major-tweak-to-its-home-screen-and-not-everyone-is-happy-about-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WzNQnR9Adrz5fZm72P2Q6U</guid>
      <description>A new Subscriptions tab has appeared on the Roku home screen, letting you pick up where you left off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech needs less than a month to pay off over $7 billion in 2025 fines, Proton warns</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/big-tech-could-need-only-one-month-to-pay-off-over-usd7-billion-in-2025-fines-proton-warns</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vDqWFgbnUGGBbB8dYBRMc7</guid>
      <description>Big Tech was slapped with $7.8 billion in fines in 2025, but Proton found this massive sum represents less than a month of free cash flow. Is it time for regulators to find new teeth?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le PC de l&#8217;ind&#233;cence : une configuration ultime mais un prix ind&#233;cent</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2958861_voici-le-pc-de-lindecence-une-configuration-ultime-mais-un-prix-indecent</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2958861_voici-le-pc-de-lindecence-une-configuration-ultime-mais-un-prix-indecent</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que votre config de gaming &#233;tait solide ? Attendez de voir ce que vient de sortir Optimum.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 87 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-87-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056484.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>If one of your New Year's resolutions was to improve your cybersecurity, it's not too late. Most of the holiday deals are over by now, but plenty of services are still offering excellent prices. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can keep your activity hidden from your ISP and any advertisers it may sell that data to &#8212; all while streaming sporting events and TV dramas from all across the globe.
We strongly recommend using a VPN, but if you jump on the very first deal you see, you might get stuck with a substandard app. It's also easy to mistakenly end up paying more than you w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vintage NASA Jet Skids to a Fiery Stop in Dramatic &#8216;Wheels-Up&#8217; Landing</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/vintage-nasa-jet-skids-to-a-fiery-stop-in-dramatic-wheels-up-landing-2000714975</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714975</guid>
      <description>A suspected mechanical issue forced the two-person crew to land the aging aircraft on its belly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelence raises $3M to smooth out the vibe-coding stack</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/modelence-raises-13-million-to-smooth-out-the-vibe-coding-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087226</guid>
      <description>How do you build tooling for the AI software stack? A company called Modelence has an interesting answer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British speaker great Ruark has made two stunning 'radiograms' for its 40th anniversary &#8212; beautiful modern wireless speakers that double as a sideboard</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/british-speaker-great-ruark-has-made-two-stunning-radiograms-for-its-40th-anniversary-beautiful-modern-wireless-speakers-that-double-as-a-sideboard</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ourCmPML4S3yfQ8yLxnGfP</guid>
      <description>Ruark celebrates its 40th with two exquisite and extremely limited edition statement pieces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge greenlights Massachusetts offshore wind project halted by Trump administration</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482447/trump-offshore-wind-energy-climate-lawsuits</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482447/trump-offshore-wind-energy-climate-lawsuits</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s the fourth halted wind project that has been allowed to go forward.
A federal judge said Tuesday that a nearly completed Massachusetts offshore wind project can continue, as the industry successfully challenges the Trump administration in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C&#8217;est historique : deux trous noirs viennent d&#8217;&#234;tre photographi&#233;s ensemble pour la premi&#232;re fois</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cest-historique-deux-trous-noirs-viennent-etre-photographies-ensemble-premiere-fois-w2t8-130496/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cest-historique-deux-trous-noirs-viennent-etre-photographies-ensemble-premiere-fois-w2t8-130496/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Pour la premi&#232;re fois, des astronomes ont r&#233;ussi &#224; capturer une image radio montrant deux trous noirs en orbite l'un autour de l'autre. Jusqu'&#224; pr&#233;sent, les astronomes n'avaient r&#233;ussi &#224; photographier que des trous noirs individuels. Mais il y a plusieurs ann&#233;es, ils ont pu disposer d'un...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Watch : cette nouvelle option va enfin vous aider &#224; ne plus jamais perdre vos cl&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2957575_avec-les-nouveaux-airtags-votre-apple-watch-devient-encore-plus-pratique-pour-trouver-vos-objets-perdus</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2957575_avec-les-nouveaux-airtags-votre-apple-watch-devient-encore-plus-pratique-pour-trouver-vos-objets-perdus</guid>
      <description>
Avec la sortie des nouveaux AirTags de deuxi&#232;me g&#233;n&#233;ration, les montres connect&#233;es d'Apple s'enrichissent d'une fonction bien pratique pour retrouver vos objets &#233;gar&#233;s. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger met le paquet pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes avec de belles promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-met-le-paquet-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-avec-de-belles-promotions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-met-le-paquet-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-avec-de-belles-promotions</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver touchent bient&#244;t &#224; leur fin ! Pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque, Boulanger ne l&#233;sine pas sur les offres : enceinte bluetooth, &#233;cran gaming g&#233;ant de 40", nouveau Redmi Note 15 en promo... Il y a de quoi se faire plaisir, mais plus pour longtemps. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valve is facing a lawsuit over 'monopoly' claims on Steam &#8211; and I'm scratching my head at this one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/valve-is-facing-a-lawsuit-over-monopoly-claims-on-steam-and-im-scratching-my-head-at-this-one</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dy8Wf2Ejz5NKhZ5ikDAepA</guid>
      <description>Valve's Steam storefront is favoured by a large majority of PC gamers, with generous discounts and pricing, but a lawsuit has called that into question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fnac et Darty multiplient les bonnes affaires avec ces derni&#232;res offres &#224; saisir avant la fin des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-multiplient-les-bonnes-affaires-avec-ces-dernieres-offres-a-saisir-avant-la-fin-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-multiplient-les-bonnes-affaires-avec-ces-dernieres-offres-a-saisir-avant-la-fin-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
C'est l'heure de la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque ! Il reste encore quelques jours pour profiter des soldes d'hiver, et les enseignes Fnac et Darty n'ont pas dit leur dernier mot. On trouve tout un tas d'offres Tech int&#233;ressantes sur les 2 sites : voici celles qui ont retenu notre attention. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI&#8217;s refreshed Prestige series laptops are now available to buy</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/msis-refreshed-prestige-series-laptops-are-now-available-to-buy-165234479.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d7666b-0ca5-41ba-b997-3d8422da27d4</guid>
      <description>The latest lineup of MSI's Prestige laptops is now available to buy. The company unveiled its next-generation business laptop at CES earlier this month, all of them powered by the latest Intel Core Ultra Series 3 processors.
Available in configurations that include up to the Intel Core Ultra 9, the updated Prestige series are equipped with chunky 91Wh batteries and, depending on the model, offer over 30 hours of 1080p video playback. In more real-world terms, if you&#8217;re on a work trip and know you won&#8217;t always have a power supply to hand, you can trust one of these to get you through a day of h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les meilleures offres tombent pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver : le TOP 50 des deals &#224; ne pas louper</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_les-meilleures-offres-tombent-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-voici-le-top-25</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_les-meilleures-offres-tombent-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-voici-le-top-25</guid>
      <description>
Il ne faut pas se le cacher, la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes est souvent le moment o&#249; l'on trouve les meilleures offres, car les e-commer&#231;ants comme Amazon, Fnac, Darty ou encore Boulanger veulent &#233;couler les derniers stocks. Avec cet article, vous serez s&#251;rs de ne manquer aucun deal Tech int&#233;ressant. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I scavenged 33 pieces of Fallout "loot" that will turn your home office into a Vault-Tec shelter</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/i-scavenged-33-pieces-of-fallout-loot-that-will-turn-your-home-office-into-a-vault-tec-shelter</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZXGvQCwbpnVZA7U5uJaZrX</guid>
      <description>Overseer-approved home office gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allbirds is closing its last brick-and-mortar store in San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/allbirds-closing-last-store-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087194</guid>
      <description>Once symbolic of a mid-2010s San Francisco tech bro, Allbirds is cutting costs to "support the long-term health of the business."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSG vs Newcastle Free Streams: How to watch Champions League 2025/26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/psg-vs-newcastle-champions-league-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nvVAkCW777MDEaSktSw9Pj</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch PSG vs Newcastle live streams from anywhere and for free, with both sides looking to secure a place in the Champions League Round of 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Months later, the Supreme Court still hasn&#8217;t decided on Trump&#8217;s emergency tariffs. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482439/months-later-supreme-court-still-hasnt-decided-trumps-emergency-tariffs-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:44:56</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482439/months-later-supreme-court-still-hasnt-decided-trumps-emergency-tariffs-heres-why</guid>
      <description>Back in November, many of the court&#8217;s nine justices expressed doubts about the legality of Trump&#8217;s tariffs.
When the Supreme Court granted an unusually quick hearing over President Donald Trump&#8217;s tariffs, a similarly rapid resolution seemed possible.After all, Trump&#8217;s lawyers told the court that speed was of the essence on an issue central to the Republican president&#8217;s economic agenda. They pointed to a statement from Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent warning that the &#8220;longer a final ruling is delayed, the greater the risk of economic disruption.&#8221;But nearly three months have elapsed since argum...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
