<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:08:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hobart Hurricanes vs Melbourne Stars Free Streams: How to watch BBL15 Knockout online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/hobart-hurricanes-vs-melbourne-stars-bbl15-knockout</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LV5bpZ7gSoMmft8GgdsAEd</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Hobart Hurricanes vs Melbourne Stars in BBL15 Knockout with a spot in Friday's Challenger up for grabs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;It is genuinely hard; we need to protect vulnerable users, while also making sure our guardrails still allow all of our users to benefit from our tools&#8221; &#8212; Sam Altman bemoans the difficulty of keeping ChatGPT safe in contentious debate with Elon Musk</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/it-is-genuinely-hard-we-need-to-protect-vulnerable-users-while-also-making-sure-our-guardrails-still-allow-all-of-our-users-to-benefit-from-our-tools-sam-altman-bemoans-the-difficulty-of-keeping-chatgpt-safe-in-contentious-debate-with-elon-musk</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PdwLXhHqV7C5KK2oKUZdbn</guid>
      <description>Sam Altman defended OpenAI&#8217;s approach to AI safety in a public clash with Elon Musk, revealing the complex challenge of building tools that protect vulnerable users without limiting everyone else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One year in, Big Tech has out-maneuvered MAGA populists</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/864759/big-tech-trump-one-year-in</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T22:33:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864759</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers about the technology and the tech bros upending American politics and the Trump administration. If you're not a subscriber yet, and you're interested in Silicon Valley's adventures in sausage-making, you should do so here! It's Q1! Surely the corporate budget will allow for it. Precisely one year [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired of seeing Low Battery pop-up on iPhone? Here are 5 simple display settings to improve your battery life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/tired-of-seeing-low-battery-pop-up-on-iphone-here-are-5-simple-display-settings-to-improve-your-battery-life</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wzerkH7oJo9DWuh5k8zT38</guid>
      <description>These easy tips can help you extend your iPhone's battery life by changing how its display behaves.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
