<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:29:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>18 grammes pour tout retenir : SwitchBot s&#8217;attaque au march&#233; de l&#8217;assistant vocal portable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2926717_18-grammes-pour-tout-retenir-switchbot-sattaque-au-marche-de-lassistant-vocal-portable</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2926717_18-grammes-pour-tout-retenir-switchbot-sattaque-au-marche-de-lassistant-vocal-portable</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s l'&#233;chec cuisant du Humane AI Pin, on pensait le march&#233; des "badges IA" mort et enterr&#233;. Mais SwitchBot n'est pas d'accord. Au CES 2026, ils d&#233;gainent le MindClip, un assistant vocal discret con&#231;u pour &#234;tre votre "second cerveau". La promesse est belle : transformer vos conversations en to-do lists. La r&#233;alit&#233; ? Elle d&#233;pendra de l'abonnement.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic LastPass breach enabling cryptocurrency theft, investigation reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/historic-lastpass-breach-enabling-cryptocurrency-theft-investigation-reveals</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CnfBYNHNNPWnec82inqVp5</guid>
      <description>Tens of millions of dollars are being stolen through cracked LastPass vaults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the RugOne Xever 7 Pro - a lightweight rugged phone with removeable battery that&#8217;s dragged down by its processor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/phone-communications/rugone-xever-7-pro-rugged-phone-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aCYeKBwafbYcj92ypneZW9</guid>
      <description>The RugOne Xever 7 Pro is a lightweight, rugged design that uses swapable batteries to extend its operating life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>281 trillions de couleurs ? Le chiffre totalement absurde (mais dr&#244;le) de la nouvelle lampe Govee</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927355_govee-devoile-3-nouvelles-lampes-matter-au-ces-2026-dont-un-puit-de-lumiere-artificiel</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927355_govee-devoile-3-nouvelles-lampes-matter-au-ces-2026-dont-un-puit-de-lumiere-artificiel</guid>
      <description>
Vous trouviez qu'il manquait de l'intelligence artificielle dans votre plafonnier ? Non ? Govee l'a fait quand m&#234;me. Le fabricant chinois profite du CES pour d&#233;voiler sa nouvelle gamme, dont la Floor Lamp 3 et ses promesses colorim&#233;triques absurdes. Mais le produit qui nous pla&#238;t, c'est peut-&#234;tre ce faux puit de lumi&#232;re ultra-lumineux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is rolling out Alexa+ for the web so you can use its assistant without a dedicated device</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazon-is-rolling-out-alexa-for-the-web-so-you-can-use-its-assistant-without-a-dedicated-device-150053826.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48cb763b-0931-4cb1-967d-46f5e4086fd8</guid>
      <description>You no longer need an Amazon device to summon Alexa since the AI assistant will be available on the Alexa.com website. Amazon will roll out the web client to its Alexa+ Early Access customers first, still featuring the company's new and improved AI assistant that was announced in February.
The web model won't be much different from the existing Alexa+ that's already available on Echo devices, Fire TV and Fire tablets. However, instead of buying into the Amazon ecosystem, Early Access customers can use any web browser to get Alexa+'s help with everything from basic questions to complex tasks, l...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. Abrams&#8217; Mysterious Next Movie May Have Found Its Title</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jj-abrams-new-movie-great-beyond-2000705331</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705331</guid>
      <description>Plus, is it really time for next Doctor rumors on 'Doctor Who' already?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bee has been busy since its acquisition by Amazon last year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/bee-has-been-busy-since-its-acquisition-by-amazon-last-year-150025311.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d1d6a66-084e-4cfc-9d45-8f198a4a756f</guid>
      <description>Bee, the company behind an always-listening AI wearable that Amazon acquired last year, has announced new features in a status update. The device is designed to run in the background of daily life and captures conversations or thoughts spoken aloud. Recording can be started or stopped with the push of a button.
Co-founder of Bee, Maria de Lourdes Zollo, says the company has shipped four major updates that will run on the existing Bee Pioneer hardware. The first is &#8220;Actions,&#8221; which connects Bee to a user's email and calendar and works to turn spoken commitments into actions. The company says th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ember Artline is Amazon's answer to Samsung's The Frame</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/ember-artline-is-amazons-answer-to-samsungs-the-frame-150015104.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d28ecd7-00a9-482c-b109-80bf177a66d4</guid>
      <description>Amazon just revealed the Ember Artline TV at CES 2026. This is a lifestyle TV that displays art, putting it in direct competition with Samsung's The Frame. The 4K QLED screen is extremely thin, at 1.5-inches, so it'll likely fit just about anywhere.
It also features a glare-reducing matte screen that has been "designed to make your art and photos look great." The Artline integrates with Amazon Photos and offers access to 2,000 pieces of free art to display. For those worried about electricity usage, the TV includes proprietary technology that senses when someone has entered or left the room an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ces lunettes remplacent votre TV : XREAL d&#233;voile les 1S au CES 2026 qui int&#232;grent une compatibilit&#233; native avec la Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/lunettes-intelligentes/2927175_ces-lunettes-remplacent-votre-tv-xreal-devoile-les-1s-au-ces-2026-qui-integrent-une-compatibilite-native-avec-la-switch-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/lunettes-intelligentes/2927175_ces-lunettes-remplacent-votre-tv-xreal-devoile-les-1s-au-ces-2026-qui-integrent-une-compatibilite-native-avec-la-switch-2</guid>
      <description>
C'est devenu une tradition au CES : XREAL sort une nouvelle paire de lunettes. Cette ann&#233;e, place aux XREAL 1S. Ne cherchez pas la r&#233;volution, c'est une &#233;volution chirurgicale : 1200p, plus de luminosit&#233; et une compatibilit&#233; native avec la Switch 2.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This egg-shaped gadget aims to demystify hormones&#8230; with pee</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852942/mira-ultra4-wand-hormone-testing-ces-2026-health</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852942</guid>
      <description>Your urine can tell you a lot about your reproductive health hormones. Unfortunately, at-home testing can be cumbersome, involving collecting samples that are then mailed out to labs. That's what health startup Mira is trying to simplify with its $249 Ultra4 Hormone Monitor. The pitch is to make highly accurate, readily available hormone testing for [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon adds to the lifestyle TV landscape with the Ember Artline TV</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853508/amazon-ember-artline-tv-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853508</guid>
      <description>Joining Samsung's The Frame, Hisense CanvasTV, TCL Nxtvision, and newly announced LG Gallery TV, is Amazon's very first art TV. The Amazon Ember Artline is a 4K edge-lit LED TV with a matte screen to reduce ambient light glare and is only 1.5 inches thick. At purchase, customers will be able to include their choice [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alexa Plus website is now available to everyone in early access</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853535/alexa-plus-website-now-available</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853535</guid>
      <description>Alexa Plus was already popping up online for some users earlier this month, and now it's officially available to everyone through an early access program. Anyone can go sign up at Alexa.com and start playing with the new web interface for Amazon's new AI chatbot. Alexa Plus was already available on all new Echo devices [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Fire TV OS gets a much-needed revamp</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853550/amazon-fire-tv-os-revamp-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853550</guid>
      <description>Amazon Fire TV has been a bit long in the tooth for a while now. Its design isn't as intuitive to navigate as Google TV, Roku, or Apple TV, and its responsiveness is frustrating. I've found it to be the weak link in Amazon's portfolio for a while now, and the only major drawback to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kwikset&#8217;s new Matter-over-Thread smart lock costs under $200</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853746/kwikset-aura-reach-matter-thread-smart-lock-price-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853746</guid>
      <description>Kwikset announced a price and release date for its Aura Reach smart lock at CES 2026 this week. A more affordable Matter-over-Thread option compared to the excellent but expensive Halo Select, the Aura Reach is available now for $189. At just under $100 less than the Halo, you are sacrificing built-in Wi-Fi and an integrated [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifx launches a smart mirror and a $30 dimmer switch that can control smart bulbs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853979/lifx-smart-mirror-dimmer-switch-matter-thread-launch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853979</guid>
      <description>Lifx, one of the original smart lighting brands, is launching a Matter-enabled smart mirror, its first US in-wall dimmer, and a cheaper line of bulbs and light strips starting at around $12. The company, which announced the new products at CES this week, says it plans to upgrade its entire current generation of devices to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon revamps Fire TV, launches its own &#8216;Artline&#8217; televisions with frames at CES</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/amazon-revamps-fire-tv-launches-its-own-artline-televisions-with-frames/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079300</guid>
      <description>Fire TV's new interface focuses on your content and offers easier, speedier navigation, Amazon says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s AI assistant comes to the web with Alexa.com</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/alexa-without-an-echo-amazons-ai-chatbot-comes-to-the-web-and-a-revamped-alexa-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079547</guid>
      <description>Amazon is bringing Alexa+ to the web with a new Alexa.com site, expanding its AI assistant beyond devices and positioning it as a family-focused, agent-style chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Tuesday, January 6 (game #1443)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-6-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Lm6EoH5DUL2tMJxmoQM3LB</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Tuesday, January 6 (game #940)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-6-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fo6mgN5QchUgZ3v8MvDEPG</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Tuesday, January 6 (game #674)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-6-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WU6kqBcjaogqaTsyNhzT2E</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Ember Artline is its answer to Samsung&#8217;s Frame &#8212; with a focus on value and AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/embargo-7am-pt-10am-et-1-5-2026-amazons-ember-artline-is-its-answer-to-samsungs-frame-with-a-focus-on-value-and-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HdsTU8jFwgGD6UhQqgWTyA</guid>
      <description>Amazon is taking on Samsung&#8217;s Frame with the Ember Artline Fire TV, a lifestyle TV that combines art display with ambient AI features and a likely lower starting price that includes the frame in the box.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is redesigning its Fire TV UI for streaming sticks and TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/amazon-is-redesigning-its-fire-tv-ui-for-streaming-sticks-and-tvs-150000622.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33981978-2d4d-4beb-832b-696efdf62538</guid>
      <description>Amazon is kicking off the new year by announcing a redesign of its Fire TV UI at CES 2026. The new UI is designed to make finding things to watch on the platform faster, while making it easier to access more of Fire TV's features straight from the home screen.On first blush, the biggest difference in the new Fire TV UI is that everything is rounder. Shows, movies and apps have rounded corners, and Amazon's changed the spacing in the interface to give everything more room to breathe. Tweaks to typography and color gradients also give the UI a more modern feel, and Amazon says it's rebuilt the c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The culture solution CEOs are missing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467608/the-culture-solution-ceos-are-missing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T15:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467608/the-culture-solution-ceos-are-missing</guid>
      <description>Skills-based volunteering is catalyzing the workforce of the future.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini la prise de notes : ce bo&#238;tier &#171;&#160;Fran&#231;ais&#160;&#187; de g&#233;nie r&#233;sume vos r&#233;unions avec ChatGPT, Claude et Gemini</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2928199_ce-boitier-ia-compatible-chatgpt-et-claude-enregistre-et-resume-vos-reunions</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2928199_ce-boitier-ia-compatible-chatgpt-et-claude-enregistre-et-resume-vos-reunions</guid>
      <description>
En 2015, Facebook promettait un assistant humain nomm&#233; Moneypenny. Dix ans plus tard, le nom revient au CES 2026, mais chez Oxtak. C'est un dictaphone dop&#233; aux st&#233;ro&#239;des et &#224; l'IA qui promet de r&#233;sumer votre vie pro.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold Hands On: This Is the Phone-Tablet Hybrid You're Looking For</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6957fa77f93229aa3801734f</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, we went hands-on with the three-panel Samsung tablet that folds up to the size of a (large) phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plier le linge et vider le lave-vaisselle : SwitchBot nous vend du r&#234;ve avec son robot Onero H1</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/robots/2926533_switchbot-se-lance-dans-la-robotique-humanoide-avec-lonero-h1-cest-soit-une-revolution-soit-une-vaste-blague</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/robots/2926533_switchbot-se-lance-dans-la-robotique-humanoide-avec-lonero-h1-cest-soit-une-revolution-soit-une-vaste-blague</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu la vid&#233;o de d&#233;mo du SwitchBot Onero H1 ? C'est impressionnant : il plie le linge, vide le lave-vaisselle, sert &#224; manger. Trop beau pour &#234;tre vrai ? Probablement. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordVPN denies data breach after hackers claim Salesforce leak &#8212; here's everything we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/nordvpn-denies-data-breach-after-hackers-claim-salesforce-leak-heres-everything-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R5AE9mhNREhUHjvFVKTU3B</guid>
      <description>Reports have surfaced of a potential data breach involving NordVPN's Salesforce tools. Here is what the hackers are claiming, and why NordVPN says your data remains secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une feuille OLED de 9 mm pour jouer en 165 Hz : LG n&#8217;a pas fait les choses &#224; moiti&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2927107_lg-w6-le-retour-du-wallpaper-oled-une-feuille-de-9-mm-qui-cache-une-bete-de-course</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2927107_lg-w6-le-retour-du-wallpaper-oled-une-feuille-de-9-mm-qui-cache-une-bete-de-course</guid>
      <description>
C'est probablement le t&#233;l&#233;viseur le plus impressionnant visuellement de ce CES 2026. La LG OLED evo W6 reprend le concept du &#171; papier peint &#187; abandonn&#233; en 2020. En gros, c'est un &#233;cran de 77 ou 83 pouces coll&#233; au mur, sans aucun c&#226;ble visible, pilot&#233; par un bo&#238;tier sans fil.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia pourrait remettre en vente une de ses cartes graphiques les plus populaires</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/nvidia-pourrait-remettre-en-vente-une-de-ses-cartes-graphiques-les-plus-populaires.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318170</guid>
      <description>Cette bonne vieille RTX 3060 pourrait revenir dans les rayons des magasins d'&#233;lectronique dans le courant du premier trimestre. Nvidia semble en effet pr&#233;parer le retour de sa carte graphique toujours tr&#232;s populaire malgr&#233; son &#226;ge. Il faut dire que la situation actuelle au niveau de la RAM plaide en faveur de ce mod&#232;le.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La B&amp;YOU Pure Fibre est d&#233;sormais plus ch&#232;re : l&#8217;offre vaut-elle toujours le coup ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2928563_la-byou-pure-fibre-est-desormais-plus-chere-loffre-vaut-elle-toujours-le-coup</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2928563_la-byou-pure-fibre-est-desormais-plus-chere-loffre-vaut-elle-toujours-le-coup</guid>
      <description>
Bouygues Telecom l'avait annonc&#233; et c'est chose faite. &#192; partir du 5 janvier 2026, l'abonnement B&amp;YOU Pure Fibre voit son tarif augmenter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personne n&#8217;en a besoin, tout le monde la veut : voici l&#8217;objet d&#233;co le plus cool du CES</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927995_switchbot-obboto-une-lampe-globe-avec-2900-leds-pour-le-pixel-art</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927995_switchbot-obboto-une-lampe-globe-avec-2900-leds-pour-le-pixel-art</guid>
      <description>
Il faut qu'on parle de l'obsession de mettre de l'IA partout. M&#234;me dans une lampe. SwitchBot d&#233;voile l'Obboto, un globe lumineux capable de g&#233;n&#233;rer des "animations d'ambiance contr&#244;l&#233;es par l'IA". Au-del&#224; du buzzword, c'est surtout un tr&#232;s joli afficheur pixel art qui pourrait bien faire de l'ombre au c&#233;l&#232;bre LaMetric Time.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bient&#244;t en Europe, le Tesla Model Y L &#224; 6 places se d&#233;couvre dans ces images in&#233;dites</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2928501_bientot-en-europe-le-tesla-model-y-l-a-6-places-se-decouvre-dans-ces-images-inedites</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2928501_bientot-en-europe-le-tesla-model-y-l-a-6-places-se-decouvre-dans-ces-images-inedites</guid>
      <description>
Jusqu'ici r&#233;serv&#233;e au march&#233; chinois, le Tesla Model Y L dot&#233;e de six places devrait bient&#244;t arriver en Europe, o&#249; il rejoindra la version Performance. L'occasion de d&#233;couvrir les croquis des designers.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL 55A300 : -60 % pour ce TV QLED en forme de tableau, la meilleure alternative au The Frame de Samsung</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2928221_tcl-55a300-60-pour-ce-tv-qled-en-forme-de-tableau-la-meilleure-alternative-au-the-frame-de-samsung</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2928221_tcl-55a300-60-pour-ce-tv-qled-en-forme-de-tableau-la-meilleure-alternative-au-the-frame-de-samsung</guid>
      <description>
Voil&#224; une belle opportunit&#233; pour s&#8217;&#233;quiper d&#8217;une TV premium &#224; prix cass&#233; : le TCL 55A300W, un TV qui se fond dans le d&#233;cor avec son design tableau et dont le prix devient nettement plus avantageux en passant de 1 305 euros &#224; 539 euros seulement. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ils sont bannis en France, ces 8 smartphones n&#8217;auraient jamais d&#251; atterrir dans votre poche</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2928461_lanfr-fait-le-menage-ces-8-smartphones-nauraient-jamais-du-atterrir-dans-votre-poche</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2928461_lanfr-fait-le-menage-ces-8-smartphones-nauraient-jamais-du-atterrir-dans-votre-poche</guid>
      <description>
L'ANFR vient de taper du poing sur la table. L'agence ordonne le retrait imm&#233;diat de huit smartphones du march&#233; fran&#231;ais. Entre des niveaux d'ondes qui d&#233;passent les bornes et des appareils vendus sans aucune certification europ&#233;enne.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackery lance un robot suiveur de soleil et une pergola photovolta&#239;que pour transformer votre jardin en centrale &#233;lectrique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2927715_jackery-devoile-un-robot-solaire-autonome-et-une-pergola-photovoltaique</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2927715_jackery-devoile-un-robot-solaire-autonome-et-une-pergola-photovoltaique</guid>
      <description>
On pensait avoir tout vu en mati&#232;re de batteries externes. Mais Jackery vient de dynamiter le CES 2026. Ici, ce n'est pas une simple station qu'on jette dans le coffre : la marque pr&#233;sente un robot autonome qui chasse le soleil et une pergola photovolta&#239;que pour votre jardin.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL d&#233;voile sa nouvelle gamme de TV X11L avec technologie SQD-Mini LED jusqu&#8217;&#224; 10 000 cd/m&#178;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tcl/2928939_tcl-devoile-sa-nouvelle-gamme-de-tv-x11l-avec-technologie-sqd-mini-led-jusqua-10-000-cd-m%c2%b2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tcl/2928939_tcl-devoile-sa-nouvelle-gamme-de-tv-x11l-avec-technologie-sqd-mini-led-jusqua-10-000-cd-m%c2%b2</guid>
      <description>
Le fabricant chinois TCL vient de r&#233;v&#233;ler au CES 2026 son nouveau t&#233;l&#233;viseur haut de gamme X11L, &#233;quip&#233; d'une technologie in&#233;dite baptis&#233;e SQD-Mini LED qui promet de repousser les limites de la qualit&#233; d'image. Avec une luminosit&#233; de 10 000 cd/m&#178;, une couverture compl&#232;te de l'espace colorim&#233;trique BT.2020 et jusqu'&#224; 20 736 zones de gradation, ce mod&#232;le entend battre des records.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft supprime l&#8217;activation des licences de Windows et d&#8217;Office par t&#233;l&#233;phone</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/microsoft-supprime-lactivation-des-licences-de-windows-et-doffice-par-telephone.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318166</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;activation des licences du syst&#232;me d&#8217;exploitation de Microsoft et de sa suite bureautique par t&#233;l&#233;phone n&#8217;est plus possible. La firme de Redmond a mis son serveur vocal d&#233;di&#233; hors service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perte de poids : Garmin lance une nouvelle fonction pour surveiller vos calories directement sur votre montre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/garmin/2928885_perte-de-poids-garmin-lance-une-nouvelle-fonction-pour-surveiller-vos-calories-directement-sur-votre-montre</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/garmin/2928885_perte-de-poids-garmin-lance-une-nouvelle-fonction-pour-surveiller-vos-calories-directement-sur-votre-montre</guid>
      <description>
Garmin a annonc&#233;, en ce d&#233;but janvier 2026, une nouvelle fonctionnalit&#233; li&#233;e aux conseils nutritionnels pour aider chacune et chacun &#224; atteindre son poids de forme en fonction de leurs objectifs. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cameron&#8217;s &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; crosses the $1B mark at the box office</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469008/james-camerons-avatar-fire-ash-crosses-1b-mark-box-office</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:38:37</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469008/james-camerons-avatar-fire-ash-crosses-1b-mark-box-office</guid>
      <description>The sci-fi epic is Hollywood&#8217;s No. 1 movie for the third straight week.
Hollywood kicked off 2026 with &#8220;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8221; atop the box office for the third straight week and with hopes for a blockbuster-filled year after a disappointing 2025.In three weeks of release, &#8220;Fire and Ash&#8221; has cleared $1 billion worldwide. The third chapter in James Cameron&#8217;s Pandora epic collected $40 million over its third weekend in North American theaters, according to studio estimates Sunday.&#8220;Fire and Ash&#8221; is doing its biggest business overseas; it&#8217;s grossed $777.1 million internationally thus far. The Walt ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici une balance connect&#233;e qui d&#233;tecte le pr&#233;diab&#232;te et l&#8217;hypertension</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/balance-connectee/2928895_withings-body-scan-2-officialisee-la-balance-connectee-qui-detecte-le-prediabete-et-lhypertension</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/balance-connectee/2928895_withings-body-scan-2-officialisee-la-balance-connectee-qui-detecte-le-prediabete-et-lhypertension</guid>
      <description>
Vous trouviez la premi&#232;re Body Scan ch&#232;re ? Attendez de voir la suite. Avec la Body Scan 2, Withings pousse le bouchon encore plus loin : d&#233;tection du pr&#233;diab&#232;te, suivi du stress et &#233;cran int&#233;gr&#233; &#224; la poign&#233;e. C'est techniquement impressionnant, mais &#224; 600 dollars, &#231;a commence &#224; faire cher le kilo en moins.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick up Amazon's latest Kindle on sale for $20 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/pick-up-amazons-latest-kindle-on-sale-for-20-off-183302556.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9865d5d-82c0-47b4-858f-2d61df88bf8c</guid>
      <description>If you're one of the many who made a New Year's resolution to read more, an ereader can help by putting your whole library (and more) at your fingertips wherever you are. While not as expensive as an iPad or another flagship tablet, these e-paper devices can be more expensive than you think, but right now you can save on one of our favorites. Amazon's base Kindle is on sale for $90 &#8212; that's $20 less than usual and only $10 more than its record-low price.
This made our list of the best ereaders, and for good reason. It's an iconic device that gets the job done. It doesn't have much by way of mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J. Crew&#8217;s new Olympic skiing capsule gives sportswear a &#8217;70s vibe shift</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465832/jcrew-olympic-skiing-collection-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:33:44</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465832/jcrew-olympic-skiing-collection-2026</guid>
      <description>J. Crew creative director Olympia Gayot on how the new collection was inspired by the Olympic archives, vintage design details, and winter gear with panache.
J. Crew just revealed its apparel collection with the U.S. Ski &amp; Snowboard teams for the 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympics. It&#8217;s an ode to retro ski aesthetics that even the most amateur athlete (or viewer) can get behind.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best tech announced at CES 2026 so far</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854159/ces-2026-best-tech-gadgets-smartphones-appliances-robots-tvs-ai-smart-home</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:29:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854159</guid>
      <description>Ahead of the CES show floor officially opening on Tuesday, January 6th, many companies have already announced new tech, gadgets, concepts, and AI-powered upgrades that will be released over this year. Yesterday's CES Unveiled event delivered even more announcements and reveals. If you're already struggling to keep on top of all the news coming out [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 opening night recap: All the early news you missed from Samsung and LG</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/ces-2026-opening-night-recap-all-the-early-news-you-missed-from-samsung-and-lg-142611832.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51a07897-d2d1-4e7c-942e-3b8bda98349f</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is still a day away from officially opening, but Sunday, January 4, delivered the first real wave of news. As has become tradition, the pre-show slate set the tone for the week ahead, anchored by Samsung&#8217;s annual First Look press conference and CES Unveiled, the latter of which where hundreds of companies previewed products before the show floor opens on January 6.Samsung once again dominated the early conversation with its First Look event, using the stage to outline how it sees AI shaping everything from TVs to home appliances in the year ahead. Rather than focusing on individual sp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk goes all-in on SMBs with new Grok Enterprise and Business offerings</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/elon-musk-goes-all-in-on-smbs-with-new-grok-enterprise-and-business-offerings</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CDuL6qVRRV34xpKmkagc6U</guid>
      <description>xAI has launched Business and Enterprise tiers for Grok with like-for-like pricing, but ChatGPT is still cheaper for casual users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's latest MagSafe charger is on sale for only $30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/apples-latest-magsafe-charger-is-on-sale-for-only-30-141707602.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ce1496f-1e48-428a-bb64-aefda025bc79</guid>
      <description>If you want a wireless charger for your iPhone and prefer to stick with Apple, Amazon has a sale that may pique your interest. The retailer is selling the one meter Apple Magsafe charger for $30, saving you $10 off the regular price, while also selling the two meter model for $40 ($10 off).&#160;


If you have an iPhone 16, iPhone 17 or iPhone Air, this cable can charge your device at 25W as long as it's connected to a 30W power adapter on the other end. While you'll need a more recent iPhone to get the fastest MagSafe charging speeds, the charger can wirelessly top up the battery of any iPhone fro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI's tiny action cam will soon get a big 8K rival from a mysterious Chinese company</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/action-cameras/djis-tiny-action-cam-will-soon-get-a-big-8k-rival-from-a-mysterious-chinese-company</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sn84x6AAp5CZXZgjNjQvTn</guid>
      <description>A new Chinese company is set to unveil a tiny modular action camera at CES 2026, and it could rival the DJI Osmo Nano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve South&#8217;s Valet is a handsome place to put your stuff</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854124/twelve-south-valet-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:14:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854124</guid>
      <description>For years, the accessory maker Twelve South has sold clever accessories for charging gadgets. Its new device, the Valet, is maybe its simplest idea ever: it's a nice-looking tray designed to be the place you drop your keys, sunglasses, and other pocket detritus, and offers a couple of ways to charge whatever needs to be [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#160;Edge is getting a Copilot-inspired redesign</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/854832/microsoft-edge-copilot-redesign-ui-features</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:14:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854832</guid>
      <description>Microsoft is preparing to launch a major UI refresh of its Edge browser soon. The software maker has started bringing the design language from Copilot to early Canary and Dev test versions of its Microsoft Edge browser. Design changes include a settings section that looks identical to the Copilot app, updated context menus, and an [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Egypt vs. Benin online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/egypt-benin-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ozhaKHRuKQ8IR3VGs7axp</guid>
      <description>How to watch AFCON for free. Live stream Egypt vs. Benin in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Au risque d&#8217;un nouveau clash avec Washington, Bruxelles remet la pression sur les g&#233;ants am&#233;ricains de la tech</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/au-risque-dun-nouveau-clash-avec-washington-bruxelles-remet-la-pression-sur-les-geants-americains-de-la-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318156</guid>
      <description>L'Europe n'a pas fini de jouer le r&#244;le de poil &#224; gratter dans la tech mondialis&#233;e et surtout am&#233;ricaine. Malgr&#233; les protestations des premiers int&#233;ress&#233;s et les gesticulations de la Maison Blanche, la Commission europ&#233;enne a bien l'intention de poursuivre, voire d'amplifier, les enqu&#234;tes contre les mastodontes US. Au risque de provoquer l'ire de Donald Trump....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your guide to the 2026 Winter Olympics, launching soon in Italy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468997/your-guide-2026-winter-olympics-launching-soon-italy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:06:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468997/your-guide-2026-winter-olympics-launching-soon-italy</guid>
      <description>The Games run from February 4&#8211;22. 
The countdown is on for the 2026 Winter Olympics in Italy.The torch relay is already underway and some of the top athletes are already making headlines. There are 16 sports in all, including some never seen before, and 116 gold medals are waiting to be awarded when competition begins in less than a month.This will be the most spread-out Winter Games in history: The two primary competition sites are the city of Milan and Cortina d&#8217;Ampezzo, the winter resort in the Dolomites that is more than 400 kilometers (250 miles) away by road. Athletes also will compete i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow the Lego CES 2026 press conference live right here</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/follow-the-lego-ces-2026-press-conference-live-right-here-130005940.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02a28a6-f21c-46c9-a5e0-dcff1b13d26a</guid>
      <description>picture alliance via Getty Images
The Lego Group is set to host its very first press conference at CES 2026 later today &#8212; but exactly what it plans to unveil is still under wraps. The iconic toy brick maker has offered no clues about what's on the agenda, leaving speculation wide open, from new video games to Formula 1 race cars.
Unlike nearly every other press event at CES today, however, Lego's event is not being livestreamed. Thankfully, Engadget is here to bridge the gap: Our own Nate Ingraham will be in the room at the Mandalay Bay in Las Vegas, liveblogging the event in real-time.&#160;
Follo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuite de donn&#233;es chez Ledger&#160;: le g&#233;ant fran&#231;ais des cryptos annonce un incident chez un prestataire</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fuite-donnees-chez-ledger-geant-francais-cryptos-annonce-incident-chez-prestataire.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318142</guid>
      <description>Ledger, le champion fran&#231;ais de la s&#233;curit&#233; des cryptos, est &#224; nouveau victime d'une fuite de donn&#233;es. Les informations personnelles de clients ayant pass&#233; commande sur Ledger.com ont &#233;t&#233; compromises. On peut redouter une nouvelle d'arnaques... ou de tentatives d'extorsion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Making-of Doc Hits Netflix Next Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-stranger-things-making-of-doc-hits-netflix-next-week-2000705046</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705046</guid>
      <description>'One Last Adventure: The Making of Stranger Things 5' may not answer all your burning questions, but it looks like an affectionate, emotional ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Makes Dashcams a Dealership Add-On</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mitsubishi-makes-dashcams-a-dealership-add-on-2000705268</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705268</guid>
      <description>The common aftermarket purchase becomes part of the carbuying process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockly&#8217;s new smart locks will support Matter and NFC</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851157/lockly-smart-lock-matter-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851157</guid>
      <description>Lockly has introduced a series of smart locks that have native Matter compatibility, meaning that they will be able to be used across different smart home systems. The Affirm Series of smart locks will come in both deadbolt and latch editions. What's more, the locks will support several ways to allow access, including not only [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google previews new Gemini features for TV at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/google-previews-new-gemini-features-for-tv-at-ces-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079326</guid>
      <description>Google TV will let you ask Gemini to find and edit your photos, adjust your TV settings and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL launches next-gen SQD mini-LED TV at CES &#8211; the &#8216;best TV in the market&#8217; for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/tcl-launches-next-gen-sqd-mini-led-tv-at-ces-the-best-tv-in-the-market-for-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fywi9UH3Z6N8vHa8gVXeaT</guid>
      <description>TCL launched the X11L SQD mini-LED, its flagship TV for 2026, at CES, along with a new RGB mini-LED TV and a budget mini-LED TV series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Fallout season 2 episode 4 on Prime Video?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/amazon-prime-video/what-is-the-release-date-for-fallout-season-2-episode-4-on-prime-video</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VpGNX6NTvkoNBazDWjHnSd</guid>
      <description>Fallout season 2's next episode will be with us shortly &#8211; here are all of the release details you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google TV is getting Gemini-powered photo editing at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/google-tv-is-getting-gemini-powered-photo-editing-at-ces-140000172.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7d74536-4d4c-4056-aa67-2bdef7eeddcc</guid>
      <description>Google is working even more Gemini features into Google TV at CES 2026. The company demoed how the AI assistant would work on its TV platform at last year's show, and this time, it's expanding the AI's features to make it easier to do things like adjust your TV's settings or edit photos.The ability to view photos stored in Google Photos has long been a feature of Google TV, but as part of this new update, Gemini will be able to do a lot more with them, too. Google says Gemini will be able to search your Google Photos library for specific people and moments, and remix those photos into differen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Saratoga Spring Water is suddenly everywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468528/why-saratoga-spring-water-is-suddenly-everywhere</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468528/why-saratoga-spring-water-is-suddenly-everywhere</guid>
      <description>Backed by Primo Brands, the iconic blue bottle is being repositioned as both aspirational and accessible.
If you&#8217;ve been noticing that cobalt-hued water bottles have started to pop up everywhere you&#8217;re not alone. The water has recently made an appearance on shelves at major retailers including Whole Foods and 7-Eleven, starred in viral social media videos created by fitness influencer Ashton Hall, adorned on tables at the Golden Globes, and beginning this week, will star in a fresh new advertising campaign featuring WNBA point guard Skylar Diggins....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo is unveiling a new mobile gaming pad at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/8bitdo-is-unveiling-a-new-mobile-gaming-pad-at-ces-134555603.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86c3be84-9f19-4df9-9e16-905e423e4c5b</guid>
      <description>Gaming peripheral company 8BitDo is teasing a new smartphone gaming pad that seems aimed exclusively at portrait-mode gamers. In a post on X, the company says the 8BitDo FlipPad will debut in the summer of 2026 and will be compatible with iOS and Android devices. It also mentions the peripheral is "officially supported by Apple."
The post doesn't give too much away, as the company will be premiering the FlipPad at CES this week. A short, rendered video shows that the mobile gaming peripheral connects via USB-C, and then flips upward on a hinge to lay flat against the bottom portion of a user's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s plan to take over Venezuela&#8217;s oil industry faces major hurdles. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469000/trumps-plan-take-over-venezuelas-oil-industry-faces-major-hurdles-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T13:39:56</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469000/trumps-plan-take-over-venezuelas-oil-industry-faces-major-hurdles-heres-why</guid>
      <description>Massive investment will be required to overcome an infrastructure in disrepair.
President Donald Trump&#8217;s plan to take control of Venezuela&#8217;s oil industry and ask American companies to revitalize it after capturing President Nicol&#225;s Maduro in a raid isn&#8217;t likely to have a significant immediate impact on oil prices.Venezuela&#8217;s oil industry is in disrepair after years of neglect and international sanctions, so it could take years and major investments before production can increase dramatically. But some analysts are optimistic that Venezuela could double or triple its current output of about 1.1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just don't immerse it: Jackery reveals world's lightest kWh-capacity IP65-rated portable power station &#8212; and it can even withstand a 1m fall</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/just-dont-immerse-it-jackery-reveals-worlds-lightest-kwh-capacity-ip65-rated-portable-power-station-and-it-can-even-withstand-a-1m-fall</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zak5Tc5G4hP5gRUweaZwF7</guid>
      <description>The Jackery Explorer 1500 Ultra is a professional-grade portable power station offering high-capacity energy, rapid recharge, IP65 durability, and extreme environmental resilience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirTag deal: Get a four-pack of the Bluetooth trackers for only $65</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airtag-deal-get-a-four-pack-of-the-bluetooth-trackers-for-only-65-202333050.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Apple keeps most of its product pricing on a tight leash, but we do see the company's AirTags go on sale pretty frequently. Another cost cut has come around for this item just in time for the holidays. Amazon is currently selling a four-pack of AirTags for $65. At a third off the regular cost, that price is pretty close to the record low discount of $63 we've seen for these Bluetooth trackers.


AirTags can be useful for people who travel frequently, helping you to keep track of essentials like your passport as well as a way to keep tabs on luggage while you're on the go. If you do purchase so...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
