<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:23:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jensen Huang Is Begging You to Stop Being So Negative About AI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jensen-huang-is-begging-you-to-stop-being-so-negative-about-ai-2000709335</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709335</guid>
      <description>"[It's] extremely hurtful, frankly, and I think we've done a lot of damage," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta plans to lay off hundreds of metaverse employees this week</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860984/meta-reality-labs-layoffs-metaverse</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T17:14:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860984</guid>
      <description>Meta's Reality Labs team is expected to lose around 10 percent of its staff, with layoffs concentrated on the division's metaverse employees, as reported by The New York Times. The layoffs are apparently a side effect of Meta's AI ambitions, which are pulling focus away from its virtual reality division. According to the Times, Meta's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Agent&#8217;s Sworn Testimony Contradicts Claims ICE&#8217;s Jonathan Ross Made Under Oath</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/fbi-agents-sworn-testimony-contradicts-claims-ices-jonathan-ross-made-under-oath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696539eea5fd331911189028</guid>
      <description>The testimony also calls into question whether Ross failed to follow his training during the incident in which he reportedly shot and killed Minnesota citizen Renee Good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An App Called &#8216;Are You Dead?&#8217; Is Climbing the Apple Charts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/an-app-called-are-you-dead-is-climbing-the-apple-charts-2000709373</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709373</guid>
      <description>The simple app is now the top paid app on China&#8217;s Apple App Store and has reached the sixth spot in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD&#8217;s FSR Redstone Frame Generation tested: image quality gets a boost, but there&#8217;s one deal-breaking catch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/amds-fsr-redstone-frame-generation-tested-image-quality-gets-a-boost-but-theres-one-deal-breaking-catch</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdRwPupNxk5hLASbSv2uQf</guid>
      <description>AMD's FSR Redstone Frame Generation image quality via Razer's eGPU dock is impressive, but is it enough to compete with Nvidia?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok&#8217;s Sexual Deepfakes Will Become Illegal in the UK This Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/groks-sexual-deepfakes-will-become-illegal-in-the-uk-this-week-2000709212</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709212</guid>
      <description>"The content which has circulated on X is vile," the UK technology secretary Liz Kendall said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Amazon bought Bee, an AI wearable</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/why-amazon-bought-bee-an-ai-wearable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081988</guid>
      <description>Amazon explains where its wearable Bee fits in and whether it will merge with Alexa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our favorite UGreen 3-in-1 wireless charger is 32 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/our-favorite-ugreen-3-in-1-wireless-charger-is-32-percent-off-right-now-214707069.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc4c398-0e79-409e-bf43-095a0740d354</guid>
      <description>Now that the winter holidays are well and truly past, now's the perfect time to take stock of your tech setup. If you were gifted (or gifted yourself) some new gear in December, make sure that you've got the proper accessories to keep that gear performing at its best. If a new way to power all those batteries would be a benefit, Amazon's currently running a discount on an excellent wireless charging pad. The UGREEN MagFlow Qi2 3-in-1 Charger Station 25W is on sale for $95. That's only a little bit above the lowest price we've ever seen for the product (which was $90), and it's still a 32 perce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngest UK Dementia Case Dies at 24</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youngest-uk-dementia-case-dies-at-24-2000709304</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709304</guid>
      <description>Less than two dozen cases of extremely early-onset frontotemporal dementia have been documented worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George R.R. Martin Still Hasn&#8217;t Finished &#8216;Winds of Winter,&#8217; but New Dunk and Egg Stories Are on His Mind</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/george-rr-martin-new-dunk-and-egg-game-of-thrones-winds-of-winter-2000709355</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709355</guid>
      <description>The 'Game of Thrones' author has the highly anticipated fantasy book on his to-do list, but he's understandably excited about 'A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These two budget airlines just announced a major merger&#8212;Amazon&#8217;s involved too</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473081/sun-country-allegiant-budget-airline-major-merger-amazon-involved-too</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473081/sun-country-allegiant-budget-airline-major-merger-amazon-involved-too</guid>
      <description>The airline industry continues to become more siloed. A new $1.5 billion deal is the latest.
Shares of the budget airline Sun Country were flying today after the carrier announced an upcoming merger with Las Vegas-based competitor Allegiant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At the 2026 Golden Globes, politics stayed on the red carpet</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473204/golden-globes-2026-politics-mostly-stayed-on-the-red-carpet</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473204/golden-globes-2026-politics-mostly-stayed-on-the-red-carpet</guid>
      <description>With awards season upon us, the Globes may have just offered a glimpse into the tepid commentary that viewers can expect during Trump&#8217;s second term. 
On the red carpet of the 2026 Golden Globes, several celebrities used their garments as vehicles of protest against Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) and spoke openly about their dissent against the current Trump administration. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg says Meta is launching its own AI infrastructure initiative</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/mark-zuckerberg-says-meta-is-launching-its-own-ai-infrastructure-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082043</guid>
      <description>Meta is ramping up its efforts to build out its AI capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid Robots Are Here&#8230; and Embarrassingly Bad at Being Our Servants</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/humanoid-robots-are-here-and-embarrassingly-bad-at-being-our-servants-ces-2026-2000709300</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709300</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 showed us the useless humanoid robots are nowhere close to doing your robot chores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Fed&#8217;s independence from the White House is guarded so closely</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473467/federal-reserve-independence-history</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473467/federal-reserve-independence-history</guid>
      <description>The importance of an independent Fed was cemented for most economists after the&#160;extended inflation spike&#160;of the 1970s and early 1980s.
The Justice Department has threatened the Federal Reserve with a criminal indictment over the testimony of Fed Chair&#160;Jerome Powell&#160;this summer regarding its building renovations, Powell said over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia's latest RTX 5090 GPU card has an audio jack &#8212; yes a headphone socket, on a video card, but no wooden trim or SSD like its predecessor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/nvidias-latest-rtx-5090-gpu-card-has-an-audio-jack-yes-a-headphone-socket-on-a-video-card-but-no-wooden-trim-or-ssd-like-its-predecessor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YNSP5XFAgAmYqtHWFYzJKd</guid>
      <description>The Asus ProArt RTX 5090 targets creative professionals with its compact dimensions, 32GB of GDDR7 memory, and an unexpected audio jack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aldi is opening 180+ new stores &#8212; here&#8217;s what&#8217;s driving the sudden surge</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473080/aldi-is-opening-180-new-stores-heres-whats-driving-the-sudden-surge</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473080/aldi-is-opening-180-new-stores-heres-whats-driving-the-sudden-surge</guid>
      <description>Aldi&#8217;s rapid expansion reflects how shoppers are trading brand names and massive aisles for simplicity and savings.
Americans stressed by high grocery bills have one bright spot to look forward to in 2026. Value-minded grocery chain Aldi is coming to more cities around the country, with 180 new stores set to open in the U.S. this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta taps Dina Powell McCormick as president and vice chairman</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473451/meta-dina-powell-mccormick-president-trump-adviser</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:12:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473451/meta-dina-powell-mccormick-president-trump-adviser</guid>
      <description>Powell McCormick was &#8216;deeply engaged&#8217; in accelerating&#160;Meta&#8217;s artificial intelligence push&#160;across platforms.
Facebook owner&#160;Meta&#160;has named Dina Powell McCormick, a former Trump administration adviser and longtime finance executive, as president and vice chairman of the tech giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why X changed its Iranian flag emoji</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473073/why-x-changed-its-iranian-flag-emoji</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:05:41</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473073/why-x-changed-its-iranian-flag-emoji</guid>
      <description>The social media platform redesigned the emoji to a version of the flag popular with opposition groups as anti-government protests sweep the country.
Iran hasn&#8217;t changed its flag, but the emoji for it has changed on X, the social network previously known as Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing markets where homebuyers are gaining power heading into spring 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473197/housing-market-where-homebuyers-are-gaining-power-heading-into-spring-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473197/housing-market-where-homebuyers-are-gaining-power-heading-into-spring-2026</guid>
      <description>In total, 17 states are back above pre-pandemic 2019 housing inventory levels. Here&#8217;s what that tells us.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego's first Pok&#233;mon sets are now available for pre-order</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/legos-first-pokemon-sets-are-now-available-for-pre-order-205527102.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d92e386-e894-457c-8939-f0e4c78dcfdd</guid>
      <description>We learned last March that Lego and Pok&#233;mon would be joining forces and the first results of their partnership are here. Pre-orders for all three kits are open now, with an expected ship date of February 27. As one might have guessed from the lightning bolts on the previous promotional image, one of the debut pocket monsters getting the brick treatment is Pikachu, complete with a Pok&#233; Ball. The 2,050-piece kit can be built to show Pikachu either leaping out of the open Pok&#233; Ball into battle or at rest staring up at the builder, closed Pok&#233; Ball between his paws. The Pikachu kit costs $200.
The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Pizza Week is here &#8212; here&#8217;s where to save on pizza</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473124/national-pizza-week-is-here-heres-where-to-save-on-pizza</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T20:49:14</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473124/national-pizza-week-is-here-heres-where-to-save-on-pizza</guid>
      <description>Chains like Casey&#8217;s, California Pizza Kitchen, and others are competing for attention with limited-time specials.
There are many made-up celebrations these days, but at least National Pizza Week delivers something tasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic announces Claude for Healthcare following OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT Health reveal</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/anthropic-announces-claude-for-healthcare-following-openais-chatgpt-health-reveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082015</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's Claude for Healthcare is unveiled about a week after OpenAI announced its ChatGPT Health product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Freezes $182 Million in Stablecoins as Reports Point to Heavy Crypto Use by Venezuela</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tether-freezes-182-million-in-stablecoins-as-reports-point-to-heavy-crypto-use-by-venezuela-2000709276</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709276</guid>
      <description>There's a new spotlight on crypto that's used to avoid sanctions after the abduction of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ&#8217;s probe into Powell sparks backlash over the Fed&#8217;s independence</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473378/powell-trump-doj-investigation-backlash-federal-reserve-independence</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T20:42:41</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473378/powell-trump-doj-investigation-backlash-federal-reserve-independence</guid>
      <description>Powell quickly found a growing number of defenders among Republicans in the Senate.
The Trump administration&#8217;s&#160;criminal investigation&#160;of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell appeared on Monday to be emboldening defenders of the U.S. central bank against the efforts of President Donald Trump to control the Fed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble founder says his new company is &#8216;not a startup&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/pebble-founder-says-his-new-company-is-not-a-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080005</guid>
      <description>Pebble's founder talks about how his new company is doing things differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell revives its XPS laptops after a boneheaded rebranding</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/dell-revives-its-xps-laptops-after-a-boneheaded-rebranding-001028029.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fcc565f-aee8-413a-b8f8-0cc5f443bc32</guid>
      <description>Last year, Dell killed off all of its PC brands, including the iconic XPS lineup, and replaced them with a simplified naming scheme. It was a move meant to make it easier for people to discern between the company's many brands, but in reality, it just just made the company's lineup even more confusing. We called it an unforced error at the time, but after seeing how much Dell's PC market share fell over 2025, it's fair to say that rebranding was an absolute marketing disaster. So, with its tail between its legs, Dell has returned to CES some welcome news for its fans: XPS lives! And the compan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 proved the PC industry is hosed this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/ces-2026-proved-the-pc-industry-is-hosed-this-year-174500314.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db798e3a-f4ab-4554-828a-98500fcc1f8f</guid>
      <description>Dell's XPS 14 currently costs over $2,000. An AMD executive predicts that PC builders will likely make piecemeal upgrades this year, instead of building entirely new systems. And new AI supercomputers from NVIDIA and AMD are gobbling up the RAM market. At CES 2026, it was hard not to notice the dire year ahead for the computing industry, one that will likely lead to higher prices and more limited availability for consumer goods across the board.Really, though, the show just confirmed what was apparent since RAM prices skyrocketed over the last few months, driven by demand from AI datacenters. ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
