<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:30:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's iPhone Air MagSafe battery is cheaper than ever right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-iphone-air-magsafe-battery-is-cheaper-than-ever-right-now-144516217.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b81fb587-99ff-4a0a-8491-b9b9460d3e9a</guid>
      <description>We found the iPhone Air to have a pretty decent battery life for such a thin-and-light phone, somewhere in the region of 27 hours if you&#8217;re continuously streaming video. But it's still a phone, arguably your most used device on a daily basis, so you may need to top it up during the day if you're using it constantly. That&#8217;s where Apple&#8217;s iPhone Air MagSafe battery pack comes in, and it&#8217;s currently on sale for $79.


This accessory only works with the iPhone Air, but much like the phone it attaches to, it&#8217;s extremely slim at 7.5mmm, so crucially doesn&#8217;t add so much bulk when attached that it def...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; le Deepal S05 : pourquoi ce SUV &#233;lectrique chinois rival du Tesla Model Y vendu en Europe nous a laiss&#233; sur notre faim</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2926673_on-a-teste-le-deepal-s05-pourquoi-ce-suv-electrique-chinois-rival-du-tesla-model-y-vendu-en-europe-nous-a-laisse-sur-notre-faim</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2926673_on-a-teste-le-deepal-s05-pourquoi-ce-suv-electrique-chinois-rival-du-tesla-model-y-vendu-en-europe-nous-a-laisse-sur-notre-faim</guid>
      <description>
On a test&#233; le nouveau SUV &#233;lectrique de Changan vendu en Europe : le Deepal S05. Il se positionne face &#224; la Tesla Model Y. Si en Chine, cette voiture &#233;lectrique est int&#233;ressante, vous allez voir qu'en Europe, c'est une toute autre histoire. Voici notre avis.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I hate my AI pet with every fiber of my being</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/877858/life-with-casio-moflin-robot-ai-pet</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877858</guid>
      <description>After a few weeks living with Casio's AI-powered pet, Moflin, I finally understand why my mother hated my Furby so much. The fuzzy, guinea-pig-adjacent puffball fits snugly in the palm of my hand. It's undeniably cute, in a weird kind of way, but the second it starts to squeak or twitch, I am hit with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logitech&#8217;s new Superstrike is a faster, more customizable gaming mouse</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/879221/logitech-gpro-x2-superstrike-gaming-mouse-pc-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879221</guid>
      <description>Enthusiast gaming keyboard tech has made the jump to gaming mice - well, to one gaming mouse so far. The $179.99 Logitech G Pro X2 Superstrike is the first to feature analog sensors that use induction to register clicks faster than microswitches used in many mice. Those sensors allow for a host of cool features [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s first-gen AirTags are still worth buying now that they&#8217;re $16 apiece</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/879325/apple-airtag-1st-generation-presidents-day-sale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879325</guid>
      <description>With Apple&#8217;s second-gen AirTags now widely available, we&#8217;re already seeing inventory of the first-gen model begin to dwindle. Case in point? Amazon is no longer selling a single AirTag, and it&#8217;s unclear when &#8212; or if &#8212; the retailer will restock the first-gen model. Thankfully, you can still grab a four-pack of the first-gen location [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Monday, February 16 (game #1484)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-16-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ym8iUHMFMSbH4oyFNbZWxj</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Monday, February 16 (game #981)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-16-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXpcaeu4ToccFdPU9zQzk3</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Monday, February 16 (game #715)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-16-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Ygpcbu5k43vNV2JLN4sZbn</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A fresh outlook and moment of lightness' &#8212; how 'grounding and energizing' Spearmint became KitchenAid's official color of 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/small-appliances/a-fresh-outlook-and-moment-of-lightness-how-grounding-and-energizing-spearmint-became-kitchenaids-official-color-of-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9Uomjfy7cCsftKsv7GaZ7i</guid>
      <description>Brittni Pertijs, Design Manager for Color, Material and Finish at Whirlpool, explains the multi-year process of choosing the definitive hue of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning VMware exit into a strategic advantage</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/turning-vmware-exit-into-a-strategic-advantage</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oo6PWn2GP3L3CvqQhCgprL</guid>
      <description>Exiting legacy cloud platforms can modernize and future-proof infrastructure while saving money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get a four-pack of first-gen AirTags on sale for only $64</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-a-four-pack-of-first-gen-airtags-on-sale-for-only-64-163619270.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e745850-e368-4111-83ab-157ddbe84ac4</guid>
      <description>Good deals on Apple products aren&#8217;t as frequent as we&#8217;d like them to be, but if there&#8217;s one of the company&#8217;s products that does seem to enjoy pretty regular price cuts, it&#8217;s the AirTag. Right now you can pick up a four-pack of Apple&#8217;s diminutive first-generation Bluetooth trackers for $64, which translates to 35 percent off and a near record low price.
Bear in mind that this deal brings the price per AirTag down to about $16 if you were to buy them individually, and when not on sale they usually cost $29. 


If you use Apple devices and consider yourself to be a serial thing-misplacer, AirTags...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darty fait une belle offre sur ce SSD T7 de Samsung avec de 2 To et inclut m&#234;me un cadeau</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2976345_darty-fait-une-belle-offre-sur-ce-ssd-t7-de-samsung-avec-de-2-to-et-inclut-meme-un-cadeau</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2976345_darty-fait-une-belle-offre-sur-ce-ssd-t7-de-samsung-avec-de-2-to-et-inclut-meme-un-cadeau</guid>
      <description>
Alors que les prix du stockage repartent &#224; la hausse en 2026, ce pack sign&#233; Samsung tombe &#224; pic pour ceux qui veulent faire des &#233;conomies sans sacrifier la qualit&#233;. Il r&#233;unit le SSD portable T7 avec 2 To de capacit&#233; et une carte microSD Evo Plus de 64 Go, le tout &#224; seulement&#160;219&#8201;euros au lieu de 249&#8201;euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day sales 2026: The best tech deals to shop this weekend from Apple, Sony, Anker and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/presidents-day-sales-2026-the-best-tech-deals-to-shop-this-weekend-from-apple-sony-anker-and-others-163000988.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba4f502-86ba-4c79-a2ff-b27b6e52c38b</guid>
      <description>You can find a lot of good deals for Presidents&#8217; Day, but to say it&#8217;s a tech-deal boon would be an overstatement. The best Presidents&#8217; Day deals are usually on mattresses, appliances and furniture, but you can find some decent tech sales thrown in as well. This year, Presidents&#8217; Day comes right after Valentine&#8217;s Day and Super Bowl 2026, which means there are even more chances to save as sales and discounts overlap. If you&#8217;re looking for a new streaming device, a fresh iPad or an upgraded vacuum so you can enter the spring-cleaning season properly, we have you covered. These are the best Presid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 8 on Hulu and Disney+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hulu/tell-me-lies-season-3-episode-8-release-date-time-disney-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZdUAX3uwvvZB3Uv7eRKwue</guid>
      <description>The end is in sight but it's not going to be pretty. When does Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 8 air on Hulu and Disney+?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 21 best Presidents' Day TV deals of 2026 &#8212; my top recommendations if you're buying a new display</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-21-best-presidents-day-tv-deals-of-2026-my-top-recommendations-if-youre-buying-a-new-display</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PcjVRU5VSWUsiDMx4WWUSb</guid>
      <description>I'm rounding up today's 21 best Presidents' Day TV sales of 2026 that I personally recommend buying if you're looking to buy a new display.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How George Washington&#8217;s mistakes in Pennsylvania&#8217;s wilderness provided valuable leadership lessons</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490268/how-george-washingtons-mistakes-pennsylvanias-wilderness-provided-valuable-leadership-lessons</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T14:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490268/how-george-washingtons-mistakes-pennsylvanias-wilderness-provided-valuable-leadership-lessons</guid>
      <description>This Presidents&#8217; Day, there are lessons to be learned from the father of our country&#8217;s worst moments. 
This Presidents&#8217; Day, I&#8217;ve been thinking about George Washington&#8212;not at his finest hour, but possibly at his worst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the 512GB Samsung P9 microSD Express card for 33 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-the-512gb-samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-for-33-percent-off-right-now-143849920.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7c1c9b1-8762-4b3b-bd34-558e13eba66f</guid>
      <description>MicroSD Express cards are still a little hard to find, considering they're pretty new and only really started becoming popular last year once the Switch 2 came out. These upgraded versions of microSD cards are the only ones compatible with the Switch 2 for expanding its storage, os if you're already starting to feel the crunch on your console, it's worth picking one up. Samsung's P9 microSD Express card is on sale right now &#8212; you can grab the 512GB version of $80, which is 33 percent off and one of the best prices we've seen.
The P9 boasts transfer speeds of up to 800MB/s, making moving games ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
