<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:33:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This UGreen 3-in-1 wireless charger is 32 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/this-ugreen-3-in-1-wireless-charger-is-32-percent-off-right-now-214707378.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc4c398-0e79-409e-bf43-095a0740d354</guid>
      <description>You can easily spruce up your nightstand or desk by decluttering a bit, replacing some of those annoying charging cables with a good wireless charging setup. One of our favorites that can handle three devices at once is the UGREEN MagFlow Qi2 3-in-1 Charger Station 25W. Normally $140, it's on sale right now for $95; that's 32 percent off and only about $5 more than its record-low price.


This is our top pick for a 3-in-1 charging pad thanks to its versatility. The UGREEN can work equally well as a permanent fixture in your home or act as a portable charging station. It boasts a foldable desig...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disclosure of Aliens Could Cause a Bitcoin Rush, Former Bank of England Analyst Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-disclosure-of-aliens-could-cause-a-bitcoin-rush-former-bank-of-england-analyst-says-2000711471</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711471</guid>
      <description>She warned of "extreme price volatility in financial markets due to catastrophising or euphoria, and a collapse in confidence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington is the latest state pursuing an age verification law for porn sites</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/washington-is-the-latest-state-pursuing-an-age-verification-law-for-porn-sites-174423529.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e41e4a87-0fb9-438f-9be1-e6f6d924d592</guid>
      <description>Washington state residents may soon be forced to produce IDs before getting onto websites with pornographic content. Within the state's House of Representatives, Rep. Mari Leavitt introduced House Bill 2112, which is informally known as the Keep Our Children Safe Act. Similar to the initiatives seen in other states, the bill proposes to restrict access to "online sexual material harmful" to anyone under 18.
In practical terms, those living in Washington state could see websites asking for digital identification or demanding the user go through an age verification system that requests a governm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This may be the reason why Netflix ditched wireless casting &#8211; but Google is still backing the tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/this-may-be-the-reason-why-netflix-ditched-wireless-casting-but-google-is-still-backing-the-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jK3p7RGiamFCUayFU9nvRc</guid>
      <description>Netflix dropping Google Cast support for modern Google TV devices may be because it wasn't being used much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Zootopia 2&#8217; Is Hollywood&#8217;s Biggest Animated Movie Ever</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/zootopia-2-is-the-biggest-animated-movie-ever-2000711544</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711544</guid>
      <description>The world has had 'Zootopia 2' fever for months, and now it's broken the biggest milestone for animated movies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TechCrunch Mobility: &#8216;Physical AI&#8217; enters the hype machine</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/18/techcrunch-mobility-physical-ai-enters-the-hype-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083423</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to TechCrunch Mobility, your hub for all things &#8220;future of transportation.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads edges out X in daily mobile users, new data shows</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/18/threads-edges-out-x-in-daily-mobile-users-new-data-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083450</guid>
      <description>Threads&#8217; daily mobile usage has quietly surpassed X as Meta leans on cross-promotion, creator tools and fast feature rollouts &#8212; even as X faces fresh controversies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans vs Patriots Free Streams: TV Channels and Preview for NFL 2026 Divisional Round Game</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/houston-texans-vs-new-england-patriots-nfl-2026-divisional-round-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dNQc3kA6zffkDAHorwhDRf</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Texans vs Patriots live streams for FREE from anywhere, in the NFL Divisional Round clash at Gillette Stadium in Foxborough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 4 on Hulu and Disney+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hulu/tell-me-lies-season-3-episode-4-release-date-time-disney-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcEtx8zfp7DAveBg6GrrGc</guid>
      <description>Last week's Hulu premiere surprised us with the first three episodes, but when will Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 4 be released?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01x6w2GJ5DTY19LQCP9NGqI</guid>
      <description>How to watch Africa Cup of Nations for free. Live stream the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Edge 70 vs iPhone Air&#160;: quel smartphone ultrafin choisir&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/versus/2933189_motorola-edge-70-vs-iphone-air-quel-smartphone-ultrafin-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/versus/2933189_motorola-edge-70-vs-iphone-air-quel-smartphone-ultrafin-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Les smartphones ultrafins seront-ils l'une des grosses tendances de 2026&#160;? En tout cas, le choix n'est pas encore d&#233;bordant, et seules quelques r&#233;f&#233;rences se pr&#233;sentent pour le moment &#224;&#160;nous. Comment choisir entre le Moto Edge 70 et l'iPhone Air&#160;?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New users can get a year of one of our favorite budgeting apps for only $50</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/new-users-can-get-a-year-of-one-of-our-favorite-budgeting-apps-for-only-50-204507576.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764214b-3509-4628-8631-8692fa12e904</guid>
      <description>A new year is the perfect time to get your spending in order, and if you're not trying to build your own spreadsheet, budgeting apps are one of the best ways to do it. To save yourself some money in the process, you can pick up a year-long subscription to Monarch Money, one of Engadget's favorite budgeting apps, for just $50 if you use code NEWYEAR2026 at checkout and you're a new subscriber. That's a 50 percent discount on the service's normal $100 price.
Monarch Money makes for a capable and detailed budgeting companion. You can use the service via apps for iOS, Android, iPadOS or the web, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#8217;s first Windows 11 update of 2026 stopped some computers from shutting down</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864032/microsofts-out-of-band-windows-11-update-bug</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T11:46:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864032</guid>
      <description>Microsoft released its first security update of 2026 for Windows 11 on January 13th. Just four days later, it was forced to release an emergency out-of-band update to fix some pretty serious bugs, the first one introduced. The security patch was stopping some systems from shutting down or hibernating properly, and also preventing some users [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici un aspirateur fran&#231;ais qui veut ringardiser Dyson sur un point pr&#233;cis : on a pu l&#8217;approcher</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/aspirateurs-balais-sans-fil/2946215_voici-un-aspirateur-francais-increvable-qui-veut-ringardiser-dyson-on-a-pu-lapprocher</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/aspirateurs-balais-sans-fil/2946215_voici-un-aspirateur-francais-increvable-qui-veut-ringardiser-dyson-on-a-pu-lapprocher</guid>
      <description>
Et si vous n'aviez plus jamais besoin de racheter un aspirateur ? C'est le pari de Deglace, une startup tricolore qui a profit&#233; du CES 2026 pour mettre en avant son premier mod&#232;le : le Fraction. Entre sa conception 100 % modulaire et ses mat&#233;riaux a&#233;ronautiques, cet appareil ne se veut pas seulement durable : il est pens&#233; pour &#234;tre p&#233;renne et r&#233;parable &#224; vie, loin de l'obsolescence programm&#233;e qui ronge le secteur.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's latest 25W MagSafe charger is on sale for $30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-latest-25w-magsafe-charger-is-on-sale-for-30-141707297.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ce1496f-1e48-428a-bb64-aefda025bc79</guid>
      <description>If you want a wireless charger for your iPhone and prefer to stick with Apple, Amazon has a sale that may pique your interest. The retailer is selling the one meter Apple Magsafe charger for $30, saving you $10 off the regular price, while also selling the two meter model for $40 ($10 off).


If you have an iPhone 16, iPhone 17 or iPhone Air, this cable can charge your device at 25W as long as it's connected to a 30W power adapter on the other end. While you'll need a more recent iPhone to get the fastest MagSafe charging speeds, the charger can wirelessly top up the battery of any iPhone from...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
