<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:39:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Finally, I&#8217;ve Found the Perfect Switch 2 Controller</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/finally-ive-found-the-perfect-switch-2-controller-2000718700</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718700</guid>
      <description>Gulikit's TT Pro and TT Max have many more stick and button options than a Switch 2 Pro controller, and they have one feature no other gamepad does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google and Microsoft-backed Terradot acquires carbon removal competitor</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/google-and-microsoft-backed-terradot-acquires-carbon-removal-competitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090493</guid>
      <description>The acquisition could mark the beginning of consolidation in the carbon removal market since removal costs remain higher than buyers would like to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe AI agents can be lawyers after all</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/maybe-ai-agents-can-be-lawyers-after-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090494</guid>
      <description>This week's release of Opus 4.6 shook up the Agentic leaderboards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turns Out Congestion Pricing Has Been Good for Drivers in the Suburbs, Too</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/turns-out-congestion-pricing-has-been-good-for-drivers-in-the-suburbs-too-2000718956</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718956</guid>
      <description>Traffic has improved inside and out of Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Knight Insisted Skeletor Had His Skull Face for &#8216;Masters of the Universe&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/travis-knight-insisted-skeletor-had-his-skull-face-for-masters-of-the-universe-2000719056</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719056</guid>
      <description>The director was not going to make the film without the Skeletor we know and love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worried you can&#8217;t wow your loved one with a Valentine&#8217;s day latte? I&#8217;ve found the perfect automatic coffee machines for you &#8211; even if your milk-frothing game is as mid as mine</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/worried-you-cant-wow-your-loved-one-with-a-valentines-day-latte-ive-found-the-perfect-automatic-coffee-machines-for-you-even-if-your-milk-frothing-game-is-as-mid-as-mine</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SLFCyMBojHPsdthArX4mk5</guid>
      <description>Tired of collapsing foam and milk spatter? I&#8217;ve assembled all of my favorite automatic coffee machines for reducing the fuss when frothing coffee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite TV to Watch the Winter Olympics Is on Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-s90f-qd-oled-tv-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69862655115bb05a5bf45c23</guid>
      <description>Forget the Super Bowl, Samsung&#8217;s Fantastic S90F QD-OLED TV is on a sweet sale just in time for the Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Outbreak in South Carolina Linked to Brain Swelling in Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/measles-outbreak-in-south-carolina-linked-to-brain-swelling-in-kids-2000718913</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718913</guid>
      <description>Several children have come down with serious complications like encephalitis and pneumonia, state health officials reported this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ loses access to Dolby Vision and HDR10+ in some European countries</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/disney-loses-access-to-dolby-vision-and-hdr10-in-some-european-countries-193930091.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c91c8c4-5448-4bca-accb-c31c1671c8d2</guid>
      <description>Disney+ subscribers in some European countries have lost access to advanced HDR features like Dolby Vision and HDR10+, TechRadar and FlatpanelsHD report. The issue was first spotted by German Disney+ subscribers on Reddit, but currently also impacts subscribers in Portugal, Poland, France and the Netherlands, according to FlatpanelsHD."Dolby Vision support for content on Disney+ is currently unavailable in several European countries due to technical challenges," Disney said in a statement. "We are actively working to restore access to Dolby Vision and will provide an update as soon as possible...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s GPT-5.3-Codex thinks deeper and wider about coding work</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488584/openai-gpt-5-3-codex-release</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T19:38:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488584/openai-gpt-5-3-codex-release</guid>
      <description>The company says its latest model&#8217;s agentic skills also apply to a broader set of knowledge work such as presentations and spreadsheets.
On Thursday, OpenAI released GPT-5.3-Codex, a new model that extends its Codex coding agent beyond writing and reviewing code to performing a much wider range of work tasks. The release comes as competition continues to heat up among AI companies vying for market share in the AI-powered coding tools space....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl on NBC: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, where to stream, start time, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-on-nbc-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-where-to-stream-start-time-and-more-175759402.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is nearly here. This weekend, the Big Game will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA. The NFL Championship Game kicks off at 6:30PM ET this Sunday, Feb. 8. Pre-game coverage starts at 12PM ET. Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the Super Bowl will be broadcast on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. Here's everything you need ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now that's a mega drive - WD reveals plans to launch 40TB HDD, and it's planning on getting to 100TB sooner than you might expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/now-thats-a-mega-drive-wd-reveals-plans-to-launch-40tb-hdd-and-its-planning-on-getting-to-100tb-sooner-than-you-might-expect</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BdAphSUXhK8U2kU8PaQJZ4</guid>
      <description>WD detailed how its 40TB hard drives and new actuator designs form a clear path toward 100TB capacities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 TVs are on the way soon, so there's no better time to buy a 2025 model &#8212; here are my top 4 picks as a TV expert</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/2026-tvs-are-on-the-way-soon-so-theres-no-better-time-to-buy-a-2025-model-here-are-my-top-4-picks-as-a-tv-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JeBi7remB5JiCb5gdpusaD</guid>
      <description>Black Friday and Prime Day are good times of year to buy a new TV, but don't underestimate the end of a TV's life cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will &#8216;Heated Rivalry&#8217; do for Olympic ice hockey what Taylor Swift did for the Super Bowl?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487755/heated-rivalry-is-doing-for-winter-olympics-2026-ice-hockey-what-taylor-swift-did-for-super-bowl</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487755/heated-rivalry-is-doing-for-winter-olympics-2026-ice-hockey-what-taylor-swift-did-for-super-bowl</guid>
      <description>HBO&#8217;s gay hockey romance series was a breakout hit&#8212;and it&#8217;s already boosting sales for the sport, just in time for Milan&#8217;s winter games.
HBO Max&#8217;s Heated Rivalry, a gay hockey romance TV series based on the Game Changers book series by Rachel Reid, is the breakout hit no one saw coming. With almost no promotion, it quickly became one of the most talked-about streaming TV shows in the U.S. after HBO Max purchased the rights from Canada&#8217;s Crave network this November, turning its two co-stars, Hudson Williams and Connor Storrie, into overnight celebrities....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber just lost its first sexual assault liability case. Here&#8217;s why it matters</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488429/uber-just-lost-its-first-sexual-assault-liability-case-heres-why-it-matters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488429/uber-just-lost-its-first-sexual-assault-liability-case-heres-why-it-matters</guid>
      <description>The company says the verdict affirms its safety efforts even as it prepares to challenge the decision in court.
A federal jury in Arizona has ordered Uber to pay $8.5 million in a lawsuit brought by a passenger who said was sexually assaulted by one of the ridesharing app&#8217;s drivers. The case marks the first time that Uber has been found liable for the safety of its drivers in a sexual assault case....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Tried What US Athletes Will Be Sleeping on at Milano Cortina</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/saatvas-winter-olympic-sleep-bundle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6984dceab7a9cd29a02639ab</guid>
      <description>Saatva is providing a bedding bundle to Team USA hockey and figure skating at the 2026 Olympic Winter Games&#8212;here are my thoughts on it as a sleep coach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s Memecoin Down 95% as Democrats Seek Answers on Crypto &#8216;Corruption&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trumps-memecoin-down-95-as-democrats-seek-answers-on-crypto-corruption-2000719005</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719005</guid>
      <description>Tough times for crypto bros whether they're the President or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There isn&#8217;t even a cynical explanation for Jeff Bezos destroying The Washington Post</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/874958/jeff-bezos-washington-post-layoffs-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T14:18:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874958</guid>
      <description>300 journalists have lost their jobs at The Washington Post. Over 300,000 readers have canceled their subscriptions. Owner Jeff Bezos, who purchased the legendary publication in 2013, has driven his reputation into the ground by using his vast empire to churn out content designed to make President Donald Trump happy: Amazon MGM Studios spent $40 [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new trailer for The Super Mario Galaxy Movie shows Yoshi absolutely devouring a Magikoopa</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/the-new-trailer-for-the-super-mario-galaxy-movie-shows-yoshi-absolutely-devouring-a-magikoopa-191807037.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">590fffc1-888a-41b3-99e6-1fdba849039a</guid>
      <description>The long wait for The Super Mario Galaxy Movie is nearly over, as the film hits theaters on April 1. To keep the hype train rolling, Illumination and Universal Pictures have dropped a short new teaser. It's exactly 30 seconds long, so you'll probably be seeing it again on TV this Sunday during the Super Bowl.
It does feature some nifty footage that we haven't seen before, including a hungry Yoshi absolutely devouring a Magikoopa. There are also shots highlighting the star cannons from The Super Mario Galaxy games and one shot that shows Rosalina bodying Bowser Jr.

There seems to be a plot poi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noble Audio has released a USB-C Bluetooth dongle for high fidelity transmission</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/noble-audio-has-released-a-usb-c-bluetooth-dongle-for-high-fidelity-transmission-191655786.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e71e82bd-b99a-4ee7-9b06-be802e971775</guid>
      <description>Noble Audio has announced the Sceptre, a pocket-sized USB-C Bluetooth transmitter meant to boost wireless audio quality from phones, laptops and tablets. The device is intended to exceed the quality offered by a device's existing hardware.
Sceptre is powered by Qualcomm's QCC5181 Bluetooth chipset and supports LDAC, aptX Adaptive, AAC and SBC codecs. Of course, to take advantage of the high quality codecs you'll need a pair of headphones that support them. The dongle has a reported wireless range of roughly 66 feet. 
Listeners use the Noble app for initial pairing and can then move the dongle ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We called them 'the best-sounding open-ear buds yet' &#8212; and now the Bose Ultra Open Earbuds are down to a record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/we-called-them-the-best-sounding-open-ear-buds-yet-and-now-the-bose-ultra-open-earbuds-are-down-to-a-record-low-price</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JGKMUGtu2rekr7cywQVNA5</guid>
      <description>The Bose Ultra Open Earbuds drop to a new low price of $199 at Amazon, so here's why now's the time to snap up some of the best open-ear buds you can buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jeffrey Epstein Fortnite account is fake</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/875014/jeffrey-epstein-fortnite-account-fake</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T14:02:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875014</guid>
      <description>Fortnite developer Epic Games says the account some people believed to be linked to Jeffrey Epstein is a "ruse." In a reply on X, the developer writes, "an existing Fortnite account owner changed their username" to "littlestjeff1," an alias spotted in several emailed receipts from YouTube in the Epstein files. The email suggests that "littlestjeff1" [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Baldur&#8217;s Gate 3&#8217; Was Always Going to Have a Weird Future</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/baldurs-gate-tv-show-hbo-hasbro-larian-2000718881</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718881</guid>
      <description>'Baldur's Gate 3' was so huge that anything that came after without Larian's involvement was going to feel a bit off for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'That's actually Chris Hemsworth': Crime 101 writer-director reveals why the Marvel star did all of his own stunts in the new heist thriller movie</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/thats-actually-chris-hemsworth-crime-101-writer-director-reveals-why-the-marvel-star-did-all-of-his-own-stunts-in-the-new-heist-thriller-movie</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7vss9duF4KZNaWjEMB79cT</guid>
      <description>Bart Layton has confirmed that Chris Hemsworth is "truly behind the wheel" during the crime movie's explosive chase sequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These countries just won the fashion Olympics</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486836/3-best-winter-olympic-uniforms</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486836/3-best-winter-olympic-uniforms</guid>
      <description>Move over, Ralph Lauren. These opening ceremony uniforms from 3 lesser-known brands are turning heads at the Winter Olympics.
The Olympics are best known as a moment for the world&#8217;s most elite athletes to demonstrate their physical prowess on the world stage. But, for a handful of apparel brands, the Games are also one of the most coveted advertising moments of the year....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Is the Latest State to Consider a Data Center Pause</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-york-is-the-latest-state-to-consider-a-data-center-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6985f52c3e6ee64d869b6d06</guid>
      <description>Red and blue states alike have introduced legislation in recent weeks that would halt data center development, citing concerns from climate to high energy prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Elon Musk is rewriting the rules on founder power</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/how-elon-musk-is-rewriting-the-rules-on-founder-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3090465</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#160;has&#160;merged&#160;SpaceX and xAI,&#160;creating&#160;what might be the blueprint for a new Silicon Valley power structure. With his&#160;$800 billion&#160;net worth already rivaling historic conglomerate GE&#8217;s peak market cap,&#160;and Musk being vocal about his view that &#8220;tech victory is decided by velocity of innovation,&#8221; the question&#160;isn&#8217;t&#160;whether a&#160;personal conglomerate&#160;can be built, but rather how far Musk himself is [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Muppets have always known how to break the internet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/the-muppet-show-special-internet-reactions</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06kfJRYsxkzKFJoHG6gx7XQ</guid>
      <description>From Rizzo's "Blinding Lights" cover to Sabrina Carpenter's chicken-backed performance, the Muppets&#8217; new special is taking over the internet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
