<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:26:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Reportedly Turned Over BitLocker Encryption Keys to the FBI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsoft-reportedly-turned-over-bitlocker-encryption-keys-to-the-fbi-2000713550</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713550</guid>
      <description>Microsoft claims it receives about 20 requests for BitLocker keys a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm not sure anyone expected this - an unlikely new entrant enters the flash drive market, and it's one for true Raspberry Pi fans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/im-not-sure-anyone-expected-this-an-unlikely-new-entrant-enters-the-flash-drive-market-and-its-one-for-the-true-raspberry-pi-fans</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CUfj8aXQantZvF4M6j949K</guid>
      <description>The Raspberry Pi Flash Drive is a compact USB 3.0 device offering fast speeds, durability, and flexibility for Pi projects..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rippling/Deel corporate spying scandal may have taken another wild turn</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/the-rippling-deel-corporate-spying-scandal-may-have-taken-another-wild-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085598</guid>
      <description>The Department of Justice may be conducting a criminal investigation. This is arguably the biggest drama between two HR startups ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched Disneyland Handcrafted &#8212; and it&#8217;s the kind of documentary you want to rewatch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/i-watched-disneyland-handcrafted-and-its-the-kind-of-documentary-you-want-to-rewatch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">StrBTqDMXYM72kYiPfQE28</guid>
      <description>Using raw archival footage restored with the Walt Disney Archives, Disneyland Handcrafted &#8211; directed by Leslie Iwerks and now streaming on Disney+ and YouTube &#8211; explores how Disneyland was built and why the ideas behind the original park still matter today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch UFC 324 for FREE</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/theres-a-sneaky-way-to-watch-ufc-324-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZsLKK7RH4LXWsoFancKZ6K</guid>
      <description>We uncovered a sneaky way to watch UFC 324 for FREE &#8211; from anywhere in the world, without coughing up for a Premium streaming subscription. Here's the trick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rival smart glasses company is suing Meta over its Ray-Ban products</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/a-rival-smart-glasses-company-is-suing-meta-over-its-ray-ban-products-205000997.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5998982e-0cd6-462c-a0ee-418106e6e5d6</guid>
      <description>Meta is being sued by Solos, a rival smart glasses maker, for infringing on its patents, Bloomberg reports. Solos is seeking "multiple billions of dollars" in damages and an injunction that could prevent Meta from selling its Ray-Ban Meta smart glasses as part of the lawsuit.Solos claims that Meta's Ray-Ban Meta Wayfarer Gen 1 smart glasses violate multiple patents covering "core technologies in the field of smart eyewear." While less well known than Meta and its partner EssilorLuxottica, Solos sells multiple pairs of glasses with similar features to what Meta offers. For example, the company'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Prep for This Weekend&#8217;s Big Winter Storm: Power, Heat, and Underwear</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-prep-for-a-winter-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6972acf52144cba86fd9342f</guid>
      <description>Bitter cold, power outages, and impassible roads are a terrible cocktail. Here&#8217;s how to prep and bunker in for an extreme winter storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about Netflix&#8217;s landmark acquisition of Warner Bros.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/what-to-know-about-netflixs-landmark-acquisition-of-warner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085519</guid>
      <description>Learn more about Netflix's acquisition of Warner Bros., considered the most historic megadeal in Hollywood, as it continues to develop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Fictional &#8216;Star Trek&#8217; Sports</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-fake-sports-calica-starfleet-academy-2000713435</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713435</guid>
      <description>After this week's episode of 'Starfleet Academy' introduced official phaser tag into 'Trek' canon, we take a look back at 60 years of boldly sporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asus will no longer add new mobile phone models in the future': CEO confirms no more Zenfone or ROG smartphones are coming as it pivots to focus on AI products</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/asus-will-no-longer-add-new-mobile-phone-models-in-the-future-ceo-confirms-no-more-zenfone-or-rog-smartphones-are-coming-as-it-pivots-to-focus-on-ai-products</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tcCk3rymzCRpLNn9gN338o</guid>
      <description>Asus halts new smartphone production amid shrinking margins, competition, and longer upgrade cycles, shifting focus toward AI servers and related hardware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers say Russian government hackers were behind attempted Poland power outage</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/researchers-say-russian-government-hackers-were-behind-attempted-poland-power-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085628</guid>
      <description>Security researchers have attributed the attempted use of destructive "wiper" malware across Poland's energy infrastructure in late December to a Russian-backed hacking group known for causing power outages in neighboring Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro handheld maker Anbernic has a new gamepad with a screen and heart rate sensor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/retro-handheld-maker-anbernic-has-a-new-gamepad-with-a-screen-and-heart-rate-sensor-201651899.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a54b6574-f246-4f91-a418-69fb2409cbfc</guid>
      <description>File this one under "Things that make you go, 'Hmmm&#8230;'" Retro handheld maker Anbernic is launching a new controller with a screen. But unlike Nintendo's Wii U controller, there's no second-screen gaming capability here. Instead, the display is designed to "make customization intuitive and effortless." Oh, and the controller also has a heart rate sensor. Because, hey, if you're going weird, I say fully commit!The Anbernic RG G01 has a 2.5-inch HD display that the company describes as an "HD smart screen." The idea is to remap buttons, program macros and change other settings without requiring so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Kills Standard Autopilot as It Pushes Buyers to Subscription-Based Option</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-kills-standard-autopilot-as-it-pushes-buyers-to-subscription-based-option-2000713524</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713524</guid>
      <description>If it wasn't bad enough that Elon Musk manufactured your car, it's getting worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched the first trailer for &#8216;The Muppet Show&#8217; &#8212; and it looks like the inspirational, celebrational, muppetsational comeback fans have been waiting for when it comes to Disney+</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/i-watched-the-first-trailer-for-the-muppet-show-and-it-looks-like-the-inspirational-celebrational-muppetsational-comeback-fans-have-been-waiting-for-when-it-comes-to-disney</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6DpLo5kXtCBpQwNxNhnHpV</guid>
      <description>It's time to put on makeup, it's time to light the lights for a new The Muppet Show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did Davos turn into a tech conference?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/how-did-davos-turn-into-a-tech-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3085516</guid>
      <description>The World Economic Forum&#8217;s annual meeting in Davos&#160;felt different this year, and not just because Meta and Salesforce took over storefronts on the main promenade.&#160;AI dominated the conversation in a way that overshadowed traditional topics like climate change and global poverty, and the CEOs&#160;weren&#8217;t&#160;holding back. There was public criticism of trade policy, warnings about AI [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We&#8217;re going to let VR be what it is&#8217; Meta CTO Andrew Bosworth addresses the major VR layoffs &#8211; and teases a new direction for the metaverse</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/were-going-to-let-vr-be-what-it-is-meta-cto-andrew-bosworth-addresses-the-major-vr-layoffs-and-teases-a-new-direction-for-the-metaverse</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TzPndwamUBhjtviNhK49Ui</guid>
      <description>Meta CTO Andrew Bosworth has explained the company's new approach to VR, the metaverse, and XR glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How OpenAI is scaling the PostgreSQL database to 800 million users</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/how-openai-is-scaling-the-postgresql-database-to-800-million-users</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1YZEzpmzcG7fxNsFJPRBuX</guid>
      <description>While vector databases still have many valid use cases, organizations including OpenAI are leaning on PostgreSQL to get things done.In a blog post on Thursday, OpenAI disclosed how it is using the open-source PostgreSQL database.OpenAI runs ChatGPT and its API platform for 800 million users on a single-primary PostgreSQL instance &#8212; not a distributed database, not a sharded cluster. One Azure PostgreSQL Flexible Server handles all writes. Nearly 50 read replicas spread across multiple regions handle reads. The system processes millions of queries per second while maintaining low double-digit mi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The workplace just got even less friendly for LGBTQ+ workers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479483/the-workplace-just-got-even-less-friendly-for-lgbtq-workers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479483/the-workplace-just-got-even-less-friendly-for-lgbtq-workers</guid>
      <description>The EEOC just struck down its harassment guidance, which outlined protections for trans and gender-nonconforming workers. 
This week, the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission rescinded its guidance on workplace harassment, in a move that could significantly undermine protections for all workers, but especially those who identify as LGBTQ+. The agency, which plays a crucial role as the federal watchdog that enforces anti-discrimination laws governing the workplace, voted on Thursday to strike down guidance that had been codified in 2024, during the Biden administration.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Nasa met en sc&#232;ne le retour des Am&#233;ricains sur la Lune comme un film&#8230; et le message est clair</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/artemis-ii-artemis-ii-nasa-devoile-retour-vers-lune-comme-bande-annonce-cinema-130502/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:57:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/artemis-ii-artemis-ii-nasa-devoile-retour-vers-lune-comme-bande-annonce-cinema-130502/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>La Nasa a publi&#233; une nouvelle vid&#233;o de pr&#233;sentation d&#8217;Artemis II et le ton est r&#233;solument spectaculaire. En moins d&#8217;une minute, images grandioses, musique dramatique et r&#233;f&#233;rences &#224; Apollo transforment le retour des humains vers la Lune en v&#233;ritable trailer de science-fiction, au service d&#8217;une...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Are Poised to Hit a Mathematical Wall, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ai-agents-are-poised-to-hit-a-mathematical-wall-study-finds-2000713493</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713493</guid>
      <description>LLMs have their limits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is stopping teens from chatting with its AI characters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866906/meta-teens-ai-characters-stop-block-new-version</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T14:50:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866906</guid>
      <description>Meta is "temporarily pausing" the ability for teens to chat with its AI characters as it develops a "new version" of the characters that will offer a "better experience." The company made the announcement in an update to a blog post from October where the company had detailed more parental controls for teen AI use. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is Very Deliberately Told Entirely From Dunk&#8217;s POV</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-interview-dunk-2000713458</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713458</guid>
      <description>Showrunner Ira Parker explained the series' stylistic approach, which stays true to the way George R.R. Martin's novella is written.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#8217;s Next Moon Rocket Runs on Shuttle Engines&#8212;Here&#8217;s the Story Behind Each One</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasas-next-moon-rocket-runs-on-shuttle-engines-heres-the-story-behind-each-one-2000713485</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713485</guid>
      <description>SLS is ready to fly and will feature three shuttle-era engines that have already flown to space.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
