<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:26:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia's latest RTX 5090 GPU card has an audio jack &#8212; yes a headphone socket, on a video card, but no wooden trim or SSD like its predecessor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/nvidias-latest-rtx-5090-gpu-card-has-an-audio-jack-yes-a-headphone-socket-on-a-video-card-but-no-wooden-trim-or-ssd-like-its-predecessor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YNSP5XFAgAmYqtHWFYzJKd</guid>
      <description>The Asus ProArt RTX 5090 targets creative professionals with its compact dimensions, 32GB of GDDR7 memory, and an unexpected audio jack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego's first Pok&#233;mon sets are now available for pre-order</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/legos-first-pokemon-sets-are-now-available-for-pre-order-205527102.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d92e386-e894-457c-8939-f0e4c78dcfdd</guid>
      <description>We learned last March that Lego and Pok&#233;mon would be joining forces and the first results of their partnership are here. Pre-orders for all three kits are open now, with an expected ship date of February 27. As one might have guessed from the lightning bolts on the previous promotional image, one of the debut pocket monsters getting the brick treatment is Pikachu, complete with a Pok&#233; Ball. The 2,050-piece kit can be built to show Pikachu either leaping out of the open Pok&#233; Ball into battle or at rest staring up at the builder, closed Pok&#233; Ball between his paws. The Pikachu kit costs $200.
The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic announces Claude for Healthcare following OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT Health reveal</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/anthropic-announces-claude-for-healthcare-following-openais-chatgpt-health-reveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082015</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's Claude for Healthcare is unveiled about a week after OpenAI announced its ChatGPT Health product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Freezes $182 Million in Stablecoins as Reports Point to Heavy Crypto Use by Venezuela</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tether-freezes-182-million-in-stablecoins-as-reports-point-to-heavy-crypto-use-by-venezuela-2000709276</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709276</guid>
      <description>There's a new spotlight on crypto that's used to avoid sanctions after the abduction of Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble founder says his new company is &#8216;not a startup&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/pebble-founder-says-his-new-company-is-not-a-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080005</guid>
      <description>Pebble's founder talks about how his new company is doing things differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell revives its XPS laptops after a boneheaded rebranding</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/dell-revives-its-xps-laptops-after-a-boneheaded-rebranding-001028029.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fcc565f-aee8-413a-b8f8-0cc5f443bc32</guid>
      <description>Last year, Dell killed off all of its PC brands, including the iconic XPS lineup, and replaced them with a simplified naming scheme. It was a move meant to make it easier for people to discern between the company's many brands, but in reality, it just just made the company's lineup even more confusing. We called it an unforced error at the time, but after seeing how much Dell's PC market share fell over 2025, it's fair to say that rebranding was an absolute marketing disaster. So, with its tail between its legs, Dell has returned to CES some welcome news for its fans: XPS lives! And the compan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 proved the PC industry is hosed this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/ces-2026-proved-the-pc-industry-is-hosed-this-year-174500314.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db798e3a-f4ab-4554-828a-98500fcc1f8f</guid>
      <description>Dell's XPS 14 currently costs over $2,000. An AMD executive predicts that PC builders will likely make piecemeal upgrades this year, instead of building entirely new systems. And new AI supercomputers from NVIDIA and AMD are gobbling up the RAM market. At CES 2026, it was hard not to notice the dire year ahead for the computing industry, one that will likely lead to higher prices and more limited availability for consumer goods across the board.Really, though, the show just confirmed what was apparent since RAM prices skyrocketed over the last few months, driven by demand from AI datacenters. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Discover Previously Unknown Species in Utah&#8217;s Great Salt Lake</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/researchers-discover-previously-unknown-species-in-utahs-great-salt-lake-2000709251</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709251</guid>
      <description>And they've proposed two "kind of crazy" ideas for how it got there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s NSFW Grok AI chatbot is forcing countries to take this extreme step</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473199/grok-ai-chatbot-nsfw-porn-pornography-is-forcing-countries-to-take-this-extreme-step-elon-musk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T20:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473199/grok-ai-chatbot-nsfw-porn-pornography-is-forcing-countries-to-take-this-extreme-step-elon-musk</guid>
      <description>The platform&#8217;s latest controversy involves Grok creating deepfake pornography of young girls and women at users&#8217; requests.
Indonesia and Malaysia are the first two countries to ban Elon Musk&#8217;s artificial intelligence tool Grok, after the generative AI essentially flooded the social media platform X with sexually explicit, lewd images of young girls and women, made without their consent....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet&#8217;s Wing Adds 150 Walmart Stores to Drone Delivery Program</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alphabets-wing-adds-150-walmart-stores-to-drone-delivery-program-2000709294</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709294</guid>
      <description>Bzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bye Bye MLC: QLC and TLC to be dominant SSD technologies amidst AI's ravenous appetite for NAND &#8212; and PLC won't probably happen till the era of Petabyte SSDs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/bye-bye-mlc-qlc-and-tlc-to-be-dominant-ssd-technologies-amidst-ai-ravenous-appetite-for-nand-and-plc-wont-probably-happen-till-the-era-of-petabyte-ssds</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kv2WwK8VuiAfvkk3S7TXCH</guid>
      <description>TrendForce shows MLC NAND retreating while TLC and QLC dominate SSDs, driven by AI workloads, data growth, and supplier strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseus&#8217; retractable travel adapter is on sale for more than 50 percent off today</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/860791/baseus-enercore-cg11-6-in-1-universal-travel-adapter-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T15:04:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860791</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re planning on traveling at all this year, the Baseus EnerCore CG11 Universal Travel Adapter is worth a look. The adapter can power up to six devices at once, and now through the end of today, January 12th, it&#8217;s on sale for just $34.19 (about $36 off) at Amazon, matching the all-time low price [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK pushes up a law criminalizing deepfake nudes in response to Grok</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860881/uk-ai-x-grok-law-criminalizing-deepfake-nudes-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T15:03:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860881</guid>
      <description>The UK is bringing a law into force that makes creating nonconsensual intimate deepfake images, like the ones that have proliferated on X because of the Grok AI chatbot, a criminal offense, as reported by the BBC. "The Data Act, passed last year, made it a criminal offence to create - or request the creation [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Is Going Full Borg to Try and Stop the Netflix-Warner Bros. Merger</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paramount-netflix-warner-bros-lawsuit-2000709200</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709200</guid>
      <description>Resistance is futile: Paramount isn't going to let Netflix grab ahold of Warner Bros. without a fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Research Exposes the Good and the Gross in Pompeii&#8217;s Baths</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-research-exposes-the-good-and-the-gross-in-pompeiis-baths-2000708925</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708925</guid>
      <description>Mount Vesuvius preserved the ancient city's water system, including evidence of filth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stranger Things behind-the-scenes doc is a lot more boring than a secret episode</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/860692/one-last-adventure-the-making-of-stranger-things-5-netflix-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860692</guid>
      <description>It's a weird time in the Stranger Things community. Following a monthslong lead-up to a finale that was so big it screened in theaters, the show's superfans have been spending their time dissecting the fifth season in order to prove that a hidden ninth episode is coming that represents the true ending of Stranger Things. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first Lego Pok&#233;mon sets have been announced, and of course the coolest is over $600</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/the-first-lego-pokemon-sets-have-been-announced-and-of-course-the-coolest-is-over-usd600</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dNNqBwWq63t7bntoc6J9</guid>
      <description>Want to be a master of Lego Pok&#233;mon? Get ready to pay up as the 8 Gym Badges are locked behind the most expensive set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Chevron played the long game for Venezuela&#8217;s oil reserves</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473291/chevron-long-game-oil-venezuela</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473291/chevron-long-game-oil-venezuela</guid>
      <description>Today, Chevron is uniquely positioned in the aftermath of the invasion to profit from Venezuela&#8217;s vast oil reserves.
On Saturday, hours after U.S. forces in Caracas killed at least 80 people and kidnapped Venezuelan President Nicol&#225;s Maduro, Donald Trump sounded less like a wartime commander than a developer surveying a newly acquired property. The country&#8217;s future,&#160;he told reporters&#160;at his Mar-a-Lago resort, belonged to &#8220;very large United States oil companies,&#8221; which would soon be pumping &#8220;a tremendous amount of wealth out of the ground.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Globes ignored this underrated body horror movie &#8212; but the Oscars didn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/the-golden-globes-ignored-this-underrated-body-horror-movie-but-the-oscars-didnt</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66VUBb2nLjFvie4jLz6R2d</guid>
      <description>The Ugly Stepsister is a criminally underrated horror movie, but it is in with the chance of being Oscar-nominated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 robots were wild, silly, and sometimes disappointing but there was one that restored my faith in robotics</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/ces-2026-robots-were-wild-silly-and-sometimes-disappointing-but-there-was-one-that-restored-my-faith-in-robotics</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aGewotYVN8zKj35cbpsRGR</guid>
      <description>We take a look at the wide range of robots on display at CES 2026 and find that Altas is still the one to watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Just Built Its Own Time System for the Moon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/china-just-built-its-own-time-system-for-the-moon-2000708991</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708991</guid>
      <description>The Moon's weaker gravity results in slightly faster clocks than on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic wants you to use Claude to &amp;#8216;Cowork&amp;#8217; in latest AI agent push</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/860730/anthropic-cowork-feature-ai-agents-claude-code</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T14:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860730</guid>
      <description>Anthropic wants to expand Claude's AI agent capabilities and take advantage of the growing hype around Claude Code - and it's doing it with a brand-new feature released Monday, dubbed "Claude Cowork." "Cowork can take on many of the same tasks that Claude Code can handle, but in a more approachable form for non-coding tasks," [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s new Cowork tool offers Claude Code without the code</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/anthropics-new-cowork-tool-offers-claude-code-without-the-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081970</guid>
      <description>Built into the Claude Desktop app, Cowork lets users designate a specific folder where Claude can read or modify files, with further instructions given through the standard chat interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Lenovo monitor has six speakers and is the only Windows PC monitor with Dolby Atmos and Dolby Vision &#8212; it even has a 4K detachable webcam</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-lenovo-monitor-has-six-speakers-and-is-the-only-windows-pc-monitor-with-dolby-atmos-and-dolby-vision-and-it-even-has-a-4k-detachable-webcam</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VFW9tpSkKTEYJ9MbibdcXc</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s Yoga Pro 27UD-10 OLED monitor combines detachable 4K video, USB4 connectivity, Dolby audio, and laptop-focused color syncing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic made a version of its coding AI for regular people</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-made-a-version-of-its-coding-ai-for-regular-people-193000363.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e96f209-4988-475c-9ec3-ef79a87a6915</guid>
      <description>If you follow Anthropic, you're probably familiar with Claude Code. Since the fall of 2024, the company has been training its AI models to use and navigate computers like a human would, and the coding agent has been the most practical expression of that work, giving developers a way to automate rote programming tasks. Starting today, Anthropic is giving regular people a way to take advantage of those capabilities, with the release of a new preview feature called Claude Cowork.The company is billing Cowork as "a simpler way for anyone &#8212; not just developers &#8212; to work with Claude." After you give...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disney+ Hulu bundle is on sale for $10 for one month right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-disney-hulu-bundle-is-on-sale-for-10-for-one-month-right-now-192814784.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b6e8a2-981f-4fc9-b476-d49dcaeed4ba</guid>
      <description>The peak time for deals on streaming services &#8212; the holiday shopping season &#8212; has come and gone, but Disney is back with a fresh offer for the new year. New and eligible returning subscribers can get one month of the ad-supported Disney+ Hulu bundle for just $10. That's $3 off the usual monthly rate for the bundle, and more than 58 percent off if you consider the prices for each service individually (Disney+ at $12 per month and, separately, Hulu also at $12 per month).
We'd be remiss if we didn't mention that this isn't quite as good as the Black Friday deal we saw last year, which offered th...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
