<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:03:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai and Boston Dynamics May Have Just Stolen the Robot Factory Narrative Away from Tesla</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hyundai-and-boston-dynamics-may-have-just-stolen-the-robot-factory-narrative-away-from-tesla-2000705841</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705841</guid>
      <description>The key question isn't who you should root for. It's whose story do you find more plausible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGIMI, best known for projectors, launches its own smart glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/xgimi-best-known-for-projectors-launches-its-own-smart-glasses-170000968.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54390b93-e1df-4254-8d11-df10a104845a</guid>
      <description>Projector maker XGIMI has turned up at CES to launch its own range of AR glasses, but don&#8217;t get the champagne out too soon. MemoMind is a new brand under which its AI-infused eyewear will be sold, with two distinct units arriving at some point in the near future. The company says it has leveraged its know-how in optics and engineering to produce glasses which are unobtrusively light, all the better for blending into your daily life. Fashionistas will even be overjoyed to learn the glasses&#8217; ship in eight different frame styles, five different temple designs and can be worn with prescription len...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD&#8217;s Latest Chips Are Betting Big on Gamers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amds-latest-chips-are-betting-big-on-gamers-2000705030</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705030</guid>
      <description>You&#8217;re going to be far more interested in AMD&#8217;s Ryzen Max than the Ryzen 400 series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware Upgrades Its Best Gaming Laptop So It Looks as Good as It Feels</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alienware-upgrades-its-best-gaming-laptop-so-it-looks-as-good-as-it-feels-2000703974</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703974</guid>
      <description>Also, for the first time in a long time, Alienware is finally making an 'ultra-slim' gaming laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware is working on new slim and cheaper gaming laptops</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851926/alienware-is-working-on-new-slim-and-cheaper-gaming-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851926</guid>
      <description>Dell-owned Alienware is looking to reach a wider swath of gamers, announcing at CES 2026 that it's working on two new laptops: one with a lower, entry-level price and one with an ultra-slim chassis. There aren't many details right now, as Alienware is only sharing some basic renders, and the behind-glass nonworking prototypes I saw [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP crammed an entire desktop computer into this keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851965/hp-crammed-an-entire-desktop-computer-into-this-keyboard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851965</guid>
      <description>HP is announcing a new mini desktop computer at CES 2026, and the whole thing is housed in a compact keyboard. The Eliteboard G1a looks like a normal office keyboard with either a captive or detachable USB-C cable, but inside it is an AMD Ryzen AI 300-series chip, stereo speakers, RAM, storage, a fan, and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD&#8217;s new Ryzen 7 9850X3D makes the best gaming CPU even faster</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855188/amd-ryzen-7-9850x3d-processor-boost-clock-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855188</guid>
      <description>AMD is introducing an improved version of its popular Ryzen 7 9800X3D processor today at CES. The new Ryzen 7 9850X3D offers up the same 8-core / 16-thread CPU as the 9800X3D, running at even faster boost clocks. "We've fine-tuned our best gaming processor in the world and have increased the boost clocks to 5.6GHz," [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD Ryzen AI 400 official: Will these laptop chips maintain AMD&#8217;s lead?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855343/amd-ryzen-ai-400-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855343</guid>
      <description>We were rightly skeptical of AMD's Ryzen AI 300 "Strix Point" laptop chips in 2024. Now they're in some of the very best laptops you can buy, arguably hitting the sweet spot of price, performance, and battery life. Today at CES, AMD is announcing its successor, the Ryzen AI 400 line - but there's nothing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD heard you like powerful gaming portables &#8212; so here are new Strix Halo chips</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855463/amd-strix-halo-ai-max-plus-388-392-handheld-gaming</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855463</guid>
      <description>AMD's Strix Halo, aka "Ryzen AI Max," is a hugely expensive chip that includes some of the most powerful integrated graphics ever made. Though AMD initially marketed it more to AI workloads with its tremendous complement of up to 128GB of RAM, it's also inspired some unprecedented gaming designs - by far the most powerful [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD unveils new AI PC processors for general use and gaming at CES</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/amd-unveils-new-ai-pc-processors-for-general-use-and-gaming-at-ces/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080003</guid>
      <description>AMD announced the latest version of its AI-powered PC chips designed for a variety of tasks from gaming to content creation and multitasking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware teases 'covert' ultraslim gaming laptop line and a new budget-friendly option at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/alienware-teases-covert-ultraslim-gaming-laptop-line-and-a-new-budget-friendly-option-at-ces-2026-as-well-as-finally-offering-oled-on-its-area-51-models</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9F9kN7TzwprE94BWnLcEGJ</guid>
      <description>Alienware announced that it will be expanding its gaming laptop portfolio in 2026 with two new classes of product: an ultraslim 'covert' gaming laptop line, and a budget-oriented gaming laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AMD Ryzen 7 9850X3D is only one of the chips Team Red announced at CES 2026&#8212;and the others might have Intel sweating</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cpu/the-amd-ryzen-7-9850x3d-is-only-one-of-the-chips-team-red-announced-at-ces-2026-and-the-others-might-have-intel-sweating</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nPSVu9S6d3gdEYc8Nb2unB</guid>
      <description>AMD's next-gen gaming CPU looks powerful, but it might play second fiddle to the new round of Ryzen AI 400 chips in the long run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware teases new super-slim and entry-level gaming laptops at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/alienware-teases-new-super-slim-and-entry-level-gaming-laptops-at-ces-2026-033000700.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413691de-1598-496f-a1c5-a36248195545</guid>
      <description>After relaunching its Area-51 brand with a new 16-inch laptop in 2025, Alienware is teasing two new laptops at CES 2026 in an attempt to reach an even larger audience. Dell's gaming brand plans to launch both entry-level and ultra-slim models later this year, and in the meantime, it's rolling out updates to its existing desktops and laptops to tide people over.Alienware isn't sharing all the details of its new laptops at CES, but we do have the highlights. The company's new "ultra-slim gaming laptop" will be around 17mm or 0.67 inches thin, and come in either 14-inch or 16-inch variants. While...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD's new Ryzen AI Max+ chips and Ryzen 7 9850X3D court desktop enthusiasts at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/amds-new-ryzen-ai-max-chips-and-ryzen-7-9850x3d-court-desktop-enthusiasts-at-ces-2026-033000587.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d93068a-302c-4cdc-8baa-6b213949a2e2</guid>
      <description>While it's nice to see desktop support in AMD's new Ryzen AI 400 chips, demanding gamers and enthusiasts will likely be more intrigued by the company's next batch of Ryzen AI Max+ chips, as well as the new Ryzen 7 9850X3D with 3D V-Cache. The former will make its way into small desktops and a handful of workhorse laptops, while the latter is another option for gamers who want the speed bump of 3D V-cache without shelling out for the $700 9950X3D.&#160; Last year, AMD debuted its Ryzen AI Max chips as a way to create a single piece of silicon with powerful CPU cores, GPU cores, NPUs and integrated m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD's Ryzen AI 400 chips are a big boost for laptops and desktops alike</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/amds-ryzen-ai-400-chips-are-a-big-boost-for-laptops-and-desktops-alike-033000635.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86a4c064-11c6-492e-8b50-df778285f612</guid>
      <description>The whole AI PC trend didn't exactly set the world on fire last year, but, like clockwork, AMD is still ready to deliver a new batch of AI chips at CES 2026. The Ryzen AI 400 processors will offer some slight speed upgrades over last year's chips, and notably, they also include AMD's first Copilot+ processors for desktops. Sure, the Copilot+ program didn't really go anywhere, but as I've argued, it at least served as a template for building capable AI PCs. Now we just need some genuinely useful AI features in Windows &#8212; Recall and Copilot's voice commands aren't really compelling enough on thei...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP's EliteBoard made me believe in keyboard computers again</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/hps-eliteboard-made-me-believe-in-keyboard-computers-again-033000955.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a465857-65de-4340-b8bf-15ecdc4b74e1</guid>
      <description>For as long as I can remember, I've always wanted to have a keyboard computer -- that is, a computer where the entire machine was stuffed inside of a keyboard. Maybe I caught a glimpse of the Commodore 64 at an impressionable age, but for whatever reason, the idea has always intrigued me. Now HP is bringing the concept back with its new EliteBoard G1a "Next Gen AI PC." It's an IT administrator's dream: It looks a typical desktop keyboard, but it has the full power of a Copilot+ AI PC inside. You can equip it with Ryzen 5 or 7 CPUs and their embedded Radeon 800 GPUs, up to 64GB of RAM and as mu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD officialise le Ryzen 7 9850X3D : ce qui change vraiment sur ce nouveau processeur de jeu</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2929153_amd-officialise-le-ryzen-7-9850x3d-ce-qui-change-vraiment-sur-ce-nouveau-processeur-de-jeu</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2929153_amd-officialise-le-ryzen-7-9850x3d-ce-qui-change-vraiment-sur-ce-nouveau-processeur-de-jeu</guid>
      <description>
Le Ryzen 7 9850X3D est officiel, mais le nouveau processeur de bureau d'AMD n'apporte finalement que tr&#232;s peu de choses par rapport au 9800X3D.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryzen AI 400 : tout savoir sur les nouvelles puces AMD qui vont booster vos prochains PC portables</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2928843_ryzen-ai-400-tout-savoir-sur-les-nouvelles-puces-amd-qui-vont-booster-vos-prochains-pc-portables</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2928843_ryzen-ai-400-tout-savoir-sur-les-nouvelles-puces-amd-qui-vont-booster-vos-prochains-pc-portables</guid>
      <description>
AMD d&#233;voile au CES une nouvelle gamme de processeurs pour PC portables avec les puces Ryzen AI 400. Une &#233;volution &#224; petits pas de l'architecture actuelle avant l'arriv&#233;e de Zen 6.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini la corv&#233;e de linge ? Pourquoi le nouveau robot de LG risque surtout de vous exasp&#233;rer</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2929933_fini-la-corvee-de-linge-pourquoi-le-nouveau-robot-de-lg-risque-surtout-de-vous-exasperer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2929933_fini-la-corvee-de-linge-pourquoi-le-nouveau-robot-de-lg-risque-surtout-de-vous-exasperer</guid>
      <description>
LG vient de d&#233;voiler son robot humano&#239;de intelligent qui promet de faire toutes les t&#226;ches m&#233;nag&#232;res &#224; votre place. J'ai pu le voir en action. Il me fait r&#234;ver, mais il m'exasp&#232;re aussi, et vous allez vite comprendre pourquoi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vivoo FlowPad turns menstrual pads into an at-home hormone test</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/849643/ces-2026-vivoo-flowpad-menstrual-pad-hormones-wearable-health</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849643</guid>
      <description>Wellness tech companies are increasingly interested in bodily fluids like blood, urine, sweat, and saliva. At CES 2026, it's time to add menstrual blood to that list, too. Health tech startup Vivoo just announced the FlowPad, a roughly $4 to $5 menstrual pad that doubles as an at-home hormone test for follicle-stimulating hormone (FSH). Users [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $300 hybrid robovac comes with a self-empyting docking station</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850979/eureka-e10-evo-plus-docking-station-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850979</guid>
      <description>Eureka is adding an even cheaper dock-equipped robovac to its lineup. During CES 2026, Eureka showed off the new E10 Evo Plus, a robovac featuring a mop pad, 10,000Pa of suction, two anti-tangle brushes, and a self-emptying docking station for just $299. It's an even better deal than the Eureka E10s, a mopping pad-equipped robovac [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eureka&#8217;s sub-$1,000 mopping robovac deploys a shield to keep your carpets dry</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851229/eureka-z50-mopping-robovac-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851229</guid>
      <description>Eureka's new Z50 robovac comes equipped with a roller mop that it will automatically lift and shield before vacuuming your carpets, preventing them from getting wet. The roller mop cover is similar to the one we saw on the Roomba Max 705 Combo last year, but it's available for a "tentative" cost of $800 as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keychron&#8217;s new mechanical keyboards offer ultralong battery life at wireless 8K polling rates</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851900/keychrons-new-mechanical-keyboards-offer-ultra-long-battery-life-at-wireless-8k-polling-rates</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851900</guid>
      <description>Keychron is announcing new Q Ultra and V Ultra mechanical keyboards at CES 2026. They're Keychron's first ZMK mechanical keyboards, an open-source firmware that's more battery efficient than the popular QMK. Keychron claims its ZMK boards can last up to 660 hours in 2.4G wireless mode with a high-speed 8,000Hz polling rate - matching wired [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now take testosterone tests with a stick, your phone, and some spit</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853211/ces-2026-eli-health-hormometer-testosterone-progesterone</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853211</guid>
      <description>At last year's CES, Eli Health announced the Hormometer - an at-home hormone test for cortisol that utilized saliva and a smartphone. For this year's show, the company is back and expanding into testosterone and progesterone. Eli Health isn't changing up how its Hormometer works. You still stick a thin cartridge attached to a wand [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAOX's wireless earbuds have a built-in EEG to monitor your brain health</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/naoxs-wireless-earbuds-have-a-built-in-eeg-to-monitor-your-brain-health-030000605.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c8d46e1-242a-48ab-b269-7d8383b6ae38</guid>
      <description>French startup NAOX is at CES with a groundbreaking wearable EEG for clinics and research, but that&#8217;s not what we&#8217;re interested in today. Because it&#8217;s also here showing off a prototype of the consumer version, which incorporates its brain-scanning technology in wireless earbuds. As early as the end of this year, your earbuds could pull double-duty, pumping out tunes and keeping an eye on your brain&#8217;s health.The product being released today is the NAOX Link NX01, an in-ear EEG designed to replace the wire-covered caps you&#8217;ve seen at a sleep clinic. It&#8217;s designed to be much more convenient for u...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivoo's toilet computer keeps an eye on your hydration</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/vivoos-toilet-computer-keeps-an-eye-on-your-hydration-030000209.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ba6583b-12fe-4e05-8f46-2662f5db2a93</guid>
      <description>Urinalysis company Vivoo has rocked up at CES 2026 with two new products designed to keep an eye on your health. The first is the Smart Toilet, which clips onto your bowl and uses optical sensors to monitor your hydration levels.
It&#8217;s an evolution of the smart toilet product it originally announced back in 2023, which used a reactive testing strip as part of its process. Here, that feature has been ditched in favor of just collecting a small sample in its pocket-shaped cup for non-contact testing before being released.
The optical sensors in question are designed to track your urine&#8217;s specific...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints today: Clues, answers for January 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nyt-connections-hint-answer-today-january-6-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04raRRwXtPLjUsxRLMcWIw7</guid>
      <description>Connections is a New York Times word game that's all about finding the "common threads between words." How to solve the puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints, answers for January 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/strands-nyt-hint-january-6-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02WzER18on1nfPb3Q0TXiBs</guid>
      <description>The NYT Strands hints and answers you need to make the most of your puzzling experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordle today: Answer, hints for January 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wordle-today-answer-january-6-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05WcqR9PH7cEREgK1e6Ukpn</guid>
      <description>Here's the answer for "Wordle" #1661 on January 6 as well as a few hints, tips, and clues to help you solve it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peacock will be the first streaming service with Dolby Vision 2 HDR and next-gen Atmos audio encoding</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/peacock-goes-all-in-on-dolby-with-vision-and-atmos-support</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cYqj2nfLgnkrsN5tAFDbE4</guid>
      <description>Finally, we know where you'll be able to find next-gen HDR and motion control</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peacock is expanding Dolby Vision and Atmos availability for live sports</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/peacock-is-expanding-dolby-vision-and-atmos-availability-for-live-sports-023000794.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b1a813d-1b73-4fa7-bc43-46dd35e75079</guid>
      <description>You&#8217;ll be able to watch more live sports programming on Peacock that supports Dolby Vision and Atmos starting this year. At the moment, the only live sports offering you can enjoy with Atmos on the service is Sunday Night Football. Now, Dolby Laboratories has announced at CES that Peacock is expanding the availability of Dolby Vision and Atmos across live sports over the coming year. Peacock will add support for both technologies to Sunday Night Football, NBA and MLB live sporting events that the streaming service will offer its subscribers. &#8220;Our partnership with Dolby ensures that whether our...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony et Honda d&#233;voilent une nouvelle voiture &#233;lectrique : un SUV plus pratique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2929975_sony-et-honda-devoilent-une-nouvelle-voiture-electrique-un-suv-plus-pratique</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2929975_sony-et-honda-devoilent-une-nouvelle-voiture-electrique-un-suv-plus-pratique</guid>
      <description>
Sony et Honda ont d&#233;voil&#233; une nouvelle voiture &#233;lectrique, qui prend la forme d'un SUV. La co-entreprise en a profit&#233; pour donner des nouvelles au sujet de la berline 1 qu'on attend depuis des ann&#233;es maintenant.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 major takeaways from Nvidia Live at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-major-takeaways-from-nvidia-live</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06Xo82tWDIYCfuZRGSYuhmu</guid>
      <description>Here are three major takeaways from Nvidia Live at CES 2026, including its focus on physical and 'open' AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Google TV Update Is a Serious Bid to Get You to Watch AI Outputs from Your Couch</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-google-tv-update-is-a-serious-bid-to-get-you-to-watch-ai-outputs-from-your-couch-2000705843</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705843</guid>
      <description>Gemini for TV is getting Nano Banana&#8212;an early attempt to answer the question "Will people watch AI stuff on TV"?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
