<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:24:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Star Wars&#8217; and Deadpool Bring Festive Themed Treats to Disneyland</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-and-deadpool-bring-festive-themed-treats-to-disneyland-2000698656</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698656</guid>
      <description>Eat your way through Disney Parks this season with Chewbacca-endorsed Life Day fare at Galaxy's Edge and chimichangas at Avengers Campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents call for New York governor to sign landmark AI safety bill</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/844062/parents-call-for-new-york-governor-to-sign-landmark-ai-safety-bill</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T17:16:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844062</guid>
      <description>A group of more than 150 parents sent a letter on Friday to New York governor Kathy Hochul, urging her to sign the Responsible AI Safety and Education (RAISE) Act, a buzzy bill that would require developers of large AI models - like Meta, OpenAI, Deepseek, and Google - to create safety plans and follow [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon pulls its bad AI video recaps after Fallout fallout</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/amazon-pulls-its-bad-ai-video-recaps-after-fallout-fallout-220358758.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a966a17f-c4ab-4715-906e-5193c66b0229</guid>
      <description>Amazon has responded to viewers catching errors in its AI-generated season recaps by apparently pulling them from Prime Video. The company announced its new Video Recaps feature in November as a way to make it easier to jump into a new season of a show, but the feature had issues: A recap created for Fallout included factual errors about the plot and the setting of the show.On Prime Video, recaps can be played in the "Extras" section if you're watching on the web, or via a dedicated "recap button" on the show's page, according to Amazon's original Video Recaps announcement. If you head to the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Accenture employee charged by DoJ for cloud security fraud</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/former-accenture-employee-charged-by-doj-for-cloud-security-fraud</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">srsejQtupKMD2J9L7MgNHK</guid>
      <description>The defendant allegedly hid her employer&#8217;s lack of security controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now is a good time to buy a Tesla &#8211; the EV giant is offering free upgrades and enticing finance deals to drive sales</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/now-is-a-good-time-to-buy-a-tesla-the-ev-giant-is-offering-free-upgrades-and-enticing-finance-deals-to-drive-sales</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FNA9BXzLKj8jFrB6cYP5cS</guid>
      <description>Been pondering buying a Tesla? It's just launched a range of incentives in North America to help boost sales &#8211; here's what you can get.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riding onboard with Rivian&#8217;s race to autonomy</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/riding-onboard-with-rivians-race-to-autonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075726</guid>
      <description>Rivian demonstrated the progress it's made, and in the process showed just how far it still has to go to make its cars autonomous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Zotac mini PC has the most powerful GPU ever bundled in a PC of this size &#8212; 16GB GeForce RTX 5060 Ti is competitive with 5070 Ti laptop edition</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-zotac-mini-pc-has-the-most-powerful-gpu-ever-bundled-in-a-pc-of-this-size-16gb-geforce-rtx-5060-ti-is-competitive-with-5070-ti-laptop-edition</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">khY8CUhAptrtj7UXuFnKCe</guid>
      <description>Zotac&#8217;s EN275060TC fits a desktop RTX 5060 Ti into a compact frame, delivering competitive performance through a hybrid PCIe power setup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Origin&#8217;s Next Mission Is Helping Redefine Who Gets to Go to Space</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/blue-origins-next-mission-is-helping-redefine-who-gets-to-go-to-space-2000699285</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699285</guid>
      <description>Should the mission proceed as planned, it will mark a major step forward for accessibility in spaceflight&#8212;sending the first wheelchair user beyond Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s favorite holiday gifts under $100</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/800440/best-gifts-under-100-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T16:22:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800440</guid>
      <description>Between all the new phones, smartwatches, and laptops we see throughout the year, it often feels like we're constantly being nudged toward shinier, more expensive gadgets. And I get it. As a self-professed gadget nerd, few things are more exciting than unboxing and setting up a new device. But the truth is, you can still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Pulls AI Recap Video After &#8216;Fallout&#8217; Mess</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-ai-recap-amazon-prime-video-anime-2000699210</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699210</guid>
      <description>Amazon is being forced to repeatedly learn a lesson: use AI slop, and get people yelling at you until you don't.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On n&#8217;y croyait plus : l&#8217;eSIM chez Free arrive sur Apple Watch, et il &#233;tait temps</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2909363_on-ny-croyait-plus-lesim-chez-free-arrive-sur-apple-watch-et-il-etait-temps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2909363_on-ny-croyait-plus-lesim-chez-free-arrive-sur-apple-watch-et-il-etait-temps</guid>
      <description>
C'est probablement la fonctionnalit&#233; la plus r&#233;clam&#233;e par les abonn&#233;s Free depuis 5 ans. L'attente est termin&#233;e : une mise &#224; jour des r&#233;glages op&#233;rateur (version 67.1) avec watchOS 26.2 vient d'activer le support des forfaits cellulaires en eSIM pour Apple Watch. Le P&#232;re No&#235;l est pass&#233; en avance chez Xavier Niel.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The long shot</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/842881/resurrection-bi-gan-interview-tracking-shot</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T16:14:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842881</guid>
      <description>The long take, the unbroken tracking shot, "the oner" - whatever you want to call it, filmmakers agree that it's one of the most difficult technical achievements in cinema. It's a feat of creativity, but also great coordination and choreography when a single, tiny mistake can ruin a shot. Some famous examples: the casino scene [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI signs deal to bring Disney characters to Sora and ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-signs-deal-to-bring-disney-characters-to-sora-and-chatgpt-144344820.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb1377cc-8db3-4931-8cd1-04f31b1995b4</guid>
      <description>It looks like Disney wasted no time delivering on CEO Bob Iger&#8217;s promise to bring AI-generated content to Disney+. On Thursday, the company announced the start of a three-year licensing agreement with OpenAI to bring more than 200 of its beloved characters, including those from Star Wars and Pixar, to the Sora app and ChatGPT.  With the deal in place, OpenAI users will be able to prompt ChatGPT to generate images that tap into Disney&#8217;s intellectual property, with costumes, props, vehicles and environments covered. The agreement does not include voices or &#8220;talent likenesses,&#8221; meaning Sora users...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Sphincters Tighten as Oracle Delays Its OpenAI Data Center Buildout</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wall-street-sphincters-tighten-as-oracle-delays-its-openai-data-center-buildout-2000699248</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699248</guid>
      <description>When the bubble pops, you can't say there weren't signs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some of our favorite gifts will cost you less than $25</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780844/best-gifts-under-25-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T16:09:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780844</guid>
      <description>Holiday shopping on a budget can feel constricting, especially if you've been invited to a white elephant or need a last-minute stocking stuffer. The good news is that, with this guide, you can leave that stress behind. Whether you're aiming for something practical or fun, we've found plenty of great gifts for under $25 - [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.2 est disponible : voici les 6 nouveaut&#233;s &#224; conna&#238;tre sur votre iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/ios/2909351_ios-26-2-est-disponible-voici-les-6-nouveautes-a-connaitre-sur-votre-iphone</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/ios/2909351_ios-26-2-est-disponible-voici-les-6-nouveautes-a-connaitre-sur-votre-iphone</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez avoir fini avec les mises &#224; jour pour 2025 ? Rat&#233;. Apple vient de d&#233;ployer iOS 26.2 et c'est plus dense qu'il n'y para&#238;t. Au menu : la traduction sur les AirPods qui arrive enfin chez nous, un Liquid Glass partout et, surtout, des failles de s&#233;curit&#233; critiques &#224; combler d'urgence.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas drops PBS, citing costs and loss of federal funding</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459720/arkansas-drops-pbs-citing-costs-and-loss-of-federal-funding</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459720/arkansas-drops-pbs-citing-costs-and-loss-of-federal-funding</guid>
      <description>The decision will end statewide access to PBS programming starting July 1, with the network rebranding as Arkansas TV.
The fallout from the Trump administration&#8217;s dramatic cuts to American public media is only just beginning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Van Dyke turns 100: The iconic actor shares these longevity tips as he celebrates a milestone birthday</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459810/dick-van-dyke-100th-birthday-iconic-actor-shares-these-longevity-tips</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459810/dick-van-dyke-100th-birthday-iconic-actor-shares-these-longevity-tips</guid>
      <description>Saturday is a big day for the entertainer extraordinaire. Here&#8217;s a look back at his impressive career&#8212;and how hitting the gym may have helped it last even longer.
Humans are a unique species, because of our collective knowledge of our own mortality. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), the average life expectancy for males in the United States is 75.8 years. That means entertainer extraordinaire Dick Van Dyke is defying statistics by turning 100 years old this Saturday, December 13....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit Sues Australia Over Teen Social Media Ban as Other Nations Consider Similar Laws</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/reddit-sues-australia-over-teen-social-media-ban-as-other-nations-consider-similar-laws-2000699275</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699275</guid>
      <description>The company says the law violates teens&#8217; political speech rights as other countries consider similar restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We found 70 stocking stuffers under $100 that are actually useful</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/843079/best-stocking-stuffers-christmas-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T15:57:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843079</guid>
      <description>Let's face it, it's easy to fixate on the big gifts that crowd around the Christmas tree. However, we'd argue that the true treasures are the small, useful, and thoughtful gifts tucked within stockings. That's why, for this guide, we've pooled together a bunch of tried-and-tested gadgets and goods to help bolster someone's everyday carry [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind-Bending &#8216;Einstein Cross&#8217; Reveals Ultrabright Supernova From an Unthinkable Distance</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mind-bending-einstein-cross-reveals-ultrabright-supernova-from-an-unthinkable-distance-2000699270</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699270</guid>
      <description>For the first time, astronomers have captured the brilliance of a superluminous supernova via gravitational lensing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With iOS 26.2, Apple lets you roll back Liquid Glass again &#8212; this time on the Lock Screen</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/with-ios-26-2-apple-lets-you-roll-back-liquid-glass-again-this-time-on-the-lock-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075684</guid>
      <description>Your iPhone clock doesn't have to be so "glassy" anymore, thanks to a new Apple software update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google and Apple roll out emergency security updates after zero-day attacks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/google-and-apple-roll-out-emergency-security-updates-after-zero-day-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075693</guid>
      <description>Apple released patches for all of its flagship devices to fix security flaws under attack. Google also updated Chrome to remediate one vulnerability exploited in the attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.2 has landed &#8212; here are the 7 biggest new features for your iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/ios/ios-26-2-has-landed-here-are-the-7-biggest-new-features-for-your-iphone</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">N3f95FvbQkjjFZBiNVLFs5</guid>
      <description>iOS 26.2 includes a few improvements to all sorts of apps and features, from AirDrop to reminders to Sleep Scores and beyond.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
