<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:38:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 200 Black Friday deals you can still get</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/832641/black-friday-2025-best-deals-tech-gadgets-still-available</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T17:33:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=832641</guid>
      <description>Black Friday is technically a thing of the past, but many of the best deals we told you about yesterday &#8212; including deep discounts on the AirPods Pro 3, the Pixel Watch 4, and the latest Kindle Paperwhite &#8212; are still kicking for now. In some cases, gadgets are out of stock at certain stores, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI says hackers have stolen $262 million in account takeover scams in 2025 so far - here's how you can stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/fbi-says-hackers-have-stolen-usd262-million-in-account-takeover-scams-in-2025-so-far-heres-how-you-can-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8NRxRrFFxsbbUoXkeffpmQ</guid>
      <description>Cybercriminals have stolen hundreds of millions through AI-driven phishing, fake stores, and account takeover scams targeting users across financial platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Fire TV Stick? No problem - this Roku Streaming Stick HD now costs as much as my Chipotle order</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/no-fire-tv-stick-no-problem-this-roku-streaming-stick-hd-now-costs-as-much-as-my-chipotle-order</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aW5tEMoSaSqHkSv9V9VptZ</guid>
      <description>The cheap Fire TV Stick alternative is now just $15</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airbus orders software fix to thousands of planes due to solar radiation risk</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/29/airbus-orders-software-fix-to-thousands-of-planes-due-to-solar-radiation-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071181</guid>
      <description>Flights were delayed and cancelled globally after Airbus ordered fixes to 6,000 of its A320 series planes, according to The Guardian. The company said it&#8217;s taking action because &#8220;analysis of a recent event involving an A320 Family aircraft has revealed that intense solar radiation may corrupt data critical to the functioning of flight controls.&#8221; Citing [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Survivor Series: WarGames - Stream it *FREE* with this trial offer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/wwe-survivor-series-wargames-free-trial</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LQttNBPA9PKSYYkbzjiKiA</guid>
      <description>Here's a quick guide on how you can stream the WWE Survivor Series: WarGames from anywhere in the world for free with this trial offer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm a VPN expert, and I've found the 3 Black Friday VPN deals you need to pick up while you still can!</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/im-a-vpn-expert-and-ive-found-the-3-black-friday-vpn-deals-you-need-to-pick-up-while-you-still-can</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UJtEa2YYheVRsRrHgJHUhe</guid>
      <description>Time's running short on some of my favorite Black Friday VPN deals of 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday sets online spending record of $11.8B, Adobe says</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/29/black-friday-sets-online-spending-record-of-11-8b-adobe-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071178</guid>
      <description>American consumers spent $11.8 billion online on Black Friday, according to data from Adobe Analytics, which says it tracks more than 1 trillion visits to U.S. retail websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta and Google could be about to sign a mega AI chip deal - and it could change everything in the tech space</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/meta-and-google-could-be-about-to-sign-a-mega-ai-chip-deal-and-it-could-change-everything-in-the-tech-space</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8S9MGFjdHP2BzAP5zKk6da</guid>
      <description>Rising demand, shifting alliances, and limited fabrication capacity create unpredictable conditions as Meta considers a long-term Google TPU hardware partnership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do people actually buy on Black Friday? Here are the most-bought items by Mashable readers in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/what-mashable-readers-bought-on-black-friday-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ehHni2N3dLYKxW09grLul</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered which of the million Black Friday deals are the most popular? Mashable readers flocked to Apple, DJI, and Pok&#233;mon deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested 15 cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T16:27:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>Editor&#8217;s note:&#160;Black Friday deals are still happening, so check out the latest and greatest discounts that today has to offer. You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Using a case relieves me of the worry that it will accumulate tons of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New West KnifeWorks Knives Are 20 Percent off Right Now (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-west-knifeworks-black-friday-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6920a5e9fc874455ea234835</guid>
      <description>These beautiful and sturdy chef's knives make great gifts (for yourself or others), and are 20 percent off right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 Best GoPro and Camera Deals for Black Friday (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/black-friday-camera-deals-2025-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69270b8147fc913b5deca1d1</guid>
      <description>Score a great deal on our favorite action cameras, 360 cameras, and more with these Black Friday sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cameron Has a Backup Plan for &#8216;Avatar&#8217; If &#8216;Fire &amp; Ash&#8217; Flops</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/james-cameron-has-a-backup-plan-for-avatar-if-fire-ash-flops-2000693222</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000693222</guid>
      <description>On the chance 'Fire &amp; Ash' isn't as big a hit as the last two 'Avatar' movies, Cameron will find a way to wrap up the series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>180+ Amazon Black Friday deals still live: AirPods, Kindles, Lego, and LG TVs are still available</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-black-friday-amazon-deals-2025-still-available</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01zT5i1aniaONbmJ6szvGdn</guid>
      <description>Amazon's Black Friday 2025 deals are still here, and you can buy Fire TVs starting at $99, plus record prices on Kindle, Bose, Lego, and Apple products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Protein Powder Deals and Supplement Steals (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/protein-powder-black-friday-deals-2025-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692749cdaf53e58219f32374</guid>
      <description>From protein supplements and electrolytes to greens powders and energy drinks, these are the discounted picks worth snagging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fujifilm X Half is on sale for what it should have originally cost</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/833668/fujifilm-x-half-camera-price-black-friday-cyber-monday</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T16:08:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=833668</guid>
      <description>Fujifilm&#8217;s unusual X Half elicited a lot of feelings from photographers when it came out earlier this year &#8212; from &#8220;That looks like so much fun,&#8221; to &#8220;Wait, it costs how much?&#8220; Its $849.95 list price felt way too high for what is, by all accounts, a fun, unserious little point-and-shoot. But its $649 sale [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve tested the latest Switch 2 controllers, and this one is the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/791574/best-switch-2-controllers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T16:00:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=791574</guid>
      <description>Editor&#8217;s note:&#160;Black Friday deals are still happening, so check out the latest and greatest discounts that today has to offer. If you choose to get an extra controller for your Nintendo Switch 2, you can spend a lot &#8212; and get a lot in return. Buying Nintendo&#8217;s own $89.99 Switch 2 Pro Controller, for instance, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behold, the black Apple Watch Ultra 2 is $200 off during Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/833432/black-apple-watch-ultra-2-black-friday-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-29T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=833432</guid>
      <description>Last year, I wrote that you do not need a black Apple Watch Ultra 2. It was simply a color refresh, I said. The original Apple Watch Ultra on your wrist was still perfectly fine. The landfills of the world were better off without Apple&#8217;s first-gen ruggedized smartwatch filling it. Also, suggesting that you spend [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best DJI deals still live after Black Friday: Record-low deals on mics, drones, power stations</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-black-friday-dji-deals-2025-still-available</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 20:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05hcvSvLUZrCx3dfaPvzSzP</guid>
      <description>The best DJI deals available to shop for Black Friday. Save on the Mic Mini, DJI Osmo 360, and DJI Mini 4K.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
