<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:40:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#160;: et si le premier appareil IA avec Jony Ive &#233;tait&#8230; une enceinte connect&#233;e&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/openai-et-si-le-premier-appareil-ia-avec-jony-ive-etait-une-enceinte-connectee.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327276</guid>
      <description>C'est d&#233;cid&#233;ment le feuilleton qui tient toute la Silicon Valley en haleine : quel sera le premier appareil d'OpenAI ? Tout ou presque y est pass&#233;, des &#233;couteurs au badge, en passant pourquoi pas par le stylo. Mais ce produit con&#231;u avec Jony Ive pourrait &#234;tre finalement assez banal, &#224; en croire une nouvelle rumeur cr&#233;dible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian man jailed for identity theft  that helped North Koreans get jobs at US companies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/ukrainian-man-jailed-for-identity-theft-that-helped-north-koreans-get-jobs-at-us-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094978</guid>
      <description>A Ukrainian man has been sentenced for helping North Koreans gain fraudulent employment at dozens of U.S. companies and funnel that money back to the regime to fund its nuclear weapons program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla loses bid to overturn $243M Autopilot verdict</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/tesla-loses-bid-to-overturn-243m-autopilot-verdict/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095005</guid>
      <description>"The grounds for relief that Tesla relies upon are virtually the same as those Tesla put forth previously during the course of trial"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI will reportedly release an AI-powered smart speaker in 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-will-reportedly-release-an-ai-powered-smart-speaker-in-2027-173344866.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1f68853-5e71-4e10-bf8e-0cea589cc12d</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is reportedly hard at work developing a series of AI-powered devices, including smart glasses, a smart speaker and a smart lamp. According to reporting by The Information, the AI company has a team of over 200 employees dedicated to the project.
The first product scheduled to be released is reported to be a smart speaker that would include a camera, allowing it to better absorb information about its users and surroundings. According to a person familiar with the project, this would extend to identifying objects on a nearby table, as well as conversations being held in the vicinity of th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman claims ChatGPT's adult mode will 'be able to safely relax the restrictions' of the chatbot, but firing a critic of the plan is a reason to be wary</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/openai/sam-altman-claims-chatgpts-adult-mode-will-be-able-to-safely-relax-the-restrictions-of-the-chatbot-but-firing-a-critic-of-the-plan-is-a-reason-to-be-wary</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5p64iQ86atqpbjeCUUEsnV</guid>
      <description>As OpenAI prepares to launch an adult mode for ChatGPT, the firing of a top internal critic has intensified concerns about safety, governance, and the company&#8217;s willingness to embrace internal dissent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Google's days numbered? Study finds AI bots are becoming more 'search-like' - and it's affecting how brands are being seen online</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/are-googles-days-numbered-study-finds-ai-bots-are-becoming-more-search-like-and-its-affecting-how-brands-are-being-seen-online</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tQtvJWmY99nwLnE2W5W2AX</guid>
      <description>Publishers are clearly reluctant to allow AI training bots, but it's imperative they allow access for AI crawlers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft teste une technologie capable de conserver des donn&#233;es pendant 10 000 ans</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2984325_microsoft-teste-une-technologie-capable-de-conserver-des-donnees-pendant-10-000-ans</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2984325_microsoft-teste-une-technologie-capable-de-conserver-des-donnees-pendant-10-000-ans</guid>
      <description>
Les &#233;quipes de Microsoft ont r&#233;alis&#233; une avanc&#233;e majeure sur le stockage de donn&#233;es sur verre. Une technologie exp&#233;rimentale qui permettrait de conserver des milliers de donn&#233;es durant 10 000 ans. &#160;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play Store&#160;: Google a bloqu&#233; 1,75 million d&#8217;apps dangereuses en 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/play-store-google-a-bloque-175-million-dapps-dangereuses-en-2025.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327269</guid>
      <description>S'il ne se passe pas une semaine, voire un jour, sans qu'une app Android se r&#233;v&#232;le &#234;tre une arnaque ou pire encore, on ne peut pas enlever &#224; Google ses efforts pour tenter de maintenir le Play Store &#224; un niveau de s&#233;curit&#233; correct. En 2025, 1,75 million d'applications potentiellement dangereuses ont &#233;t&#233; &#233;cart&#233;es de la boutique officielle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart glasses in court are a privacy nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/882030/smart-glasses-in-court-meta-mark-zuckerberg</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T12:11:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882030</guid>
      <description>When Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg arrived at a Los Angeles courthouse on Wednesday, he did so with a team that appeared to be wearing Meta's camera-equipped Ray-Ban smart glasses. Judge Carolyn Kuhl was concerned. According to CNBC, Kuhl warned anyone recording with the glasses, "If you have done that, you must delete that, or you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13-hour AWS outage reportedly caused by Amazon's own AI tools</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/13-hour-aws-outage-reportedly-caused-by-amazons-own-ai-tools-170930190.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a17f916d-18e0-47e3-939e-e9e6a677cbb7</guid>
      <description>A recent Amazon Web Services (AWS) outage that lasted 13 hours was reportedly caused by one of its own AI tools, according to reporting by Financial Times. This happened in December after engineers deployed the Kiro AI coding tool to make certain changes, say four people familiar with the matter.
Kiro is an agentic tool, meaning it can take autonomous actions on behalf of users. In this case, the bot reportedly determined that it needed to "delete and recreate the environment." This is what allegedly led to the lengthy outage that primarily impacted China.
Amazon says it was merely a "coincide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How OpenAI&#8217;s mission makeover is a test for whether AI serves society or&#160;shareholders</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91492770/openai-mission-makeover-test-for-whether-ai-serves-society-or-shareholders</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T17:08:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91492770/openai-mission-makeover-test-for-whether-ai-serves-society-or-shareholders</guid>
      <description>OpenAI had dropped its commitment to safety from its mission statement.
OpenAI, the maker of the most popular AI chatbot, used to say it aimed to build artificial intelligence that &#8220;safely benefits humanity, unconstrained by a need to generate financial return,&#8221; mission statement. But the ChatGPT maker seems to no longer have the same emphasis on doing so &#8220;safely.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Pok&#233;mon Presents will air next week to celebrate Pok&#233;mon Day 2026 and 30 years of the series &#8212; here's when to tune in and what to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-next-pokemon-presents-will-air-next-week-to-celebrate-pokemon-day-2026-and-30-years-of-the-series-heres-when-to-tune-in-and-what-to-expect</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3UCSW6KFWByuFhn9gTmrQn</guid>
      <description>The Pok&#233;mon Company has announced thatthe next Pok&#233;mon Presents will air next week on February 27, coinciding with Pok&#233;mon Day 2026 and the series's 30th anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA targets March 6 for Artemis 2 launch to take astronauts around the Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-targets-march-6-for-artemis-2-launch-to-take-astronauts-around-the-moon-170727116.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf8bedaa-f90c-4505-8ea8-e6652d8b6032</guid>
      <description>The Artemis 2 launch is edging closer as NASA has now set a target date for the 10-day mission to get underway. The agency is aiming to launch as soon as March 6 following a successful wet dress rehearsal on Thursday. The first attempt, which took place in early February, failed due to a hydrogen leak.During Thursday's rehearsal, NASA was able to fuel the Space Launch System (SLS) rocket with more than 700,000 gallons of liquid propellant and complete two runs of terminal count &#8212; the final step of the launch countdown &#8212; at the Kennedy Space Center in Florida.  While there was a hiccup due to a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Mobile Season 2 is here with some awesome new skins and a Lunar New Year event</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/mobile-gaming/call-of-duty-mobile-season-2-is-here-with-some-awesome-new-skins-and-a-lunar-new-year-event</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2gozaYfat8bA8DdoSCKj6U</guid>
      <description>Call of Duty: Mobile Season 2 has launched, bringing a wealth of new content to the FPS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Paradise&#8217; Season 2 Breaks Out of the Bunker and Brings Even More Tension and Thrills</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paradise-season-2-review-hulu-2000720809</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720809</guid>
      <description>Sterling K. Brown and Julianne Nicholson star in the post-apocalyptic series, returning to Hulu February 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrefour fait fortement chuter le prix de ce TV 4K Neo QLED 65&#8243;, 100 Hz et HDMI 2.1 sign&#233; Samsung</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2420472_carrefour-fait-fortement-chuter-le-prix-de-ce-tv-4k-neo-qled-de-65-100-hz-hdmi-2-1-signe-samsung</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2420472_carrefour-fait-fortement-chuter-le-prix-de-ce-tv-4k-neo-qled-de-65-100-hz-hdmi-2-1-signe-samsung</guid>
      <description>
Si vous souhaitez vous offrir un grand TV 4K de 65 pouces, mais sans pour autant vous ruiner, alors le Samsung TQ65QN85D pourrait bien vous convenir. Ce mod&#232;le QLED imposant est en ce moment propos&#233; &#224; seulement 779 euros au lieu de 1 499 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Safety Meets the War Machine</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/backchannel-anthropic-dispute-with-the-pentagon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698e319b992baed990efb280</guid>
      <description>Anthropic doesn&#8217;t want its AI used in autonomous weapons or government surveillance. Those carve-outs could cost it a major military contract.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Make way for the best TV show of 2026 so far' &#8212; Paradise season 2 on Hulu continues to knock an apocalyptic nightmare out of the park</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hulu/paradise-season-2-review-disney-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7SnCAw33cR5pfjsbLu93VJ</guid>
      <description>Paradise season 2 on Hulu and Disney+ has bigger twists, turns and emotions than season 1 &#8212; and it&#8217;s the most invested you&#8217;ll be in a TV show in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads posts can now be shared directly to your Instagram Story without leaving the app</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/threads-posts-can-now-be-shared-directly-to-your-instagram-story-without-leaving-the-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094960</guid>
      <description>The new Threads feature lets you share your posts &#8212; or anyone else's &#8212; to your Instagram Story without leaving the Threads app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer and Asus have stopped support for laptops in German patent dispute &#8212; and I think this is a truly worrying situation for consumers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/acer-and-asus-have-stopped-support-for-laptops-in-german-patent-dispute-and-i-think-this-is-a-truly-worrying-situation-for-consumers</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2LBTqGbX4n6jWZ2M96YbGZ</guid>
      <description>Needing a VPN to get support for your laptop is not an acceptable situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon blames human employees for an AI coding agent&amp;#8217;s mistake</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/882005/amazon-blames-human-employees-for-an-ai-coding-agents-mistake</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T11:52:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882005</guid>
      <description>Amazon Web Services suffered a 13-hour outage to one system in December as a result of its AI coding assistant Kiro's actions, according to the Financial Times. Numerous unnamed Amazon employees told the FT that AI agent Kiro was responsible for the December incident affecting an AWS service in parts of mainland China. People familiar [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&amp;#8217;s first ChatGPT gadget could be a smart speaker with a camera</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/882077/openai-chatgpt-smart-speaker-camera-glasses-lamp</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T11:52:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882077</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's first hardware release will be a smart speaker with a camera that will probably cost between $200 and $300, according to The Information. The device will be able to recognize things like "items on a nearby table or conversations people are having in the vicinity," The Information says, and it will have a Face [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piggyback&#8217;s fantastic Metroid Prime art book is nearly 30 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/821108/metroid-prime-1-3-a-visual-retrospective-art-book-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T11:51:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=821108</guid>
      <description>Metroid Prime 4: Beyond launched on the Nintendo Switch and Switch 2 in December, but if you&#8217;re itching for some more lore, Metroid Prime 1&#8211;3: A Visual Retrospective is a nice way to dig in, especially now that it&#8217;s on sale. Normally $49.99, you can currently buy the hardcover version for $36.59 (about $13 off) [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Galaxy Buds 4 dummy models have surfaced ahead of Galaxy Unpacked &#8212; and no one can ignore the striking resemblance to AirPods</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/two-galaxy-buds-4-dummy-models-have-surfaced-ahead-of-galaxy-unpacked-and-no-one-can-ignore-the-striking-resemblance-to-airpods</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EzFeftTDL2fNJiXiYX6vrC</guid>
      <description>More images of the Galaxy Buds 4 have leaked on X, and they confirm a lot of new upgrades we were expecting to see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;I Bought This Before Elon Went Crazy&#8217; Bumper Stickers Won&#8217;t Work on the New $60,000 Cybertruck</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/i-bought-this-before-elon-went-crazy-bumper-stickers-wont-work-on-the-new-60000-cybertruck-2000724535</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724535</guid>
      <description>Tesla introduced its cheapest Cybertruck model this week amid struggling sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#8217;s First Crewed Mission to the Moon in 50 Years Has Never Looked Closer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasas-first-crewed-mission-to-the-moon-in-50-years-has-never-looked-closer-2000724453</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724453</guid>
      <description>With a wet dress rehearsal successfully concluded, the Artemis 2 mission could launch in a matter of weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Rules Most of Donald Trump&#8217;s Tariffs Are Illegal</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/supreme-court-trump-tariffs-ruling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965536f98129f40ccaf80cd</guid>
      <description>In a 6-3 ruling, justices upended the Trump administration&#8217;s signature economic policy, potentially putting the US government on the hook for at least $175 billion in tariff refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Story 5 takes aim at creepy AI toys: &#8216;I&#8217;m always listening&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/toy-story-5-takes-aim-at-creepy-ai-toys-im-always-listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094957</guid>
      <description>Addictive, AI-enabled tablets are taking over, and also, Woody is balding in the new Toy Story movie, out June 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome reveals a host of new productivity tools - including a much-wanted split screen boost, and improved PDF annotation</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/google-chrome-reveals-a-host-of-new-productivity-tools-including-a-much-wanted-split-screen-boost-and-improved-pdf-annotation</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YYWW3JfTNTLK7YPMjVi3uJ</guid>
      <description>Google has added Split View, PDF annotation and save-to-Drive features to Chrome 145 to make your work even more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; C&#8217;est tellement efficace &#187; : on a test&#233; Grok dans deux Tesla, l&#8217;IA capable du meilleur comme du pire</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2984261_cest-tellement-efficace-on-a-teste-grok-dans-deux-tesla-lia-capable-du-meilleur-comme-du-pire</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2984261_cest-tellement-efficace-on-a-teste-grok-dans-deux-tesla-lia-capable-du-meilleur-comme-du-pire</guid>
      <description>
Grok, l'intelligence artificielle de xAI, arrive sur les Tesla via une mise &#224; jour &#224; distance. Nous avons pu l'essayer sur deux voitures diff&#233;rentes, de quoi percevoir les qualit&#233;s et les limites de cet assistant... un brin particulier.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Shocks World by Correctly Declaring Trump&#8217;s Global Tariffs Unconstitutional</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/supreme-court-shocks-world-by-correctly-declaring-trumps-global-tariffs-unconstitutional-2000724541</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724541</guid>
      <description>The landmark 6-3 ruling knocks down a load-bearing beam of Trump's economic agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh God, Vibe Coding on Smart Glasses Is a Thing Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oh-god-vibe-coding-on-smart-glasses-is-a-thing-now-2000724466</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724466</guid>
      <description>Two 2026 buzzwords for the price of one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prop bet</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/business/881967/polymarket-kalshi-journalism-sponsorship-ad</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T11:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881967</guid>
      <description>Substack has updated its partnership with betting platform Polymarket, "introducing native tools that make it easier to share, discuss, and debate prediction market data directly on Substack." Additionally, Polymarket will effectively pay "a cohort of creators," including Matt Yglesias, to use its data though the newsletter platform's pilot sponsorships program. This is just the latest [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coup de tonnerre&#160;: la Cour supr&#234;me invalide les droits de douane de Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/coup-de-tonnerre-la-cour-supreme-invalide-les-droits-de-douane-de-trump.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327235</guid>
      <description>C'est un &#233;norme coup de tonnerre au-dessus de la Maison Blanche. La Cour supr&#234;me am&#233;ricaine a en effet d&#233;cid&#233; &#224; une large majorit&#233; que Donald Trump ne pouvait pas d&#233;cider seul d'imposer des droits de douane au monde entier. L'arr&#234;t a des cons&#233;quences politiques et &#233;conomiques majeures, aux &#201;tats-Unis comme &#224; l&#8217;international.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s Prime Power Bank can quickly charge three devices, and it&#8217;s down to $80</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/881989/anker-prime-power-bank-20k-200-w-monster-hunter-wilds-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T11:08:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881989</guid>
      <description>Juggling multiple chargers for your gadgets while you&#8217;re commuting, working from a cafe, or traveling can get heavy (and pricey!) fast, which is why today&#8217;s deal on the Anker Prime Power Bank (20K, 200W) is worth checking out. It can quickly charge three devices at once &#8212; including laptops &#8212; and it&#8217;s down to just [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple : le code source de macOS 26.3 confirme 3 nouveaux produits pour la keynote, voici ce qu&#8217;on sait</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2985017_apple-le-code-source-de-macos-26-3-confirme-3-nouveaux-produits-pour-la-keynote-voici-ce-quon-sait</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2985017_apple-le-code-source-de-macos-26-3-confirme-3-nouveaux-produits-pour-la-keynote-voici-ce-quon-sait</guid>
      <description>
Alors qu'Apple vient tout juste de confirmer un &#233;v&#233;nement sp&#233;cial pour le 4 mars 2026, une fuite d&#233;voile d&#233;j&#224; une partie du programme. Au menu : le tr&#232;s attendu MacBook abordable sous puce d'iPhone et des &#233;crans Studio Display flambant neufs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Proton VPN extensions slip into Chrome Web Store &#8212; here&#8217;s how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/fake-proton-vpn-extensions-slip-into-chrome-web-store-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PkdzgjzWFtjs6nBTnPDWmQ</guid>
      <description>Proton has warned that fake VPN extensions using its branding appeared in the Chrome Web Store, with takedowns taking weeks. Here&#8217;s what happened, the risks for users, and how to protect yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISS Experiment Reveals the Secret Ingredient for Asteroid Mining: Microbes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iss-experiment-reveals-the-secret-ingredient-for-asteroid-mining-microbes-2000724479</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724479</guid>
      <description>An experiment on board the ISS tested the use of microorganisms to mine asteroids in the microgravity environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capcom asks players not to share Resident Evil Requiem spoilers ahead of launch after early copies leaked &#8212; 'We really want everyone to enjoy the game's story'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/capcom-asks-players-not-to-share-resident-evil-requiem-spoilers-ahead-of-launch-after-early-copies-leaked-we-really-want-everyone-to-enjoy-the-games-story</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pTsenjhvBJvBUiXqenwTD9</guid>
      <description>Capcom has asked players not to leak Resident Evil Requiem spoilers ahead of the game's official launch next week after physical copies of the game leaked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s metaverse leaves virtual reality</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/meta-metaverse-leaves-vr-horizon-worlds-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094929</guid>
      <description>Meta said it's shifting focus for Horizon Worlds to be "almost exclusively mobile" and that it will separate its Quest VR platform from the virtual world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Could Be Heading to a Big Queer Love Triangle</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-lgbtq-jay-den-darem-kyle-2000724518</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724518</guid>
      <description>One star thinks so, at least.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve spent months with the Drop + Epos PC38X wired gaming headset, and its audiophile audio quality and performance are hard to beat</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/drop-epos-pc38x-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rprdC9V9kFEsDiMjEFrEyk</guid>
      <description>The Drop + Epos PC38X could almost be considered old now, but it&#8217;s still great. If you can find it in stock, then it&#8217;s an easy recommendation for those looking for a wired gaming headset that can make your games&#8217; audio sing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a job market this bleak, more candidates pay for &#8216;reverse recruiting&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495390/in-a-job-market-this-bleak-more-candidates-pay-for-reverse-recruiting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495390/in-a-job-market-this-bleak-more-candidates-pay-for-reverse-recruiting</guid>
      <description>These days, unemployment stretches for months&#8212;so some workers are hiring recruiting agencies to do the groundwork for them.
Those in steady employment in 2026 might feel like they won the lottery, as the number of job openings dwindles at the same time as layoffs continue to hit.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI&#8217;s Osmo Pocket 4 Is Going to Be a Certified Hit if This Leak Is Real</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/djis-osmo-pocket-4-is-going-to-be-a-certified-hit-if-this-leak-is-real-2000724496</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724496</guid>
      <description>So long as DJI can skirt the U.S. ban, we may get a vlogging camera built for shooting at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Motors slashes 12% of its workforce as it seeks profitability</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/lucid-motors-slashes-12-of-its-workforce-as-it-seeks-profitability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094945</guid>
      <description>The layoffs affect hundreds of full-time workers in the US, according to an internal memo obtained by TechCrunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the &#8216;AI inflection point&#8217; means for journalism</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91492550/what-ai-inflection-point-means-journalism</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:42:41</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91492550/what-ai-inflection-point-means-journalism</guid>
      <description>All the mainstream attention on AI is creating pressure for journalists to increase their output. Here&#8217;s what they should do instead.
It&#8217;s hard to tell AI news from AI hype at the best of times, but the most recent surge around agents, triggered by many developers embracing Claude Code a couple of months ago, feels like something different. With the viral freakout over Moltbook, the agent social network, and the Super Bowl ad slap fight between OpenAI and Anthropic, AI has escalated to a new level of mainstream attention....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
