<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:03:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>There's no gaming chair quite like the ThunderX3 Core, and after two years, I'm still stuck to it like glue</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/thunderx3-core-gaming-chair-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8hW9AsxpHoCvECNQnVnS6W</guid>
      <description>The ThunderX3 Core gaming chair is an excellent ergonomic seat that adapts to your awkward positioning and ensures you're comfy and supported while you game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s artsy Frame TV has dropped to a record-low price for a limited time</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/883331/samsung-2025-frame-tv-anker-nano-travel-adapter-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T10:53:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883331</guid>
      <description>Not everybody wants their living room to be dominated by a big, hulking TV screen. Luckily, Samsung&#8217;s 2025 Frame TV, which is designed to fade into the background when idle, is discounted to its lowest price to date at Woot. Now through February 28th, the 43- and 55-inch panels are on sale for $587.99 ($312 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I found a great monitor deal for photo and video editing: 27-inch Acer Predator QD-OLED delivers rich color, deep contrast, and sharp 1440p detail &#8212; and it&#8217;s $160 off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/i-found-a-great-monitor-deal-for-photo-and-video-editing-27-inch-acer-predator-qd-oled-delivers-rich-color-deep-contrast-and-sharp-1440p-detail-and-its-usd160-off</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nkhRho4WKFvai96Noynczc</guid>
      <description>This Acer 27-inch Predator monitor deal lets creatives step up to 280Hz OLED performance for a fraction of the usual cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: The Galaxy S26 series, AI and other products we might see on February 25</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-the-galaxy-s26-series-ai-and-other-products-we-might-see-on-february-25-130000135.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company has announced its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year will take place on February 25, where it is expected to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup. Official invites have  been shared, but actual information on what devices are arriving then is still not completely confirmed. But as usual, we know a lot about what&#8217;s expected at Unpacked.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live from San Francisco tomorrow, and we'll most likel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine&#8217;s startups keep building</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/ukraines-startups-keep-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095951</guid>
      <description>In the four years since Russia&#8217;s full-scale invasion of their country, Ukrainian startups have done more than survive: they are still building and growing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta and AMD Team Up to Take on Nvidia in Massive AI Chip Deal</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meta-and-amd-team-up-to-take-on-nvidia-in-massive-ai-chip-deal-2000725893</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725893</guid>
      <description>The agreement could see Meta deploy up to 6 gigawatts of AMD chips for its data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen meatball recall: Product sold at Aldi could cause serious harm. Check your freezer now</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497774/frozen-meatballs-recalled-aldi-bremer-product-has-serious-risk-check-your-freezer-now</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T15:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497774/frozen-meatballs-recalled-aldi-bremer-product-has-serious-risk-check-your-freezer-now</guid>
      <description>An alert from the U.S. Food Safety and Inspection Service warns of a risk of injury if the recalled meatballs are consumed.
Meatball fans beware: A nationwide recall is underway for a popular brand of frozen meatballs sold at Aldi. The recall is due to the possibility that the product may contain metal fragments, which could cause serious injury if consumed. Here&#8217;s what you need to know....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ta&#239;wan et la menace chinoise&#160;: ce qui emp&#234;che Tim Cook de dormir</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/taiwan-et-la-menace-chinoise-ce-qui-empeche-tim-cook-de-dormir.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327845</guid>
      <description>Que se passerait-il si d'aventure, la Chine d&#233;cidait de passer &#224; l'acte et reprenait le territoire de Ta&#239;wan par la force ? Ce sc&#233;nario du pire a fait perdre le sommeil &#224; Tim Cook et pour cause : Ta&#239;wan produit la majorit&#233; des puces au sein de l'iPhone et d'&#224; peu pr&#232;s tous les appareils &#233;lectroniques au monde.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAM prices are sky-high, but you can take $80 off this 32GB G.SKILL Trident Z5 RGB DDR5-6000 kit right now using a promo code at Newegg</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ram-prices-are-sky-high-but-you-can-take-usd80-off-this-32gb-g-skill-trident-z5-rgb-ddr5-6000-kit-right-now-using-a-promo-code-at-newegg</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cJo2mvkSrHzqZaSrFSon4</guid>
      <description>Save $80 on 32GB of G.SKILL Trident Z5 RGB DDR5-6000 right now &#8212; a rare discount in today&#8217;s pricey DDR5 market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 14-inch portable laptop screen extender with a 1080p FHD IPS display will massively boost your productivity &#8212; and it's cheaper than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-14-inch-portable-laptop-screen-extender-with-a-1080p-fhd-ips-display-will-massively-boost-your-productivity-and-its-cheaper-than-ever</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cTFFvwSnzGXKESyt538DkL</guid>
      <description>Aoker's 14-inch portable laptop screen extender with a 1080p FHD IPS display can seriously boost your productivity and it's 21% off right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why enterprise AI ambitions are outpacing legacy modernization</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/why-enterprise-ai-ambitions-are-outpacing-legacy-modernization</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SHeRTTyk5A3FWhPrw2NRMX</guid>
      <description>Enterprise leaders want AI at scale, but legacy systems are holding transformation back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crimson Desert will feature both AMD's FSR Redstone and Nvidia's DLSS 4 &#8212; but we might not even need them</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/crimson-desert-will-feature-both-amds-fsr-redstone-and-nvidias-dlss-4-but-we-might-not-even-need-them</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cxUYwJVJbPnHSRN2mmQ23g</guid>
      <description>Pearl Abyss is hard at work optimizing Crimson Desert, and the additions of AMD's FSR Redstone and Nvidia's DLSS 4 tech are bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFERIY P280 Portable Power Station Review</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/aferiy-p280-portable-power-station-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bNUX7trBuG7GFXww5qT9p3</guid>
      <description>The AFERIY P280 is a serious bit of kit, designed for users who genuinely need high output rather than casual campsite top-ups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADT just bought the company that invented Wi-Fi motion sensing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/883661/adt-smart-home-security-origin-wireless-ai-wi-fi-motion-presence-sensing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T10:20:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883661</guid>
      <description>ADT, the 150-year-old company best known for home security, has acquired Origin Wireless in a $170 million deal to expand the capabilities of its security and smart home offerings. Origin Wireless developed algorithms that analyze how wireless RF signals bounce around a space to detect the presence and movements of people and objects without the [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nutribullet's new blender can hit speeds of 20,000rpm &#8212; your vegetables won't know what hit them</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/juicers-blenders/nutribullets-new-blender-can-hit-speeds-of-20-000rpm-your-vegetables-wont-know-what-hit-them</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bMTMfKvbhXWHEwECZsg6F6</guid>
      <description>The Nutribullet Core Power is packing a mighty 1,400-watt motor to handle difficult blending jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta strikes up to $100B AMD chip deal as it chases &#8216;personal superintelligence&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/meta-strikes-up-to-100b-amd-chip-deal-as-it-chases-personal-superintelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096083</guid>
      <description>Meta is buying billions of dollars in AMD AI chips in a multiyear deal tied to a 160 million-share warrant, deepening its push to diversify beyond Nvidia and expand data center capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian hackers target European firms with new spear-phishing cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/russian-hackers-target-european-firms-with-new-spear-phishing-cyberattacks</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QqVf2ENsZKPxMRFCZVWY57</guid>
      <description>APT28 resurfaces once again, targeting Western organizations with spear-phishing lures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TED&#8217;s Audacious Project raises $1 billion in 2 days to fund initiatives for these winning nonprofits</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497708/teds-audacious-project-raises-1-billion-2-days-fund-initiatives-winning-nonprofits</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T15:10:25</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497708/teds-audacious-project-raises-1-billion-2-days-fund-initiatives-winning-nonprofits</guid>
      <description>35 major donor families pledged $1.03 billion to nonprofits undertaking multiyear projects. 
Last October, 35 major donor families, calling their collaborative The Audacious Project, gathered in California and committed $1.03 billion to more than a dozen nonprofits whose proposed projects span multiple years and take on major challenges.The collaborative, housed at TED, announced the winning nonprofits Tuesday, after spending more than a year selecting the groups and helping them sharpen pitches for larger projects than philanthropic funders typically support. It&#8217;s not until the donors meet in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The invisible supply chain inside every mobile app</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-invisible-supply-chain-inside-every-mobile-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saU6U2TrSygWdgwTxYNCeh</guid>
      <description>Most mobile app risk comes from software your organization didn&#8217;t build, approve, or even know existed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oura launches a proprietary AI model focused on women&#8217;s health</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/oura-launches-a-proprietary-ai-model-focused-on-womens-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096089</guid>
      <description>The&#160;model&#160;supports questions spanning the full reproductive health spectrum, from early menstrual cycles through menopause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;For All Mankind&#8217; Season 5 Looks Like an All Out Martian Revolution</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/for-all-mankind-season-5-trailer-apple-tv-2000725680</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725680</guid>
      <description>Apple TV's alternate reality space race show returns on March 27, and here's the full trailer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final 4 days to save up to $680 on your TechCrunch Disrupt 2026 pass</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/final-4-days-to-save-up-to-680-on-your-techcrunch-disrupt-2026-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095367</guid>
      <description>Just 4 days left before savings of up to $680 on your TechCrunch Disrupt 2026 pass end on February 27 at 11:59 p.m. PT. Register to save at one of the most anticipated tech events of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the Control Panel ever die? Rare feature migration to Settings spotted in Windows 11, but don't get your hopes up for more of this</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/will-the-control-panel-ever-die-rare-feature-migration-to-settings-spotted-in-windows-11-but-dont-get-your-hopes-up-for-more-of-this</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xriN5Wd4ucqPv6GAbVxyrE</guid>
      <description>Microsoft shifts another Windows 11 feature to Settings from the Control Panel &#8212; but I expect the latter will still be with us in the 2030s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilo launches KiloClaw, allowing anyone to deploy hosted OpenClaw agents into production in 60 seconds</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/kilo-launches-kiloclaw-allowing-anyone-to-deploy-hosted-openclaw-agents-into</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5xagBDpjQ1Z8TEj3PZ227T</guid>
      <description>In the rapidly evolving landscape of artificial intelligence, the distance between a developer&#8217;s idea and a functioning agent has historically been measured in hours of configuration, dependency conflicts, and terminal-induced headaches. That friction point changed today. Kilo, the AI infrastructure startup backed by GitLab co-founder Sid Sijbrandij, has announced the general availability of KiloClaw, a fully managed service designed to deploy a production-ready OpenClaw agent in under 60 seconds.By eliminating the &#8220;SSH, Docker, and YAML&#8221; barriers that have gatekept high-end AI agents, Kilo is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It just got easier for your company to hire immigrant tech workers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496954/it-just-got-easier-for-your-company-to-hire-immigrant-tech-workers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T15:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496954/it-just-got-easier-for-your-company-to-hire-immigrant-tech-workers</guid>
      <description>The AI-powered immigration law firm Ellis wants to simplify work visa applications for companies&#8212;and workers&#8212;with a new subscription service that starts at $2,000 a month.
As President Trump has cracked down on all kinds of immigration, tech workers and students have been caught in the crosshairs. In a bid to curb use of the H-1B visa&#8212;a program that allows employers to hire skilled talent from abroad and is widely used across the tech industry&#8212;Trump imposed a whopping $100,000 fee on new applications last year.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Windscribe feature lets you wipe saved Wi-Fi networks with one click</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/new-windscribe-feature-lets-users-wipe-saved-wi-fi-networks-with-one-click</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pAYFYEoCu7xjwvxvusC28D</guid>
      <description>The Clear Wi-Fi History feature debuts in Windscribe&#8217;s Windows, Mac, and Linux VPN apps, adding a new layer of privacy on desktop. Here's all you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philips Baristina is the most affordable bean-to-cup coffee maker I've ever tested &#8212; and it's seriously impressive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/philips-baristina-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SPT3mu4JobuXHVihqzoYDP</guid>
      <description>A bargain espresso machine that makes brewing with fresh beans as simple as using coffee pods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT Changing the Way We Write?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/chat-gpt-em-dash-open-ai-hyphen</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01Bu8FGNBt3lKgaTuMPLDhT</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT's now characteristic em dash is more than a sign to spot AI writing &#8211; it's a centuries-old  literary tradition under threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backrooms teaser brings an internet urban legend to terrifying life</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/backrooms-teaser-a24-kane-parsons</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">076U0JkYpcRUVKOV2QGbHRi</guid>
      <description>Director Kane Parsons adapts his viral "Backrooms" shorts to the big screen. Chiwetel Ejiofor and Renate Reinsve star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic launches new push for enterprise agents with plugins for finance, engineering, and design</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/anthropic-launches-new-push-for-enterprise-agents-with-plugins-for-finance-engineering-and-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096091</guid>
      <description>It's a major opportunity to grow Anthropic&#8217;s enterprise client base &#8212; and a significant threat to SaaS products currently performing those functions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft appoints three Assassin's Creed veterans to oversee the franchise at newly formed Vantage Studios</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/ubisoft-appoints-three-assassins-creed-veterans-to-oversee-the-franchise-at-newly-formed-vantage-studios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vfFptnEGDSzx99khdiExKX</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft has named three experienced Assassin's Creed developers to lead the franchise at the company's newly formed Tencent-funded subsidiary, Vantage Studios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft has big plans for the next generation of SharePoint - and it might be the best way to get users to not hate it so much any more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-has-big-plans-for-the-next-generation-of-sharepoint-and-it-might-be-the-best-way-to-get-users-to-not-hate-it-so-much-any-more</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hDxAB6FhY8vZdWxNNZFMDX</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has given us the first look at a fresh new SharePoint design, as sharing with M365 is also set to get easier and smarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare disease&#160;isn&#8217;t&#160;rare&#8212;it&#8217;s&#160;a healthcare blind spot</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497745/rare-disease-isnt-rare-its-a-healthcare-blind-spot</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T14:32:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497745/rare-disease-isnt-rare-its-a-healthcare-blind-spot</guid>
      <description>A neonatologist shares why uncertainty shouldn&#8217;t be an accepted starting point in medicine.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's LaLiga blocks US government's Freedom.gov portal in piracy crackdown</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/spains-laliga-blocks-us-governments-vpn-enabled-freedom-gov-in-piracy-crackdown</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">euyH7p2aAMjP7fK2cD4BaS</guid>
      <description>Freedom.gov goes dark in Spain as football league nukes Cloudflare IPs. Here's all we know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Claude Code Claude Codes</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/883604/claude-code-ai-future-creator-privacy-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T09:20:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883604</guid>
      <description>Claude Code is a developer tool for developers. And yet, over the last year and especially the last few months, the team at Anthropic has seen a huge number of people, across industries and disciplines, figure out how to access their terminal so that they could build new stuff too. Few AI products have found [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497740/the-future-of-fashion</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T14:16:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497740/the-future-of-fashion</guid>
      <description>How AI collapses the distance between imagination and reality.
You&#8217;re invited to a holiday party with a dress code&#8212;cocktail attire. Instead of panic-scrolling through a bunch of dresses that look great on someone else and questionable on you, you open your laptop. A runway show starts in your living room. The lighting is cinematic. The music hits. And every model walking the runway is YOU. Same body, same proportions, same posture. You toggle the scene from dramatic spotlights to natural daylight to a candlelit restaurant, watching how each dress moves and fits in real life before you pick the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL Bandbox Solo Review: An AI Speaker You Can Actually Love</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jbl-bandbox-solo-review-an-ai-speaker-you-can-actually-love-2000724702</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724702</guid>
      <description>AI tools in music don't have to be slop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26&#160;: les offres de pr&#233;commande fuitent, pourquoi il ne faut surtout pas acheter la version 256 Go</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/samsung-galaxy-s26-les-offres-de-precommande-fuitent-pourquoi-il-ne-faut-surtout-pas-acheter-la-version-256-go.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327786</guid>
      <description>&#192; quelques heures de l'annonce officielle, les bonus de pr&#233;commande des Galaxy S26 se d&#233;voilent. Voici tout ce qu'il faut savoir et comment maximiser vos &#233;conomies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Sri Lanka vs. New Zealand in the 2026 T20 World Cup online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/sri-lanka-new-zealand-t20-world-cup-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07aEEummnLOJLVbz9pfDez4</guid>
      <description>How to watch T20 World Cup for free. Live stream Sri Lanka vs. New Zealand in the 2026 T20 World Cup for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conduent data breach grows, affecting at least 25M people</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/conduent-data-breach-grows-affecting-at-least-25m-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096048</guid>
      <description>The number of people affected by a data breach at government contractor giant Conduent is growing, as millions of people continue to receive notices warning them that hackers stole their personal data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Coogler's X-Files reboot gets the green light at Hulu</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/ryan-cooglers-x-files-reboot-gets-the-green-light-at-hulu-140735536.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ded6dcd-93e4-476e-9cff-0b1fab7a9daa</guid>
      <description>Good news for all Ryan Coogler fans: The Sinners director is bringing back a beloved TV show. Hulu has officially green lit a pilot of Coogler's X-Files reboot, a project three years in the making, Deadline reports.  Coogler has a five-year exclusive television deal with Disney, Hulu's parent company.&#160;
Coogler is directing and writing the pilot episode, with Jennifer Yale coming on as showrunner. She previously held the role on The Copenhagen Test. Actress Danielle Deadwyler, known for roles in Till and The Harder They Fall, has signed on as co-lead.&#160;
The show will follow the original storylin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC transit workers hit by Qilin ransomware - thousands of members possibly affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/nyc-transit-workers-hit-by-qilin-ransomware-thousands-of-members-possibly-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bQJG8CV9FEaTJpRd2E39na</guid>
      <description>Qilin hits the Local 100 of TWA, leaking sensitive member data to the dark web.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
