<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:28:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fate of the Old Republic&#8217; Puts &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; at an Incredible Crossroads</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-fate-of-the-old-republic-canon-legends-kotor-2000699066</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699066</guid>
      <description>Which way, Jedi? Either will change the relationship between 'Star Wars' and its past forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Don&#8217;t Want to Miss This Year&#8217;s Geminid Meteor Shower</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-dont-want-to-miss-this-years-geminid-meteor-shower-2000699108</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699108</guid>
      <description>All conditions favor a dazzling show across the skies this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD CEO Lisa Su Isn&#8217;t Afraid of the Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-amd-ceo-lisa-su-isnt-afraid-of-the-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939b36dac300a7f1db48d18</guid>
      <description>In this episode of Uncanny Valley we take you through our recent conversation with Lisa Su, and go behind the scenes of our Big Interview event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topping's new desktop DAC comes fully loaded for a very low price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/toppings-new-desktop-dac-comes-fully-loaded-for-a-very-low-price</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JT9DydSM6QfYUax6QLKX7W</guid>
      <description>Topping's E50 II DAC delivers a lot of musical bang for less than two hundred bucks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Kwon Gets 15 Years for $40 Billion Crypto Collapse as Victims Testify to Destruction He Caused</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/do-kwon-gets-15-years-for-40-billion-crypto-collapse-as-victims-testify-to-destruction-he-caused-2000699082</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699082</guid>
      <description>The collapse of Terraform Labs was part of a greater deleveraging event in crypto that culminated in the fall of FTX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA's new wireless charger is as cute as it is practical</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/ikeas-new-wireless-charger-is-as-cute-as-it-is-practical-195013422.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd893951-2e74-44bb-b869-441c312dc5d6</guid>
      <description>IKEA's revamp of its smart home products doesn't end with Matter support. The furniture and home goods company also has a line of new Qi wireless chargers, the best of which, the V&#196;STM&#196;RKE wireless charger, combines the functionality of a PopSockets-style phone grip with cable storage.
The $10 V&#196;STM&#196;RKE wireless charger is reminiscent of a bagel or donut, if you could take the top half of those ring-shaped foods and turn them inside out to create a cozy grip for your fingers. That same red silicone design also makes for a perfect place to store the charger's built-in USB-C cable, according to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers posing as law enforcement are tricking Big Tech to get access to private data</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-posing-as-law-enforcement-are-tricking-big-tech-to-get-access-to-private-data</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5s4kVqD2XEM6K2NBxLGyHM</guid>
      <description>Companies are being phished for data too, and sometimes compromised police inboxes are abused.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK, what&#8217;s going on with LinkedIn&#8217;s algo?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/ok-whats-going-on-with-linkedins-algo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:38:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075418</guid>
      <description>Women ran an experiment to see if LinkedIn's new algo was being sexist and thought they proved it. But there's more complexity involved, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel set to buy AI chip specialist as it scrambles to catch up with AMD, Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/intel-set-to-buy-ai-chip-specialist-as-it-scrambles-to-catch-up-with-amd-nvidia</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92g7647uRmfTGkxxbEg5qg</guid>
      <description>Intel plans to buy SambaNova but faces mounting pressure as valuation concerns shadow the sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything to Remember Before &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/everything-to-remember-before-avatar-fire-and-ash-2000696727</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696727</guid>
      <description>With James Cameron's latest blockbuster on the way, it's time to refresh yourself on the world of Pandora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.2 is here with Liquid Glass, AirDrop, and Apple Music updates</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839534/apple-iphone-ipad-mac-update-26-2</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T14:18:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839534</guid>
      <description>Today, Apple officially released iOS 26.2 for iPhone 11 and newer devices, which includes new Lock Screen customizations for you to adjust the opacity level, as well as the ability to use AirDrop with people who aren't in your contacts by sharing a one-time code with them instead. There are also new updates going out [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft buys 3.6M metric tons of carbon removal from bioenergy plant</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/microsoft-buys-3-6m-metric-tons-of-carbon-removal-from-bioenergy-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075667</guid>
      <description>Microsoft's data center ambitions have imperiled its 2030 pledge to remove more carbon than it generates, making carbon removal credits all but necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geminids peak 2025: A meteor shower will light up the December sky tonight. Here&#8217;s what time to look up</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459786/geminid-meteor-shower-peak-tonight-december-2025-geminids-best-time-to-see</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T19:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459786/geminid-meteor-shower-peak-tonight-december-2025-geminids-best-time-to-see</guid>
      <description>This cosmic phenomenon will put on one heck of a show this weekend, and the moon will cooperate, too&#8212;so don&#8217;t miss it.
If the holiday hustle and bustle is stressing you out, the night sky is providing a perfect moment to pause and wonder at some majesty this weekend, as the Geminid meteor shower (Geminids) is set to peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonys Afeela electric vehicle will offer digital license plates</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/sony-afeela-digital-license-plate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05XPVzlOHriqpoqk999PyqI</guid>
      <description>Sony's upcoming electric Afeela car will let you get up to unprecedented vanity plate shenanigans with a digital license plate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mmm, Qi donuts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843720/ikea-qi-2-wireless-charger-vastmarke-silicone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T14:10:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843720</guid>
      <description>After announcing new Matter-compatible smart home devices and stylish wireless speakers over the past few months, Ikea continues to expand its consumer electronics offerings with three new wireless chargers. They're limited to 15W Qi2.0 charging rates but are well priced and feature designs that look more like home decor accents than traditional tech accessories. The [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AT&amp;T data breach settlement deadline is almost here. How to file a claim in the $177 million case.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/att-data-breach-settlement-claim-7500-dollars</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05EfpkjvYu3nHoeziHvkopZ</guid>
      <description>Following a massive customer data breach, AT&amp;T is paying out a $177 million class action settlement. Learn how to file a claim before the December deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthfront IPO: Stock price closely watched today as financial platform starts trading on the Nasdaq</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459820/wealthfront-ipo-stock-price-today-financial-platform-on-nasdaq</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T19:04:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459820/wealthfront-ipo-stock-price-today-financial-platform-on-nasdaq</guid>
      <description>The Palo Alto company, which aims to provide financial services for Gen Z and millennial investors, joins a number of fintechs to go public this year.
Wealthfront Corporation is looking to rake in the wealth after going public on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalshi users are in an uproar over their Time &#8216;Person of the Year&#8217; bets</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459584/kalshi-polymarket-time-magazine-artificial-intelligence-sam-altman</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T19:02:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459584/kalshi-polymarket-time-magazine-artificial-intelligence-sam-altman</guid>
      <description>The storied magazine picked &#8220;Architects of AI&#8221;&#8212;not &#8220;AI.&#8221; 
Time magazine has named the &#8220;Architects of AI&#8221; as its 2025 Person of the Year, a decision that has sparked significant backlash from gamblers who lost out on semantics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanning Beds Are Giving Us Skin Cancer Where the Sun Doesn&#8217;t Shine</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tanning-beds-are-giving-us-skin-cancer-where-the-sun-doesnt-shine-2000699139</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699139</guid>
      <description>New research highlights the unique dangers of the UV radiation provided by tanning beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sued by preservationists over his White House ballroom project</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459815/trump-sued-preservationists-white-house-ballroom</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T19:00:22</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459815/trump-sued-preservationists-white-house-ballroom</guid>
      <description>The president has bypassed the federal government&#8217;s usual building practices and historical reviews with the East Wing demolition. 
President Donald Trump was sued on Friday by preservationists asking a federal court to halt&#160;his White House ballroom project&#160;until it goes through multiple independent reviews and wins approval from Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Government Websites Are Hosting PDFs Promoting Porn and Scams</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/u-s-government-websites-are-hosting-pdfs-promoting-porn-and-scams-2000699133</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699133</guid>
      <description>Not exactly a public service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33 practical smart home gifts that make everyday life a little easier</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/800449/best-practical-smart-home-gift-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T14:00:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800449</guid>
      <description>Smart home products are all about making everyday life a little easier, which is why they're some of the best and most thoughtful gifts you can give. Some people go all out building a multi-gadget IoT kingdom (like our resident smart home expert, Jen Pattison Tuohy), but a smart home is whatever your recipient wants [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube finally gets the TV update we've been waiting for &#8211;and there are 5 handy upgrades</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/youtube-finally-gets-the-tv-update-weve-been-waiting-for-and-there-are-5-handy-upgrades</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CJuf7NXHnwsHjWWC2NPQLG</guid>
      <description>The YouTube app for TVs is finally getting a long-promised makeover&#8211;here are all the handy improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move over, Bang &amp; Olufsen: Germany's Loewe is expanding to the US and it's bringing its super-premium OLED TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/move-over-bang-and-olufsen-germanys-loewe-is-expanding-to-the-us-and-its-bringing-its-super-premium-oled-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gxDmvpwQmUGLbZvHM5oNPK</guid>
      <description>Loewe's high-end OLEDs include some very striking designs and unusual materials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone is wrong about AI regulation, and the history of the Internet proves it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/everyone-is-wrong-about-ai-regulation-and-the-history-of-the-internet-proves-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RkDo5rGXohW6bwjAkZ7hRb</guid>
      <description>The US White House wants to stop states from regulating AI, and the states want their own AI regulation. What if they're both wrong?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director found guilty of scamming Netflix out of $11 million</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843923/hollywood-director-netflix-conviction-fraud-carl-rinsch</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:54:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843923</guid>
      <description>Hollywood director Carl Erik Rinsch was convicted of scamming $11 million from Netflix to spend on luxury items, including five Rolls-Royces and a Ferrari, as reported earlier by Deadline. A New York jury found Rinsch guilty of several charges on Thursday, including fraud and money laundering. Rinsch, who's known for directing 47 Ronin, was charged [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts for dads that have everything (but deserve more)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780847/best-dad-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:45:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780847</guid>
      <description>What do you get the man who says he has everything? It's a tough question - and one you have a limited amount of time to answer, given the holidays are nearly upon us. You could try dropping subtle hints or asking friends and family for suggestions, but they might save their best ideas for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why SpaceX Is Finally Gearing Up to Go Public</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/why-spacex-is-finally-gearing-up-to-go-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693c4753199888f1c10473e2</guid>
      <description>Like so many things in Elon Musk's orbit, a lot of it may come down to AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 devs dropped a big update after sweeping The Game Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/clair-obscur-expedition-33-devs-dropped-a-big-update-after-sweeping-the-game-awards-183628313.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b93d5a9-bdea-476a-8fc8-9849a55a04d8</guid>
      <description>Sandfall Interactive, the developer of Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, knows how to ride the wave. Right after the visually stunning RPG finished dominating The Game Awards, the team dropped a free "Thank You" content update for fans.This is no minor patch. It adds a playable environment and new boss battles for late-game players. The "Thank You" update also adds new music tracks, a Photo Mode and new text and UI localizations. On top of that, you'll find quality-of-life tweaks, including improved performance on handheld PCs.Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 won a record-breaking nine categories at The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday shoppers: Try these smart money-saving tips this holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459800/holiday-shopping-save-money-tips-experts</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T18:33:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459800/holiday-shopping-save-money-tips-experts</guid>
      <description>You can take advantage of websites that give you cash back on your grocery shopping or buy gifts in advance, experts say.
The holiday season means time with family and new memories, but it can also mean lots of spending&#8212;sometimes too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh Great, Smart Glasses That Record Everything You Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oh-great-smart-glasses-that-record-everything-you-say-2000699011</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699011</guid>
      <description>It's just audio for now, but the Mira set an icky precedent for always-on recording in smart glasses.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
