<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Il est maintenant possible de cr&#233;er des mini-applications aliment&#233;es par IA directement dans Gemini</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/il-est-maintenant-possible-de-creer-des-mini-applications-alimentees-par-ia-directement-dans-gemini.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315874</guid>
      <description>Il y a quelques mois, Google a annonc&#233; la sortie d&#8217;Opal, un outil destin&#233; &#224; coder simplement. Gr&#226;ce &#224; lui, il est possible de cr&#233;er des mini-applications sans programmation. Cet outil est d&#233;sormais accessible via Gemini sur le web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung will show off its expanded Micro RGB TV series at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/samsung-will-show-off-its-expanded-micro-rgb-tv-series-at-ces-141716449.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40be3553-908d-4f84-a6cd-aff65bd9abd0</guid>
      <description>Last year at CES, Samsung debuted its first mainstream Micro RGB TV, a 115-inch model that surprised us with its rich, vivid colors and $30,000 price tag. Now, the company has announced that it will be showing off an entire lineup of Micro RGB TVs at CES 2026 ranging from 55- to 115-inch models, promising to set "a new standard for premium home viewing."&#160;
As a reminder, Micro RGB is a unique new technology similar to Mini LED displays. Unlike the white backlights used on Mini LEDs, though, it uses tiny red, green and blue LEDs that produce more accurate colors and offer smaller and more contro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rad Power Bikes files for bankruptcy protection</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846201/rad-power-bikes-chapter-11-bankruptcy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:14:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846201</guid>
      <description>Rad Power Bikes, the once dominant electric bicycle brand in the US, filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection this week as it seeks to sell of its company. The move comes less than a month after Rad Power said it could not afford to recall its older e-bike batteries that had been designated a fire [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung P9 microSD Express card for Switch 2 drops to a record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-for-switch-2-drops-to-a-record-low-price-141947215.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50325636-eafa-42d9-b1ab-c62966fc036d</guid>
      <description>The Nintendo Switch 2 was the console launch of the year, and if you got your hands on one at launch, you may now be thinking about expanding its storage. There weren't a ton of microSD Express cards on the market with the Switch 2 first came out, and while they are still not ubiquitous today, you have more options than you did earlier this year. One of the latest to come out is Samsung's P9 Express card, and it's on sale right now.
Currently, you can pick up the 256GB Samsung P9 Express microSD Express Card for $33, down from $55. The 40 percent discount brings the microSD down to a new all-t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia s&#8217;appr&#234;terait &#224; r&#233;duire drastiquement la production de ses cartes graphiques</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2913571_nvidia-sappreterait-a-reduire-drastiquement-la-production-de-ses-cartes-graphiques</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2913571_nvidia-sappreterait-a-reduire-drastiquement-la-production-de-ses-cartes-graphiques</guid>
      <description>
Nvidia aurait d&#233;cid&#233; de freiner la production de ses cartes graphiques &#224; destination du grand public au premier trimestre 2026 pour faire face &#224; la crise de la RAM actuelle.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skana&#160;Robotics helps fleets of underwater robots communicate with each other</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/skana-robotics-helps-fleets-of-underwater-robots-communicate-with-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076834</guid>
      <description>Skana Robotics built a decision-making algorithm that helps unmanned vessels react and adapt to data from other vessels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet products hit by further security flaws - giving hackers access to systems and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/fortinet-products-hit-by-further-security-flaws-giving-hackers-access-to-systems-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jsE7H34HCiJ2FVcyH72C3J</guid>
      <description>Two new Fortinet flaws are being actively abused in the wild in reconnaissance attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best games to play on Xbox Game Pass in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/845376/xbox-games-pass-best-games-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:00:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845376</guid>
      <description>From pervasive layoffs to continued price hikes, things didn't go so well for Xbox in 2025. But even though Game Pass, the Xbox subscription service, isn't quite the deal it once was, there are still a lot of excellent titles to check out. This was an especially good year for indie titles, with breakout hits [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best shows streaming on Apple TV in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/845366/apple-tv-best-shows-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:00:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845366</guid>
      <description>Apple's streaming service got a new name this year - it dropped the "plus" and is now just Apple TV - but its actual programming didn't change all that much. And that's good news for sci-fi fans, as the service continued to cement itself as the preeminent destination for the genre in the streaming era. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best shows to stream on Disney Plus and Hulu from 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/845355/disney-plus-hulu-best-shows-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:00:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845355</guid>
      <description>Disney Plus and Hulu had an eventful year. Not only did the streaming services release a swath of exciting original shows and new seasons, but they're also in the midst of a transformation that will further integrate Hulu with Disney Plus. The "unified" app experience will have a revamped interface that's supposed to make it [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What could&amp;#8217;ve been Google&amp;#8217;s worst year turned into one of its best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/840856/google-end-of-year-recap-lawsuits-antitrust-ai-gemini-epic</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840856</guid>
      <description>2025 could have been a pretty disastrous year for Google. The company came in knowing it had three major legal battles to fight, increasing competition in the burgeoning AI market, and a new US president to adapt to. It looked possible - perhaps likely - that the company might be broken up and forced to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s 2025 in review</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/842852/https-www-theverge-com-tech-841025-2025-review-games-streaming-politics</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_package&amp;p=842852</guid>
      <description>The year 2025 has been, to put it mildly, eventful. If you&#8217;re like me, you&#8217;ve felt as if it&#8217;s pretty much impossible to keep up with things; every day brings something new, much of it baffling or enraging. But that&#8217;s not the case for everything &#8212; and so, as with past years, we&#8217;re using this [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Pluribus episode 8 on Apple TV?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/apple-tv-plus/what-is-the-release-date-for-pluribus-episode-8-on-apple-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SGMtJmZZB9QzZ35GkW5oDb</guid>
      <description>Pluribus' eighth episode is set to be released later this week &#8211; here's when we expect it'll arrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech bent the knee for Trump in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/big-tech-bent-the-knee-for-trump-in-2025-140000365.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61d6656a-4cf6-4f88-932d-9dbb70c6e15e</guid>
      <description>Sure, we've seen millions poured into lobbying and other means of influence during every presidency, but the last two years set a whole new bar. Business leaders, including those from almost every Big Tech company, stepped over themselves to prove fealty to Donald Trump's second administration. It's easy to see why: Their kowtowing was meant to secure regulatory favors, gain tax and tariff advantages and avoid Trump's ire. Ultimately, it was all in the service of appeasing their shareholders. Why else would Apple CEO Tim Cook, someone who typically cultivates a progressive image, hand deliver ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents fail 63% of the time on complex tasks. Patronus AI says its new 'living' training worlds can fix that.</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/ai-agents-fail-63-of-the-time-on-complex-tasks-patronus-ai-says-its-new</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6eUnHGQyoKL3Ki3t6Pp5gn</guid>
      <description>Patronus AI, the artificial intelligence evaluation startup backed by $20 million from investors including Lightspeed Venture Partners and Datadog, unveiled a new training architecture Tuesday that it says represents a fundamental shift in how AI agents learn to perform complex tasks.The technology, which the company calls "Generative Simulators," creates adaptive simulation environments that continuously generate new challenges, update rules dynamically, and evaluate an agent's performance as it learns &#8212; all in real time. The approach marks a departure from the static benchmarks that have lon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Ray-Ban Meta glasses just got a major audio update &#8212; especially for Spotify users</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/your-ray-ban-meta-glasses-just-got-a-major-audio-update-especially-for-spotify-users</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NzXtqeMNM3WCp5KNdRN6mN</guid>
      <description>Latest Ray-Ban Meta update brings Conversation Focus and Spotify soundtracking to you smart specs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo retire 250 &#8364; &#224; ce puissant laptop avec &#233;cran OLED 120 Hz et Ryzen AI 7 juste avant No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2912947_lenovo-retire-250-e-a-ce-puissant-laptop-avec-ecran-oled-120-hz-et-ryzen-ai-7-juste-avant-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2912947_lenovo-retire-250-e-a-ce-puissant-laptop-avec-ecran-oled-120-hz-et-ryzen-ai-7-juste-avant-noel</guid>
      <description>
Si vous cherchez un laptop performant pour bien commencer l'ann&#233;e, ce mod&#232;le de chez Lenovo pourrait bien vous plaire : avec son sublime &#233;cran OLED et sa puce Ryzen AI 7, le voil&#224; en promotion &#224; 849 euros contre 1 099 euros de base. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi l&#8217;&#233;tiquette obligatoire des voitures va radicalement changer dans les prochains mois</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2913275_pourquoi-letiquette-obligatoire-des-voitures-va-radicalement-changer-dans-les-prochains-mois</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2913275_pourquoi-letiquette-obligatoire-des-voitures-va-radicalement-changer-dans-les-prochains-mois</guid>
      <description>
Dans son &#171; paquet automobile &#187;, revenant notamment sur l'interdiction de vente de voitures thermiques en 2035, la Commission europ&#233;enne a introduit une nouvelle r&#232;gle sur l'&#233;tiquette &#233;nergie des voitures &#233;lectriques et thermiques neuves. Au programme, un affichage enrichi et standardis&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11&#160;: Microsoft d&#233;voile les nouveaut&#233;s &#224; venir dans la mise &#224; jour 26H1, voici tout ce qu&#8217;il faut retenir</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/windows-11-microsoft-devoile-les-nouveautes-a-venir-dans-la-mise-a-jour-26h1-voici-tout-ce-quil-faut-retenir.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315905</guid>
      <description>Microsoft a publi&#233; il y a quelques jours une nouvelle build de Windows 11 aupr&#232;s des membres de son programme Insider. Au programme, de nombreuses nouveaut&#233;s qui arriveront sans doute avec la mise &#224; jour 26H1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piratage au minist&#232;re de l&#8217;Int&#233;rieur : comment des hackers ont acc&#233;d&#233; aux fiches S</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/securite-applications/2913605_piratage-au-ministere-de-linterieur-comment-des-hackers-ont-accede-aux-fiches-s</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/securite-applications/2913605_piratage-au-ministere-de-linterieur-comment-des-hackers-ont-accede-aux-fiches-s</guid>
      <description>
On savait la s&#233;curit&#233; de l'&#201;tat parfois perfectible, mais l&#224;, on franchit un cap. Le groupe ShinyHunters revendique l'acc&#232;s aux bases de donn&#233;es les plus sensibles de Beauvau. Entre le logiciel CHEOPS et les identifiants partag&#233;s en clair, le minist&#232;re vient de s'offrir une le&#231;on de cybers&#233;curit&#233; dont il se serait bien pass&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Best Food Gifts, as Tested by Our Tastebuds (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-food-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">681531b59c460cecc5771650</guid>
      <description>From tinned fish to baked goodies, you can deliver the best-tasting treats to their door&#8212;even if you don&#8217;t live close by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; En s&#8217;accrochant d&#233;sesp&#233;r&#233;ment au moteur thermique &#187;, l&#8217;Europe est-elle en train de donner les cl&#233;s de notre industrie automobile &#224; la Chine ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2913285_en-saccrochant-desesperement-au-moteur-thermique-leurope-est-elle-en-train-de-donner-les-cles-de-notre-industrie-automobile-a-la-chine</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2913285_en-saccrochant-desesperement-au-moteur-thermique-leurope-est-elle-en-train-de-donner-les-cles-de-notre-industrie-automobile-a-la-chine</guid>
      <description>
Sous la pression de l'Allemagne, la Commission europ&#233;enne propose officiellement de revenir sur le dogme du "tout &#233;lectrique", offrant un sursis inesp&#233;r&#233; aux moteurs thermiques via une usine &#224; gaz r&#233;glementaire. Un revirement politique vendu comme du pragmatisme, mais qui ressemble furieusement &#224; un sabordage industriel face &#224; la Chine.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluesky claims its new contact import feature is &#8216;privacy-first&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846175/bluesky-find-your-friends-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T08:23:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846175</guid>
      <description>Bluesky is finally letting you find people you already know, one of several common features on other social platforms, like notifications and bookmarks, that have been notably absent at the growing upstart. Unlike rivals, it claims it's not sacrificing privacy to do it. The Find Friends feature is "privacy-first by design," unlike what Bluesky says [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entre Netflix et Paramount, Warner Bros a choisi son camp</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/2913537_entre-netflix-et-paramount-warner-bros-a-choisi-son-camp</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/2913537_entre-netflix-et-paramount-warner-bros-a-choisi-son-camp</guid>
      <description>
Le feuilleton qui secoue Hollywood vient de prendre un tournant d&#233;cisif. Le conseil d&#8217;administration de Warner Bros Discovery a tranch&#233; : il demande &#224; ses actionnaires de rejeter l&#8217;offre de 108 milliards de dollars de Paramount Skydance. Pourquoi refuser un tel ch&#232;que ? Parce que derri&#232;re les chiffres, la r&#233;alit&#233; financi&#232;re est bien plus fragile qu'il n'y para&#238;t.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get half off MasterClass subscriptions for the holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-half-off-masterclass-subscriptions-for-the-holiday-season-150520799.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b02af539-ee42-4564-83c2-a1439939b074</guid>
      <description>If you want to learn a new skill in the new year or brush up on some skills you already have, MasterClass could be a good option for you. It's even more accessible now that the company is running a holiday promotion that knocks 50 percent off subscriptions. For the top-tier Premium plan, which includes offline mode and use on up to six devices, you'll pay $120 for the year instead of the usual $240. The entry-level plan, which supports just one device and doesn't offer offline viewing, is marked down to $60 from $120.


Over the past few years, MasterClass has grown to over 200 classes, sessio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Rolls Out Free Generative AI for Creative Cloud Pro Users as a Limited-Time Bonus</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/adobe-rolls-out-free-generative-ai-for-creative-cloud-pro-users-as-a-limited-time-bonus-2000696575</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696575</guid>
      <description>Over 20 AI-enhanced apps and tools, including unlimited Firefly and 3rd-party image generations, make Adobe the industry leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon &amp; Co s&#8217;habillent en p&#232;re No&#235;l pour livrer vos cadeaux &#224; temps : voici les meilleures offres Tech &#224; glisser sous le sapin</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913097_cest-noel-dans-une-semaine-voici-les-meilleures-offres-pour-avoir-ses-cadeaux-a-temps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913097_cest-noel-dans-une-semaine-voici-les-meilleures-offres-pour-avoir-ses-cadeaux-a-temps</guid>
      <description>
Si vous n'avez pas encore fini vos achats de fin d'ann&#233;e, pas d'inqui&#233;tudes. Il reste encore une semaine et beaucoup d'enseignes comme Amazon, Boulanger ou encore Cdiscount et Fnac-Darty, continuent de faire des offres avec une livraison garantie avant le 25 d&#233;cembre. Voici les promotions en temps r&#233;el qui peuvent sauver votre No&#235;l. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Discovery rejects Paramount's hostile bid</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/warner-bros-discovery-rejects-paramounts-hostile-bid-131055882.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b68373cf-ab90-4ac0-8779-da1107cd50eb</guid>
      <description>Warner Bros. Discovery's board has formally rejected the $108 billion takeover bid from Paramount Skydance, the company announced. WBD said it remains committed to its $82.7 billion deal with Netflix, which would close some time next year, pending regulatory approval.&#160;
"[The board] has unanimously determined that the tender offer launched by Paramount Skydance on December 8, 2025 is not in the best interests of WBD and its shareholders and does not meet the criteria of a "Superior Proposal" under the terms of WBD's merger agreement with Netflix announced on December 5, 2025," the studio said i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 Best Stocking Stuffers (2025): Unique and Unconventional</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-stocking-stuffers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">671bcf6b65121b8b5d058224</guid>
      <description>Start off on the right foot (and buy the grown-ups some time to make coffee) with these excellent, tiny gifts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacuum cleaner features ranked from 'essential' to 'unnecessary', by a professional tester</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/vacuum-cleaner-features-ranked-from-essential-to-unnecessary-by-a-professional-tester</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wAhZDX3Tf3wXCC5ho8dxXd</guid>
      <description>From headlamps to sliders, these are the features worth prioritizing, and those you can ignore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan oil giant PVDSA hit by cyberattack amid US conflict</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/venezuelan-oil-giant-pvdsa-hit-by-cyberattack-amid-us-conflict</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3FLsvwHGeZer534V5fre7j</guid>
      <description>The Venezuelan Oil Ministry has been hit by a cyberattack, which it believes was carried out by the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gizmodo Tech Reporter Jody Serrano&#8217;s 11 Fun and Funky Coffee Mugs for Those Who Think It&#8217;s Too Complicated to Give Tech Gifts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gizmodo-tech-reporter-jody-serranos-11-fun-and-funky-coffee-mugs-for-those-who-think-its-too-complicated-to-give-tech-gifts-2000700167</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700167</guid>
      <description>What's the common denominator among all tech enthusiasts? Coffee mugs. They're the best underrated gift. The nerdier the better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul McGann Addresses Those Bizarre Rumors About a &#8216;Doctor Who&#8217; Return</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paul-mcgann-doctor-who-billie-piper-ai-set-pictures-2000700400</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700400</guid>
      <description>Plus, get a new look at Christopher Nolan's take on 'The Odyssey'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best subscription gifts to send to your loved ones this Christmas: Disney+ bundle, MasterClass, Field Notes and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-subscription-gifts-to-send-to-your-loved-ones-this-christmas-disney-bundle-masterclass-field-notes-and-more-141830326.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a7539fe-7e42-38f1-84c0-462b893fa96c</guid>
      <description>There are way too many online services and subscriptions to keep track of these days, but the flip side is there&#8217;s a tool for just about everything. Time is just about up to get a physical gift shipped in time for the holidays, so below we&#8217;ve pulled together some of our favorite digital gifts and subscriptions, including time-tested video, music and gaming services as well as tools to clear your mental space and learn new skills. There are also a few subscriptions that provide ongoing, IRL deliveries, if you think your giftee will appreciate the nostalgic charm of a physical object.
Best digit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 2025, wearables made a hard pivot to AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/838876/2025-ai-wearables-smart-glasses-pendants-fitness</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=838876</guid>
      <description>Years from now, I'll look back at 2025 as the year when a fundamental shift happened in wearable technology. Over the last decade, the category has been synonymous with health and fitness. In many ways, that association is still the primary one. But this year, I've seen an increasing number of tech companies pitch another [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexa Home Theater: Everything you need to know about Amazon's newest Echo feature</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/alexa-home-theater-everything-you-need-to-know-about-amazons-newest-echo-feature-130000328.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e569cf5c-f654-4867-baed-83e0c96154d0</guid>
      <description>When Amazon&#8217;s latest Echo speakers arrived in October, a feature the company spent time hyping during its fall devices event was missing. Alexa Home Theater arrived in late November, allowing owners of a recent Fire TV device and either of the new Echo speakers the ability to use up to five units and an Echo Sub as a surround sound setup. The main selling point is that the underlying tech allows you to put the speakers wherever you want and Alexa Home Theater will handle the rest. A robust array of speakers is a considerable investment, though, and there are limitations to Amazon&#8217;s latest play...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch PSG vs. Flamengo online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/psg-vs-flamengo-fifa-intercontinental-cup-final-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0219lZfmQ9n37LALQpjtSmf</guid>
      <description>How to watch FIFA Intercontinental Cup for free. Live stream PSG vs. Flamengo in the FIFA Intercontinental Cup final for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft explains how Windows 11's AI agents will get access to your files &#8211; but bigger worries remain</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/microsoft-explains-how-windows-11s-ai-agents-will-get-access-to-your-files-but-bigger-worries-remain</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GMkCmPaHZoEuEVG9FVYcuk</guid>
      <description>Microsoft calms some fears about Windows 11's AI agents, clarifying permissions around file access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le t&#233;lescope Nancy Grace Roman percera-t-il l'&#233;nigme de l'&#233;nergie noire en &#233;tudiant les vides cosmiques ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-telescope-nancy-grace-roman-percera-t-il-enigme-energie-noire-etudiant-vides-cosmiques-128653/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:48:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-telescope-nancy-grace-roman-percera-t-il-enigme-energie-noire-etudiant-vides-cosmiques-128653/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>L'expansion de l'Univers semble s'acc&#233;l&#233;rer sous l'effet paradoxalement r&#233;pulsif de la gravitation en pr&#233;sence de la myst&#233;rieuse &#233;nergie noire. Mais sa nature sera peut-&#234;tre r&#233;v&#233;l&#233;e en &#233;tudiant les &#233;tranges vides cosmiques entre les filaments form&#233;s d'amas de galaxies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La bonne affaire du jour, c&#8217;est ce TV 4K QLED gigantesque de 98&#8243; et 144 Hz avec 480 &#8364; de remise</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913251_la-bonne-affaire-du-jour-cest-ce-tv-4k-qled-gigantesque-de-98-et-144-hz-avec-480-e-de-remise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913251_la-bonne-affaire-du-jour-cest-ce-tv-4k-qled-gigantesque-de-98-et-144-hz-avec-480-e-de-remise</guid>
      <description>
M&#234;me si ce n'est pas &#224; la port&#233;e de tous, il est possible d'avoir un TV g&#233;ant d'une diagonale de 98 pouces pour un prix raisonnable, comme ce TCL 98P8K qui passe de 1 999 euros &#224; 1 521 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; un code promo.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Revamped iMac Pro Could Be Big, Expensive, and Exactly What I Need</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/revamped-imac-pro-could-be-big-expensive-and-exactly-what-i-need-2000700452</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700452</guid>
      <description>A giant iMac would also cost a fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI reveals major hire to lead global Stargate data center expansion</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/openai-reveals-major-hire-to-lead-global-stargate-data-center-expansion</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nsuNzNgVUFGyubXgo2Y4yG</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's Stargate expansion to boost government adoption of AI is being led by former UK Chancellor George Osborne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walmart just dropped a gaming laptop with an RTX 5070 Ti for $1,299 &#8211; the lowest price I've seen yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/walmart-just-dropped-a-gaming-laptop-with-an-rtx-5070-ti-for-usd1-299-the-lowest-price-ive-seen-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ZrfwaEo48QGqXcwbUYDCi</guid>
      <description>Get an MSI gaming laptop with a high-end RTX 5070 Ti graphics card for just $1,299 with this last-minute deal at Walmart.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
