<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:18:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I just want to keep unfolding the Samsung Z Trifold</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854352/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T23:02:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854352</guid>
      <description>Holding the Z Trifold confirmed my suspicions: it's a tablet with a phone attached. And after spending an hour folding and unfolding it, I'm pretty much ready to trade in the single-hinge foldable I've been carrying for the past couple of weeks. I used the Google Pixel 10 Pro Fold over the holidays as my [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is This the Thinnest Tablet Ever?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/is-this-the-thinnest-tablet-ever-2000705357</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705357</guid>
      <description>Maybe?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG TVs at CES 2026: A stunning Wallpaper set, glorious Micro RGB colors and a better Gallery TV</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/lg-tvs-at-ces-2026-a-stunning-wallpaper-set-glorious-micro-rgb-colors-and-a-better-gallery-tv-033739600.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d852af20-a0db-4d1d-8922-0ed895316e13</guid>
      <description>LG usually announces its CES TV lineup well ahead of the show, but this year the company had a surprise at CES 2026: The return of its ultra-thin "Wallpaper" TV. Now it's toting a gorgeous OLED screen and wireless connectivity, and it's about as thin as a pencil. We got a chance to check out the Wallpaper TV in action during a CES preview event, as well as the previously announced Gallery and Micro RGB sets. LG still has its typically OLED and LED sets around, but it's clear that 2026 will be filled with intriguing TVs for a variety of consumers.LG's 2026 Wallpaper OLED TVDevindra Hardawar for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG brought back the Wallpaper TV for CES and ditched the companion sound bar</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/lg-brought-back-the-wallpaper-tv-for-ces-and-ditched-the-companion-sound-bar-030057927.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70a8d691-0bd2-434b-a313-e68dacacba6c</guid>
      <description>It's been nearly 10 years since LG first introduced its Wallpaper TV that was so thin that the mounting process felt like applying wallpaper. After eventually discontinuing the ultra-thin TVs in 2020, LG is finally reviving the Wallpaper TV series with the OLED evo W6 that will make its debut at CES 2026. LG is marketing the updated Wallpaper TV as the "world's thinnest" OLED that's truly wireless, making some major upgrades to the original.
Instead of the companion soundbar that housed all the ports, LG designed the Zero Connect Box that hosts all the inputs and can transmit from up to roughl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut the fridge door!</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853758/shut-the-fridge-door</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853758</guid>
      <description>Samsung's latest update to its Family Hub smart fridge line adds a feature I've always wanted - voice-activated door opening and closing. Using the device's built-in Bixby voice control, you will soon be able to say "Shut the fridge door," or "Open the door," and your machine will obey. According to a press release from [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG&#8217;s Wallpaper OLED TV returns to CES, and it&#8217;s wafer thin</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853886/lgs-wallpaper-oled-tv-returns-to-ces-and-its-wafer-thin</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T22:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853886</guid>
      <description>The amazingly thin wallpaper design from LG is back. The first Wallpaper TV was released back in 2017, and it's been six years since we saw the last one. But LG has revived the product line with the LG OLED evo W6, and I've seen it here at CES. The TV body is only 9mm [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung reveals upgraded OLED TVs and super-sized screens at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/embargoed-5th-jan-3am-gmt-samsung-reveals-upgraded-oled-tvs-super-sized-screens-and-a-new-lifestyle-projector-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cGPi2i5BUMtXkPwJbXCvT</guid>
      <description>Samsung has announced its TVs for 2026, and they include new OLEDs and big screen LEDs, alongside the previously revealed micro RGB sets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I saw Samsung's world-first 130-inch RGB TV &#8212; and it's one beautiful beast</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/i-saw-samsungs-world-first-130-inch-rgb-tv-and-its-one-beautiful-beast</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">W2DpFnvxhfwDoe2kMNJXVT</guid>
      <description>It comes in a special frame-like stand so you don't need to worry about how the hell you'll wall-mount it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live &#8212; all the latest news from the world's biggest tech show</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/ces-2026-live-all-the-latest-news-from-the-worlds-biggest-tech-show</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bUWC3trkCwNntuhmUmmGkC</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is about to get underway and we're live at the show &#8211;here's all of the latest tech news from Vegas as it happens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweekar turns the Tamagotchi into a physical AI pocket pet that won't die on you</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/sweekar-turns-the-tamagotchi-into-a-physical-ai-pocket-pet-that-wont-die-on-you-023525228.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a3fbcba-5920-49ef-b571-5cd38cdbf9be</guid>
      <description>Takway, a startup that wants to be the "Nintendo of the AI robot era," has unveiled a Tamagotchi-like virtual pet at CES 2026 that's meant to go with you everywhere and develop a unique personality in the process. Sweekar is an AI companion built into a palm-sized toy, a cutesy egg-shaped device with ears and a screen for its face. As with a Tamagotchi, you'll have to feed and play with it to keep it happy and healthy, and its mood and facial expressions will reflect your care. But this virtual pet will remember your voice and the activities you've done together &#8212; and once it's grown up, it wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese startup Ludens AI brought two very adorable robots to CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/japanese-startup-ludens-ai-brought-two-very-adorable-robots-to-ces-2026-021914130.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b65eed8a-78cb-474d-a297-6f1cf96d3e7d</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is already shaping up to be an interesting year for robots. But while some companies are chasing humanoids that can help you do stuff, there are also a surprising number of robots whose main job is to be cute and keep you company.Japanese startup Ludens AI is showing off two extremely adorable robot companions at CES. Cocomo is an autonomous robot pet that can follow you around the house and respond to voice and touch. It has a fuzzy, egg-shaped body, but the version we saw at CES was wearing an orange suit with ears that made it look a bit like a teddy bear. It was moving around on a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
