<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:38:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Block, the parent of Square and Cash App, is laying off over 4,000 people</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/block-the-parent-of-square-and-cash-app-is-laying-off-over-4000-people-223343068.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbc52635-39ff-4560-8b58-3e95b29b5f4e</guid>
      <description>Block is the latest business to announce layoffs, with the operator of payment platforms Square and Cash App opting to cut jobs in favor of using more AI tools. The financial tech company, helmed by Twitter founder Jack Dorsey, is slashing its current staff of 10,000 to "just under 6,000." CNBC highlighted a letter Block sent to shareholders announcing the decision to nearly halve its workforce. According to the message from Dorsey:&#160;"The core thesis is simple. Intelligence tools have changed what it means to build and run a company. We're already seeing it internally. A significantly smaller t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal might not be looking to sell itself, report</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/paypal-might-not-be-looking-to-sell-itself-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097629</guid>
      <description>PayPal may not be in talks to be acquired, sources have told Semafor, after a previous news report that Stripe was sniffing around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Block cuts nearly half of its staff in AI gamble</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885710/jack-dorsey-block-layoffs-job-cuts-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T17:11:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885710</guid>
      <description>Jack Dorsey's Block, the financial tech company that runs Square and the Cash app, is cutting its workforce by "nearly half" and axing more than 4,000 jobs. The company will shrink from more than 10,000 people to less than 6,000, Dorsey says in a post on X. And the reason why? AI. "We're not making [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tinkerer accidentally gets access to thousands of DJI Romo robot vacuums</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/tinkerer-accidentally-gets-access-to-thousands-of-dji-romo-robot-vacuums</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Dgw2B3xJgCWqWcmk4QQBWB</guid>
      <description>A tinkerer accidentally accessed thousands of DJI Romo vacuums, exposing live video, floor plans, and raising serious IoT privacy concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo leak reveals a foldable gaming handheld that&amp;#8217;s also a Windows laptop</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885656/lenovo-legion-go-fold-concept-leak</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T17:08:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885656</guid>
      <description>Lenovo's next gaming laptop could be a shapeshifting foldable called the Legion Go Fold, which can be used as a laptop or a handheld gaming PC with two different display sizes, as WindowsLatest reports. Leaked images of the device show it attached to both a keyboard and controllers, with a hinge in the middle of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guitar Hero vets RedOctane reveal their new music game</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/guitar-hero-vets-redoctane-reveal-their-new-music-game-220809719.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8baafaac-426b-40a3-b76c-059f5f85af69</guid>
      <description>RedOctane Games, a relaunched version of one of the studios behind the very first Guitar Hero, has shared a first trailer for its new music game, Stage Tour. The original RedOctane was shut down by Activision in 2010, and only recently reformed under Embracer Freemode to create a new music game franchise in August 2025. Stage Tour is playable solo or with other players in a band, according to RedOctane, and supports inputs from a keyboard and mouse on top of the expected guitar, drums and microphone accessories. The studio plans to primarily offer the game digitally, but hopes to also sell a b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Melting Glaciers Actually Slow Climate Change?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/could-melting-glaciers-actually-slow-climate-change-2000727302</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727302</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s a comforting idea, but a new study did not find evidence to support it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Got Its Best Ratings for 30 Minutes of Men Hobbling</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-episode-6-ratings-hbo-game-of-thrones-2000727248</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727248</guid>
      <description>The season one finale of the 'Game of Thrones' spin-off sent its battered characters off into the sunset with many, many eyeballs watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why no magnets in Galaxy S26? Samsung R&amp;#038;D chief explains</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/885616/samsung-galaxy-s26-no-magnets-because-people-use-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T16:57:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885616</guid>
      <description>Magnet rings have changed my life. I grip and mount and satisfyingly snap awesome accessories on and off my phone all day. Even Samsung sells neat ones like these folding magnetic mirrors. But unlike Apple and Google, Samsung refuses to put the magnets inside the phone. Why? I asked Samsung's Won-Joon Choi, the executive in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Will Notify Parents When Teens Use Search Terms Related to Suicide</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/instagram-will-notify-parents-when-teens-use-search-terms-related-to-suicide-2000727276</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727276</guid>
      <description>The new safety feature comes as social media platforms face growing legal pressure over how they affect minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman&#8217;s Creepy Eyeball-Scanning Verification Service Is Coming to a Gap Store Near You</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altmans-creepy-eyeball-scanning-verification-service-is-coming-to-a-gap-store-near-you-2000727253</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727253</guid>
      <description>Keep your eye out for the orb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Elusive Color in Chemistry Might Surprise You</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-most-elusive-color-in-chemistry-might-surprise-you-2000727128</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727128</guid>
      <description>The answer is a &#8220;perfect red,&#8221; and its discovery might be worth billions of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is a gimbal inside a smartphone' &#8212; Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra Super Steady Horizontal Lock really can handle a 360-degree turn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/this-is-a-gimbal-inside-a-smartphone-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-super-steady-horizontal-lock-really-can-handle-a-360-degree-turn</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AXSec4rUCM2mJbXcs8UjZU</guid>
      <description>I put Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra's new Super Steady Horizontal Lock video mode to the test and color me impressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Says iPhone and iPad Are Approved to Handle Some Classified Data</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/apple-says-iphone-and-ipad-are-approved-to-handle-some-classified-data-2000727267</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727267</guid>
      <description>No assembly required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone sales could be in for their biggest drop ever</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/885638/smartphone-decline-ram-shortage-idc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T16:22:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885638</guid>
      <description>The smartphone industry could experience a record-breaking decline in 2026 as a result of the RAM shortage stemming from memory-hungry AI giants. That's according to the latest report from the International Data Corporation (IDC), which forecasts smartphone shipments to plummet 12.9 percent this year, marking its "lowest annual shipment volume in more than a decade." [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta sues advertisers in Brazil and China over 'celeb bait' scams</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-sues-advertisers-in-brazil-and-china-over-celeb-bait-scams-190000268.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88ee3eff-08ff-4e55-9039-e876ca0e4132</guid>
      <description>Meta has sued the people and groups behind three scam operations that used images and deepfakes of celebrities to lure users to scam websites. According to the company, the three entities were based in China and Brazil and targeted people in the US, Japan and other countries. The ads promoted fraudulent investment schemes and fake health products.Meta said that it had filed lawsuits against several people in Brazil who promoted fake or unapproved healthcare products and online courses promoting them. The company also sued a China-based entity it says used ads featuring celebrities "as part of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Wake Up to 800,000 Notifications From Observatory Watching the Night Skies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/astronomers-wake-up-to-800000-notifications-from-observatory-watching-the-night-skies-2000727018</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727018</guid>
      <description>The first batch of alerts from the Vera Rubin Observatory drew attention to new asteroids, supernovae, and active galactic nuclei.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google paid startup Form Energy $1B for its massive 100-hour battery</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/google-paid-startup-form-energy-1b-for-its-massive-100-hour-battery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097617</guid>
      <description>The deal paves the way for Form Energy to raise a new funding round before potentially going public next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Therapist Will Be Hearing About &#8216;Smiling Friends&#8217; Ending</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/my-therapist-will-be-hearing-about-smiling-friends-ending-2000727119</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727119</guid>
      <description>The creators of Adult Swim's smash-hit animated comedy series announced the series is ending after season three, with two 'straggler' episodes to follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung exec confirms you can blame RAM &#8212; and other materials &#8212; for the Galaxy S26&#8217;s higher pricetag</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885566/samsung-ram-galaxy-s26-price</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:57:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885566</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy S26 and S26 Plus are "more of the same for more money," my colleague Allison Johnson reported this week. Now, Samsung is confirming what we previously only suspected: RAMageddon is partly to blame. Samsung's Won-Joon Choi, the COO of its mobile business, tells The Verge that the memory shortage alone made a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This AI Agent Is Designed to Not Go Rogue</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ironcurtain-ai-agent-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699f224a94854663df474d0d</guid>
      <description>The new open source project IronCurtain uses a unique method to secure and constrain AI assistant agents before they flip your digital life upside down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandisk reveals its next-generation of portable SSDs for creatives on the move &#8212; but there's enough for office workers there too</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sandisk-reveals-its-next-generation-of-portable-ssds-for-creatives-on-the-move-but-theres-enough-for-office-workers-there-too</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7UHwjhNxdRSFwHVctmDzSc</guid>
      <description>Sandisk introduces three portable SSD models with varying speeds, durability, and security features to meet modern creative and everyday storage needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC declines to enforce a kids privacy law for data collected to verify users&#8217; ages</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/885592/ftc-age-verification-childrens-online-privacy-enforcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:42:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885592</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission is encouraging companies to adopt age verification technologies by announcing it will not enforce a children's online privacy law against certain websites that collect and use minors' personal data in order to verify their ages. "Age verification technologies are some of the most child-protective technologies to emerge in decades," Christopher Mufarrige, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis Lost $26.3 Billion Last Year, Says It&#8217;s Pivoting Back to Combustion Engines</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stellantis-lost-26-3-billion-last-year-says-its-pivoting-back-to-combustion-engines-2000727243</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727243</guid>
      <description>Jeep's parent company is struggling as the U.S. swerves away from EVs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
