<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:23:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Sony Honda Afeela CES 2026 presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/how-to-watch-the-sony-honda-afeela-ces-2026-presentation-130048804.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55dc3f84-855b-40ed-9b3d-0dc382a60c59</guid>
      <description>
Sony's CES 2026 press conference is just a few days away, and this year comes with a twist: Rather than an overview of Sony's electronics, video game and Hollywood studio plans for the new year, the presser will have a more narrow focus: electric vehicles. Sound odd? That's because the traditional end-of-press-day slot isn't just Sony, but rather Sony Honda Mobility &#8212; the joint venture responsible for the Afeela 1 electric car that has been showcased at CES for the better part of a decade. But this year, we'll get to see an all-new concept model at the event.&#160;
How to watch the Sony Afeela CES...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash says it banned driver who seemingly faked a delivery using AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/04/doordash-says-it-banned-driver-who-seemingly-faked-a-delivery-using-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079541</guid>
      <description>DoorDash seems to have confirmed a viral story about a driver using an AI-generated photo to lie about making a delivery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govee&#8217;s New Smart Ceiling Light Gives You AI Art to Look Up To</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/govees-new-smart-ceiling-light-gives-you-ai-art-to-look-up-to-2000704713</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704713</guid>
      <description>The Govee Ceiling Light Ultra sounds like a needlessly extravagant smart home light, but that's pretty on-brand for Govee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold Hands-On: Way Better Than I Expected</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on-way-better-than-i-expected-2000705200</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705200</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, I finally got some time with Samsung's Z Trifold foldable phone, and I'm very impressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditch the February resolution slump with this habit-tracking powerhouse</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/habitify</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RdxHpvfVc82xkautkZXkUH</guid>
      <description>Homescreen Heroes: Habitify turns fleeting New Year's goals into permanent lifestyle changes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This autonomous solar-powered robot costs 1p, is smaller than a grain of salt, and communicates through 'wiggles of a little dance'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-autonomous-solar-powered-robot-costs-1p-is-smaller-than-a-grain-of-salt-and-communicates-through-wiggles-of-a-little-dance</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gryUPofLW76RByQLBSrcCF</guid>
      <description>Sub-millimeter autonomous robots can swim, sense temperature, and communicate through miniature movements, opening new possibilities for medicine and microscale manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xreal&#8217;s Cheapest AR Glasses Just Got Better (and Cheaper)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xreals-cheapest-ar-glasses-just-got-better-and-cheaper-2000705194</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705194</guid>
      <description>It's hard to argue with a lower price and better specs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the NVIDIA CES 2026 press conference with Jensen Huang live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-nvidia-ces-2026-press-conference-with-jensen-huang-live-130028602.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a8ad1a0-9035-4f52-a4e0-783ee7c9700b</guid>
      <description>CFOTO via Getty Images
During CES 2025, NVIDIA spent much of its keynote touting its leading position in artificial intelligence. Still, the company managed to squeeze in a few notable hardware announcements, including its RTX 5000-series GPUs and Project Digits desktop supercomputer (later redubbed Spark). For this year's show, the company's website says it's "lighting up CES 2026 with the power of AI." To that end, NVIDIA is going big in Las Vegas, promising hands-on demos in its Fontainebleau booth, replete with the "latest NVIDIA solutions driving innovation and productivity across industr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG's 'Aerominum' Gram Pro laptops feel impossibly light and strong</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lgs-aerominum-gram-pro-laptops-feel-impossibly-light-and-strong-200317743.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abdf8260-a0d5-4757-9469-76666ccad982</guid>
      <description>For years, LG has pushed its ultra-light Gram laptops as a way to stand out from the PC crowd, for better or worse. I was't a big fan of the flex-prone case in the 2017 Gram, and we had similar concerns with the first 17-inch Gram in 2019. But in fairness, it's been a while since we've reviewed one, and we found a lot to like in our preview of last year's AI-equipped model. Now LG is back with a major Gram Pro redesign at CES 2026, which features a new aluminum/magnesium alloy it's dubbed "Aerominum." And finally, it seems LG has found a balance between building a super-light notebook (the 16-...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliro arrives &#8211; the smart lock standard is set to launch this year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/854091/aliro-smart-lock-standard-launches-2026-apple-uwb-nfc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T15:00:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854091</guid>
      <description>The long-delayed smart lock standard Aliro is finally launching. The first specification, which standardizes NFC-based tap-to-unlock and UWB hands-free unlocking for smart locks, will arrive early this year, according to the Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA). "We're delighted to share that Aliro, the CSA's standardized credential and communication protocol that lets trusted smartphones and wearables act [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Dispatch&#8217; Stats Show Millions of Players Put the Work In</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dispatch-stats-show-millions-of-players-put-the-work-in-2000705126</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705126</guid>
      <description>It came in late, but 'Dispatch' became the talk of the town last year as players fell for its gameplay, characters...basically all of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Wants Venezuela's Oil. Getting It Might Not Be So Simple</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-wants-venezuelas-oil-getting-it-might-not-be-so-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695aac1ba9a1aef626dfded0</guid>
      <description>The administration has made it clear that Nicol&#225;s Maduro's capture was tied to Venezuela's vast oil reserves. Much less certain is how US companies will actually access them&#8212;or if they even want to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel beats AMD on sheer value as it ranks 7 CPUs in PassMark's top 10 Price Performance leaderboard &#8212; AMD gets number 1 but it's just an entry level Ryzen 5 on clearance sales</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/intel-beats-amd-on-sheer-value-as-it-ranks-7-cpus-in-passmarks-top-10-price-performance-leaderboard-amd-gets-number-1-but-its-just-an-entry-level-ryzen-5-on-clearance-sales</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXhNktC3rWkfn7iXJmtcAH</guid>
      <description>Intel dominates PassMark&#8217;s price performance rankings as seven of its CPUs appear in the top ten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Lego CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/how-to-watch-the-lego-ces-2026-press-conference-live-130005019.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 19:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02a28a6-f21c-46c9-a5e0-dcff1b13d26a</guid>
      <description>picture alliance via Getty Images
Are you a Lego Adult? No guilt implied &#8212; we hear you, whether you enjoy building Death Stars, Starship Enterprises or even just the occasional flower bouquet. But you may be surprised to hear that the Lego Group is set to host its very first press conference at CES 2026. Exactly what it plans to unveil is still under wraps, however. The iconic toy brick maker has offered no clues about what's on the agenda, leaving speculation wide open, from new video games to Formula 1 race cars.
Here's how you can watch Lego's presentation at CES, along with what we think t...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
