<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:25:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise : Dell lance le XPS 13 2026, le plus fin et le moins cher de son histoire</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926223_surprise-dell-lance-le-xps-13-2026-le-plus-fin-et-le-moins-cher-de-son-histoire</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926223_surprise-dell-lance-le-xps-13-2026-le-plus-fin-et-le-moins-cher-de-son-histoire</guid>
      <description>
On pensait avoir tout vu avec les nouveaux XPS 14 et 16. Et l&#224;, surprise. Dell a sorti de son chapeau un produit qui n'existait m&#234;me pas sur les plans il y a trois mois. Un XPS 13 in&#233;dit, ultra-fin, et surtout&#8230; accessible. Dell veut remettre sa marque star dans les mains du grand public, et &#231;a promet.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#8217;s Nadella wants us to stop thinking of AI as &#8216;slop&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/microsofts-nadella-wants-us-to-stop-thinking-of-ai-as-slop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079735</guid>
      <description>Nadella wants us to think of AI as a human helper instead of a slop-generating job killer. New data for 2026 indicates he could be right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz Chases After Tesla&#8217;s FSD With MB.Drive Assist Pro</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mercedes-benz-chases-after-teslas-fsd-with-mb-drive-assist-pro-2000705309</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705309</guid>
      <description>Mercedes&#8217; Level 2 advanced driving system now tackles city streets in the all-new electric CLA and other 2026 and beyond cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jensen Huang Says Nvidia&#8217;s New Vera Rubin Chips Are in &#8216;Full Production&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/nvidias-rubin-chips-are-going-into-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695bf9e5df89435b356af9f5</guid>
      <description>The chip giant says Vera Rubin will sharply cut the cost of training and running AI models, strengthening the appeal of its integrated computing platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber&#8217;s Not Done With Self-Driving Cars Just Yet. It&#8217;s Designing a New Robotaxi With Lucid and Nuro</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ubers-not-done-with-self-driving-cars-just-yet-its-designing-a-new-robotaxi-with-lucid-and-nuro-2000705643</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705643</guid>
      <description>Uber is back to self-driving taxis with a Nuro-powered driverless Lucid Gravity EV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cet &#233;cran Acer tourne &#224; 1 kHz, mais attention &#224; ce pi&#232;ge</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/acer/2929805_cet-ecran-acer-tourne-a-1-khz-mais-attention-a-ce-piege</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/acer/2929805_cet-ecran-acer-tourne-a-1-khz-mais-attention-a-ce-piege</guid>
      <description>
Acer d&#233;voile sa nouvelle gamme de moniteurs gaming au CES 2026. L'un d'eux affiche une fr&#233;quence record de 1000 Hz, du jamais vu.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD at CES 2026: Live updates from CEO Lisa Su's keynote presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/amd-at-ces-2026-live-updates-from-ceo-lisa-sus-keynote-presentation-190012370.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c864a817-a6e7-423f-ab33-fb69dbcbdab4</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA and Intel had their moment in the spotlight, and now it's AMD's turn. The chipmaker is kicking off CES 2026 on Monday night, where it'll cover its latest AI developments and perhaps show off its newest Ryzen chips. It's the kickoff keynote of CES 2026, and CEO Dr. Lisa Su is expected to outline how AMD's hardware will power the AI revolution &#8212; and what the company can offer partners and consumers that those aforementioned rivals can't.&#160;&#160;
We'll tell you how to tune in to the livestream and what else you can expect to see.
How to watch AMD's keynote live
Dr. Su will deliver a keynote spee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel launches new Core Ultra 300 series processors at CES 2026. Will Panther Lake deliver the win that Intel needs?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cpu/intel-launches-new-core-ultra-300-series-processors-at-ces-2026-will-panther-lake-deliver-the-win-that-intel-needs</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oi8MbcJDBbscwCbDkLvX9R</guid>
      <description>Intel Panther Lake leaves its cage starting this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MSI Crosshair 16 Max HX features a slimmer chassis and stronger specs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850944/ces-2026-msi-crosshair-16-max</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850944</guid>
      <description>The latest MSI Crosshair gaming laptop announced at CES today doesn't make any major changes, but does manage to fit improved specs into less space. According to MSI, the Crosshair 16 Max HX is 14.3 percent thinner than its predecessor, a difference of 2mm. The slightly more svelte chassis comes with slightly updated specs, including [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prise en main Dell XPS 14 et 16 (2026) : l&#8217;anti-MacBook est enfin de retour avec 43h d&#8217;autonomie et de l&#8217;OLED Tandem</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926213_prise-en-main-dell-xps-14-et-16-2026-lanti-macbook-est-enfin-de-retour-avec-43h-dautonomie-et-de-loled-tandem</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926213_prise-en-main-dell-xps-14-et-16-2026-lanti-macbook-est-enfin-de-retour-avec-43h-dautonomie-et-de-loled-tandem</guid>
      <description>
L'anti-MacBook est de retour, et il est &#233;nerv&#233;. Avec ses nouveaux XPS 14 et 16, Dell corrige les erreurs du pass&#233; (les touches tactiles ont disparu). Ils int&#232;grent aussi une dalle Tandem OLED in&#233;dite et promettent jusqu'&#224; 40 heures d'autonomie en vid&#233;o. J'ai pass&#233; un moment avec la version noire matte &#224; New York. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra l&#233;ger, ultra puissant : MSI met la barre tr&#232;s haute avec son PC Prestige</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2929597_ultra-leger-ultra-puissant-msi-met-la-barre-tres-haute-avec-son-pc-prestige</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2929597_ultra-leger-ultra-puissant-msi-met-la-barre-tres-haute-avec-son-pc-prestige</guid>
      <description>
Les nouveaux processeurs Intel permettent aux fabricants de produire de nouveaux design. Le tout nouveau MSI Prestige en est l'incarnation.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber reveals the design of its robotaxi at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/uber-reveals-the-design-of-its-robotaxi-at-ces-2026-230056302.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab014c87-79f6-4149-8024-fafc5a6b11aa</guid>
      <description>Waymo is getting a good look at the competition as Uber revealed the design of its robotaxi that's due to launch in San Francisco later this year. The upcoming robotaxi is a result of a partnership announced in July between Uber, Lucid and Nuro. The plan is still to deploy at least 20,000 Lucid EVs that will use the Nuro Driver autonomous driving tech and be available through the Uber platform.
It's important to note that the robotaxi reveal will be a "production intent design," so there may be some modifications to the version that will eventually hit the streets. However, the partnership sta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell Admits It Made a Huge Mistake When It Abandoned XPS</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dell-admits-it-made-a-huge-mistake-when-it-abandoned-xps-2000705053</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705053</guid>
      <description>Though not all its famed brands are coming back alongside a new XPS 14 and 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the Jim Henson Company Bring &#8216;Magic: The Gathering&#8217; to Life</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/magic-the-gathering-lorwyn-eclipsed-jim-henson-trailer-2000705747</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705747</guid>
      <description>Missing 'Dark Crystal'? This is about as close to the next best thing you'll get for a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer's Predator Helios Neo 16S AI laptop can be outfitted with Intel's new Core Ultra 9 386H CPU</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/acers-predator-helios-neo-16s-ai-laptop-can-be-outfitted-with-intels-new-core-ultra-9-386h-cpu-230048825.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">587cf8f7-941b-4848-87b3-150753ab5cd3</guid>
      <description>Acer just announced the Predator Helios 16S AI gaming laptop at CES 2026. This computer is filled with both bells and whistles, making it a decent choice for modern gamers.
To that end, the laptop can be equipped with up to an Intel Core Ultra 9 386H processor. This is Intel's upcoming flagship mobile processor that has previously been known as Panther Lake. The Helios 16S AI can also be outfitted with up to the NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5070 GPU.
Acer
It comes with a 16-inch WQXGA OLED display that offers true HDR imaging support. The laptop can be loaded with up to 64GB of RAM and up to 2TB of stor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI fait le m&#233;nage dans ses portables gaming et monte en gamme</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/msi-fait-le-menage-dans-ses-portables-gaming-et-monte-en-gamme.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317253</guid>
      <description>Les joueurs qui refusent le moindre compromis sur leur passe-temps pr&#233;f&#233;r&#233; et qui veulent aussi &#234;tre mobiles n'ont plus &#224; vivre dans l'ombre d'une tour de bureau. Le march&#233; des portables gaming leur offre de nombreuses possibilit&#233;s pour assouvir leur passion d&#233;vorante (et vider leur compte en banque), comme on le voit chez MSI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonprofit Behind NPR and PBS Votes to Shut Down After Trump Killed Funding</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nonprofit-behind-npr-and-pbs-votes-to-shut-down-after-trump-killed-funding-2000705671</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705671</guid>
      <description>As many as 80 public radio stations could close within the next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All of HP&#8217;s Gaming Laptops Are Now Under the HyperX Umbrella</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hp-maxes-out-its-max-gaming-laptop-now-with-more-hyperx-2000704515</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704515</guid>
      <description>We also got a first look at the improvements in the new HyperX Omen X 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia New Rubin Platform Shows Memory Is No Longer &#8216;Afterthought&#8217; in AI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nvidia-new-rubin-platform-shows-memory-is-no-longer-afterthought-in-ai-2000705639</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705639</guid>
      <description>The company unveiled the platform and more at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s Most Powerful Galaxy Book 6 Ultra Shoves Nvidia RTX 5070 and 5060 GPUs Inside</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/samsung-galaxy-book-6-hands-on-features-2000705653</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705653</guid>
      <description>The company's new Galaxy Book 6, 6 Pro, and 6 Ultra laptops are all about performance and battery life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s Galaxy Book 6 series launches at CES with Intel&#8217;s newest chips and a refined design</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/samsungs-galaxy-book-6-series-ces-2026-intel-panther-lake-230010324.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eac44ab2-71e9-453c-993d-5e9db743f2b6</guid>
      <description>In addition to huge TVs, compact projectors, Trifolds and more, Samsung announced a new family of laptops at CES called the Galaxy Book 6 series. The company says it&#8217;s focused on what matters and on what you, hopefully, want in your next laptop. That means Intel&#8217;s latest chips, a cleaner design and battery life that lasts longer than a day. They&#8217;re really thin, too.
Timed alongside Intel&#8217;s CES announcements, the whole Galaxy Book 6 series features new Panther Lake chips, optimized by Samsung for three new laptops: The Galaxy Book 6 Ultra, Galaxy Book 6 Pro and Galaxy Book 6.
The 16-inch Galaxy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chez MSI, un grand coup de balai dans les gammes bureautiques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/chez-msi-un-grand-coup-de-balai-dans-les-gammes-bureautiques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317215</guid>
      <description>Chez MSI, l'heure est &#224; la simplification. Le coup de balai est bienvenu, au moins dans la gamme bureautique qui mena&#231;ait de devenir aussi dense et touffue que le catalogue de puces d'Intel ! On fait le point sur ce que le constructeur nous a r&#233;serv&#233; pour le CES.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is Uber&#8217;s new robotaxi from Lucid and Nuro</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/this-is-ubers-new-robotaxi-from-lucid-and-nuro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079859</guid>
      <description>The production-intent version, unveiled at CES 2026 on Monday, will be an exceptionally roomy entry into the growing robotaxi market later this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperX&#8217;s 2026 gaming monitor lineup includes a 500Hz QD-OLED</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/845706/hyperx-qdoled-500hz-v-stripe-curved-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845706</guid>
      <description>From laptops to monitors, HyperX is the brand you'll see on much of HP's new gaming-focused products launched at CES 2026. And despite the branding switch, this year's slate of monitors might be the company's most competitive batch yet. The cheapest of the three QD-OLEDs announced is the HyperX Omen OLED 27q, a 27-inch 1440p [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperX&#8217;s name is on HP&#8217;s new Omen gaming laptops</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/845774/hyperx-omen-15-16-max-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845774</guid>
      <description>HP's branding is missing on its new gaming laptops (and gaming monitors) announced at CES 2026 - HP-owned HyperX has gotten a big promotion in its place. This swap is the biggest aesthetic change in the Omen lineup (the logo is on the lid and on the screen's bottom bezel). In other words, not much [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperX&#8217;s new gaming keyboards were made to be yanked apart</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/846558/hyperx-origins-2-gaming-wired-keyboard-customization-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846558</guid>
      <description>The next generation of HyperX's Origins wired keyboards debuted at CES 2026, and the company has focused on adding more performance and customization. For example, its new Origins 2 and Origins 2 Pro are both 65-percent options with high-profile keys that boast a PCB with hot-swappable switches that doesn't require soldering to tweak. The Origins [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell is eating humble pie and bringing back the XPS brand</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851047/dell-xps-14-16-13-laptops-brand-return-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851047</guid>
      <description>Nearly one year ago to the day, Dell killed off its long-standing XPS brand name in favor of milquetoast Premium, Plus, Pro, and Pro Max monikers - but it's back for CES 2026. The new XPS 14 and XPS 16 laptops look to win back fans of the "Extreme Performance System" with Dell's thinnest designs [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the sleekest MSI laptops I&#8217;ve ever seen</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851382/these-are-the-sleekest-msi-laptops-ive-ever-seen</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851382</guid>
      <description>MSI is announcing a revamped Prestige business laptop line for CES 2026 with thinner designs, OLED displays, 2-in-1 options, bigger trackpads, and Intel's new Panther Lake chips. The Prestige 14 AI Plus and Prestige 16 AI Plus are the flagship clamshells of the line, and there are also 2-in-1 versions on offer called the Prestige [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new Stealth 16 laptop from MSI finally looks stealthy (well, a little)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851516/msi-stealth-16-laptop-gaming-looks-stealthy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851516</guid>
      <description>MSI is announcing a new Stealth 16 AI Plus gaming laptop for CES 2026. Borrowing a little from its business-class brethren, the new Stealth has a thinner and lighter design, features a larger trackpad, and comes standard with a 240Hz OLED display (though some global regions may start with IPS). It'll run $2,099 with an [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What on Earth is HP doing with its gaming laptop branding?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851812/hp-hyperx-omen-name-gaming-laptop-branding-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851812</guid>
      <description>Among HP's many announcements for CES, its biggest overall change is for its gaming division. HP's Omen line of gaming laptops, monitors, and desktops are dropping the HP name entirely and instead will henceforth be branded as HyperX. The HP Omen 16 Max laptop becomes the HyperX Omen 16 Max. HP Omen monitors will become [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Acer laptop has a massive haptic trackpad with stylus support</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852213/acer-swift-16-ai-intel-edge-nitro-predator-laptops-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852213</guid>
      <description>Acer is announcing a selection of new laptops for CES 2026: small refreshes across its Swift lines and a few Nitro and Predator gaming laptops. But there's nothing small about the haptic trackpad on the new Acer Swift 16 AI, which Acer claims is the world's largest haptic one. Big trackpads are fairly prevalent on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Acer&#8217;s giant Nitro Blaze 11 gaming handheld?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852473/acer-nitro-blaze-11-gaming-handheld-what-happened</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852473</guid>
      <description>Acer made a big splash at CES 2025 with the announcement of its surfboard-sized Nitro Blaze 11 gaming handheld, but its targeted second-quarter release came and went long ago. There's been no word of the chunky 11-inch Blaze or its smaller siblings. I was initially hyped enough to try such an oversized handheld that I [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia wants to be the Android of generalist robotics</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/nvidia-wants-to-be-the-android-of-generalist-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080048</guid>
      <description>Nvidia unveiled a full-stack robotics ecosystem at CES 2026, including foundation models, simulation tools, and hardware. It wants to be the default platform for robotics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell un-retires its iconic XPS brand at CES 2026: "We're getting back to our roots"</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/dell-un-retires-its-iconic-xps-brand-at-ces-2026-were-getting-back-to-our-roots</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5KLJzKRXYjhBmYPKcA64YW</guid>
      <description>Dell announced at CES 2026 that it will be bringing back the iconic XPS brand after briefly retiring it as part of its rebranding effort last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell XPS 14 2026 and XPS 16 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows-laptops/dell-xps-14-2026-and-xps-16-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JMdvoVjbt8hCbE8EmzyKDH</guid>
      <description>The Dell XPS 14 and Dell XPS 16 return in 2026 with a new look and some major improvements over their predecessors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer's CES 2026 reveals include laptops, displays, and... a gaming-themed e-scooter, apparently</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/acers-ces-2026-reveals-include-laptops-displays-and-a-gaming-themed-e-scooter-apparently</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">T5JczKKDLaJyFAsUajGtiU</guid>
      <description>Acer revealed a whole host of new laptops at CES, along with an impressive new esports monitor and an electric scooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperX is working with brain-scanning company Neurable on a gaming headset that aims to offer 'prevention of tilt' and 'good practice, not crap practice'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-accessories/hyperx-is-working-with-brain-scanning-company-neurable-on-a-gaming-headset-that-aims-to-offer-prevention-of-tilt-and-good-practice-not-crap-practice</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">P3pqZqzYLpQd8HWCCB2jXW</guid>
      <description>Exclusive: Neurable's CEO explains how tracking brainwaves will made you better at games, whether you're a pro eSports player or not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI unveils new gaming and Prestige business laptops at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/msi-unveils-new-gaming-and-prestige-business-laptops-at-ces-2026-230000027.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7886a51a-673f-4b17-b03f-8c08af69776e</guid>
      <description>MSI has presented its refreshed Prestige lineup of business laptops, as well as its next-generation Raider, Stealth and Crosshair gaming models at this year&#8217;s CES. The Raider 16 Max HX is a 300w laptop, which the company says its its most powerful gaming model yet. It can supply 175w to its GeForce RTX 5090 or RTX 5080 GPU, while feeding 125w to its Intel Core Ultra 200HX processor at the same time under full-load conditions. To be able to handle that kind of power, MSI equipped it with a new cooling system consisting of three fans, six heat pipes, five exhaust vents and phase-change thermal c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer goes big on the haptic trackpad for CES with the Swift 16 AI laptop</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/acer-goes-big-on-the-haptic-trackpad-for-ces-with-the-swift-16-ai-laptop-230000750.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">039810ff-05c5-41dd-8aa4-cd2eb3594896</guid>
      <description>Acer has a handful of laptop updates at this year's CES show. The headlining item is the addition of the Acer Swift 16 AI to the company's flagship line. This laptop has what the company says is currently the world's largest haptic touchpad at 5.5mm by 109.7mm, and it can support up to MPP 2.5 stylus inputs. The screen is a 16-inch 3K OLED WQXGA+ touch display with HDR, a 120 Hz refresh rate and 100% DCI-P3 color gamut. On the inside, the Swift 16 AI can be kitted with up to an Intel Core Ultra X9 388H processor with built-in Intel Arc B390 graphics. The whole package is in a 14.9mm thin chass...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: HP says the HyperX Omen Max 16 is the most powerful 16-inch gaming laptop in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/ces-2026-hp-says-the-hyperx-omen-max-16-is-the-most-powerful-16-inch-gaming-laptop-in-the-world-230000272.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dec7c65-7950-497a-ac88-81181759bb39</guid>
      <description>This year HP is making an important change by taking its name off its gaming hardware entirely and letting its HyperX branding take center stage. At CES 2026, the company is celebrating this transition in a big way with Omen Max 16, which is being heralded as the world&#8217;s most powerful gaming laptop with fully internal cooling.Now the last part of that claim is a bit of a cop out, but considering that most gamers probably don&#8217;t want to lug around a notebook with hoses coming out the back, it&#8217;s an understandable qualifier. Plus, with a total platform power of 300 watts that includes support for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;C&#8217;&#233;tait inacceptable&#160;&#187; : Dell avoue son &#233;chec, la marque XPS est de retour et les vraies touches aussi</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926185_cetait-inacceptable-dell-avoue-son-echec-la-marque-xps-est-de-retour-et-les-vraies-touches-aussi</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926185_cetait-inacceptable-dell-avoue-son-echec-la-marque-xps-est-de-retour-et-les-vraies-touches-aussi</guid>
      <description>
Vous vous souvenez du d&#233;sastre de la gamme Dell 2025 ? Ces noms &#224; rallonge et ces choix ergonomiques douteux ? C'est termin&#233;. Pour le CES 2025, la direction de Dell vient de faire son mea culpa. La marque XPS revient au centre du jeu, et c'est une victoire pour le bon sens.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything NVIDIA announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/everything-nvidia-announced-at-ces-2026-225653684.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29e2c7bd-fe16-414f-bbd5-59e8cb1322d2</guid>
      <description>Jensen Huang took to the CES stage on Monday to share the latest from NVIDIA,  and while the presentation was more a refresher of technologies the company has been working on for the past few years, there were a couple of notable announcements. NVIDIA announced  Alpamayo, a family of open-source reasoning models designed to guide autonomous vehicles through difficult driving situations. The centerpiece of the release is Alpamayo 1 , a 10-billion parameter chain-of-thought system NVIDIA says is capable of approaching driving more like a human being would. The model works by breaking down unexpe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"The entire stack is being changed" - Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang looks ahead to the next generation of AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-entire-stack-is-being-changed-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-looks-ahead-to-the-next-generation-of-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">s7HFJfH7uYxfwnfazxwmQP</guid>
      <description>From factories to gaming, AI is coming to the world around us - and Nvidia CEO reveals a bit more on what this will look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm Shows Off AI-Powered Maps, a New Feature to Level Up Self-Driving Cars</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/qualcomm-shows-off-ai-powered-maps-a-new-feature-to-level-up-self-driving-cars-2000705695</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705695</guid>
      <description>HERE maps give Qualcomm&#8217;s self-driving car demos an AI edge with predictions on road condition beyond the car&#8217;s line of sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Dressed as the Pink Ranger Takes Down White Supremacist Websites Live Onstage</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hacker-dressed-as-the-pink-ranger-takes-down-white-supremacist-websites-live-onstage-2000705690</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705690</guid>
      <description>Now that's a performance that needs an encore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold hands-on: Flexing is believing at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on-flexing-is-believing-at-ces-2026-224343480.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">358a9f49-439d-4582-ad93-1f442ed611df</guid>
      <description>When I first heard whispers about the Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold, I immediately felt conflicted. On one hand it felt like the natural evolution of bi-fold phones like the Z Fold 7. But on the other, all this fancy tech comes with an even higher price &#8212; around $2,500 based on current conversion rates from Korean won &#8212; not to mention the added bulk you get from a third folding panel. So even as someone who has used a foldable as my daily driver for almost a decade straight, it felt like Samsung&#8217;s latest high-end phone was going backwards in terms of both portability and affordability. But then at ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, Lego, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Company That Just Buys Bitcoin Booked $17 Billion in Q4 Losses</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-company-that-just-buys-bitcoin-booked-17-billion-in-q4-losses-2000705317</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705317</guid>
      <description>Strategy's business model results in wild swings, but since it hasn't sold any bitcoin, these are just paper losses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google TV's new Gemini features range from useful to unnecessary</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/google-tvs-new-gemini-features-range-from-useful-to-unnecessary-222900001.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fdbff36-57f2-459b-b46b-3e2c72746e6f</guid>
      <description>I met up with a few people from Google at the Encore Villas during CES (which is just 2,500 feet from my hotel but took 28 minutes to walk to, thanks to Vegas&#8217;s pedestrian-averse design [also I got lost]). Once there, I saw what &#8220;more Gemini&#8221; will mean for people with a Google TV. The AI integration ranged from useful to probably unnecessary. The most useful bit, for me at least, came at the end. It&#8217;s admittedly a boring, but now you an adjust your TV&#8217;s settings just by talking. In the demo, Salahuddin Choudhary, Google&#8217;s Gemini for Android product lead said, &#8220;Can you boost the dialogue?&#8221; and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust me, you have never seen a mini PC like this &#8212; Keebmon is a Ryzen AI-powered PC with a mechanical keyboard, a 21:9 touchscreen display, 64GB RAM, and an 8TB SSD</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/you-have-never-seen-a-mini-pc-like-this-keebmon-is-a-ryzen-ai-powered-pc-with-a-mechanical-keyboard-a-21-9-touchscreen-display-64gb-ram-and-an-8tb-ssd</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a5gK444cMV5mjPyofFHgL</guid>
      <description>Keebmon is a &#8220;folding&#8221; mini PC combining a touchscreen, mechanical keyboard, and high-end Ryzen processor with extensive connectivity and upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia launches powerful new Rubin chip architecture</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/nvidia-launches-powerful-new-rubin-chip-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079726</guid>
      <description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang officially launched the company&#8217;s new Rubin computing architecture, which he described as the state of the art in AI computing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Awards Peter Thiel&#8211;Backed Nuclear Startup $900 Million</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/us-awards-peter-thiel-backed-nuclear-startup-900-million-2000705701</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705701</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Energy announced today that it is  awarding $2.7 billion to three companies to boost domestic uranium enrichment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego&#8217;s New &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Smart Brick Sets Look Like a Big Risk</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lego-smart-bricks-star-wars-price-release-date-ces-2026-2000705664</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705664</guid>
      <description>Lego is using the galaxy far, far away to launch one of its biggest innovations in years... and it's already raising eyebrows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics&#8217; next-gen humanoid robot will have Google DeepMind DNA</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/boston-dynamicss-next-gen-humanoid-robot-will-have-google-deepmind-dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079851</guid>
      <description>Google's AI research lab is working with Boston Dynamics to make Atlas act more like a human.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, RFK Jr. Are Officially Tearing Down the Childhood Vaccine Schedule</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-rfk-jr-are-officially-tearing-down-the-childhood-vaccine-schedule-2000705661</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705661</guid>
      <description>Vaccines for diseases like rotavirus and meningococcal disease will no longer be universally recommended by the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia launches Alpamayo, open AI models that allow autonomous vehicles to &#8216;think like a human&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/nvidia-launches-alpamayo-open-ai-models-that-allow-autonomous-vehicles-to-think-like-a-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079883</guid>
      <description>Nvidia unveiled Alpamayo at CES 2026, which includes a reasoning vision language action model that allows an autonomous vehicle to think more like a human and provide chain-of-thought reasoning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At CES 2026, Samsung&#8217;s AI Living vision leaves no device un-AI&#8217;d</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-ai-living-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02U455zuXEPl9nFwfe2Peqq</guid>
      <description>Inside Samsung&#8217;s AI Living Exhibit at CES 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the CES 2026 Nvidia keynote livestream now</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-nvidia-keynote-livestream</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05n5hW0RYeCjcLmuPTZdOue</guid>
      <description>The tech world will be tuning in to see Nvidia's CES keynote speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 AMD Keynote livestream: See it live</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-amd-keynote-livestream</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07nIqAUXPBbwULfbJEDtUrF</guid>
      <description>AMD CEO Dr. Lisa Su will deliver a keynote address at CES, helping kick off the major tech event. You can watch the livestream on Monday, Jan. 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwanese infrastructure suffered over 2.5 million Chinese cyberattacks per day in 2025, report reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/taiwanese-infrastructure-suffered-over-2-5-million-chinese-cyberattacks-per-day-in-2025-report-reveals</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">coVZZXZh2RDi9tAjFSBdfM</guid>
      <description>It's all part of a "hybrid war" against the island, a report claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra might not get any camera upgrades &#8212; but that's fine if it means we avoid a price hike</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-might-not-get-any-camera-upgrades-but-thats-fine-if-it-means-we-avoid-a-price-hike</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xiRYKxFXqXxasfdS2CvhJR</guid>
      <description>It seems that the Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra could launch with the same quad-camera system as last year&#8217;s model, but there could be an excellent reason for the lack of upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon will let you use Alexa+ from the web without a dedicated device</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/amazon-alexa-plus-web-browser-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">062gRPTDQY5p3efi7H6TGub</guid>
      <description>Amazon's souped up AI voice assistant will be usable straight from a website, no device needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nouveaux LEGO Star Wars avec briques &#171;&#160;Smart Play&#160;&#187; : voici &#171;&#160;la plus grosse &#233;volution depuis 50 ans&#160;&#187;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929691_nouveaux-lego-star-wars-la-plus-grosse-evolution-depuis-50-ans-ils-integrent-une-technologie-revolutionnaire-de-smart-play</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929691_nouveaux-lego-star-wars-la-plus-grosse-evolution-depuis-50-ans-ils-integrent-une-technologie-revolutionnaire-de-smart-play</guid>
      <description>
C'est probablement l'annonce la plus excitante du CES 2026 pour les grands enfants que nous sommes (ou que je suis). LEGO lance le Smart Play. L'id&#233;e ? Une brique intelligente capable de d&#233;tecter les mouvements et de communiquer avec les autres, sans l'horrible design des sets Mario. La marque promet la plus grosse &#233;volution depuis 50 ans. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NASA Chief Pushes Back on Claims Agency Is Trashing Its History</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-nasa-chief-pushes-back-on-claims-agency-is-trashing-its-history-2000705698</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705698</guid>
      <description>Following reports that closing the agency&#8217;s largest research library would result in the loss of precious scientific and historic materials, Jared Isaacman wants to set the record straight.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
