<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:24:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s Legion Go 2 Now Comes with SteamOS</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lenovos-legion-go-2-now-comes-with-steamos-2000704396</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704396</guid>
      <description>The biggest, costliest, and most enticing handheld now has a better OS and price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Week Later, Rainbow Six Siege Is Apparently Under Attack Again, This Time with Brainrot</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-week-later-rainbow-six-siege-is-apparently-under-attack-again-this-time-with-brainrot-2000705226</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705226</guid>
      <description>The outage and service degradation is accompanied by a bunch of "67" jokes (if you can call them "jokes").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Polti RollySteam : que vaut le balai laveur vapeur de la marque embl&#233;matique italienne ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/aspirateurs-balais-sans-fil/aspirateur-laveur/2923885_test-du-polti-rollysteam-que-vaut-le-balai-laveur-vapeur-de-la-marque-emblematique-italienne</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/aspirateurs-balais-sans-fil/aspirateur-laveur/2923885_test-du-polti-rollysteam-que-vaut-le-balai-laveur-vapeur-de-la-marque-emblematique-italienne</guid>
      <description>
Polti, figure embl&#233;matique du nettoyage &#224; la vapeur, tente de se faire une place sur le march&#233; ultra-concurrentiel des aspirateurs balais laveurs. Avec le RollySteam, la marque italienne promet d'allier l'agilit&#233; d'un balai sans-fil &#224; la puissance hygi&#233;nique de la vapeur. Une promesse s&#233;duisante sur le papier, mais que vaut-elle face &#224; la concurrence de plus en plus pr&#233;sente ? R&#233;ponse dans ce test complet.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belkin announces a wireless HDMI dongle that doesn't need Wi-Fi access</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/belkin-announces-a-wireless-hdmi-dongle-that-doesnt-need-wi-fi-access-215513179.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bd118a0-f209-4678-9ab1-27be0c006e77</guid>
      <description>Belkin has announced a plug-and-play casting system at CES 2026 that allows for screen sharing from a laptop, tablet or smartphone to another display without Wi-Fi or Bluetooth. The $150 ConnectAir Wireless HDMI Display Adapter comes with a USB-C transmitter dongle and a USB-A to HDMI receiver that can be connected to a TV, monitor or projector to wirelessly cast over a range of up to 131 feet (40 meters).&#160;Belkin's ConnectAir Wireless USB-C transmitter and HDMI receiverBelkinThe ConnectAir Wireless casts in 1080p at 60Hz, with latency under 80ms according to Belkin. It's compatible with USB-C ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG reveals its laundry-folding robot at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/lg-reveals-its-laundry-folding-robot-at-ces-2026-215121021.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4290a65d-014e-45bc-8214-f56182cc455e</guid>
      <description>LG has unveiled its humanoid robot that can handle household chores. After teasing the CLOiD last week, the company has offered its first look at the AI-powered robot it claims can fold laundry, unload the dishwasher, serve food and help out with other tasks.&#160;The CLOiD has a surprisingly cute "head unit" that's equipped with a display, speakers, cameras and other sensors. "Collectively, these elements allow the robot to communicate with humans through spoken language and 'facial expressions,' learn the living environments and lifestyle patterns of its users and control connected home appliance...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can a social app fix the &#8216;terrible devastation&#8217; of social media?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/04/can-a-social-app-fix-the-terrible-devastation-of-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079543</guid>
      <description>Twitter co-founder Biz Stone and Pinterest co-founder Evan Sharp have raised new funding for a social media app that helps users "plan with intention."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le Tineco Floor One i7 Fold : il r&#232;gle un des plus gros d&#233;fauts des aspirateurs laveurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tineco/2926777_voici-le-tineco-floor-one-i7-fold-il-regle-un-des-plus-gros-defauts-des-aspirateurs-laveurs</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tineco/2926777_voici-le-tineco-floor-one-i7-fold-il-regle-un-des-plus-gros-defauts-des-aspirateurs-laveurs</guid>
      <description>
C'est un des probl&#232;mes des aspirateurs laveurs depuis cinq ans : essayez de les pencher pour nettoyer sous un lit, et le moteur boit la tasse. Tineco arrive au CES 2026 avec une solution radicale. Le Floor One i7 Fold promet de se coucher totalement &#224; plat. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Sony Honda Afeela CES 2026 presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/how-to-watch-the-sony-honda-afeela-ces-2026-presentation-130048804.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55dc3f84-855b-40ed-9b3d-0dc382a60c59</guid>
      <description>
Sony's CES 2026 press conference is just a few days away, and this year comes with a twist: Rather than an overview of Sony's electronics, video game and Hollywood studio plans for the new year, the presser will have a more narrow focus: electric vehicles. Sound odd? That's because the traditional end-of-press-day slot isn't just Sony, but rather Sony Honda Mobility &#8212; the joint venture responsible for the Afeela 1 electric car that has been showcased at CES for the better part of a decade. But this year, we'll get to see an all-new concept model at the event.&#160;
How to watch the Sony Afeela CES...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash says it banned driver who seemingly faked a delivery using AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/04/doordash-says-it-banned-driver-who-seemingly-faked-a-delivery-using-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079541</guid>
      <description>DoorDash seems to have confirmed a viral story about a driver using an AI-generated photo to lie about making a delivery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govee&#8217;s New Smart Ceiling Light Gives You AI Art to Look Up To</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/govees-new-smart-ceiling-light-gives-you-ai-art-to-look-up-to-2000704713</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704713</guid>
      <description>The Govee Ceiling Light Ultra sounds like a needlessly extravagant smart home light, but that's pretty on-brand for Govee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold Hands-On: Way Better Than I Expected</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on-way-better-than-i-expected-2000705200</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705200</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, I finally got some time with Samsung's Z Trifold foldable phone, and I'm very impressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditch the February resolution slump with this habit-tracking powerhouse</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/habitify</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RdxHpvfVc82xkautkZXkUH</guid>
      <description>Homescreen Heroes: Habitify turns fleeting New Year's goals into permanent lifestyle changes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This autonomous solar-powered robot costs 1p, is smaller than a grain of salt, and communicates through 'wiggles of a little dance'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-autonomous-solar-powered-robot-costs-1p-is-smaller-than-a-grain-of-salt-and-communicates-through-wiggles-of-a-little-dance</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gryUPofLW76RByQLBSrcCF</guid>
      <description>Sub-millimeter autonomous robots can swim, sense temperature, and communicate through miniature movements, opening new possibilities for medicine and microscale manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xreal&#8217;s Cheapest AR Glasses Just Got Better (and Cheaper)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xreals-cheapest-ar-glasses-just-got-better-and-cheaper-2000705194</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705194</guid>
      <description>It's hard to argue with a lower price and better specs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
