<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:51:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ayaneo&#8217;s new Windows handheld will cost up to $4,299 with maxed out specs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876521/ayaneo-next-2-windows-handheld-ryzen-ai-max-395-indiegogo-preorder</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:49:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876521</guid>
      <description>Ayaneo opened preorders for its next Windows 11 handheld and it looks like a powerhouse. The Ayaneo Next 2 is 13.45 inches wide, 10.3-inches tall, and weighs 3.14 pounds. That's more than twice as heavy as the original Ayaneo Next that launched back in 2022, and it easily outweighs the Steam Deck and Switch 2. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Figure Skaters Get Heat for Using AI-Generated Music</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/olympic-figure-skaters-get-heat-for-using-ai-generated-music-2000720192</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720192</guid>
      <description>"So you want the world to respect your art but don't give a shit about the art of music that helps you do it?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Physics Behind the Quadruple Axel, the Most Difficult Jump in Figure Skating</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/2026-winter-olympics-figure-skating-quadruple-axel-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698b3cd301ac8aa5897ea131</guid>
      <description>Are you speechless watching US figure skater Ilia Malinin on the ice? Science explains how it&#8217;s possible the Quad God can do more than four full rotations in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sent personal and financial information of student journalist to ICE</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/google-sent-personal-and-financial-information-of-student-journalist-to-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091670</guid>
      <description>The tech giant handed over the personal information of a journalist and student who attended a pro-Palestinian protest in 2024. This is the latest example of ICE using its controversial subpoena powers to target people critical of the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Trachtenberg&#8217;s Paramount Deal Doesn&#8217;t Kill His &#8216;Predator&#8217; Plans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dan-trachtenbergs-paramount-deal-doesnt-kill-his-predator-plans-2000720290</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720290</guid>
      <description>The director of 'Prey' and 'Predator: Badlands' spoke to io9 about his filmmaking future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of xAI&#8217;s founding team has now left the company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/nearly-half-of-xais-founding-team-has-now-left-the-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091548</guid>
      <description>Out of the twelve-person founding team, only seven are still at the company (counting Elon).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Says Americans Need More Protein. His Grok-Powered Food Website Disagrees</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/rfk-jr-says-americans-need-more-protein-his-grok-powered-food-website-disagrees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6989ff959814f92797042bfb</guid>
      <description>The site Realfood.gov uses Elon Musk's Grok chatbot to dispense nutrition information&#8212;some of which contradicts the government&#8217;s new guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favorite Switch 2 controller is 30 percent off for today only</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876544/easysmx-s10-switch-2-wireless-controller-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:27:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876544</guid>
      <description>The EasySMX S10 is a fantastic wireless controller for the Switch 2 that offers nearly as many features as Nintendo&#8217;s $90 gamepad. I ranked it as the best Switch 2 controller you can buy, thanks to its satisfying rumble sensation in games, support for motion controls as well as Nintendo&#8217;s amiibo NFC figures, plus the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Dictionary of English Slang Is Now Free Online to Help You Talk Like a Zoomer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/largest-dictionary-of-english-slang-is-now-free-online-to-help-you-talk-like-a-zoomer-2000720203</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720203</guid>
      <description>It'd probably help the New York Times, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'As adoption grows, confidence in safeguards must rise with it': Microsoft reveals new tool which can track backdoors in LLMs - and it's hoping this will restore trust in AI across the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/as-adoption-grows-confidence-in-safeguards-must-rise-with-it-microsoft-reveals-new-tool-which-can-track-backdoors-in-llms-and-its-hoping-this-will-restore-trust-in-ai-across-the-world</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JyJCCcHGCogw63uCopmyWG</guid>
      <description>Microsoft introduced a scanner that detects poisoned open-weight language models by analyzing attention behavior, memorization leaks, and trigger flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord says &amp;#8216;vast majority&amp;#8217; of users won&amp;#8217;t see its new age verification setup</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876575/discord-age-verification-vast-majority-users-inference</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:17:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876575</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Discord released an update clarifying that the "vast majority of people can continue using Discord exactly as they do today," without needing to use a face scan or ID to verify their age so they can use the platform without restrictions. Discord states in the post that "age prediction" using information Discord already [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is offering Meta AI-powered animations for profile photos</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/facebook-is-offering-meta-ai-powered-animations-for-profile-photos-201022506.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17919990-988c-428f-8773-4eb8806058e9</guid>
      <description>Meta has been going all in on AI, whether people want it or not, and now it's bringing more features in that vein to Facebook. The network's latest move is to let people use Meta AI to animate their profile photos. Because what better way to express your individuality than to use a pre-canned AI-generated animation on your own face?Meta AI is also coming for your Facebook Stories and Memories. The network's Restyle lets you use gen-AI to change up the aesthetic of your posts. You can once again use pre-canned stylings or give the AI assistant your own prompt.In the company's own words, the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get two years of Surfshark VPN for up to 87 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-two-years-of-surfshark-vpn-for-up-to-87-percent-off-123000309.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b286225-32f8-41dc-9bc9-bf699f554c51</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been thinking about signing up for a VPN, Surfshark has solid deals on its two-year plans right now. Surfshark&#8217;s One plan is 87 percent off right now when you pay for two years upfront, plus you&#8217;ll get three extra months free. That comes out to a total of $62 for the first 27 months of access.
We&#8217;ve generally liked Surfshark as a straightforward, speedy service for everyday use, and it&#8217;s one of the picks in our guide to the best VPNs. In our Surfshark review, we found it delivered excellent speeds overall and reliably unblocked Netflix across most of our test servers, which makes thi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Einstein avait donn&#233; la cl&#233; de l'&#233;nigme des exoplan&#232;tes Tatooines de Star Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-einstein-avait-donne-cle-enigme-exoplanetes-tatooines-star-wars-130931/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:03:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-einstein-avait-donne-cle-enigme-exoplanetes-tatooines-star-wars-130931/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Quand on pense &#224; la th&#233;orie de la relativit&#233; g&#233;n&#233;rale d'Einstein, on pense imm&#233;diatement aux trous noirs, aux trous de ver, et bien s&#251;r aux ondes gravitationnelles et au Big Bang. Pourtant, la premi&#232;re application de la th&#233;orie d'Einstein a &#233;t&#233; en m&#233;canique c&#233;leste, avec le mouvement des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brendan Fraser-Rachel Weisz &#8216;Mummy&#8217; Reunion Is Coming in 2028</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mummy-4-release-date-brendan-fraser-rachel-weisz-2000720240</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720240</guid>
      <description>The much-anticipated fourth 'Mummy' film will be directed by Matt Bettinelli-Olpin and Tyler Gillett and now has a release date to look forward to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 bargain-priced soundbars that will instantly upgrade your TV's disappointing built-in sound &#8212; without breaking the bank</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/4-bargain-priced-soundbars-that-will-instantly-upgrade-your-tvs-disappointing-built-in-sound-without-breaking-the-bank</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dobCKMwWRiGya2zCUgX38K</guid>
      <description>Put more boom in your room with these cut-price soundbar deals, including Dolby Atmos options</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cure for the memory crisis? John Carmack envisions fiber cables replacing RAM for AI usage, which would mean a better future for us all</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/a-cure-for-the-memory-crisis-john-carmack-envisions-fiber-cables-replacing-ram-for-ai-usage-which-would-mean-a-better-future-for-us-all</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UjW4yFuQ8sp94CWcce8i9a</guid>
      <description>Fiber aside, there could be a nearer-term way of alleviating the memory crisis, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmarterTools network breached using auth-bypass attack against single unpatched virtual machine</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/smartertools-network-breached-using-auth-bypass-attack-against-single-unpatched-virtual-machine</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">U8r9evWkPHukY5LyxZuHGe</guid>
      <description>Just one neglected server was enough to suffer a ransomware infection but this time, the damage was minimal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target CEO shuffles leadership team as his first big move after taking over</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490437/target-michael-fiddelke-sales</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490437/target-michael-fiddelke-sales</guid>
      <description>It is the first substantial change under CEO Michael Fiddelke, a 20-year company veteran who took over for Brian Cornell this month. 
Target CEO Michael Fiddelke is reshuffling his leadership team and making other changes shortly after stepping into the top job at the retailer that has struggled operationally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir CEO Alex Karp Recorded a Video About ICE for His Employees</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/palantir-ceo-alex-karp-employee-questions-on-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6986287b89651d97f0bdbbac</guid>
      <description>In a video shared with Palantir employees, Alex Karp did not explain how ICE is utilizing the company&#8217;s products. Instead, workers were told they can sign NDAs if they want detailed information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount sweetens its bid for Warner Bros. Discovery with &#8216;additional benefits&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490430/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-hollywood</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T19:49:46</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490430/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-hollywood</guid>
      <description>The new March 2 deadline marks the third time Paramount has pushed back the expiration of its tender offer.
Paramount is again sweetening its&#160;hostile takeover bid&#160;for Warner Bros. Discovery, while again extending the deadline for its tender offer as it scrambles for more shareholder support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le robot humano&#239;de de Xpeng chute lourdement lors d&#8217;une d&#233;monstration &#224; Shenzhen</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2973023_le-robot-humanoide-de-xpeng-chute-lourdement-lors-dune-demonstration-a-shenzhen</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2973023_le-robot-humanoide-de-xpeng-chute-lourdement-lors-dune-demonstration-a-shenzhen</guid>
      <description>
&#192; Shenzhen, le robot Iron de Xpeng s'est effondr&#233; en pleine d&#233;monstration devant une foule compacte.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI releases recovered footage from Nancy Guthrie&amp;#8217;s Nest cam</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876542/fbi-nancy-guthrie-nest-cam-video</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T14:43:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876542</guid>
      <description>More than a week after Nancy Guthrie disappeared, the FBI has released footage from a Nest camera by Guthrie's front door. FBI Director Kash Patel says on X that law enforcement has been working with "private sector partners" and that the video was "recovered from residual data located in backend systems." Google spokesperson Patrick Seybold [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s how Rivian changed the rear door manual release on the R2</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/heres-how-rivian-changed-the-rear-door-manual-release-on-the-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091502</guid>
      <description>Rivian, along with other automakers, has been under pressure to make the manual door releases easier to access. The new R2 SUV does that &#8212; here's how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook adds new AI features, animated profile photos, and backgrounds for text posts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/facebook-adds-new-ai-features-animated-profile-photos-and-backgrounds-for-text-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091608</guid>
      <description>Facebook's new AI features let users animate their profile pics, restyle their Stories and Memories, and add  backgrounds to text posts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pensions Bet That Google Will Still Be Raking in Cash a Hundred Years From Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pensions-bet-that-google-will-still-be-raking-in-cash-a-hundred-years-from-now-2000720177</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720177</guid>
      <description>Long live Google. Your pension might depend on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are 15 last-minute tech gadgets from Amazon that I'd actually want to receive for Valentine's Day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/here-are-15-last-minute-tech-gadgets-from-amazon-that-id-actually-want-to-receive-for-valentines-day</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qKuQwZQV6UPrrnCY8jhNRW</guid>
      <description>Forget flowers and chocolates - I'm rounding up 15 last-minute tech gadget gifts for Valentine's Day that I'd actually want to receive this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Flanagan Has His Next Stephen King Adaptation: &#8216;The Mist&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mike-flanagan-has-his-next-stephen-king-adaptation-the-mist-2000720205</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720205</guid>
      <description>Yes, there was already a movie and a show, but now we're getting a new take on the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Itch.io bundle to help Minnesota includes over 1,200 games and costs just $10</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/this-itchio-bundle-to-help-minnesota-includes-over-1200-games-and-costs-just-10-190643987.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a962fc9-017d-499a-974f-a47c5fe9dfc2</guid>
      <description>You have likely heard about the masked agents of ICE mucking around in Minnesota for the past few months, resulting in numerous violent incidents and deaths. Itch.io is hosting a bundle to help raise money for the Immigrant Law Center of Minnesota, which was organized by charity creator Jes Wade.
The No ICE in Minnesota bundle includes nearly 1,300 video games and tabletop games and costs just $10, though those with deep pockets can certainly donate more than that. It has a goal of $100,000, which it certainly is on pace to meet.

There are some nifty titles here, particularly for those intere...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I made the switch to 4K Blu-ray and have never looked back &#8212; these are the discs I'd recommend above all others</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/i-made-the-switch-to-4k-blu-ray-and-have-never-looked-back-these-are-the-discs-id-recommend-above-all-others</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Wi6eLJD3ELudwTFLsofm5d</guid>
      <description>These six 4K UHD Blu-ray discs will make excellent additions to anyone's collection &#8211; whether you're new to the format or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick admits to meeting Epstein, reversing previous claims</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490422/jeffrey-epstein-files-howard-lutnick</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490422/jeffrey-epstein-files-howard-lutnick</guid>
      <description>Lutnick is the highest-profile U.S. official to face bipartisan calls for his resignation amid revelations of his ties to Epstein.
Under questioning from Democrats Tuesday, Commerce Secretary&#160;Howard Lutnick&#160;acknowledged that he had met with&#160;Jeffrey Epstein&#160;twice after his 2008 conviction for soliciting prostitution from a child, reversing Lutnick&#8217;s previous claim that he had cut ties with the late financier after 2005....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Bankman-Fried wants a re-trial for fraud charges</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/sam-bankman-fried-wants-a-re-trial-for-fraud-charges-185910093.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80604916-f793-44fc-bef5-f2557d9766d3</guid>
      <description>Former cryptocurrency poster boy Sam Bankman-Fried is trying to get another chance in court. He has filed a request that for a new trial on claims that new witness testimony could alter the case made against him by prosecutors, according to Bloomberg. His odds for getting the re-trial, where he'd be representing himself, seem pretty slim. This is a separate motion from a formal appeal of his previous conviction.Bankman-Fried is one of many cryptocurrency leaders who have since been prosecuted for fraud. After being jailed for witness tampering, he was found guilty of seven charges of fraud and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Russie annonce des restrictions sur Telegram pour &#171;&#160;violation&#160;&#187; de la loi</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-10/la-russie-annonce-des-restrictions-sur-telegram-pour-violation-de-la-loi.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:55:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1a9f7de2d4732e987e38a5d142717f6</guid>
      <description>Le fondateur de l&#8217;application Telegram a d&#233;nonc&#233; mardi les restrictions annonc&#233;es par les autorit&#233;s russes sur la messagerie, y voyant une atteinte &#224; la &#171;&#160;libert&#233; des citoyens&#160;&#187; et une tentative de forcer les Russes &#224; migrer vers une messagerie locale plus facile &#224; contr&#244;ler.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
