<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:40:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>1Password plans are getting more expensive soon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/1password-plans-are-getting-more-expensive-soon-213236400.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f12be096-0514-4b55-bdf4-855353ed4e0a</guid>
      <description>1Password is increasing prices for its individual and family plans. The individual rate is increasing from nearly $36 a year to $48, while the family option will cost $72 instead of $60. In emails sent to users, the business announced that the new rates will take effect for users at their next subscription renewal after March 27.&#160;It's a sizable price hike, but 1Password hasn't been incrementally inching its fees higher every couple years like we see so often for streaming subscriptions. This is the biggest bump we've seen to its rates in several years, even though the company has been adding e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s new 1.9GW clean energy deal includes massive 100-hour battery</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/googles-new-1-9gw-clean-energy-deal-includes-massive-100-hour-battery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096436</guid>
      <description>Form Energy's iron-air batteries will store wind and solar power to keep the data center running 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple will build the Mac Mini in the US and you can probably thank AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/macs/apple-will-build-the-mac-mini-in-the-us-and-you-can-probably-thank-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VsSxXRLJ5xcqZC5Ww5Urqd</guid>
      <description>Better than a golden plaque</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CarGurus data breach affects 12.5 million accounts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/cargurus-data-breach-affects-12-5-million-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096432</guid>
      <description>Automotive marketplace CarGurus was the target of a data breach in which the names, email addresses, phone numbers, and physical addresses of millions of customers were stolen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic won&#8217;t budge as Pentagon escalates AI dispute</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/anthropic-wont-budge-as-pentagon-escalates-ai-dispute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096435</guid>
      <description>The Pentagon has given Anthropic until Friday to loosen AI guardrails or face potential penalties, escalating a high-stakes dispute that raises questions about government leverage, vendor dependence, and investor confidence in defense tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let me see some ID: age verification is spreading across the internet</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/883855/age-verification-internet-apps-laws-privacy-safety</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T16:05:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=883855</guid>
      <description>Age verification is a reality on a growing number of social media platforms, requiring an ID or facial scan for full access to everything from YouTube to Roblox. The age-gating wave is coming along with calls for stronger child safety measures online, despite concerns about privacy, security, and censorship.&#160; In the US, lawmakers are pushing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Might Not Pick Up on Its Big Cliffhanger Just Yet</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-season-2-maekar-2000725956</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725956</guid>
      <description>New adventures await Dunk and Egg in season two, but what will House Targaryen be up to in the meantime?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord delays age verification to address user concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/discord-delays-age-verification-to-address-user-concerns-205500482.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69affb55-045a-46f3-99cb-ecd18db4c445</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, Discord said it would be enacting an age verification policy. The platform faced some initial concerns from users about turning over their IDs and personal information, particularly given how poorly similar policies have been going elsewhere. Discord announced today it will delay and make some changes to its plans in response to the ongoing backlash.The first change is that Discord is postponing the global rollout of its age verification plans until the second half of 2026. The company noted that it would meet its legal obligations in places where they exist, likely in thos...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord delays global rollout of age verification after backlash</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/discord-delays-global-rollout-of-age-verification-after-backlash/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096379</guid>
      <description>The company added that 90% of users won&#8217;t need to verify their age and will be able to keep using Discord as usual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A teacher was killed during an ICE chase last week. Why you probably didn&#8217;t hear about it</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497866/a-teacher-was-killed-during-an-ice-chase-last-week-why-you-probably-didnt-hear-about-it</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497866/a-teacher-was-killed-during-an-ice-chase-last-week-why-you-probably-didnt-hear-about-it</guid>
      <description>Though different than earlier ICE-related civilian deaths, the incident has also been far less visible. Experts say it may reflect longstanding media biases.
One week ago, a Savannah, Georgia, woman was killed during an Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) pursuit. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novo Nordisk&#8217;s Latest Weight Loss Drug Might Be Its Best Yet&#8212;and a Much-Needed Win</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/novo-nordisks-new-weight-loss-drug-might-be-its-best-yet-and-a-much-needed-win-2000725962</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725962</guid>
      <description>Over a 24 week period, people on UBT251 lost up to 20% of their body weight on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon has reportedly given Anthropic until Friday to let it use Claude as it sees fit</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/the-pentagon-has-reportedly-given-anthropic-until-friday-to-let-it-use-claude-as-it-sees-fit-203549467.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02865f17-7bf6-415a-b262-346a028b08ae</guid>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth will reportedly give Anthropic until Friday to drop certain guardrails for military use, as reported by Axios. The outlet also reported that CEO Dario Amodei met with Hegseth yesterday as the Pentagon ratcheted up pressure on the AI company to give in to its demands.
The makers of Claude have reportedly been offered an ultimatum: Either yield to the government's demands to remove limits for certain military applications, or potentially be forced to tailor its AI model to the government's needs under the Defense Production Act.
Anthropic, for its part, has said th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram head pressed on lengthy delay to launch teen safety features, like a nudity filter, court filing reveals</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/instagram-head-pressed-on-lengthy-delay-to-launch-teen-safety-features-like-a-nudity-filter-court-filing-reveals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096211</guid>
      <description>An email chain with Instagram head Adam Mosseri indicated the company was aware of teen safety issues in DMs in 2018, but didn't launch its unwanted nudity filter until 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founders of long-lost weather app Dark Sky return with a new forecast platform, and it&#8217;s already better than Apple&#8217;s unreliable flagship weather predictions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/founders-of-long-lost-weather-app-dark-sky-return-with-a-new-forecast-platform-and-its-already-better-than-apples-unreliable-flagship-weather-predictions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">M2eGKyxYtSMz8xHW7PWUxd</guid>
      <description>After parting ways with Apple, Dark Sky founders are back with a new forecast app, Acme Weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Leaders Warn European War on American Big Tech Comes With Real Security Risks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/military-leaders-warn-european-war-on-american-big-tech-comes-with-real-security-risks-2000726045</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726045</guid>
      <description>Military officials say Europe is too dependent on U.S. tech to break away now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft says OpenClaw is "not appropriate to run on a standard personal or enterprise workstation" &#8212; so should you be worried?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/microsoft-says-openclaw-is-unsuited-to-run-on-standard-personal-or-enterprise-workstation-so-should-you-be-worried</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4kbMpGMyfHPrQkRShnqdQA</guid>
      <description>Microsoft warns OpenClaw&#8217;s design blends automation and persistent credentials, creating structural risks unsuitable for standard personal or enterprise workstations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Airlines plans a much smaller future as it tries to survive bankruptcy &#8212; again</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497876/spirit-airlines-plans-a-much-smaller-future-as-it-tries-to-survive-bankruptcy-again</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T20:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497876/spirit-airlines-plans-a-much-smaller-future-as-it-tries-to-survive-bankruptcy-again</guid>
      <description>A new bankruptcy proposal shows the airline cutting its Airbus fleet further and shrinking its network in hopes of stabilizing by late spring or early summer.
Spirit Airlines is hanging on by a thread &#8211;but it is hanging on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Now Own an Official Version of the Superior &#8216;Star Trek&#8217; Mug</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-deep-space-nine-official-coffee-mug-raktajino-2000726005</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726005</guid>
      <description>After Picard's tea mug made a comeback a few years ago, it's time for the better 'Trek' mug&#8212;and better beverage&#8212;to get the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sent an AI-generated push alert that included a racial slur</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-sent-an-ai-generated-push-alert-that-included-a-racial-slur-195951493.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9620b47a-f76a-47b1-9cf6-52dbfc742d0a</guid>
      <description>Google sent out an AI-generated news alert that included the N-word, according to reporting by Deadline. The push notification featured a link to a story by The Hollywood Reporter regarding an incident at the recent BAFTA Film Awards. The word appeared in the notification under the link.
This was first spotted by Instagram user Danny Price, who accompanied a screengrab with a caption reading "what an interesting Black History Month this has turned out to be." Google has since apologized and said that it has "removed the offensive notification" and is "working to prevent this from happening aga...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Bluetooth Speaker Is on Sale for $50 Off Right Now</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/jbl-flip-7-deal-0223/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699c92e1c3e34b153305c790</guid>
      <description>JBL's fabulous Flip 7 speaker is on super sale for $100. Grab this go-anywhere companion on the cheap before the nice weather hits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File-Sharing Network Soulseek Has Been Flooded With AI Homer Simpson Cover Songs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/file-sharing-network-soulseek-has-been-flooded-with-ai-homer-simpson-cover-songs-2000725979</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725979</guid>
      <description>Slop has come for the pirates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's the first teaser for A24's adaptation of The Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/heres-the-first-teaser-for-a24s-adaptation-of-the-backrooms-194300513.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e668cff7-af1a-4f2f-800f-7a2fea33e1d6</guid>
      <description>Three years after announcing plans to produce a film based on the viral YouTube short, The Backrooms (Found Footage) in 2023, A24 has released the first teaser for its adaptation. Backrooms, as the film is now called, is directed by the short's original creator, Kane Parsons, and will be released on May 29, 2026.The teaser offers little to go on for anyone who hasn't watched the original short or the series of videos Parsons made after it, but it is replete with The Backrooms' hallmark: ominous liminal spaces. Layered over footage of stranger and stranger rooms (or perhaps one room becoming th...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
