<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:53:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The best Apple deals you can still shop in Cyber Monday&#8217;s final hours</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/827826/best-black-friday-apple-deals-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T23:20:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=827826</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re planning to gift an Apple device this holiday season &#8212; or treat yourself &#8212;&#160;time is now running out to take advantage of the latest Cyber Monday promos. The annual shopping holiday is already down to its final hours, and we&#8217;re starting to see some items go up in price or out of stock. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only a few hours left! Get the Razer Basilisk V3 X HyperSpeed at nearly 50% off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/peripherals-accessories/only-a-few-hours-left-get-the-razer-basilisk-v3-x-hyperspeed-at-nearly-50-percent-off</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9YGWYFxEEZZkoLHWhTcKFM</guid>
      <description>Best Buy has a time attached to this deal, so you know it means business. Don't wait for this deal to disappear!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Verge-approved gifts are still available for up to 60 percent off for Cyber Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/833050/cyber-monday-2025-gift-ideas-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T23:04:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=833050</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re hoping to whittle down your wish list before the holiday panic truly sets in, Cyber Monday presents a prime opportunity. Many of the tech-y gifts we recommend for Christmas, graduation, Mother&#8217;s Day, and other celebratory events throughout the year are receiving their steepest discounts to date. These aren&#8217;t random picks, either; they&#8217;re items [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does it mean when Uncle Sam is one of your biggest shareholders? Chip startup xLight is about to find out</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/01/what-does-it-mean-when-uncle-sam-is-one-of-your-biggest-shareholders-chip-startup-xlight-is-about-to-find-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071698</guid>
      <description>You can imagine how this is all going over in Silicon Valley, where the libertarian ethos runs deep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Monday Kindle deals are still live - here are two bundles I recommend before they're gone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/cyber-monday-kindle-deals-are-still-live-here-are-two-bundles-i-recommend-before-theyre-gone</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Yjb5xaVNJudA8TfM6AszQM</guid>
      <description>The Amazon Kindle Colorsoft bundle with a charging dock and the Amazon Kindle Scribe Essentials bundle are both at all-time low prices and come with deluxe accessories worth having.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung officialise le Galaxy Z TriFold : un &#233;cran de 10 pouces qui tient dans la poche</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2894769_samsung-officialise-le-galaxy-z-trifold-un-ecran-de-10-pouces-qui-tient-dans-la-poche</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2894769_samsung-officialise-le-galaxy-z-trifold-un-ecran-de-10-pouces-qui-tient-dans-la-poche</guid>
      <description>
La course au "Tri-Fold" est lanc&#233;e. Quelques mois apr&#232;s le choc Huawei Mate XT, Samsung r&#233;plique enfin. Le Galaxy Z TriFold n'est pas un prototype : c'est un monstre de puissance avec Snapdragon 8 Elite et une charni&#232;re en titane. Mais attention, la facture risque d'&#234;tre sal&#233;e.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arcee aims to reboot U.S. open source AI with new Trinity models released under Apache 2.0</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/arcee-aims-to-reboot-u-s-open-source-ai-with-new-trinity-models-released</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1AqYEeMpSMHnH3N6Xd7ZrW</guid>
      <description>For much of 2025, the frontier of open-weight language models has been defined not in Silicon Valley or New York City, but in Beijing and Hangzhou.Chinese research labs including Alibaba's Qwen, DeepSeek, Moonshot and Baidu have rapidly set the pace in developing large-scale, open Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) models &#8212; often with permissive licenses and leading benchmark performance. While OpenAI fielded its own open source, general purpose LLM this summer as well &#8212; gpt-oss-20B and 120B &#8212; the uptake has been slowed by so many equally or better performing alternatives. Now, one small U.S. company is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last chance Cyber Monday Apple deals &#8211; shop record-low prices on AirPods, iPads, MacBooks, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/last-chance-cyber-monday-apple-deals-shop-record-low-prices-on-airpods-ipads-macbooks-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wFxtG7JFBr4ymwD6zqsZ5S</guid>
      <description>Cyber Monday Apple deals are ending soon, and I'm rounding up all the best offers still available, featuring record-low prices on AirPods, iPads, MacBooks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop the presses: Dyson discounts the Gen5Outsize after Black Friday by 52% &#8211; now just AU$799</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/stop-the-presses-dyson-discounts-the-gen5outsize-after-black-friday-by-51-percent-now-just-au799</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Tsepsga7fxgEukVuhgbq9H</guid>
      <description>Who knew our favourite Black Friday deal would come on December 2? Get in quick to grab one of Dyson's two most premium stick vacuums at half price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are 50+ Cyber Monday deals you can still get for $100 or less</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/833655/cyber-monday-best-cheap-tech-deals-under-100-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T22:35:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=833655</guid>
      <description>When the deals are flying fast and furious, it can be easy to overspend, especially when OLED TVs, laptops, and other great pieces of tech are cheaper than they&#8217;ve ever been. You don&#8217;t have to spend a lot to find gift-worthy deals, though. If you&#8217;re working with a tighter budget, we&#8217;ve found plenty of gadgets [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We found 45 of the best last-minute Cyber Monday&#160;deals under $30</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/835702/cyber-monday-best-cheap-tech-deals-under-30-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=835702</guid>
      <description>One of the pitfalls of&#160;Cyber Monday is getting overwhelmed by deep discounts on premium gadgets. After all, who wouldn&#8217;t want to save hundreds, if not thousands, of dollars on a high-end gaming laptop or a spiffy OLED TV? But these luxury items, while great, can still easily set you back three or four figures. Luckily, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'd buy this Galaxy S25 Ultra deal in a heartbeat, even though the Galaxy S26 Ultra is almost here</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/id-buy-this-galaxy-s25-ultra-deal-in-a-heartbeat-even-though-the-galaxy-s26-ultra-is-almost-here</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83aCmjoNCRCVgNGRKSoDce</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy S25 Ultra is down to an all-time low, and even though the Galaxy S26 Ultra is right around the corner, this deal is worth buying because this phone has staying power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These great Cyber Monday tech deals will likely be gone tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/834422/cyber-monday-2025-best-deals-tech-gadgets-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T22:13:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=834422</guid>
      <description>December is kicking off with a bang. Cyber Monday is today, and it&#8217;s one of your last chances to score major deals before the holiday rush plows us all over. It&#8217;s a great moment to snag gadgets &#8212; many of which have been tested by The Verge &#8212; at (or close to) all-time lows if [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Z Trifold&#160;: Samsung plie le jeu (deux fois) avec son nouveau smartphone de 10 pouces</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/galaxy-z-trifold-samsung-plie-le-jeu-deux-fois-avec-son-nouveau-smartphone-de-10-pouces.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1312873</guid>
      <description>Surprise ! Samsung a pr&#233;sent&#233; cette nuit ce qui sera sans doute son dernier smartphone de l'ann&#233;e, le Galaxy Z Trifold. Si ce nom vous rappelle quelque chose, quoi de plus normal : la rumeur court depuis des mois sur cet appareil &#224; deux charni&#232;res qui d&#233;voile un &#233;cran digne d'une grande tablette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Pips hints, answers for December 2, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pips-nyt-games-hints-answers-easy-medium-hard-december-2</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05ottqIznVhqfFbMBrVFetp</guid>
      <description>The New York Times' latest game, Pips, brings domino fun to your desktop. How to play Pips as well as hints in case you get stuck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections Sports Edition today: Hints and answers for December 2, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nyt-connections-sports-edition-hint-answer-today-december-2-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">063wKt56sT23tfTWekUeYrC</guid>
      <description>Connections: Sports Edition is a New York Times word game about finding common sports threads between words. How to solve the day's puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints today: Clues, answers for December 2, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nyt-connections-hint-answer-today-december-2-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">027Gb2Vs8cOjsYHkn8wxQb4</guid>
      <description>Connections is a New York Times word game that's all about finding the "common threads between words." How to solve the puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints, answers for December 2, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/strands-nyt-hint-december-2-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04pvmsd4OQ4j8U74kS2lscy</guid>
      <description>The NYT Strands hints and answers you need to make the most of your puzzling experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordle today: Answer, hints for December 2, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wordle-today-answer-december-2-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00fd8Pgu9zKbTgc7hckdbAM</guid>
      <description>Here's the answer for "Wordle" #1626 on December 2 as well as a few hints, tips, and clues to help you solve it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last call for Cyber Monday TV deals &#8211; the best offers still available on Samsung, LG, Hisense, TCL, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/last-call-for-cyber-monday-tv-deals-the-best-offers-still-available-on-samsung-lg-hisense-tcl-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2oRY6mKCGo7BTFUFTjynY</guid>
      <description>Cyber Monday is coming to a quick close, but there's still time to grab an exceptional TV deal.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
