<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:40:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta seeks to limit evidence in child safety case</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/meta-seeks-to-limit-evidence-in-child-safety-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085084</guid>
      <description>Meta is set to go on trial in New Mexico for allegedly failing to protect minors. The company is requesting a broad swath of information not be allowed to be presented in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rare, Deadly Fungus Is Making People Sick in Tennessee</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-rare-deadly-fungus-is-making-people-sick-in-tennessee-2000712977</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712977</guid>
      <description>At least 36 cases of histoplasmosis and possibly one death have been reported in the state since last fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Bezos and Blue Origin want to help provide high-speed satellite internet across the globe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/jeff-bezos-and-blue-origin-want-to-help-provide-high-speed-satellite-internet-across-the-globe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gpAshKjDifBSkLd2Wh45UQ</guid>
      <description>Blue Origin will offer a LEO/MEO satellite internet network for enterprises and governments, but not consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dacia Spring &#224; 5 900 euros : voici comment ce pays casse le prix de la voiture &#233;lectrique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2952607_dacia-spring-a-5-900-euros-voici-comment-ce-pays-casse-le-prix-de-la-voiture-electrique</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2952607_dacia-spring-a-5-900-euros-voici-comment-ce-pays-casse-le-prix-de-la-voiture-electrique</guid>
      <description>
5 900 euros pour une voiture &#233;lectrique neuve. C'est le tarif affich&#233; par la Dacia Spring en Allemagne gr&#226;ce &#224; un alignement des plan&#232;tes assez unique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forza Horizon 6 will hit Xbox Series X/S and PC on May 19</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/forza-horizon-6-will-hit-xbox-series-xs-and-pc-on-may-19-183242726.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc2b9c5f-3523-41bd-a810-fee126209886</guid>
      <description>Forza Horizon 6 is taking the racing series to Japan for the first time, and now we know exactly when you&#8217;ll be able to hit the virtual streets of Tokyo. The game will arrive on Xbox Series X/S, PC and Xbox Cloud on May 19, with an early access period commencing on May 15. That lines up with earlier reports about the release date(s) after an in-game ad supposedly appeared in Forza Horizon 5. The upcoming title will hit PS5 later this year.The standard edition of Forza Horizon 6 is expected to cost $70, though it will be on Xbox Game Pass Ultimate and PC Game Pass. To jump in a few days early, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI pin is beneath Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/an-ai-pin-is-beneath-apple-182744647.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a9c4806-23e0-4b7e-8496-a6afa6f6c483</guid>
      <description>So it's come to this: Apple is reportedly working on a wearable AI pin. According to The Information, it is going to be a small device with "multiple cameras, a speaker, microphones and wireless charging." It sounds like the perfect gadget to pair with the long-awaited AI-powered Siri update, which will also reportedly work as a chatbot. But while many Apple rumors conjure up an air of excitement, the notion of an Apple AI pin sounds downright baffling. Worse, it just seems desperate.&#160;Apple, the company known for taking its time to jump into new categories with more thoughtful solutions than i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google now offers free SAT practice exams, powered by Gemini</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/google-now-offers-free-sat-practice-exams-powered-by-gemini/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085134</guid>
      <description>Google now offers a way for college-bound students to take free SAT practice exams with the help of Gemini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurosky et W Social : tout savoir sur les deux alternatives europ&#233;ennes &#224; X et Threads</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2952595_eurosky-et-w-social-tout-savoir-sur-les-deux-alternatives-europeennes-a-x-et-threads</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2952595_eurosky-et-w-social-tout-savoir-sur-les-deux-alternatives-europeennes-a-x-et-threads</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu passer cette lettre ouverte &#224; Ursula von der Leyen ? L'Europe ne veut plus d&#233;pendre des caprices d'Elon Musk. Pour remplacer la plateforme am&#233;ricaine, deux projets sortent du bois : Eurosky et W Social. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forza Horizon 6 launches in May</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865355/forza-horizon-6-xbox-developer-direct-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T13:18:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865355</guid>
      <description>Forza Horizon 6 will launch on Xbox Series X / S and PC on May 19th, Xbox and developer Playground Games announced during Thursday's Developer Direct showcase. If you preorder the Premium Edition, you can play starting May 15th. The game will come to PS5 later this year. The game has the largest map in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici ce que le &#171;&#160;Starlink&#160;&#187; de Jeff Bezos promet : un d&#233;bit de 6 TBit/s partout sur Terre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/2952579_voici-ce-que-le-starlink-de-jeff-bezos-promet-un-debit-de-6-tbit-s-partout-sur-terre</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/2952579_voici-ce-que-le-starlink-de-jeff-bezos-promet-un-debit-de-6-tbit-s-partout-sur-terre</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que la guerre des &#233;toiles se jouait uniquement entre Starlink et Kuiper ?Jeff Bezos vient de sortir une nouvelle carte de sa manche : TeraWave. Un r&#233;seau de 5 408 satellites pens&#233; pour les entreprises, avec des technologies optiques qui laissent les experts perplexes. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korg's new experimental synthesizer combines acoustic sounds with electronic control</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/korgs-new-experimental-synthesizer-combines-acoustic-sounds-with-electronic-control-180809332.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0de8a06-753c-4133-976c-dbea7e7fb5b0</guid>
      <description>Korg just officially unveiled the Phase8 synthesizer, after years of tinkering by a team led by legendary engineer Tatsuya Takahashi. This is a highly experimental synthesizer, but it's not a concept unit. It'll be available for purchase in April.
The Phase8 uses a new form of "acoustic synthesis" that combines acoustic sound generation with electronic control. Takahashi says the synthesizer is "beyond analog vs. digital" and "beyond electronics" altogether. It features chromatically tuned steel resonators, which creates an acoustic sound similar to that of a kalimba. These signals can be mani...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like an Avalanche: Wild Video Captures the Violent Trigger Behind Solar Flares</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/like-an-avalanche-wild-video-captures-the-violent-trigger-behind-solar-flares-2000712926</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712926</guid>
      <description>Solar Orbiter captured the most detailed view of a solar flare, observing the build-up of events that lead to the explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy has slashed $100 off the Asus ROG Xbox Ally 3 &#8212; and get three-months free Xbox Game Pass Premium</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/best-buy-has-slashed-usd100-off-the-asus-rog-xbox-ally</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ut3DdxYACjBvVkdEAAMsS4</guid>
      <description>The ASUS ROG Ally hits near record-low price, making it a better proposition compared to the Steam Deck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Makes a Prank War Out of One of the Oldest Debates in &#8216;Star Trek&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-episode-3-recap-2000712640</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712640</guid>
      <description>'Vitus Reflux' pushes the show's balance between 'Star Trek' ideas and its youthful vibe to a fun, if fruitless, stretching point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CEO of celeb fav gym Dogpound launches $5M fund to back wellness companies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/former-ceo-of-celeb-fav-gym-dogpound-launches-5m-fund-to-back-wellness-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084701</guid>
      <description>Jenny Liu is a solo first-time GP looking to back underrepresented wellness founders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok generated an estimated 3 million sexualized images&#160;&#8212; including 23,000 of children &#8212;&#160;over 11 days</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/grok-generated-an-estimated-3-million-sexualized-images--including-23000-of-children--over-11-days-175053250.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98f36b3d-e1cf-4748-9f68-adf54b55e798</guid>
      <description>We already knew xAI's Grok was barraging X with nonconsensual sexual images of real people. But now there are some numbers to put things in perspective. Over an 11-day period, Grok generated an estimated 3 million sexualized images &#8212; including an estimated 23,000 of children.Put another way, Grok generated an estimated 190 sexualized images per minute during that 11-day period. Among those, it made a sexualized image of children once every 41 seconds.On Thursday, the Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH) published its findings. The British nonprofit based its findings on a random sample of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Developer Direct 2026: the biggest games and announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/865573/xbox-developer-direct-2026-the-biggest-games-and-announcements</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T12:50:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=865573</guid>
      <description>In a now-annual tradition, Microsoft is kicking off the year with a showcase of some of its biggest upcoming games. Last year&#8217;s edition of the Xbox Developer Direct had some big names, like Doom: The Dark Ages and a little game called Clair Obscur: Expedition 33. And we already know the three main titles that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If there's one TV I recommend watching the Super Bowl on, it's LG's 65-inch C5 OLED TV &#8212; $1,300 off at Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/if-theres-one-tv-i-recommend-watching-the-super-bowl-on-its-lgs-65-inch-c5-oled-tv-usd1-300-off-at-best-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Q99S87ANrVAnLPmpsrSwS3</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the upcoming Super Bowl, LG's stunning 65-inch C5 OLED, our best-rated TV, is on sale for a massive $1,300 discount at Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Agents Are &#8216;Doxing&#8217; Themselves</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-agents-are-doxing-themselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696f977f81397433db57a96c</guid>
      <description>The alleged risks of being publicly identified have not stopped DHS&#160; and ICE employees from creating profiles on LinkedIn, even as Kristi Noem threatens to treat revealing agents' identities as a crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;They are starting to realize no one wants Horizon integration&#8217; &#8212; Meta announces a major Quest 3 change, but is it a blessing or a curse in disguise?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/they-are-starting-to-realize-no-one-wants-horizon-integration-meta-announces-a-major-quest-3-change-but-is-it-a-blessing-or-a-curse-in-disguise</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R6dUfA9rgMBLbvmhrch6Gn</guid>
      <description>Your Meta Quest 3 is getting a big Horizon-related change in update v85.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: TV channel, where to stream and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-tv-channel-where-to-stream-and-more-173222003.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>We might still be in the midst of the playoffs, but that doesn't mean we can't plan ahead for Super Bowl LX. For those of you who just can't with Roman numerals, thats Super Bowl 60, and it's taking place this year at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA, on February 8, starting at 6:30 p.m. ET.&#160;
Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the championship game will be broadcast on Super Bowl Sunday on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. And it's not just the game that we're excited for, either. This year's halftime performer is singer and rapper Bad Bunny, and there will be pre-gam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Invincible&#8217; Season 4 Brings the War Home in March</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/invincible-season-4-trailer-amazon-2000712828</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712828</guid>
      <description>Dinosaurs, dads, and demons all threaten to give Mark a hard time when 'Invincible' returns in two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This group of workers is winning the AI adoption race</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478672/this-group-of-workers-is-winning-the-ai-adoption-race</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478672/this-group-of-workers-is-winning-the-ai-adoption-race</guid>
      <description>With fewer practical constraints and more direct benefits, independently employed professionals are leveraging the technology at higher rates
After spending much of his career in marketing, Daniel Hebert pivoted into Software as a Service (SaaS) sales for a high-growth startup in 2018. But what started out as a dream job soon turned into a nightmare....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deux ans apr&#232;s la cr&#233;ation de sa filiale &#233;lectrique Ampere, Renault fait machine arri&#232;re</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/deux-ans-apres-la-creation-de-sa-filiale-electrique-ampere-renault-fait-machine-arriere.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322017</guid>
      <description>C'&#233;tait une id&#233;e int&#233;ressante sur le papier : regrouper les activit&#233;s &#233;lectrique et logicielle du groupe Renault sous une seule et unique ombrelle, celle d'Ampere. La structure, forte de 11&#160;000 salari&#233;s, devait voler de ses propres ailes en Bourse&#8230; mais le principe de r&#233;alit&#233; a &#233;t&#233; le plus fort. L'entit&#233; devrait finalement r&#233;int&#233;grer la maison-m&#232;re....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think AI is just for deepfakes? Adobe reveals a new slate of pro filmmakers using Firefly Foundry to overhaul production workflows</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/think-ai-is-just-for-deepfakes-adobe-reveals-a-new-slate-of-pro-filmmakers-using-firefly-foundry-to-overhaul-production-workflows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mq4Q8Jz6hnFPwJyhwN7HCM</guid>
      <description>Lights, camera, prompting with Adobe's new Firefly Foundry suite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sennheiser Is Making Headphone Parties for Your TV a Thing</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sennheiser-is-making-headphone-parties-for-your-tv-a-thing-2000712965</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712965</guid>
      <description>This is either the best or worst idea ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under Armour cyberattack may put over 7 million at risk - but it's staying quiet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/under-armour-cyberattack-may-put-over-7-million-at-risk-but-its-staying-quiet</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dKeHFfuYFi3mDgggU5tKw4</guid>
      <description>The retailer is yet to confirm, or deny the claims, while Have I Been Pwned? adds millions of new emails to its archive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invincible season 4 trailer reveals new heroes and villains, the start of the Viltrumite War &#8212; and a mid-March release date for the hit Prime Video show's next entry</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/amazon-prime-video/invincible-season-4-trailer-reveals-new-heroes-and-villains-the-start-of-the-viltrumite-war-and-a-mid-march-release-date-for-the-hit-prime-video-show</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GtJGLwN33YSMDaChXeFnV7</guid>
      <description>Amazon has released the official trailer for Invincible season 4 &#8211; and confirmed when it'll make its Prime Video debut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why This Weekend&#8217;s Winter Storm Is Going to Suck Extra Bad</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-this-weekends-winter-storm-is-going-to-suck-extra-bad-2000712994</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712994</guid>
      <description>A warming Arctic set the stage for a massive winter storm expected to stretch 2,000 miles across the Eastern U.S. this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wix launches 'Harmony' -  a hybrid approach to vibe coding and visual design</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-building/wix-launches-harmony-a-hybrid-approach-to-vibe-coding-and-visual-design</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sK8Zus9cKXKWdpTMvTEnwP</guid>
      <description>Wix Harmony doesn't live in a 'bubble' and won't break the site's code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This NYC auction celebrating America&#8217;s 250th birthday will feature rare and iconic documents</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479404/this-nyc-auction-celebrating-americas-250th-birthday-will-feature-rare-iconic-documents</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:15:22</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479404/this-nyc-auction-celebrating-americas-250th-birthday-will-feature-rare-iconic-documents</guid>
      <description>Highlights include a 1776 broadside printing of the Declaration of Independence with an estimated value of $3&#8211;$5 million.
As the United States prepares to celebrate its 250th birthday, an auction in New York will feature rare items that trace the nation&#8217;s history.The event Friday at Christie&#8217;s, dubbed &#8220;We the People: America at 250,&#8221; will bring together foundational political texts, iconic American art and rare historical artifacts.Among the highlights is a rare 1776 broadside printing of the Declaration of Independence produced in New Hampshire by printer Robert Luist Fowle, estimated at $3 m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeForce Now adds support for flight controllers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/geforce-now-adds-support-for-flight-controllers-171047006.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a421f52b-97d6-4ae8-bd04-6d90c0ac6092</guid>
      <description>It only seems right that cloud gaming should welcome virtual pilots, and that&#8217;s definitely now the case if GeForce Now is your streaming platform of choice. One of the most frequently requested features from its community according to NVIDIA, flight control support has now been added to its GeForce Now offering, meaning you can live your Top Gun fantasies without worrying about your rig buckling under the pressure.
The first compatible peripheral is the Thrustmaster T.Flight HOTAS One &#8212; which incidentally NVIDIA is giving away to five winners of a competition it&#8217;s currently running, along with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling fusion power company General Fusion to go public via $1B reverse merger</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/struggling-fusion-power-company-general-fusion-to-go-public-via-1b-reverse-merger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085056</guid>
      <description>General Fusion's merger with an acquisition company will net the company over $300 million. Just last year, the company ran into trouble raising money from other investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 87 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>In a chaotic world, one thing you can count on is your own common-sense steps toward better cybersecurity. Most of the holiday deals are over by now, but plenty of services are still offering excellent prices. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart online trackers.
We strongly recommend using a VPN, but you might get stuck with a substandard app if you jump on the very first deal you see. You might also mistakenly end up paying more than you want to, as even otherwise respectab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Trailer for &#8216;Maul&#8212;Shadow Lord&#8217; Proves Crime Does Pay</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-maul-shadow-lord-trailer-release-date-2000712526</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712526</guid>
      <description>The new Disney+ animated series shows the ex-Sith still has plenty of evil life left in him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony announces its first turntables in years</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865333/sony-new-turntables-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865333</guid>
      <description>Sony is releasing a new turntable for the first time since 2019. Two, in fact. The entry-level PS-LX3BT ($399.99) and step-up PS-LX5BT ($499.99) are designed for easy operation with both wired and Bluetooth hi-res audio. Both turntables include one-button automatic playback - which starts the turntable, raises and lowers the tonearm on the vinyl, and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free TV startup Telly only had 35,000 units in people&#8217;s homes last fall</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/865645/telly-units</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865645</guid>
      <description>This is Lowpass by Janko Roettgers, a newsletter on the ever-evolving intersection of tech and entertainment, syndicated just for The Verge subscribers once a week. When free TV startup Telly came out of stealth in 2023, it did so with big promises: Company executives told the media at the time that Telly would ship 500,000 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Code is suddenly everywhere inside Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/865689/microsoft-claude-code-anthropic-partnership-notepad</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865689</guid>
      <description>Developers have been comparing the strengths and weaknesses of Anthropic's Claude Code, Anysphere's Cursor, and Microsoft's GitHub Copilot for months now, looking for a winner. While no individual AI coding tool manages to be the best at every task that software developers do each day, Claude Code is increasingly coming out on top for its [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 biggest rumored upgrades coming to your iPhone in iOS 27 &#8211; including the long-awaited new Siri</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/ios/the-5-biggest-rumored-upgrades-coming-to-your-iphone-in-ios-27-including-the-long-awaited-new-siri</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">j5MEBVBg44zNMERuL9v2uJ</guid>
      <description>iOS 27 looks set to be heavily AI-based, but we're also hearing about possible performance and satellite connectivity improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony updates a cult-favorite cheap Bluetooth turntable with not one but two new models &#8211; but there's a catch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/sony-updates-a-cult-favorite-cheap-bluetooth-turntable-with-not-one-but-two-new-models-but-theres-a-catch</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93fAQTcwiKUrbwhsgFtqhd</guid>
      <description>Sony's finally updated its fan-favorite PS-LX310BT deck &#8211; but the budget-friendly pricing hasn't carried over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World leaders text just like us</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478145/world-leaders-text-just-like-us</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478145/world-leaders-text-just-like-us</guid>
      <description>Turns out top-level diplomatic back-channelling isn&#8217;t so different from blowing up the group chat. 
President Donald Trump&#8217;s late-night Truth Social posting spree on Tuesday&#8212;doubling down on his Greenland ambitions and threatening any who try to get in his way&#8212;also included a flurry of leaked texts from the leaders of NATO, France, Finland, and Norway.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Q&amp;A with Amanda Askell, the lead author of Anthropic&#8217;s new &#8216;constitution&#8217; for AIs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479037/anthropic-claude-amanda-askell-constitution-ai-chatbot</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479037/anthropic-claude-amanda-askell-constitution-ai-chatbot</guid>
      <description>The Anthropic philosopher explains how and why her company updated its guide for shaping the conduct and character of its models.
Welcome to AI Decoded, Fast Company&#8217;s weekly newsletter that breaks down the most important news in the world of AI. I&#8217;m Mark Sullivan, a senior writer at Fast Company,covering emerging tech, AI, and tech policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un tr&#233;sor cosmique en France : cette m&#233;t&#233;orite contient des grains plus anciens que le Soleil</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-tresor-cosmique-france-cette-meteorite-contient-grains-plus-anciens-soleil-w2t8-130194/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-tresor-cosmique-france-cette-meteorite-contient-grains-plus-anciens-soleil-w2t8-130194/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Les m&#233;t&#233;orites fascinent, d'abord parce qu'elles viennent de l'espace interplan&#233;taire et qu'il&#160;nous est ainsi permis&#160;en quelque sorte de le toucher des mains sur Terre, mais aussi parce que nous sommes bien conscients qu'elles nous connectent aux plus vieilles archives de la formation du Syst&#232;me...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony d&#233;poussi&#232;re le vinyle : ses nouvelles platines s&#8217;occupent de tout, m&#234;me du Bluetooth HD</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2951103_sony-ps-lx3bt-et-ps-lx5bt-deux-nouvelles-platines-vinyles-sans-fil-pour-seduire-novices-et-passionnes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2951103_sony-ps-lx3bt-et-ps-lx5bt-deux-nouvelles-platines-vinyles-sans-fil-pour-seduire-novices-et-passionnes</guid>
      <description>
Avec les PS-LX3BT et PS-LX5BT, Sony introduit deux platines vinyles sans fil automatiques, pens&#233;es pour simplifier l&#8217;acc&#232;s au vinyle tout en proposant une connectivit&#233; Bluetooth avanc&#233;e et une conception soign&#233;e.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day laptop sales 2026: today's best early deals from Dell, Best Buy, and others, plus what to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/deals/presidents-day-laptop-sales-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44fD3e4ZF7tD8qdwa6yY3c</guid>
      <description>The President's Day laptop sales are just around the corner now - get ready with our handy guide, which includes great early deals you can shop right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo continues robotaxi ramp up with Miami service now open to public</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/waymo-continues-robotaxi-ramp-up-with-miami-service-now-open-to-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085051</guid>
      <description>Waymo is opening its driverless robotaxis to the public in Miami, starting with a 60-square-mile service area and plans to reach the airport "soon."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube TV is solving an issue that subscribers have been complaining about for years &#8211; this is how it&#8217;s lifting its &#8216;all or nothing&#8217; subscription plans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/youtube-tv-is-solving-an-issue-that-subscribers-have-been-complaining-about-for-years-this-is-how-its-lifting-its-all-or-nothing-subscription-plans</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bejNQBQKUuB9qDFWxHBHgX</guid>
      <description>YouTube TV is scrapping its Basic Plan for over 10 new specialized subscription tiers, as well as a big upgrade for multiview streaming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver : la 3e d&#233;marque d&#233;marre fort, voici les offres qui m&#233;ritent votre argent</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949895_soldes-dhiver-3e-demarque-meilleures-offres-en-direct</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949895_soldes-dhiver-3e-demarque-meilleures-offres-en-direct</guid>
      <description>
Cela fait d&#233;j&#224; deux semaines que les soldes d'hiver ont commenc&#233; en France et que les e-commer&#231;ants tels qu'Amazon, Fnac, Darty, Boulanger ou encore Cdiscount partagent des offres. Depuis hier, c'est la 3e d&#233;marque et les promotions se multiplient. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft shovels more features into Windows 11's Notepad &#8212; but isn't it time the company focused on fixing things instead?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/microsoft-shovels-more-features-into-windows-11s-notepad-but-isnt-it-time-the-company-focused-on-fixing-things-instead</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Kjwzd6s8YNgM4He9tqAsn6</guid>
      <description>Is this going to irritate a fair few Windows 11 users? You can pretty much bank on that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD's Ryzen 7 9850X3D CPU will arrive on January 29 and cost $499</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/amds-ryzen-7-9850x3d-cpu-will-arrive-on-january-29-and-cost-499-165000446.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18432a3f-0177-4630-855b-b231efe66360</guid>
      <description>At CES earlier this month, AMD announced the Ryzen 7 9850X3D, a more wallet-friendly take on its $700 9950X3D. The company promised the new chip would be out sometime in the first three months of the year, and it's going to arrive a bit sooner than you might have expected. It can be all yours on January 29 for $499.AMD says the 9850X3D builds on the 9800X3D with an 400MHz upgrade to the boost clock. It can reach boost speeds of 5.6GHz. The Ryzen 7 9850X3D is an 8-core CPU with 16 threads and 104MB of combined L2 and L3 cache. AMD is employing its 3D V-cache tech so it can vertically stack more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland proposes new law allowing police to use spyware</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/ireland-proposes-new-law-allowing-police-to-use-spyware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085064</guid>
      <description>The Irish government announced that it wants to pass a law that would grant police more surveillance powers, such as using spyware to fight serious crime, while aiming to protect the privacy rights of its citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score this 100-inch Hisense U7 Mini LED 4K TV for over $1,000 off &#8212;&#160;its best price ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-22-hisense-u7-mini-led-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02YzCQcsPeaFvnNBAczyP2A</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the Super Bowl and the Winter Olympics, the Hisense 100-inch U7 Mini LED 4K TV is on sale for 37% off at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why nobody&amp;#8217;s stopping Grok</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/865275/grok-deepfake-undressing-elon-musk-content-moderation</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865275</guid>
      <description>Today&#8217;s episode of Decoder is about X, Grok, and Elon Musk. By now we&#8217;re several weeks into one of the worst, most upsetting, and most stupidly irresponsible AI controversies in the short history of generative AI. Grok, the chatbot made by Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI, is able to make all manner of AI-generated images, including nonconsensual [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars 2026: The biggest surprises out of the nominations list</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/oscars-2026-surprises</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03zRnYDJzPeGETQ3HuBYK0p</guid>
      <description>What surprise has you cheering?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinners leads 2026 Oscar nominations with record-breaking 16 nods &#8212; and it's been joined by a surprise Apple TV movie on the Best Picture shortlist</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/sinners-leads-2026-oscar-nominations-with-record-breaking-16-nods-and-its-been-joined-by-a-surprise-apple-tv-movie-on-the-best-picture-shortlist</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4JpopY9htngardBnUDapcS</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Oscar nominees list has been revealed &#8212; and Sinners' record-breaking haul isn't the biggest talking point for me.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
