<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:28:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GLP-1 Drugs Like Ozempic Might Have a Side Effect Nobody Expected</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/glp-1-drugs-like-ozempic-might-have-a-side-effect-nobody-expected-2000696194</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696194</guid>
      <description>A new study finds a possible association between GLP-1 drugs like semaglutide and chronic cough, though the authors are calling for more research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&#8217;s user growth has slowed, report finds</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/chatgpts-user-growth-has-slowed-report-finds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073318</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT's global monthly active users only grew by around 5% from August to November, while Gemini's users grew by about 30%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Jujutsu Kaisen: Execution&#8217; Is All the Worst Impulses of the Anime Compilation Film Format</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jujutsu-kaisen-execution-review-culling-game-gkids-2000695768</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695768</guid>
      <description>Mappa's theatrical hodgepodge of a compilation film and preview of 'Jujutsu Kaisen' season 3 showcases the inherent flaws of the popular supernatural shonen series more than its merits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI readiness: Philanthropy&#8217;s hidden multiplier</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91454955/ai-readiness-philanthropys-hidden-multiplier</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91454955/ai-readiness-philanthropys-hidden-multiplier</guid>
      <description>The difference between social impact reaching thousands versus millions often comes down to investing in AI.
When film cameras were invented, people&#160;didn&#8217;t&#160;become filmmakers overnight. We pointed cameras at theater stages, digitizing what already existed. It took us a while to reimagine what film cameras could unlock. The real opportunity&#160;wasn&#8217;t&#160;recording theater plays. It was stepping outside and inventing&#160;cinema.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantone&#8217;s &#8216;Cloud Dancer&#8217; color party is a recession indicator</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/design/839364/pantones-cloud-dancer-color-of-the-year-party</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T14:59:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839364</guid>
      <description>Pantone's color of the year for 2026 is white - sorry, Cloud Dancer. Pantone announced the shade on Thursday, and describes it as a "discrete white hue offering a promise of clarity." The accompanying image shows a person with cropped hair in billowy white clothing, arms outstretched over a background of clouds. "PANTONE 11-4201 Cloud [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An influential article that called Monsanto&#8217;s Roundup safe for humans has been retracted 25 years later</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455427/herbicide-safety-article-monsanto-roundup-retracted-25-years-later</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T19:50:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455427/herbicide-safety-article-monsanto-roundup-retracted-25-years-later</guid>
      <description>The paper, which had a major impact on policymaking, appears to have been based on unpublished studies by the controversial agricultural company. 
In April 2000, Elsevier published an article in the journal Regulatory Toxicology and Pharmacology, which claimed that the herbicide Roundup (glyphosate) from the Monsanto Company didn&#8217;t pose a risk of cancer or other health issues for humans....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Mobile&#8217;s refurbished iPhones are an unsurprisingly bad deal</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/839123/trump-mobile-refurbished-iphones-galaxy-phones-apple-samsung</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T14:34:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839123</guid>
      <description>It's been well established that the Trump Phone doesn't exist. But that isn't the only phone Trump Mobile sells. It also offers a range of refurbished Apple and Samsung handsets that you can buy right now. You really shouldn't though. I was relieved reading Allison's coverage over the last two weeks to discover that not [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Official: The Original Theatrical Cut of &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Is Coming Back to Theaters</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-original-version-rerelease-2000696337</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696337</guid>
      <description>Lucasfilm is celebrating the film's 50th anniversary on February 17, 2027, in the best possible way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&#8217;s favorite inflation indicator stayed elevated in September as spending weakened</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455815/inflation-fed-september-spending-economy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455815/inflation-fed-september-spending-economy</guid>
      <description>The data indicate that core inflation was muted in September and will bolster the case for a cut to the Fed&#8217;s key interest rate at its next meeting Dec. 9-10. 
The Federal Reserve&#8217;s preferred measure of inflation changed little in September, likely easing the way to a widely expected interest rate cut by the&#160;central bank next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Softbank CEO Wants to Build &#8216;Trump Industrial Parks&#8217; on Federal Land to Boost AI: Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/softbank-ceo-wants-to-build-trump-industrial-parks-on-federal-land-to-boost-ai-report-2000696243</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696243</guid>
      <description>The idea sounds similar to Trump's "freedom cities" first pitched in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol takes down crypto and laundering network worth 700 million</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/europol-takes-down-crypto-and-laundering-network-worth-700-million</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pbFfYwtFKKA25o8WivGGCV</guid>
      <description>A two-stage campaign resulted in the arrest of nine and the seizure of cash, crypto, and other valuables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horses is a hit, but its studio might still be in trouble</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839164/horses-interview-santa-ragione-steam-ban-censorship</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T14:00:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839164</guid>
      <description>After indie narrative horror game Horses was banned from Steam two years ago, it put the studio, Santa Ragione, at risk of closure. Studio cofounder and Horses producer Pietro Righi Riva had to make a difficult phone call to the game&#8217;s director, Italian filmmaker Andrea Lucco Borlera. &#8220;I was terrified for him,&#8221; Riva said in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Avengers: Endgame&#8217; Is Returning to Theaters Before &#8216;Doomsday&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avengers-endgame-rerelease-2026-doomsday-marvel-2000696326</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696326</guid>
      <description>The biggest Marvel film of all time will be in theaters in September to get audiences ready for 'Avengers: Doomsday'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Bird Swallowed 800 Rocks and Choked to Death, Scientists Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ancient-bird-swallowed-800-rocks-and-choked-to-death-scientists-say-2000696218</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696218</guid>
      <description>&#8220;When birds are sick, they start doing weird things.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome can now autofill details from your Google account</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/838987/google-chrome-android-ios-desktop-autofill-account-wallet</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=838987</guid>
      <description>Google has announced several autofill improvements being rolled out to the mobile and desktop versions of Chrome. The updates will give autofill access to more of your data from places like Google Wallet and make it easier to select the right info a form is asking for when there are multiple suggestions. Autofill can now [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to expand travel ban to more than 30 countries</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455810/travel-ban-noem-trump-administration-national-guard-shooting</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455810/travel-ban-noem-trump-administration-national-guard-shooting</guid>
      <description>In the wake of the National Guard shooting, the administration already ratcheted up restrictions on the 19 countries included in the initial travel ban.
The Trump administration will be expanding&#160;its ban on travel&#160;for citizens of certain countries to more than 30, Homeland Security Secretary Kristi Noem said, in&#160;the latest restriction&#160;to come since a man from Afghanistan was accused of&#160;shooting two National Guard members....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Deals From the Silk &amp; Snow Cyber Week Sale (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/silk-snow-deals-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692cae76d042757baf0afacf</guid>
      <description>For a few more days, you can save on mattresses and bed frames from one of our favorite makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market nears an all-time high</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455806/stock-market-nears-all-time-high</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T18:47:11</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455806/stock-market-nears-all-time-high</guid>
      <description>Renewed hopes for a cut to interest rates by the Fed at its meeting next week helped stocks recover some losses.
The U.S. stock market is flirting with its all-time high on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now use Pixel phones as a Switch 2 webcam</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839133/google-pixel-smartphone-nintendo-switch-2-webcam</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T13:46:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839133</guid>
      <description>When it launched the Switch 2&#8217;s compatibility with various webcams was hit or miss. A webcam isn&#8217;t a necessary accessory, but since the Switch 2 lacks one of its own, you need one to take full advantage of the console&#8217;s GameChat feature that can livestream players&#8217; faces during multiplayer matches. Switch 2 webcam compatibility has [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android malware threat can wipe your bank account</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/android-malware-bank-account-fake-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02wN2CeuKf7nzJfrubsVjSZ</guid>
      <description>There's a new malicious way for bad actors to get access to your bank account using Android.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Luigi Mangione trial is all about narrative control</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/839054/luigi-mangione-evidence-suppression-new-york-internet-fandom-media</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839054</guid>
      <description>On Monday, several dozen members of the public are lined up outside 100 Centre Street in Lower Manhattan, hoping to squeeze into the courtroom to hear testimony from witnesses called by the state against Luigi Mangione - the man accused of shooting and killing UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson a year ago. Despite the endless news [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
