<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:27:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Move over Thanos, this June Marvel&#8217;s Avengers will face their greatest foe yet &#8212; Strixhaven&#8217;s best elephant mage, and I can&#8217;t wait</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/move-over-thanos-this-june-marvels-avengers-will-face-their-greatest-foe-yet-strixhavens-best-elephant-mage-and-i-cant-wait</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rgVUj3bRbUtesrAfasTbeQ</guid>
      <description>We've got a better look at the Marvel decks coming to Magic: The Gathering, but I'm much more excited for Secrets of Strixhaven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo reportedly raising a $16B funding round</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/31/waymo-reportedly-raising-a-16-billion-funding-round/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088510</guid>
      <description>Waymo is reportedly finalizing a new funding round that will value the robotaxi company at $110 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX seeks federal approval to launch 1 million solar-powered satellite data centers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/31/spacex-seeks-federal-approval-to-launch-1-million-solar-powered-satellite-data-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088505</guid>
      <description>SpaceX's filing claims these satellites will be &#8220;a first step towards becoming a Kardashev II-level civilization&#160;&#8212;&#160;one that can harness the Sun&#8217;s full power."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Still Loyal to &#8216;House of the Dragon&#8217; Despite Creative Strife</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hbo-still-loyal-to-house-of-the-dragon-despite-creative-strife-2000716180</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716180</guid>
      <description>Behind the scenes turmoil isn't stopping the network's excitement for the return of 'House of the Dragon' later in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT or Super Bowl? OpenAI premium ads could cost as much as a prime NFL TV slot - but which is better value?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/chatgpt-or-super-bowl-openai-premium-ads-could-cost-as-much-as-a-prime-nfl-tv-slot-but-which-is-better-value</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WX2tchnQpCuCLciocib6iX</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is launching ChatGPT ads with NFL-level pricing, offering impression data only, raising questions about engagement and advertising value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s Pick for Fed Chair Points to Growing Bitcoin-Dollar Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trumps-pick-for-fed-chair-points-to-growing-bitcoin-dollar-synthesis-2000716347</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716347</guid>
      <description>Warsh's hawkish stance on Fed policy may have disappointed the crypto world, but he said Bitcoin was effectively gold for anyone under the age of 40.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA is still planning to make a 'huge' investment in OpenAI, CEO says</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/nvidia-is-still-planning-to-make-a-huge-investment-in-openai-ceo-says-205521528.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07237b44-9b41-430b-9f97-9ce38adb5588</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang told reporters that the company will "invest a great deal of money" in OpenAI's latest funding round, according to Bloomberg, after The Wall Street Journal on Friday reported that the two companies were rethinking a previous $100 billion deal that hasn't "progressed beyond the early stages" of negotiations. Speaking to reporters in Taipei this weekend, Huang reportedly said it could be "the largest investment we've ever made."&#160;NVIDIA and OpenAI jointly announced in September that NVIDIA would be investing up to $100 billion in OpenAI to build 10 gigawatts of AI data cen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayaneo's Pocket S Mini has the perfect aspect ratio for revisiting classic console games</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ayaneos-pocket-s-mini-has-the-perfect-aspect-ratio-for-revisiting-classic-console-games-203926701.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">639a7323-61aa-419e-b092-5ab7d5503052</guid>
      <description>There may be plenty of gaming handhelds out there, but there aren't many horizontal options that let you play childhood favorites in the original 4:3 aspect ratio. To address that gap, Ayaneo launched a premium option with the Pocket S Mini. As a "true 4:3 retro handheld," the Pocket S Mini won't have those pesky vertical black bars whenever you're emulating video games from the CRT television era.
Handhelds like the Anbernic RG405M and even Ayaneo's own Pocket Air Mini already offer a 4:3 aspect ratio, but the Pocket S Mini presents a more high-end build with a full metal frame and a glass fr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;No more Minnesota nice, Minneapolis will strike&#8221;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/871606/minneapolis-general-strike-anti-ice-protest</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-31T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=871606</guid>
      <description>It was too cold to take off my mittens and check Google Maps so I put my faith in the trickle of bundled-up people ahead of me. All of them were carrying signs and wearing whistles around their necks on top of layers and layers of winter clothing. At first there were dozens of us [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
