<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:33:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GOG is already working on native Linux support</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/875425/gog-native-linux-support</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T15:23:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875425</guid>
      <description>GOG recently posted a job listing for a senior software engineer focused on porting its Galaxy desktop client to Linux. Now, in reply to a Reddit AMA, the GOG team has revealed that work on native Linux support is already underway. It's still too early to give an ETA, according to the Reddit thread. But [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charli XCX Is a Demonic Brat in Takashi Miike&#8217;s &#8216;Untitled Tokyo&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/charli-xcx-is-a-demonic-brat-in-takashi-miikes-untitled-tokyo-2000719231</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719231</guid>
      <description>Get ready to see Charli XCX go horror mode in the next horror project from Takeshi Miike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I went back to Linux and it was a mistake</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/875077/linux-was-a-mistake</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T14:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875077</guid>
      <description>It's a complete coincidence that I installed Linux around the same time as my colleagues Nathan Edwards and Stevie Bonifield. A few months ago, I decided to breathe new life into a 2019 Dell XPS 15 that had been collecting dust for a couple of years. Despite its (at the time) high-end Core i7 CPU [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to stream the 2026 Super Bowl for free this weekend: Patriots vs. Seahawks time, where to watch and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-stream-the-2026-super-bowl-for-free-this-weekend-patriots-vs-seahawks-time-where-to-watch-and-more-124512717.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b2b14-4380-47f2-9cb8-bd2dfe744915</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Super Bowl between the New England Patriots and the Seattle Seahawks will air on NBC this Sunday, Feb. 8. The Big Game will also stream live on Peacock. If you no longer subscribe to cable, don't have access to NBC over the air and aren't currently signed up for Peacock, there are still ways to watch Super Bowl LX &#8212; and Bad Bunny's history-making Super Bowl Halftime Show &#8212; for free. Here's how to tune in.&#160;
How to watch Super Bowl LX free:




Date: Sunday, Feb. 8
Time: 6:30 p.m. ET
Location: Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.
TV channel: NBC, Telemundo
Streaming: Peacock, DirecTV, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Mobile&#8217;s T1 Phone is apparently still coming, but it&#8217;ll be uglier and more expensive</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/trump-mobiles-t1-phone-is-apparently-still-coming-but-itll-be-uglier-and-more-expensive-190626835.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba0919f7-0364-4745-a6d4-bd0017221eee</guid>
      <description>Trump Mobile is already failing to deliver on some early promises, according to the latest report from The Verge. The report revealed the near-final design of the T1 smartphone and uncovered some major changes with pricing and manufacturing.
The Verge spoke with Don Hendrickson and Eric Thomas, two of the three execs behind Trump Mobile, about the company's first smartphone, which will get a more expensive price tag and no longer boast being made in the USA. Thanks to a screenshot from the report, we can see that the latest T1 design also changed the camera array, which first resembled the iPh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les voitures chinoises calent en France, le panneau solaire Tesla qui fonctionne &#224; l&#8217;ombre et le VTC Decathlon abordable &#8211; Le r&#233;cap&#8217; Survolt&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2969725_les-voitures-chinoises-calent-en-france-le-panneau-solaire-tesla-qui-fonctionne-a-lombre-et-le-vtc-decathlon-abordable-le-recap-survoltes</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2969725_les-voitures-chinoises-calent-en-france-le-panneau-solaire-tesla-qui-fonctionne-a-lombre-et-le-vtc-decathlon-abordable-le-recap-survoltes</guid>
      <description>
Une nouvelle semaine bien charg&#233;e dans l'univers de la mobilit&#233; &#233;lectrique ! Entre l'efficacit&#233; des mesures fran&#231;aises contre l&#8217;arriv&#233;e massive des v&#233;hicules chinois, les innovations technologiques comme les nouveaux panneaux solaires Tesla, et le lancement d&#8217;un VTC &#233;lectrique tr&#232;s malin chez Decathlon, l'actu a de quoi faire r&#233;agir. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested 3 affordable OLED TVs from LG, Samsung and Philips side-by-side &#8212; here&#8217;s which one I&#8217;d buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/i-tested-3-affordable-oled-tvs-from-lg-samsung-and-philips-side-by-side-heres-which-one-id-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ts8YHxJFXYZwh6ZoKGgT3Y</guid>
      <description>Affordable but excellent OLED doesn't have to be a rarity, so I tested three top models to see which was worth the investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cet &#233;cran LG utile pour votre PC qui peut se transformer en SmartTV perd presque 50 % de son prix chez Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2968467_cet-ecran-lg-utile-pour-votre-pc-qui-peut-se-transformer-en-smarttv-perd-presque-50-de-son-prix-chez-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2968467_cet-ecran-lg-utile-pour-votre-pc-qui-peut-se-transformer-en-smarttv-perd-presque-50-de-son-prix-chez-amazon</guid>
      <description>
Du haut de ses 34 pouces, le LG MyView Smart Monitor est un &#233;cran utile pour celles et ceux qui travaillent &#224; domicile ou qui souhaitent avoir une Smart TV sans quitter leur chaise de bureau. Chez Amazon, il perd 49 % de son prix et tombe &#224; 229,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
