<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:33:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic Launches New Model That Spots Zero Days, Makes Wall Street Traders Lose Their Minds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anthropic-launches-new-model-that-spots-zero-days-makes-wall-street-traders-lose-their-minds-2000718648</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718648</guid>
      <description>Opus 4.6 has arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GeekBook X14 Pro is one of the lightest laptops I&#8217;ve tested, and it packs plenty of power at a reasonable price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/geekom-geekbook-x14-pro-laptop-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f8Nh8yvMt5bsfxfocF7QS</guid>
      <description>The GeekBook X14 Pro is an ultra-lightweight 14-inch display laptop featuring Windows 11 Pro and a premium build with a stylish magnesium alloy outer. Inside, an impressive CPU and GPU offer a powerful combination, making it a great option for business and creative use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Plot of &#8216;The Darwin Incident&#8217; Is Bananas, But I&#8217;ve Gotta See What This Monkey Does Next</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-plot-of-the-darwin-incident-is-bananas-but-ive-gotta-see-what-this-monkey-does-next-2000718445</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718445</guid>
      <description>The Prime Video anime series has everything: a human-chimpanzee lead, vegan eco-terrorists, and high school drama with a blush of romance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TTT-Discover optimizes GPU kernels 2x faster than human experts &#8212; by training during inference</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/ttt-discover-optimizes-gpu-kernels-2x-faster-than-human-experts-by-training</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TUr5kwAyRGSBTWZTA8kdZ</guid>
      <description>Researchers from Stanford, Nvidia, and Together AI have developed a new technique that can discover new solutions to very complex problems. For example, they managed to optimize a critical GPU kernel to run 2x faster than the previous state-of-the-art written by human experts.Their technique, called &#8220;Test-Time Training to Discover&#8221; (TTT-Discover), challenges the current paradigm of letting models &#8220;think longer&#8221; for reasoning problems. TTT-Discover allows the model to continue training during the inference process and update its weights for the problem at hand.The limits of 'frozen' reasoningCu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Possible Lunar Impact in 2032 Could Spark Days of Meteor Showers on Earth</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-possible-lunar-impact-in-2032-could-spark-days-of-meteor-showers-on-earth-2000718658</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718658</guid>
      <description>The space rock has a 4.3% chance of striking the Moon in six years&#8212;and it could generate a flash nearly as bright as Venus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordVPN review 2025: Innovative features, a few missteps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/nordvpn-review-2025-innovative-features-a-few-missteps-163000578.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd3be014-d14b-4ac2-ad5d-4ae3aa73cc14</guid>
      <description>When we say that NordVPN is a good VPN that's not quite great, it's important to put that in perspective. Building a good VPN is hard, as evidenced by all the shovelware VPNs flooding the market. NordVPN may not be perfect, but it's easily top-five caliber and excels in certain use cases.
First, the bad: NordVPN's apps could all stand to undergo a little more quality control, with elements distracting from other elements and inconsistent designs from platform to platform. At least one of its FAQ pages directly contradicts itself. And while all the server locations could unblock Netflix, the on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans attack &amp;#8216;woke&amp;#8217; Netflix &#8212; and ignore YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/874655/netflix-warner-bros-republican-culture-war-ted-sarandos-hearing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T16:40:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874655</guid>
      <description>When Netflix co-CEO Ted Sarandos entered the Senate office building on Tuesday, he got thrown a curveball. What started as a standard antitrust hearing relating to the Warner Bros. merger quickly devolved into a performative Republican attack about the spread of "woke" ideology on the streaming service. At the same time, arguably a much more [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Post is retreating from Silicon Valley when it matters most</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/the-washington-post-is-retreating-from-silicon-valley-when-it-matters-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090063</guid>
      <description>The Bezos-owned newspaper gutted its San Francisco bureau and coverage of tech &#8212; including journalists reporting on Amazon and Blue Origin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit Details Horrifying 911 Call Before Tesla Driver Died While Trapped Inside Car</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lawsuit-details-horrifying-911-call-before-tesla-driver-died-while-trapped-inside-car-2000718671</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718671</guid>
      <description>A wrongful death lawsuit claims a 20-year-old driver was unable to escape a burning vehicle due to faulty electronic doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our focus areas are enterprise... and just continuing to grow at the premium, you know, higher-end of the market': AMD CEO plays down global memory shortage, says she expects PC market to shrink</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/our-focus-areas-are-enterprise-and-just-continuing-to-grow-at-the-premium-you-know-higher-end-of-the-market-amd-ceo-plays-down-global-memory-shortage-says-she-expects-pc-market-to-shrink</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">j6eCgxFLdC8JDWYKUyWcdk</guid>
      <description>AMD reports strong revenue growth while acknowledging rising RAM and SSD prices and predicting a shrinking PC market overall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyalty Is Dead in Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/model-behavior-loyalty-is-dead-in-silicon-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697d18dab8c7ce5e411f04be</guid>
      <description>Founders used to be wedded to their companies. Now, anyone can be lured away for the right price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A16z VC&#160;wants founders to stop stressing over insane ARR numbers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/a16z-vc-wants-founders-to-stop-stressing-over-insane-arr-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090068</guid>
      <description>A16z VC Jennifer Li&#8288;, who oversees some of the firm's fastest growing AI companies, warns founders not to believe every ARR claim made on X.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Predator: Badlands&#8217; Is Roaring Onto Hulu Next Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/predator-badlands-streaming-release-date-2000718653</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718653</guid>
      <description>Sci-fi's odd couple extraordinaire is coming to streaming just in time for Valentine's Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Cops Frequently Got Caught Planting Drugs in 2017</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cops-planting-drugs-2010s-body-cameras-2000718559</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718559</guid>
      <description>Look. All technology comes with a learning curve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X's latest Community Notes experiment allows AI to write the first draft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/xs-latest-community-notes-experiment-allows-ai-to-write-the-first-draft-210605597.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">858633a6-0d81-4f6b-8496-9422e3005804</guid>
      <description>X is experimenting with a new way for AI to write Community Notes. The company is testing a new "collaborative notes" feature that allows human writers to request an AI-written Community Note.&#160;It's not the first time the platform has experimented with AI in Community Notes. The company started a pilot program last year to allow developers to create dedicated AI note writers. But the latest experiment sounds like a more streamlined process.&#160;According to the company, when an existing Community Note contributor requests a note on a post, the request "now also kicks off creation of a Collaborative...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iron Lung&#8217;s path to theaters was unique, even if the movie isn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/874500/iron-lung-theater-box-office-markiplier</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874500</guid>
      <description>As a movie, Iron Lung is occasionally thrilling but mostly forgettable. It's a small-budget horror flick that has some cool ideas and pulls them off in an extremely efficient way, creating a sense of tension that unfortunately never turns into outright scares. But the most important thing about it is what it represents. At a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I compared nearly 20 of the best noise-cancelling headphones, and the two best cheap options have great deals right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/i-compared-nearly-20-of-the-best-noise-cancelling-headphones-and-the-two-best-cheap-options-have-great-deals-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Wh2yPZJRegC3zVHCFmFDgG</guid>
      <description>Don't miss these budget bargains for blocking outside noise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nike is being investigated for anti-white discrimination. It could upend corporate DEI.</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487190/nike-is-being-investigated-for-anti-white-discrimination-it-could-upend-corporate-dei</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487190/nike-is-being-investigated-for-anti-white-discrimination-it-could-upend-corporate-dei</guid>
      <description>The EEOC is investigating the sportswear giant over DEI-related discrimination&#8212;a case that could make an example of Nike and create a chilling effect across corporate America. 
The federal agency that enforces anti-discrimination laws in the workplace made an unexpected disclosure this week: Nike was under investigation for its approach to diversity, equity, and inclusion, due to claims that the company had discriminated against white employees and job applicants.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You&#8217;re Sick of This Brutal Cold, Boy Do We Have News for You</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/if-youre-sick-of-this-brutal-cold-boy-do-we-have-news-for-you-2000718571</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718571</guid>
      <description>Although the eastern U.S. is facing another frigid weekend, forecast models suggest temperatures will rise significantly in the latter half of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s new Claude Opus 4.6 aims to think through bigger codebases</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488000/anthropics-new-claude-opus-4-6-aims-to-think-through-bigger-codebases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T20:44:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488000/anthropics-new-claude-opus-4-6-aims-to-think-through-bigger-codebases</guid>
      <description>The company&#8217;s latest AI model improves long-context understanding, agentic coding, and knowledge-work tasks while matching Opus 4.5 pricing.
Anthropic is out with a new model called Claude Opus 4.6, an upgrade to its top-of-the-line Opus 4.5 model that launched in November. The new release could add new capabilities to Anthropic&#8217;s Claude Code coding assistant, which is facing growing competitive pressure from OpenAI&#8217;s Codex....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The price of Bitcoin drops below $65,000</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874603/bitcoin-price-drop-cryptocurrency</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T15:38:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874603</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, Bitcoin's value fell over 10 percent in a single day, dropping to around $64,000, the lowest it has been since the 2024 Presidential election, as CNBC reports. After crossing $100,000 in November 2024 and peaking at over $122,000 in October 2025, the cryptocurrency has been in a steady decline for the last several [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, Jeffrey Epstein Is Probably Not Satoshi Nakamoto</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/no-jeffrey-epstein-is-probably-not-satoshi-nakamoto-2000718652</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718652</guid>
      <description>There are lots of revelations about Epstein's relationship with the crypto world in the files. That's not one of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, where to stream, start time, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-where-to-stream-start-time-and-more-175759112.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is less than a week away. This year's game will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA, and the Bay Area will be host to loads of other football events this week, too, including Thursday's NFL Honors, where we'll learn who this season's MVP is. (That event, which will be held in San Francisco, will air live on NBC and the NFL Network on Thursday at 9...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is that a mini PC or a NES? Acemagic Retro X3 features some familiar casing, but with a welcome hardware boost inside</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-retro-mini-pc-is-a-proper-trip-down-memory-lane-acemagic-retro-x3-brings-back-the-grey-casing-but-with-a-welcome-hardware-boost-inside</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7X3xewCBbJdvZB6khqLm29</guid>
      <description>Acemagic&#8217;s Retro X3 mini PC blends nostalgic beige design with modern Ryzen performance, modular upgrades, and versatile connectivity options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa launches a new platform aimed at helping small businesses access capital and gain exposure</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487719/visa-launches-a-new-platform-aimed-at-helping-small-businesses-access-capital-and-gain-exposure</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T20:35:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487719/visa-launches-a-new-platform-aimed-at-helping-small-businesses-access-capital-and-gain-exposure</guid>
      <description>The program, Visa &amp; Main, identifies and is built around helping address what Visa calls the most pressing challenges that entrepreneurs face.
Visa announced a new platform designed to stimulate small businesses through a variety of tools and network opportunities on Thursday in advance of major sporting events this year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
