<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:25:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Despite the Hate, the &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Finale Smashed Netflix&#8217;s Ratings Records</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/despite-the-hate-the-stranger-things-finale-smashed-netflixs-ratings-records-2000706347</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706347</guid>
      <description>Not everyone loved the way it ended, but plenty of eyeballs still made time to watch 'The Rightside Up.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Everything revealed, from Nvidia&#8217;s debuts to AMD&#8217;s new chips to Razer&#8217;s AI oddities</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/ces-2026-everything-revealed-from-nvidias-debuts-to-amds-new-chips-to-razers-ai-oddities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080516</guid>
      <description>CES 2026&#160;is in full swing in Las Vegas, with the show floor open to the public after a packed couple of days&#160;occupied by&#160;press conferences from the likes of Nvidia, Sony, and AMD&#160;and previews from Sunday&#8217;s Unveiled event.&#160; As has been the case for the past two years at CES, AI is at the forefront of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Sullivan is furious that Trump destroyed his AI foreign policy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/856815/jake-sullivan-interview-ai-chips-nvidia-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T17:46:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/856815/how-silicon-valley-turned-trump-into-a-fellow-broligarch</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers about Big Tech, Big Government, and the big paradigm shifts that result from their collision. Not a subscriber yet? It's a new year, so why not treat yourself? In 2022, Jake Sullivan, then national security adviser under President Joe Biden and a powerful figure in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable health devices could generate a million tons of e-waste by 2050</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/wearable-health-devices-could-generate-a-million-tons-of-e-waste-by-2050/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080528</guid>
      <description>The most surprising part is that the plastic isn't the biggest problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quake is now Steam Deck Verified</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/quake-is-now-steam-deck-verified-223009852.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29218391-4db1-4ab0-8627-20a5aed314bb</guid>
      <description>Bethesda announced on X today that Quake is now a Steam Deck Verified title. The 1996 game from the legendary id Software has also been designated Handheld Optimized for the Xbox ROG Ally devices. As one of the OG boomer shooters, Quake still commands a sizable and passionate fan base, and it's now available on just about every gaming platform imaginable.&#160;Since rolling out its verification program, several thousands of games have been designated as supported for the Steam Deck. Valve has more recently been preparing to have additional gaming devices run its SteamOS platform. Even though Xbox R...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A viral Reddit post alleging fraud from a food delivery app turned out to be AI-generated</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/a-viral-reddit-post-alleging-fraud-from-a-food-delivery-app-turned-out-to-be-ai-generated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080328</guid>
      <description>When fake content goes viral, the damage has already been done, even if the post is debunked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok Is Pushing AI &#8216;Undressing&#8217; Mainstream</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/grok-is-pushing-ai-undressing-mainstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d30e7a225d53752746fb1</guid>
      <description>Paid tools that &#8220;strip&#8221; clothes from photos have been available on the darker corners of the internet for years. Elon Musk&#8217;s X is now removing barriers to entry&#8212;and making the results public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Hyperkin and Gamesir made a modular game controller for your smartphone, tablet and even your Switch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/hyperkin-and-gamesir-x5-alteron-modular-game-controller-ces-2026-221853624.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a23962a4-423e-4396-94bd-510772939566</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;ve been using the same smartphone controller on my iPhone for years. That&#8217;s partly because most options are so similar. Announced at CES 2026, the X5 Alteron couldn&#8217;t be more different. It&#8217;s a collaboration between GameSir (which loves unusual peripheral dalliances) and Hyperkin (retro-leaning controller maker).
The X5 Alteron is apparently the world's first fully modular mobile games controller. While the headline feature might be the stick/d-pad/button modules, the X5 Alteron has a very accommodating vice grip that works with devices from iPhone and Android phones through to the Switch ser...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin Wants Passengers to Use Meta&#8217;s Neural Band to Control Car Screens</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/garmin-wants-passengers-to-use-metas-neural-band-to-control-car-screens-2000706357</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706357</guid>
      <description>Passengers could use Meta&#8217;s Neural Band wearable to control Garmin&#8217;s car infotainment features without using a touchscreen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia just unexpectedly tanked these stocks, and here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470119/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-unexpectedly-tanked-data-center-cooling-stocks-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T22:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470119/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-unexpectedly-tanked-data-center-cooling-stocks-heres-why</guid>
      <description>CEO Jensen Huang&#8217;s comments fueled concerns that sent shares of data center companies tumbling on Tuesday.
Investors are feeling less hot about the makers of cooling systems for data centers after the CEO of Nvidia Corp. stoked concerns that demand for their products could dry up.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odds of Trump Seizing Greenland and Panama Canal Rise on Prediction Markets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/odds-of-trump-seizing-greenland-and-panama-canal-rise-on-prediction-markets-2000706329</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706329</guid>
      <description>The White House told Reuters that "utilizing the U.S. military is always an option" when asked about Greenland on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel's Core Ultra Series 3 let me play 'Battlefield 6' at 190 fps on a Lenovo ultraportable</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/intels-core-ultra-series-3-let-me-play-battlefield-6-at-190-fps-on-a-lenovo-ultraportable-220952246.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14fe7c76-10f8-4ad5-af94-6aeff4df4a15</guid>
      <description>How far has Intel's embedded Arc&#160;graphics come over the years? Enough to let me play Battlefield 6 at up to 190 fps in 1080p, with the graphics settings set to high, all on an unassuming Lenovo IdeaPad Pro 5. There was no need for dedicated graphics, just the Intel Core Ultra X9 388H's built-in Arc B390 GPU. There's a catch, of course: Intel's XeSS3 AI upscaling and 4X frame generation is the big reason why I was able to see such high fps figures. I was playing Battlefield 6 on a controller, with the Lenovo laptop connected to a TV, and I was surprised by how smooth the gameplay felt. There wa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary HDD brand that created 3.5-inch format makes surprising comeback at CES 2026 &#8212; could illustrious names like Maxtor, Iomega or SyQuest be next?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/legendary-hdd-brand-that-created-3-5-inch-format-makes-surprising-comeback-at-ces-could-illustrious-names-like-maxtor-iomega-or-syquest-be-next</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iR2Qv8CdThSKKSwMavNRca</guid>
      <description>Once a pioneer of PC hard drives, Conner reappears at CES 2026 with a very different product focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Director of &#8216;Greenland 2: Migration&#8217; Explains the Enduring Appeal of Disaster Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-director-of-greenland-2-migration-explains-the-enduring-appeal-of-disaster-movies-2000703715</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703715</guid>
      <description>Ric Roman Waugh directs the sequel to his 2020 hit, with Gerard Butler returning to face the post-apocalypse on a comet-ravaged Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony Patent Would Unleash AI &#8216;Ghosts&#8217; to Beat Games for You When They Get Too Hard</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-patent-would-unleash-ai-ghosts-to-beat-games-for-you-when-they-get-too-hard-2000706270</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706270</guid>
      <description>Maybe one day, we'll get an AI that can watch the movies for us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWC debuts PCIe Gen4-class 8TB Thunderbolt 5 external SSD, the largest and fastest in its category &#8212; but it won't be cheap</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/owc-debuts-pcie-gen4-class-8tb-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-the-largest-and-fastest-in-its-category-but-it-wont-be-cheap</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ovqT6emoyzFhenfCuAyqGh</guid>
      <description>OWC introduces an 8TB Thunderbolt 5 SSD offering high transfer speeds, broad compatibility, rugged design claims, and pricing well above mainstream portable storage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#8217;s Jensen Huang wins engineering group&#8217;s top award</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467925/nvidia-jensen-huang-wins-iee-chips-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467925/nvidia-jensen-huang-wins-iee-chips-ai</guid>
      <description>Huang is awarded the IEEE Medal of Honor for pioneering work in GPU-accelerated computing.
Nvidia&#8217;s Jensen Huang is one of the tech industry&#8217;s longest-serving chief executives, leading the chipmaker since&#160;cofounding&#160;it in 1993. Now&#160;he&#8217;s&#160;the recipient of a long-standing technology award: the IEEE Medal of Honor,&#160;established&#160;by a predecessor of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers in 1917.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best Kindle deals right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21539047/best-amazon-kindle-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T16:26:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21539047/best-amazon-kindle-deals</guid>
      <description>When it comes to finding a device to read ebooks, you have a few options to choose from. You can always buy a tablet or use your phone, but those devices are multipurpose and can be used for a ton of things, like surfing the web or doomscrolling on X or Bluesky. If you are [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
