<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:21:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram wants to limit hashtag spam</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847739/instagram-hashtag-spam-limit</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T16:16:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847739</guid>
      <description>If you're tired of seeing Instagram posts with a seemingly endless list of hashtags, Instagram is making a change to stop that. In a post today, Instagram chief Adam Mosseri said that the platform will now cap hashtags to five per post. "While I know it can be tempting to use more, a few specific [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart to pay $60M to settle FTC claims it deceived consumers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/instacart-to-pay-60m-to-settle-ftc-claims-it-deceived-consumers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077553</guid>
      <description>The federal agency alleged Instacart misled consumers with unlawful tactics, causing them to pay higher fees while also denying refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best foldable phone you can buy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/635839/best-foldable-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=635839</guid>
      <description>A foldable phone isn&#8217;t for the faint of heart. They&#8217;re generally heavier, pricier, and have less capable cameras than a standard slab-style phone. They&#8217;re also still not as durable as regular smartphones, though they&#8217;re not nearly as fragile as they once were. In fact, thanks to Google, we finally have a foldable phone we can [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eli Lilly&#8217;s Experimental Pill Could Help You Ditch GLP-1 Obesity Shots, Trial Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/eli-lillys-experimental-pill-could-help-you-ditch-glp-1-obesity-shots-trial-finds-2000701348</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701348</guid>
      <description>People who switched from semaglutide or tirzepatide to orforglipron largely maintained their weight loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;Open innovation is the foundation of AI progress&#8221; says Jensen Huang as Nvidia reveals big open source AI push - major acquisition sealed and new models on the way</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/open-innovation-is-the-foundation-of-ai-progress-says-jensen-huang-as-nvidia-reveals-big-open-source-ai-push-major-acquisition-and-new-models-on-the-way</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Bp7Z5U4m25Frzpm6d5L4A</guid>
      <description>Nvidia acquires SchedMD and launches Nemotron 3 open models, providing datasets, AI tools, and libraries for multi-agent workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG forced a Copilot web app onto its TVs but will let you delete it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847685/lg-copilot-web-app-delete</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T15:31:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847685</guid>
      <description>LG says it will let users delete the Microsoft Copilot shortcut it installed on newer TVs after several reports highlighted the unremovable icon. In a statement to The Verge, LG spokesperson Chris De Maria says the company "respects consumer choice and will take steps to allow users to delete the shortcut icon if they wish." [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&amp;#8217;s Gemini app can check videos to see if they were made with Google AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847680/google-gemini-verification-ai-generated-videos</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T15:31:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847680</guid>
      <description>Google expanded Gemini's AI verification feature to videos made or edited with the company's own AI models. Users can now ask Gemini to determine if an uploaded video is AI-generated by asking, "Was this generated using Google AI?" Gemini will scan the video's visuals and audio for Google's proprietary watermark called SynthID. The response will [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Was a Turning Point for &#8216;Star Trek&#8217;, Whether It Knew It or Not</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-2025-retrospective-section-31-strange-new-worlds-skydance-2000701013</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701013</guid>
      <description>With the 60th anniversary and the launch of a new show, 2026 is shaping up to be a vital year for 'Star Trek'&#8212;but 2025 was where the steps towards that big year really started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirTags are back on sale, with a four-pack retailing for $65</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airtags-are-back-on-sale-with-a-four-pack-retailing-for-65-202333979.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Apple keeps most of its product pricing on a tight leash, but we do see the company's AirTags go on sale pretty frequently. Another cost cut has come around for this item just in time for the holidays. Amazon is currently selling a four-pack of AirTags for $65. At a third off the regular cost, that price is pretty close to the record low discount of $63 we've seen for these Bluetooth trackers.&#160;


If you place an order quickly, the AirTags should arrive in time for Christmas, making this a solid choice as a gift for someone with a tendency to misplace stuff. AirTags can also be useful for peopl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT launches an app store, lets developers know it&#8217;s open for business</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/chatgpt-launches-an-app-store-lets-developers-know-its-open-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077506</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is looking to populate its flagship chatbot with a host of new user experiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As data center backlash grows across the country, Change.org sees a surge of related petitions in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460617/data-center-backlash-wave-of-change-org-petitions-in-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T20:20:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460617/data-center-backlash-wave-of-change-org-petitions-in-2025</guid>
      <description>The online platform says petitions related to data center projects grew substantially as the year progressed. Last year, there was only one. 
The rapid growth of data centers during the AI boom has been a dominating narrative of 2025&#8212;and, in many instances, not a popular one.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Signs Executive Order Loosening Federal Cannabis Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-signs-executive-order-loosening-federal-cannabis-restrictions-2000701438</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701438</guid>
      <description>The order won't legalize cannabis at the federal level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto chip shortage: Honda will pause production in Japan and China</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/auto-chip-shortage-honda-will-pause-production-in-japan-and-china-200857591.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">965d4db1-6e2c-40e4-80bc-b331d9f5112c</guid>
      <description>The ripples of the auto industry's chip shortage are still being felt, as evidenced by Honda. Bloomberg reported on Wednesday that the automaker will suspend production in Japan on January 5 and 6. (Honda didn't specify the affected factories.) In addition, all three of the automaker's Guangqi Honda Automobile plants in China will shut down from December 29 to January 2.The halt is an outgrowth of a chip shortage stemming from a recent geopolitical proxy war in the Netherlands, of all places. In October, the Dutch government, bowing to pressure from the Trump administration, seized control of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickle Robot adds Tesla veteran as&#160;first&#160;CFO</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/pickle-robot-adds-tesla-veteran-as-first-cfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077498</guid>
      <description>Jeff Evanson recently joined Pickle Robot as the company's first CFO as the startup has allegedly expanded its partnership with UPS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s favorite holiday gifts under $100</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/800440/best-gifts-under-100-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800440</guid>
      <description>Between all the new phones, smartwatches, and laptops we see throughout the year, it often feels like we're constantly being nudged toward shinier, more expensive gadgets. And I get it. As a self-professed gadget nerd, few things are more exciting than unboxing and setting up a new device. But the truth is, you can still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A lifeline in real time</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462740/a-lifeline-in-real-time</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462740/a-lifeline-in-real-time</guid>
      <description>Micro-philanthropy can help a women-led Sumatra coffee cooperative recover from natural disaster.
In the heart of Aceh province in northwestern Sumatra, the Ketiara Cooperative, led by the remarkable Ibu Rahmah, is facing a crisis unfolding as we speak. This community of women-led farmers was devastated by the rare Cyclone Senyar over the Thanksgiving weekend, which caused catastrophic mudslides. Farms have been decimated, homes destroyed, and two vital bridges have been washed away, isolating entire villages and cutting off access to essentials like food, clean water, and electricity. Hundred...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why British politicians are flocking to American tech giants</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/why-british-politicians-are-flocking-to-american-tech-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077473</guid>
      <description>Former British Chancellor of the Exchequer George Osborne has joined OpenAI as managing director and head of OpenAI for Countries. He also will run Coinbase's internal advisory council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&#8217;s mobile app hits new milestone of $3B in consumer spending</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/chatgpts-mobile-app-hits-new-milestone-of-3b-in-consumer-spending/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077496</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT has reached $3B in lifetime mobile consumer spending in just 31 months, faster than TikTok and major streaming apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Odyssey&#8217; Poster Throws a Bone to All Those Armor Complaints</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-odyssey-poster-christopher-nolan-greek-armor-2000701416</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701416</guid>
      <description>And we mean that literally. Christopher Nolan directs the 2026 epic starring Matt Damon and Tom Holland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProPublica&#8217;s New Tool Provides Drug Info the FDA Won&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/propublicas-new-tool-provides-drug-info-the-fda-wont-2000701357</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701357</guid>
      <description>The first-of-its-kind app to help you find out where your generic drugs come from and see the track records of the factories that made them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Miss This Kindle Sale: Paperwhite, Colorsoft, and Accessories</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/last-minute-christmas-kindle-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6943426eb265e31526036e35</guid>
      <description>If your favorite reader is the one left on your Christmas list, good news: Several Kindles and Kindle accessories are on sale right now for your last-minute shopping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Displace Hub can make your normal TV wireless</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/the-displace-hub-can-make-your-normal-tv-wireless-193837460.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e068ce1-8e69-439b-9f53-8dcfb91c3471</guid>
      <description>Displace first tried its hand at reimagining the TV in 2023, with a wireless screen that suctions onto walls and features built-in rechargeable batteries. At CES 2026, the company is not only introducing new versions of its own TVs, it's also showing off the Displace Hub, an accessory that can make other TVs wireless.The Displace Hub is a wall-mounting system with some extra bells and whistles. It combines the "active-loop suction" of Displace&#8217;s TVs, with a rechargeable battery that can power whatever screen you mount on it and a built-in PC that runs Displace's "ambient computing platform." T...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anyone for a slice of record Pi? New landmark sees 314 trillion digits calculated as news site trounces Google Cloud - for now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/anyone-for-a-slice-of-record-pi-new-landmark-sees-314-trillion-digits-calculated-as-news-site-trounces-google-cloud-for-now</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">E4mQ7g4w4WhGHGavV2dce5</guid>
      <description>StorageReview computed 314 trillion digits of pi on one server, finishing faster and using far less energy than cloud-based records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is bringing even more ads to the App Store</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/apple-is-bringing-even-more-ads-to-the-app-store-193416921.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">709ba0fe-6b15-42d9-9b65-7663171f276e</guid>
      <description>Apple just announced it will be integrating more ads into the App Store because our poor eyeballs must be assaulted at all times. The company plans on littering search results with advertisements beginning next year.
Currently, the App Store only has one ad spot. That's at the very top of search results. If you search for something like Instagram it's likely that top spot will be filled with an ad for a rival social media platform. The new ads will appear further down the actual search results.
Apple says that advertisers won't have to alter their campaigns, as the ads will "run in either the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Are U.S. Dams Holding Up? New Satellite Data Warns of Trouble</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-are-u-s-dams-holding-up-new-satellite-data-warns-of-trouble-2000701259</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701259</guid>
      <description>There's never been a giant dam failure in the US modern era, and a team of researchers is looking to keep it that way.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
