<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:42:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>These Amazon devices are just too good (and cheap) to skip &#8212; Fire TV Sticks, Blink cameras, Ring Doorbells, Echo, and more from $17.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/these-amazon-devices-are-just-too-good-and-cheap-to-skip-fire-tv-sticks-blink-cameras-ring-doorbells-echo-and-more-from-usd17-99</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48RQMo6k54JQ2P6Mzv5tHo</guid>
      <description>Amazon is slashing prices on its best-selling tech devices, and I've rounded up the 21 best deals that are worth buying, including Fire TV Sticks, Ring Doorbells, Blink cameras, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This RTX 5060 desktop is the perfect starter PC for creators - and it's just $1079 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-rtx-5060-desktop-is-the-perfect-starter-pc-for-creators-and-its-just-usd1079-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GfabdcBXspZbQsTcSnG8Uo</guid>
      <description>The Ipason Xelra desktop is down to $1,079 and pairs a Ryzen 5 9600X with an RTX 5060 for fast, creator-ready performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth Really Hurts on This Week&#8217;s &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-truth-really-hurts-on-this-weeks-a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-2000714600</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714600</guid>
      <description>The tournament begins, but another major crisis soon takes over in 'The Squire.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming free-to-play RPG Sea of Remnants will get a new season 'every 10 weeks' with a big world expansion 'every 20 weeks'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/upcoming-free-to-play-rpg-sea-of-remnants-will-get-a-new-season-every-10-weeks-with-a-big-world-expansion-every-20-weeks</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7hK6JWmRHtPitVsi4LKjP</guid>
      <description>Developer Joker Studio has outlined a release cadence for its live service support of upcoming RPG Sea of Remnants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada Computers &amp; Electronics reveals data breach - customer data exposed, here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/canada-computers-and-electronics-reveals-data-breach-customer-data-exposed-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8RQCqqycKpM6azC8UzYNJH</guid>
      <description>Some customers see credit card information also exposed, with police already notified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abxylute&#8217;s new Switch 2 controller is for all the die-hard GameCube fans</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/872223/abxylute-nintendo-switch-2-controller-n6-n9c-gamecube-retro</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T12:23:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872223</guid>
      <description>Abxylute, the company behind the M4 magnetic mobile gamepad, has announced a new pair of controllers for the Nintendo Switch 2 designed to replace the stock Joy-Cons while playing in handheld mode. Both are "launching soon" on Kickstarter and feature a design where the Switch 2 docks to the controllers so they can connect to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-to-Compute Laws Are Spreading Across the US, as Electricity Bills Skyrocket</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/right-to-compute-laws-are-spreading-across-the-us-as-electricity-bills-skyrocket-2000716730</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716730</guid>
      <description>The new laws would make it harder for states and cities to regulate AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Baby Universe Really Was a Goopy Soup, Research Suggests</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-baby-universe-really-was-a-goopy-soup-research-suggests-2000716678</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716678</guid>
      <description>The early universe is full of mysteries, but we can now at least be sure it was soupy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok, which maybe stopped undressing women without their consent, still undresses men</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/grok-which-maybe-stopped-undressing-women-without-their-consent-still-undresses-men-170750752.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95f550e0-9bd8-41ad-be45-f78f0cbc13a3</guid>
      <description>It looks like Grok is still being gross. Elon Musk says his chatbot stopped making sexualized images without a person's consent, but The Verge recently discovered this is not entirely true. It maybe (and I say maybe) stopped undressing women without their consent, but this doesn't seem to apply to men.
A reporter with the organization ran some tests with Grok and found that the bot "readily undresses men and is still churning out intimate images on demand." He confirmed this with images of himself, asking Grok to remove clothing from uploaded photos. It performed this task for free on the Grok...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $400! LG&#8217;s 27-inch OLED UltraGear monitor is now less than $500, but act fast - it won't stay this price for long</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/save-usd400-lgs-27-inch-oled-ultragear-monitor-is-now-less-than-usd500-but-act-fast-it-wont-stay-this-price-for-long</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WMWd8rzSr58GnqKwSktyLZ</guid>
      <description>LG 27-inch UltraGear OLED monitor is down to $499.99 and combines a QHD OLED panel with a 240Hz refresh rate and ultra-fast response times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best board games to gift and play this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-board-games-to-gift-and-play-this-year-125529271.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b67d713-c1e1-4ea2-a3a8-ab47cde9ad9f</guid>
      <description>It's become cliche to say that we live in a golden age of board games, but to paraphrase the great stoic philosopher Andy Bernard, it's great to know you're in the good old days before you've left them. Great titles are still coming out by the thousands every year, from crowd-pleasing party games to genre-bending, theme-heavy Euros. Whether the gamer in your life is looking for a mind-warping challenge, a fun evening with friends or something in-between, we've got new releases or old favorites they'll love.
Best board games to gift and play




























Check out the rest of our...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meilleur smartphone Samsung Galaxy : pour quel mod&#232;le opter en 2026&#8201;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/386688_quels-smartphone-samsung-choisir-parmi-les-differentes-gammes-galaxy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/386688_quels-smartphone-samsung-choisir-parmi-les-differentes-gammes-galaxy</guid>
      <description>
La firme cor&#233;enne propose l'une des gammes de smartphones les plus compl&#232;tes sur le march&#233; de la t&#233;l&#233;phonie. Quel est le t&#233;l&#233;phone Samsung qui est fait pour vous ? Vous trouverez ici les d&#233;tails de leur catalogue et surtout nos conseils pour choisir le plus adapt&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi ce pack Samsung Galaxy S25 Ultra chez Boulanger est un excellent deal, m&#234;me avec l&#8217;arriv&#233;e du prochain S26 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2963437_pourquoi-ce-pack-samsung-galaxy-s25-ultra-chez-boulanger-est-un-excellent-deal-meme-avec-larrivee-du-prochain-s26</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2963437_pourquoi-ce-pack-samsung-galaxy-s25-ultra-chez-boulanger-est-un-excellent-deal-meme-avec-larrivee-du-prochain-s26</guid>
      <description>
Boulanger a attendu la fin des soldes pour d&#233;gainer un pack tr&#232;s attractif autour du Samsung Galaxy S25 Ultra. M&#234;me si le nouveau mod&#232;le s&#8217;appr&#234;te &#224; sortir, cette offre reste int&#233;ressante gr&#226;ce &#224; une remise de 24 %, qui permet de s&#8217;offrir un smartphone premium complet sans payer le prix fort.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"VPNs are next on my list" &#8211; France set to evaluate VPN use following social media ban for under-15s</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/vpns-are-next-on-my-list-france-set-to-evaluate-vpn-use-following-social-media-ban-for-under-15s</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tnLVcKpJMcDGhtLvLGbxeW</guid>
      <description>France&#8217;s National Assembly has passed a bill that will ban children under 15 from using social media platforms. Lawmakers are now considering how to stop teens from using VPNs to bypass the restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s 2026 Valentine&#8217;s Day gift guide (for her)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/865281/valentines-day-2026-gift-ideas-for-her-girlfriend-wife-partner</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T11:45:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865281</guid>
      <description>Valentine's Day often comes with more pressure than it needs to. At heart, though, February 14th is about showing appreciation for the people you care about in ways that feel thoughtful and sincere. And while big displays of romance can do that, it's often the quieter, more personal gestures - or a meaningful gift that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 dollars de plus : m&#234;me Raspberry Pi n&#8217;&#233;chappe pas &#224; la hausse des prix des PC</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2963579_60-dollars-de-plus-meme-raspberry-pi-nechappe-pas-a-la-hausse-des-prix-des-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2963579_60-dollars-de-plus-meme-raspberry-pi-nechappe-pas-a-la-hausse-des-prix-des-pc</guid>
      <description>
La crise de la RAM continue de faire grimper les prix et m&#234;me Raspberry ne peut rien y faire. Le petit PC autrefois low-cost continue de voir son prix augmenter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirPods Pro 3 just plummeted to a record-low price &#8212; yes, even cheaper than $199!</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/airpods-pro-3-just-plummeted-to-a-record-low-price-yes-even-cheaper-than-usd199</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ocvKN6PTzDpdcM99jEVtYK</guid>
      <description>Apple's AirPods Pro 3 have dropped to an all-new lowest seen price, only on Verizon &#8211; and they'll make for an amazing half-time show&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, start time, where to stream and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-start-time-where-to-stream-and-more-175759610.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

MVP candidate Drake Maye and the New England Patriots face Sam Darnold and the Seattle Seahawks at Super Bowl LX, which will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA this year. It's hard to believe we're less than a week away from the championship game, which will be held this Sunday, Feb. 8 with kickoff scheduled for 6:30 p.m. ET. But before we can get to all of that action, we've also got the Pro Bowl Games on Tuesday and the NFL Honors on Thu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Ancient River Seemed to Flow Uphill. Now We Know Why</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-ancient-river-seemed-to-flow-uphill-now-we-know-why-2000716673</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716673</guid>
      <description>The Green River may have had some help from a dripping crust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian ransomware hackers allegedly hit Tulsa airport in cyberattack, dump private files online as proof</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/russian-ransomware-hackers-allegedly-hit-tulsa-airport-in-cyberattack-dump-private-files-online-as-proof</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rG7jSAzLVYiTdCrwuBWHrf</guid>
      <description>The infamous Qilin group strikes again, this time targeting a major US airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaks Just Spoiled Sony&#8217;s New WF-1000XM6 Wireless Earbuds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/leaks-spoiled-sony-wf-1000xm6-wireless-earbuds-2000716625</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716625</guid>
      <description>Spoiler alert: they look pretty nice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney is still 'hard at work' on creating its unified Hulu and Disney+ app, departing CEO says &#8212; and its new late 2026 release window is the perfect time for another vexing price hike</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-is-still-hard-at-work-on-creating-its-unified-hulu-and-disney-app-departing-ceo-says-and-its-new-late-2026-release-window-is-the-perfect-time-for-another-vexing-price-hike</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5mo9phSXeDDqcTaiWDnuTW</guid>
      <description>Disney's combined streaming app has a revised launch window &#8212; and the cynic in me has an idea of when it might launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: The Galaxy S26 lineup and everything else we expect</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-the-galaxy-s26-lineup-and-everything-else-we-expect-130000999.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hands-on coverage of Samsung's new smartphones soon after they're announced. While we wait for an official invite, here's everything we expect Samsung will introduce at the first Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026.What is Unpacked 2026 taking place?But...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Super Bowl LX on a 100-inch screen: 6 portable projectors perfect for hosting a game-day party</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/best-super-bowl-portable-projector-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oDB726LNsEC5XKRkzxbUV</guid>
      <description>Kickoff starts here with $449 budget picks to premium 4K laser projectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#8217;s next for domains in 2026: leveling the field for builders and small businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/whats-next-for-domains-in-2026-leveling-the-field-for-builders-and-small-businesses</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cWeSY7LnxAENqAe3378Gpi</guid>
      <description>A look at domain names and blockchain identifiers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard's quality assurance workers finally have a union contract</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/blizzards-quality-assurance-workers-finally-have-a-union-contract-162614979.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a577967-6056-470f-b7d4-950de58876b5</guid>
      <description>Almost three years after starting the bargaining process with Microsoft, quality assurance workers at two Blizzard locations have ratified a union contract. The agreement covers 60 workers at Blizzard Albany and Blizzard Austin.The agreement includes guaranteed pay increases across the three years of the contract, assurances that workers will be given fair credits and recognition on games that ship, discrimination-free disability accommodations, restrictions on crunch (i.e. mandatory overtime) and "protection to immigrant workers from unfair discipline and loss of seniority while streamlining ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPVanish launches Threat Protection Pro to stop malware even when you&#8217;re not connected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/ipvanish-launches-threat-protection-pro-to-stop-malware-even-when-youre-not-connected</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hLRCSkJEkJx6FNyjrw6fag</guid>
      <description>IPVanish has launched a beta version of Threat Protection Pro for Windows. Powered by VIPRE antivirus tech, it scans downloads and blocks ads even when your VPN is off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 bug breaks the entire desktop for some users &#8212; but luckily there's a fix</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/windows-11-bug-breaks-the-entire-desktop-but-luckily-theres-a-fix</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">D9AMDhaiYBEA6yAztvY8Li</guid>
      <description>Wondering why your Windows 11 desktop keeps vanishing? It's because of this nasty bug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The pros and cons of workplace perfectionism</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480904/pros-cons-workplace-perfectionism</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T16:19:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480904/pros-cons-workplace-perfectionism</guid>
      <description>It may be better to strive for &#8220;excellencism&#8221;.
Biographies of exceptional achievers tend to explain their success through personality traits, highlighting the &#8220;killer psychological weapons&#8221; that made them great. So, Steve Jobs&#8217;s abrasiveness is reframed as visionary perfectionism, Elon Musk&#8217;s impulsivity as bold risk-taking, and Jeff Bezos&#8217;s relentlessness as uncompromising customer obsession. The same retrospective alchemy applies to women: Oprah Winfrey&#8217;s emotional intensity becomes radical empathy and authenticity; Indra Nooyi&#8217;s discipline and conscientiousness are recast as values-driven, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry, 8K TVs Have Flopped</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sorry-8k-tvs-have-flopped-2000716663</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716663</guid>
      <description>Nobody wanted four times the pixels for many times the price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-two-year-plans-are-up-to-81-percent-off-right-now-180602205.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $88 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.14 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If I needed a portable power station for outages and camping, the Anker Solix C1000 is the one I&#8217;d buy &#8212; and it&#8217;s nearly half price at just $429</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/if-i-needed-a-portable-power-station-for-outages-and-camping-the-anker-solix-c1000-is-the-one-id-buy-and-its-nearly-half-price-at-just-usd429</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NvMCK6EY6UDu5BySAgRjRi</guid>
      <description>Anker Solix C1000 Gen 2 portable power station is just $429 and delivers 2,000W power, 3,000W peak, with a full recharge in under an hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Indispensable pour l&#8217;achat entre particuliers &#187; : voici l&#8217;avis sur carVertical de nos lecteurs pour acheter leur voiture d&#8217;occasion [Sponso]</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2956773_indispensable-pour-lachat-entre-particuliers-voici-lavis-sur-carvertical-de-nos-lecteurs-pour-acheter-leur-voiture-doccasion</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2956773_indispensable-pour-lachat-entre-particuliers-voici-lavis-sur-carvertical-de-nos-lecteurs-pour-acheter-leur-voiture-doccasion</guid>
      <description>
Entre la peur des compteurs trafiqu&#233;s et celle des accidents dissimul&#233;s, acheter un v&#233;hicule d&#8217;occasion est souvent une source de stress. Pour y rem&#233;dier, nous avons confi&#233; le service de rapports d'historique carVertical &#224; cinq de nos lecteurs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Year&#8217;s Other Amazing &#8216;Predator&#8217; Movie Is Finally Getting Some Love (Exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/last-years-other-amazing-predator-movie-is-finally-getting-some-love-exclusive-2000715241</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715241</guid>
      <description>Mutant is releasing the soundtrack for 'Predator: Killer of Killers' on vinyl, with 'Badlands' on the way too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Soothing Sleep Noise Might Be Sabotaging Your Dreams</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/that-soothing-sleep-noise-might-be-sabotaging-your-dreams-2000716424</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716424</guid>
      <description>People subjected to pink noise may experience fewer minutes of REM sleep, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markiplier&#8217;s Indie Sci-Fi Horror Movie Thrashed &#8216;Melania&#8217; at the Box Office This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iron-lung-box-office-markiplier-melania-amazon-2000716665</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716665</guid>
      <description>'Iron Lung', independently funded by the Youtuber, narrowly lost the box office number 1 spot to 'Send Help'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With more than 400 unique NPCs, free PS5 pirate adventure Sea of Remnants is shaping up to be one of the most ambitious games ever made &#8212; I&#8217;ve already played 10 hours, and I can&#8217;t get enough</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/sea-of-remnants-hands-on-preview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hxZhScniYFV7MFQWXbVHMS</guid>
      <description>I go hands-on with the upcoming free-to-play pirate RPG Sea of Remnants, diving deep into the vast ocean of content it offers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce VTT &#233;lectrique taill&#233; pour les randonn&#233;es perd 300 &#8364; chez Intersport, une affaire &#224; ne pas rater</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2963307_ce-vtt-electrique-taille-pour-les-randonnees-perd-300-e-chez-intersport-une-affaire-a-ne-pas-rater</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2963307_ce-vtt-electrique-taille-pour-les-randonnees-perd-300-e-chez-intersport-une-affaire-a-ne-pas-rater</guid>
      <description>
Alors que les soldes 2026 touchent &#224; leur fin, on trouve de tr&#232;s bonnes r&#233;f&#233;rences en promotion c&#244;t&#233; v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique. Parmi eux, on compte le Nakamura E-Summit 740 Open, un VTT confortable, puissant et endurant qui passe de 1 599 euros &#224; 1 299 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony&#8217;s last-gen, but still great 1000XM5 are cheaper than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/872182/sony-xm5-noise-canceling-headphones-super-bowl-tv-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T10:55:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872182</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s rare for Sony&#8217;s flagship headphones, even slightly outdated models, to receive a big discount. However, the&#160;WH-1000XM5&#160;in black or silver is selling at its lowest-ever price today at&#160;Adorama&#160;when you enter the code&#160;JHCE9834&#160;at checkout (it&#8217;s the last step before placing the order). Originally $399, they&#8217;re $204.56 &#8212; practically half price. According to historic pricing data from [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Nothing headphones are on the way, and this leak says they'll be more budget focused &#8212; and I hope they copy one particular trait of other budget headphones</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/more-nothing-headphones-are-on-the-way-and-this-leak-says-theyll-be-more-budget-focused-and-i-hope-they-copy-one-particular-trait-of-other-budget-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WUQ4VjdZMXgwWa7DkTfwnb</guid>
      <description>Nothing's next headphones are set to be budget spins on the Headphone (1), and we've got early release window and pricing leaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strava fait le m&#233;nage : des millions d&#8217;activit&#233;s supprim&#233;es pour triche au v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2963449_strava-fait-le-menage-des-millions-dactivites-supprimees-pour-triche-au-velo-electrique</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2963449_strava-fait-le-menage-des-millions-dactivites-supprimees-pour-triche-au-velo-electrique</guid>
      <description>
Strava a indiqu&#233; avoir supprim&#233; 3,9 millions d'activit&#233;s de cyclisme suppl&#233;mentaires, suspect&#233;es d'avoir &#233;t&#233; r&#233;alis&#233;es en v&#233;lo &#224; assistance &#233;lectrique dans le but de modifier les classements de segment. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP fundraising data reveals a &#8216;war chest&#8217; for Republicans ahead of the 2026 midterms</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485196/gop-fundraising-data-reveals-war-chest-republicans-ahead-2026-midterms</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T15:49:54</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485196/gop-fundraising-data-reveals-war-chest-republicans-ahead-2026-midterms</guid>
      <description>2025 year-end filings with the Federal Election Commission reveal that Republicans are ahead of Democrats in fundraising.
The Republican National Committee has vastly outpaced Democrats in the crush for cash ahead of the midterm elections, holding a nearly $100 million advantage at the close of 2025, according to year-end filings to the Federal Election Commission.As Democrats have struggled in the Trump era, the RNC tallied $172 million raised in 2025, with $95 million cash on hand at year&#8217;s end. In contrast, the Democratic National Committee posted $145 million for the year, with $14 million...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenClaw: all the news about the trending AI agent</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/872091/openclaw-moltbot-clawdbot-ai-agent-news</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T10:47:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=872091</guid>
      <description>An open-source AI agent called OpenClaw (formerly known as both Clawdbot and Moltbot) that runs on your own computer and &#8220;actually does things&#8221; is taking off inside tech circles. Users interact with OpenClaw via messaging apps like WhatsApp, Telegram, Signal, Discord, and iMessage, giving it the keys to operate independently, managing reminders, writing emails, or [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 TV deals: The best sales this week on OLEDs and other smart TVs ahead of kickoff</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/super-bowl-2026-tv-deals-the-best-sales-this-week-on-oleds-and-other-smart-tvs-ahead-of-kickoff-160000485.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19a8ed95-5057-4f9e-952b-502d925814e1</guid>
      <description>The big game is one of the few instances now in the US where most people gather around the TV to watch the live event together. While the teams playing in Super Bowl 2026 are the true stars of the show (and Bad Bunny, of course), your TV is a pretty important part of the puzzle of putting together an excellent Super Bowl party. Maybe you&#8217;ve been thinking about replacing an aging set, or you&#8217;re itching for a full refresh of your home theater setup &#8212; either way, you&#8217;ll want to try to get a good deal on a new TV. Thankfully, the weeks leading up to the Super Bowl can be a great time to shop for a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
