<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:15:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Swiss Suicide Pod Gets an AI-Powered Mental Fitness Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/controversial-swiss-suicide-pod-gets-an-ai-powered-mental-fitness-upgrade-2000712092</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712092</guid>
      <description>It's better than ChatGPT encouraging you to kill yourself, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Taken So Long to Find a New James Bond, Riz Ahmed Made a TV Show About It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/bait-riz-ahmed-james-bond-prime-video-2000712006</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712006</guid>
      <description>Prime Video's 'Bait' follows an actor who may just be the next man to play Bond, James Bond, for Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 Best Shows on Apple TV, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (January 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63cf1b483f042fa5827033d7</guid>
      <description>Hijack, Pluribus, and The Morning Show are among the best shows on Apple TV this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Tying Your Shoelaces Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/are-you-tying-your-shoelaces-wrong-2000712041</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712041</guid>
      <description>And will it matter when everything comes crashing down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Veronika&#8217; Is the First Cow Known to Use a Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/veronika-is-the-first-cow-known-to-use-a-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fc71753fb9d147ff09b31</guid>
      <description>This is the first recorded instance of a bovine using tools from her environment to relieve an itch&#8212;leaving scientists astonished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google has finally killed the Stadia Bluetooth tool &#8212; but this person rescued it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/864543/google-has-finally-killed-the-stadia-bluetooth-tool-but-this-person-rescued-it</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T14:50:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864543</guid>
      <description>Did you save your Google Stadia controller like I told you last month? It's still not too late. This week, Google has finally removed the tool that converts the now-useless controller into a decent Bluetooth gamepad. But there's another way. Christopher Klay, who previously developed the Stadia Enhanced browser extension, is one of many who [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon CEO Andy Jassy says tariffs are starting to drive up product prices</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/amazon-ceo-andy-jassy-says-tariffs-are-starting-to-drive-up-product-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083995</guid>
      <description>Jassy said on Tuesday that while Amazon is trying to keep prices low, price hikes may be unavoidable in some cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon CEO Says Tariff Price Increases Likely to Hit Your Wallet This Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-ceo-says-tariff-price-increases-likely-to-hit-your-wallet-this-year-2000712020</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712020</guid>
      <description>Tariffs are starting to "creep in" to product prices as companies' efforts to absorb price increases run out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want some AI with your Pi? Raspberry Pi 5 gets an LLM upgrade with new AI HAT+ 2 - but will it be powerful enough?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/want-some-ai-with-your-pi-raspberry-pi-5-gets-an-llm-upgrade-with-new-ai-hat-2-but-will-it-be-powerful-enough</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pGnqRHuocgXSR6SbAAPcy4</guid>
      <description>Raspberry Pi AI HAT+ 2 enables local LLM and VLM workloads with 40 TOPS, 8 GB memory, and PCIe connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Details a New Minnesota-Based Detention Network That Spans 5 States</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-detention-network-minnesota-5-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696f86aad7ef6580ac2201e2</guid>
      <description>Internal ICE planning documents propose spending up to $50 million on a privately run network capable of shipping immigrants in custody hundreds of miles across the Upper Midwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new &#8216;Be The People&#8217; campaign wants to turn hundreds of millions of Americans into problem-solvers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477823/be-the-people-campaign-wants-to-unite-hundreds-of-millions-of-americans-to-solve-problems</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T19:11:40</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477823/be-the-people-campaign-wants-to-unite-hundreds-of-millions-of-americans-to-solve-problems</guid>
      <description>Be The People builds on research that indicates many people want to contribute to their communities but don&#8217;t know how.
As the official celebrations of the&#160;250th anniversary&#160;of the signing of the Declaration of Independence culminate on July 4, a well-financed, privately funded initiative will kick off to try to connect hundreds of millions of Americans with efforts to solve local problems....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even George R.R. Martin Was Surprised by That Poop Scene in &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-poop-scene-george-rr-martin-2000712028</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712028</guid>
      <description>Toilet humor arrives early in the series premiere of HBO's new 'Game of Thrones' spinoff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFLX: Netflix makes a big move today as stock markets crater. Now all eyes are on its earnings</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477838/netflix-nflx-q4-earnings-stock-markets-crater-today-warner-bros-discovery-cash-bid-paramount</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477838/netflix-nflx-q4-earnings-stock-markets-crater-today-warner-bros-discovery-cash-bid-paramount</guid>
      <description>The streaming giant&#8217;s fourth-quarter results will be closely watched as it continues to compete with Paramount to buy Warner Bros. Discovery.
All eyes are on Netflix, which is set to report fourth-quarter earnings after Tuesday&#8217;s closing bell. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These fake Chrome extensions will crash your browser so that hackers can sneak in - here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/these-fake-chrome-extensions-will-crash-your-browser-so-that-hackers-can-sneak-in-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XhK4mXpF2TCH2T9jDsykWm</guid>
      <description>Don't fall for this new ClickFix variant which will crash your browser first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How brands can build AI that inspires</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477958/how-brands-can-build-ai-that-inspires</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T18:41:37</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477958/how-brands-can-build-ai-that-inspires</guid>
      <description>In a world fixated on efficiency and productivity, brands that use AI to spark creativity become consumer favorites.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akai's MPC XL groovebox is the most powerful device the company has ever made</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/akais-mpc-xl-groovebox-is-the-most-powerful-device-the-company-has-ever-made-183952483.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37d85553-27e5-46c0-86d2-789438fed154</guid>
      <description>Akai just revealed its most powerful standalone groovebox, the MPC XL. For the uninitiated, the MPC has been around since the 1980s and pretty much defined hip hop from that era. The line has continuously iterated to keep up with the times and the XL looks to be the baddest of them all.
First of all, it offers four times the processing power of previous MPCs, which is enough to load up to 32 virtual instruments at the same time. This is assisted by a full 16GB of RAM, which is a whole lot in this era of AI tomfoolery. The XL can handle 16 audio tracks simultaneously. In my experience with prev...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s discounted microSD Express card more than doubles your Switch 2 storage</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/864404/samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T13:36:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864404</guid>
      <description>If you buy digital games for the Nintendo Switch 2, Samsung&#8217;s P9 microSD Express card offers an easier way to expand your storage without constantly deleting games to make room. It&#8217;s cheaper than other microSD cards, and it&#8217;s an even better value right now, with the 512GB version priced at $79.99 ($40 off) &#8212; just [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life is Strange will bring the Max and Chloe story to an end in new game</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/864438/life-is-strange-reunion-release-date-max-chloe</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864438</guid>
      <description>A little over a decade ago, Life is Strange burst onto the scene with a unique blend of teen drama and interactive storytelling. That first game told the story of Max Caulfield, who had the supernatural ability to reverse time, and her best friend Chloe Price. Now developer Deck Nine Games is finally bringing their [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life is Strange: Reunion has been revealed and is the 'emotional conclusion' of Max and Chloe's story</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/life-is-strange-reunion-has-been-revealed-and-is-the-emotional-conclusion-of-max-and-chloes-story</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FTEcVjZUd8jdSYs7APp84J</guid>
      <description>Square Enix has revealed Life is Strange: Reunion, the next entry in the Life is Strange series, with the fan-favorite Chloe set to return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The memory price hike crisis could get even worse, as US threatens 100% tariffs &#8211; this is how it could affect you</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/the-memory-price-hike-crisis-could-get-even-worse-as-us-threatens-100-percent-tariffs-this-is-how-it-could-affect-you</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z7W8uHN558vWNffYELa7ih</guid>
      <description>Consumers in the US now face an additional danger in terms of factors that could seriously hike the price of laptops and PCs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street and Europe stocks slump after Trump&#8217;s tariff threats on NATO members</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477810/wall-street-europe-stocks-slump-after-trumps-tariff-threats-nato-members</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477810/wall-street-europe-stocks-slump-after-trumps-tariff-threats-nato-members</guid>
      <description>The losses were widespread and led by technology stocks.
Stocks slumped in morning trading on Wall Street Tuesday after President Donald Trump threatened to hit eight NATO members with new tariffs as&#160;tensions escalate&#160;over his attempts to assert American control over Greenland.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
