<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:03:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This game controller has a force feedback steering wheel lodged in the middle</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/this-game-controller-has-a-force-feedback-steering-wheel-lodged-in-the-middle-034521141.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa498c94-348a-44e9-a9d4-922945e85909</guid>
      <description>Not everyone remembers the unique controllers that never quite made it. As third-party peripheral makers attempt to offer gamers something different to the likes of DualSense and Joy-Cons, they often have to go in a different direction. GameSir&#8217;s Swift Drive (apparently a working product name) is definitely that. And if you remember 1998&#8217;s JogCon for the PS1, there&#8217;s definitely some shared DNA.
It features a compact steering wheel at the center of an otherwise typical controller design. It&#8217;s also got force feedback, tech usually found in (full-size!) steering wheel controllers. GameSir says it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel is planning a custom Panther Lake CPU for handheld PCs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857252/intel-handheld-gaming-pc-panther-lake-custom-cpu</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T22:16:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857252</guid>
      <description>Intel announced yesterday that it's developing an entire "handheld gaming platform" powered by its new Panther Lake chips, and joining an increasingly competitive field. Qualcomm is hinting about potential Windows gaming handhelds showing up at the Game Developers Conference in March, and AMD's new Strix Halo chips could lead to more powerful handhelds. According to [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Motorola unveils Razr Fold, a book-style foldable phone</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-motorola-razr-fold-foldable-phone-debut</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00XpnQzuCj1CY6tnAz6gNdy</guid>
      <description>Motorola has unveiled the Razr Fold at CES 2026, a book-style foldable phone which focuses on productivity rather than nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McKinsey and General Catalyst execs say the era of &#8216;learn once, work forever&#8217; is over</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/mckinsey-and-general-catalyst-execs-say-the-era-of-learn-once-work-forever-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080615</guid>
      <description>Calacanis, General Catalyst's Taneja, and McKinsey's Sternfels discussed how AI is reshaping technology and the labor force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints today: Clues, answers for January 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nyt-connections-hint-answer-today-january-7-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">012r337AdNSfD6lXtBTUpn0</guid>
      <description>Connections is a New York Times word game that's all about finding the "common threads between words." How to solve the puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints, answers for January 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/strands-nyt-hint-january-7-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06QD6fynsiBfirqF4M0OOQg</guid>
      <description>The NYT Strands hints and answers you need to make the most of your puzzling experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordle today: Answer, hints for January 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wordle-today-answer-january-7-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">021uslZJ0k5F6T23QKDe6rH</guid>
      <description>Here's the answer for "Wordle" #1662 on January 7 as well as a few hints, tips, and clues to help you solve it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s Manus news is getting different receptions in Washington and Beijing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/metas-manus-news-is-getting-different-receptions-in-washington-and-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080617</guid>
      <description>Chinese officials are reportedly reviewing whether the Meta deal violates technology export controls, potentially giving Beijing leverage it wasn't initially perceived as having.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo is building an AI assistant that &#8216;can act on your behalf&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/857053/lenovo-ai-assistant-qira</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T21:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857053</guid>
      <description>While most attention in the AI race is focused on model builders and cloud platforms, Lenovo sits closer to millions of users than most companies. As the world's top PC maker by volume, Lenovo ships tens of millions of devices every year. What it decides to ship, bundle, and integrate can directly shape how AI [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
