<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:20:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Mobile's T1 still doesn't exist, but the company is now selling refurbished phones</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/trump-mobiles-t1-still-doesnt-exist-but-the-company-is-now-selling-refurbished-phones-191740570.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1bee505-9a99-49cb-8933-595567fa579b</guid>
      <description>The T1 smartphone from Trump Mobile remains non-existent vaporware, but the company is still finding new ways to take people's money. Anyone who desperately wants to fund this sham can now buy a refurbished phone from the company. The business's website has listings for "Renewed" models of the Samsung S24 and S23 and the iPhone 15 and 14. Gizmodo noticed that Trump Mobile is selling these other brands' phones for the same cost, or sometimes more, than the same refurbs from other retailers.&#160;Seems pretty par for the course. NBC News opted to order one of the T1 phones in August to track its deve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Seeks Cyber Upgrade to Better Surveil and Investigate Its Employees</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-seeks-cyber-upgrade-to-better-surveil-and-investigate-its-employees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6944158f17f8230f56a84949</guid>
      <description>The agency plans to renew a sweeping cybersecurity contract that includes expanded employee monitoring as the government escalates leak investigations and casts internal dissent as a threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Image Shows 2 Protoplanets Smashing Into Each Other, Forming Giant Dust Cloud</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/unprecedented-image-shows-2-protoplanets-smashing-into-each-other-forming-giant-dust-cloud-2000701287</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701287</guid>
      <description>First it was an exoplanet. Then it became a dust cloud. Now it's bringing a cosmic revelation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn&#8217;s profile verification push is accelerating &#8212; and India is leading the charge in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/linkedins-profile-verification-push-is-accelerating-and-india-is-leading-the-charge-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077445</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn profile verification adoption in India has risen about 80% in the past 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 great gift ideas that should arrive in time for Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/846378/best-last-minute-gifts-ideas-airpods-pro-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T13:42:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846378</guid>
      <description>You don&#8217;t need to deal with long mall lines or crowded parking lots just to wrap up your holiday shopping, but you probably already knew this. Some of the best deals are online, and even though Christmas is now just a few days away, a lot of Verge-approved gifts should still arrive on time if [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation cooled in November, but data may be distorted</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462970/inflation-consumer-prices-november</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T18:40:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462970/inflation-consumer-prices-november</guid>
      <description>Thursday&#8217;s report gave investors, businesses, and policymakers their first look at CPI since the September numbers were released on Oct. 24.
At a time when Americans are frustrated and angry over the high cost of living, the government released a report Thursday showing that inflation had cooled unexpectedly in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Probe Instacart&#8217;s Al-Fueled Pricing Experiments on Groceries</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/feds-probe-instacarts-al-fueled-pricing-experiments-on-groceries-2000701379</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701379</guid>
      <description>The price is wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A massive new DDoS botnet has already snared 1.8 million devices - here's what we know about Kimwolf</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-massive-new-ddos-botnet-has-already-snared-1-8-million-devices-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CBcFwUGAxbxjPiYdt8BxqE</guid>
      <description>Researchers discovered a new botnet called Kimwolf, allegedly built by the same brain behind AISURU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was &#8216;The Force Awakens&#8217; the Savior of &#8216;Star Wars,&#8217; or a Sacrifice?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/was-the-force-awakens-the-savior-of-star-wars-or-a-sacrifice-2000699725</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699725</guid>
      <description>It's hard to separate 'The Force Awakens' from everything that happened in its wake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Teaser Is Online, But It&#8217;s Not the One You Want</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avengers-doomsday-teaser-online-countdown-russo-brothers-2000701364</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701364</guid>
      <description>The Russo Brothers released a short clip that isn't the more substantial video that should be in theaters soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media is merging with a Google-backed fusion energy company in a deal worth $6 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/trump-media-is-merging-with-a-google-backed-fusion-energy-company-in-a-deal-worth-6-billion-180910779.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62c70882-77ce-4d7b-8404-4a9ed93f1c27</guid>
      <description>Trump media, the company behind the president's personal social media platform Truth Social, is inexplicably merging with a Google-backed fusion energy company called TAE Technologies. The deal is worth $6 billion, according to reporting by Financial Times.
Why is an entity known for publishing frenzied hot takes by the president at 3AM combining with a fusion energy company? Who the heck really knows, but a statement says the two organizations will join together to build the "world's first utility-scale fusion power plant." This would be huge, if true, as there are currently no operational co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 21-year-old dropouts raised $2M to build Givefront, a fintech for nonprofits</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/these-21-year-old-dropouts-raised-2m-to-build-givefront-a-fintech-for-nonprofits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077076</guid>
      <description>YC-backed Givefront is building a fintech designed specifically for nonprofits, including food banks, churches, and homeowner associations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot Games found a motherboard security flaw that helps PC cheaters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847539/riot-games-motherboard-security-flaw-pc-cheaters-anti-cheat</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T13:01:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847539</guid>
      <description>Riot Games says a security flaw in many recent motherboards could be exploited by cheaters undetected, and now companies including Asrock, Asus, Gigabyte, and MSI have released BIOS updates to address the issue. According to Riot, "had this issue gone unnoticed, it would have completely nullified all existing DMA detection and prevention tech currently on [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 best gifts under $25 for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-11-best-gifts-under-25-for-2025-140042203.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed1a9e09-5eb8-4f57-9f1c-a7a202af8266</guid>
      <description>The most hyped tech is often also the most expensive: flagship smartphones, ultra-powerful gaming laptops, immersive VR headsets and the like. But it would be wrong to assume that those are the only pieces of technology worth gifting. You don&#8217;t have to drain your wallet to get someone a cool gadget that will both be useful and make their lives easier. There are more solid, affordable gadgets out there now more than ever, but that also means you&#8217;ll discover some junk along the way. We&#8217;ve collected our favorite pieces of tech under $25 that make great gifts and help you to stick to a budget.
Bes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Wear OS features you're probably not using, but should be</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/3-wear-os-features-youre-probably-not-using-but-should-be</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wXT2gUWnrXnkz5BwT2pR5n</guid>
      <description>Smartwatches are more feature-filled than ever, but that can make it difficult to know where to start to make the most out of your tech. Here are some features you might have missed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A lot of people cry using the app &#8212; we&#8217;ve had users say it put into words things they&#8217;d been struggling with for years' : Mark Manson on the problem with self-help and why his AI app is different</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/a-lot-of-people-cry-using-the-app-weve-had-users-say-it-put-into-words-things-theyd-been-struggling-with-for-years-mark-manson-on-the-problem-with-self-help-and-why-his-ai-app-is-different</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xdAgWCcyCG9VMijdca7Gre</guid>
      <description>Mark Manson explains why he&#8217;s betting on an AI mentor over another self-help book &#8212; and how personalization may be reshaping the future of self-improvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondhand shopping is bigger than ever in 2025. Here&#8217;s how to thrift your holiday gifts the right way</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462858/thrifting-second-hand-shopping-tips-holiday-trend-2025-christmas-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462858/thrifting-second-hand-shopping-tips-holiday-trend-2025-christmas-gift-ideas</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Thriftmas&#8217; is surging in popularity this year as more Americans facing affordability issues look to buy vintage.
Christmas is coming, and our bank accounts are getting, well, obliterated. But luckily, it&#8217;s no longer just your quirky aunt who appreciates a good secondhand store: Shopping for gently used items, especially during the holidays, is now on trend. And if you get on board, you might be able to save a bundle by swapping your mall run for a day of thrifting.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FrandroidOffreMoi une cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/anker/2915625_frandroidoffremoi-une-camera-de-securite</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/anker/2915625_frandroidoffremoi-une-camera-de-securite</guid>
      <description>
On se tourne du c&#244;t&#233; de la s&#233;curit&#233; pour le jour 18 de notre calendrier de l'Avent. Tentez de gagner la cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; Eufy Solocam E42 avec notre concours #FrandroidOffreMoi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple opens up iOS in Japan in response to new regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/apple-opens-up-ios-in-japan-in-response-to-new-regulations-174854950.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e3fd528-9ae3-4fa5-b524-acc88551b9d7</guid>
      <description>You can add Japan to the list of regions where Apple has been forced to do something it would rather not: open up the App Store. On Thursday, the company announced changes to iOS in Japan to comply with the nation's Mobile Software Competition Act (MSCA). The tighter regulations for Apple and Google, which overlap with Europe's, took effect today. Users in the US and elsewhere won't see any of these changes.Apple's changes in iOS 26.2 in Japan revolve around alternative app stores, payments outside the App Store and browser choice. The company worked with Japanese regulators on new protections...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The JBL Flip 7 Bluetooth speaker is under $100 for the first time</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-jbl-flip-7-speaker-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03P2dBHTt7ytTbNSt7l38MR</guid>
      <description>The JBL Flip 7 portable Bluetooth speaker is on sale at Amazon for only $99.95. That's 33% off and its lowest price on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultra-Realistic AI Face Swapping Platform Driving Romance Scams</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-ultra-realistic-ai-face-swapping-platform-driving-romance-scams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67d9b883d699e181128c195e</guid>
      <description>Capable of creating &#8220;nearly perfect&#8221; face swaps during live video chats, Haotian has made millions, mainly via Telegram. But its main channel vanished after WIRED's inquiry into scammers using the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay prepared with $70 off the DJI Power 1000 V2 portable power station</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-dji-power-1000-v2-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ZyKGfiuzHFRyX3FwZy28Z</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, save $70 on the DJI Power 1000 V2 portable power station at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Il n&#8217;y a pas eu de nouveau piratage massif de Bouygues Telecom, c&#8217;est un coup de bluff</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2915175_il-ny-a-pas-eu-de-nouveau-piratage-massif-de-bouygues-telecom-cest-un-coup-de-bluff</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2915175_il-ny-a-pas-eu-de-nouveau-piratage-massif-de-bouygues-telecom-cest-un-coup-de-bluff</guid>
      <description>
Sur le Dark Web, un pirate affirme avoir d&#233;rob&#233; plus de 6 millions de donn&#233;es clients Bouygues Telecom. Heureusement, c'est faux, m&#234;me si en soi il y a bien eu une fuite.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidy up your home with the Ecovacs Deebot X11 for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-ecovacs-deebot-x11-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00rHw3HcR9kohHQB3lZJhuN</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, get the Ecovacs Deebot X11 for its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media Wants to Become a Nuclear Fusion Company</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-media-wants-to-become-a-nuclear-fusion-company-2000701354</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701354</guid>
      <description>Trump Media just announced a $6 billion deal with an Alphabet-backed outfit that would create one of the first publicly traded fusion companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Shark AI Ultra robot vacuum clean your floors for under $250</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-shark-ai-ultra-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07hHQnUHziDzjpJFQkje12V</guid>
      <description>The Shark AI Ultra robot vacuum is on sale at Amazon for $249.99, down from the normal price of $549.99. That's a 55% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurry! Claim your free ByteSim for your next trip to Japan exclusively on TechRadar</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hurry-claim-your-free-bytesim-for-your-next-trip-to-japan-exclusively-on-techradar</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KA3Avqro5LsHQe2qpzFRzJ</guid>
      <description>TechRadar readers can grab a limited free eSIM + ongoing savings for future trips.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
