<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:24:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Plant and Gardening Gifts From LetPot (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/letpot-plant-and-gardening-gifts-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69399e063149627b5f4d33cd</guid>
      <description>The brand best known for its Aerogarden dupes actually has a wide range of indoor garden supplies. These are the products I've tested and would buy myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uh-oh &#8212; Nvidia could drastically reduce supply of its RTX 5000 gaming GPUs in 2026, cutting production by up to 40%</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/uh-oh-nvidia-could-drastically-reduce-supply-of-its-rtx-5000-gaming-gpus-in-2026-cutting-production-by-up-to-40-percent</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5WGJRzuDrBox2AUSKj9UTi</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is rumored to be cutting supply of RTX 5000 models by 30% to 40% in the first half of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Facebook test makes link-sharing a paid feature for creators</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/a-facebook-test-makes-link-sharing-a-paid-feature-for-creators-224632957.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">082682d2-324e-4430-98a8-2736a415f065</guid>
      <description>Creators and publishers have long worried about Meta's ability to throttle links to outside content. Now, the company is testing out a new scheme that effectively puts link-sharing behind a paywall for creators on Facebook.Under the test, a Meta Verified subscription will determine how many links a creator can share another profile per month. According to a screenshot shared by social meda consultant Matt Navarra, creators in the test recently received a notification from Meta informing them that "certain Facebook profiles without Meta Verified, including yours, will be limited to sharing link...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Predicts AGI by 2026 (He Predicted AGI by 2025 Last Year)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-predicts-agi-by-2026-he-predicted-agi-by-2025-last-year-2000701007</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701007</guid>
      <description>The robot uprising has been postponed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Monsterverse Loves Wyatt Russell So Much It&#8217;s Giving Him His Own Show</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/monsterverse-wyatt-russell-spinoff-apple-tv-2000701053</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701053</guid>
      <description>So, yes, he's younger Kurt Russell again in a new spinoff to 'Monarch: Legacy of Monsters,' coming to Apple TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers find mysterious lemon-shaped exoplanet with NASA's Webb telescope</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/astronomers-find-mysterious-lemon-shaped-exoplanet-with-nasas-webb-telescope-223722244.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5a5d930-5b37-4601-a9ac-89ea76f9a52b</guid>
      <description>Space is full of unsolved mysteries, and a team using NASA&#8217;s James Webb Space Telescope have recently turned up a doozy. "I remember after we got the data down, our collective reaction was 'What the heck is this?' It's extremely different from what we expected," said Peter Gao of the Carnegie Earth and Planets Laboratory in Washington, a co-author on the study. The researchers found an exoplanet dubbed PSR J2322-2650b that orbits a small, dense star emitting electromagnetic radiation known as a pulsar. They are an example of a black widow system, where a rapidly spinning pulsar is paired with ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brendan Carr doesn&#8217;t regret his threats to broadcasters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/846845/fcc-senate-commerce-oversight-hearing-brendan-carr</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T17:35:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846845</guid>
      <description>A defiant Brendan Carr testified before the Senate Commerce Committee on Wednesday in his first public appearance before lawmakers since threatening broadcasters who aired comedian Jimmy Kimmel's show. Over the course of nearly three hours, the Federal Communications Commission chairman ping-ponged between heated exchanges with Democrats and largely muted questions from Republicans. But at least [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPhones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23618862/best-iphone-camera-battery-screen-guide</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T17:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23618862/best-iphone-camera-battery-screen-guide</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been holding off on getting a new iPhone, now&#8217;s the perfect time to size up your options. Apple&#8217;s 2025 iPhone lineup is now available, which includes the iPhone 17, 17 Pro, 17 Pro Max, and a brand-new model, the ultra-thin iPhone Air. These new phones offer a number of new features over their [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Isaacman is NASA's new leader</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/jared-isaacman-is-nasas-new-leader-220833691.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf534aea-a343-4253-b8c9-6032d53ab63a</guid>
      <description>NASA has a leader again. On Wednesday, the US Senate confirmed Jared Isaacman as the agency's administrator, with a 67-30 vote. The billionaire entrepreneur (and Elon Musk ally) will have his hands full navigating political waters while managing a severely downsized workforce.You might recall that this wasn't Isaacman's first shot at the job. He was nominated to the post earlier this year. But days before he was scheduled for a confirmation vote, President Donald Trump withdrew his nomination.The reversal reportedly came after the president was told that Isaacman had donated to prominent Democ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Wicked&#8217; Director Jon M. Chu on &#8216;What Makes Art Beautiful&#8217; in the AI Era</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-wicked-director-jon-m-chu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939b3dfcb2dfff8af097e81</guid>
      <description>In this episode of Uncanny Valley, we bring you our conversation with Jon M. Chu from WIRED&#8217;s Big Interview event, fresh on the heels of directing Wicked: For Good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford is switching some battery focus from cars to data centers - with plans for huge 20GWh capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ford-is-switching-some-battery-focus-from-cars-to-data-centers-with-plans-for-huge-20gwh-capacity</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zNZsAYVp3J2GEkFeQLf6V4</guid>
      <description>Ford halts electric pickup production and redirects battery investments toward stationary energy storage for grids, data centers, and residential systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboard's charts are increasingly weighted towards on-demand streaming, but not enough for YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/billboards-charts-are-increasingly-weighted-towards-on-demand-streaming-but-not-enough-for-youtube-220238291.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bf442e1-2011-4fe7-8775-00fec52dae9d</guid>
      <description>YouTube announced that it will no longer share data with Billboard for the creation of the Billboard Hot 100 and other charts because the video platform doesn't believe they're calculated fairly. The issue lies, per YouTube, with how Billboard weighs on-demand streams in its rankings: The publication weighs streams from paid music streaming services over ad-supported streams, and YouTube just so happens to run an ad-supported streaming service.Much like getting a book on The New York Times Bestseller list, landing a spot on the Billboard charts doesn't carry quite the same importance that it o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI might change app design forever</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459774/openai-might-change-app-design-forever</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459774/openai-might-change-app-design-forever</guid>
      <description>WIth OpenAI&#8217;s new app store now open, design execs at Canva, Figma, Adobe, and Target explain their first integrations into ChatGPT and answer the question: What even is an app when it&#8217;s part of a conversation with AI? 
When Apple launched the App Store in 2008, it was impossibly influential to the future of the internet. The all-powerful world wide web was sliced and diced into bite-sized apps oft-dubbed Web 2.0. What followed was not just software that fit in your pocket. From TikTok to Uber, these camera-wielding, GPS-integrated, cloud-connected platforms changed the way we lived....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snag the Kobo Clara Colour on sale for a record-low price at Amazon &#8212; save $20 right now</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-17-kobo-clara-colour-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06Qr8fdC9wJONNz5vEwoRPM</guid>
      <description>The Kobo Clara Colour is on sale for $139.99 at Amazon, down from the usual price of $159.99. That's a 13% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vesuvius Exploded in August&#8212;So Why Were Pompeii Victims Wearing Heavy Clothing?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/vesuvius-exploded-in-august-so-why-were-pompeii-victims-wearing-heavy-clothing-2000700770</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700770</guid>
      <description>Despite the fact that Mount Vesuvius triggered one of the most infamous ancient tragedies, not everyone agrees on exactly when it took place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>With a good virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart those online trackers that watch you sleep and show you weird personalized ads. Although we strongly recommend using a VPN, jumping on the first deal that comes along might get you stuck with a substandard app. Beyond that, even otherwise respectable VPNs sometimes frame their prices in misleading ways, with advertised deals not always as available as they seem to be.
Even so, there are some great bargains on the table. For the holiday season, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Isaacman confirmed as next head of NASA</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/jared-isaacman-confirmed-as-next-head-of-nasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077127</guid>
      <description>Isaacman will run the space agency at a time when Trump is trying to both downsize it and task it with returning astronauts to the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Group Extorts Pornhub Over Premium User Data</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hacker-group-extorts-pornhub-over-premium-user-data-2000700978</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700978</guid>
      <description>If you can't trust a porn site with your credit card, who can you trust?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sigourney Weaver Wishes There Was More &#8216;Galaxy Quest,&#8217; But There Probably Won&#8217;t Be</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sigourney-weaver-wishes-there-was-more-galaxy-quest-but-there-probably-wont-be-2000700972</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700972</guid>
      <description>The actress would like to see DreamWorks re-release the film to honor the late, great Alan Rickman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell reportedly preparing massive price hikes for commercial clients - and warns "Ordering today for future delivery DOES NOT lock in current pricing"</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dell-reportedly-preparing-massive-price-hikes-for-commercial-clients-and-warns-ordering-today-for-future-delivery-does-not-lock-in-current-pricing</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TgSeBqF8xZWtQCQuTHjR8A</guid>
      <description>Dell will increase commercial product prices starting December 17 due to memory shortages, affecting laptops, desktops, mini workstations, and AI-enabled devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple may be making an iMac Pro with an M5 Max chip</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/apple-imac-m5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 21:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06o3abxaAmvbK6sN2cXGCwR</guid>
      <description>There may be an iMac Pro with the M5 chip coming to Apple users soon, if leaked documents are to be believed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
