<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:26:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A viral Reddit post alleging fraud from a food delivery app turned out to be AI-generated</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/a-viral-reddit-post-alleging-fraud-from-a-food-delivery-app-turned-out-to-be-ai-generated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080328</guid>
      <description>When fake content goes viral, the damage has already been done, even if the post is debunked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok Is Pushing AI &#8216;Undressing&#8217; Mainstream</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/grok-is-pushing-ai-undressing-mainstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d30e7a225d53752746fb1</guid>
      <description>Paid tools that &#8220;strip&#8221; clothes from photos have been available on the darker corners of the internet for years. Elon Musk's X is now removing barriers to entry&#8212;and making the results public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Hyperkin and Gamesir made a modular game controller for your smartphone, tablet and even your Switch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/hyperkin-and-gamesir-x5-alteron-modular-game-controller-ces-2026-221853624.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a23962a4-423e-4396-94bd-510772939566</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;ve been using the same smartphone controller on my iPhone for years. That&#8217;s partly because most options are so similar. Announced at CES 2026, the X5 Alteron couldn&#8217;t be more different. It&#8217;s a collaboration between GameSir (which loves unusual peripheral dalliances) and Hyperkin (retro-leaning controller maker).
The X5 Alteron is apparently the world's first fully modular mobile games controller. While the headline feature might be the stick/d-pad/button modules, the X5 Alteron has a very accommodating vice grip that works with devices from iPhone and Android phones through to the Switch ser...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin Wants Passengers to Use Meta&#8217;s Neural Band to Control Car Screens</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/garmin-wants-passengers-to-use-metas-neural-band-to-control-car-screens-2000706357</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706357</guid>
      <description>Passengers could use Meta&#8217;s Neural Band wearable to control Garmin&#8217;s car infotainment features without using a touchscreen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odds of Trump Seizing Greenland and Panama Canal Rise on Prediction Markets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/odds-of-trump-seizing-greenland-and-panama-canal-rise-on-prediction-markets-2000706329</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706329</guid>
      <description>The White House told Reuters that "utilizing the U.S. military is always an option" when asked about Greenland on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel's Core Ultra Series 3 let me play 'Battlefield 6' at 190 fps on a Lenovo ultraportable</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/intels-core-ultra-series-3-let-me-play-battlefield-6-at-190-fps-on-a-lenovo-ultraportable-220952246.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14fe7c76-10f8-4ad5-af94-6aeff4df4a15</guid>
      <description>How far has Intel's embedded Arc&#160;graphics come over the years? Enough to let me play Battlefield 6 at up to 190 fps in 1080p, with the graphics settings set to high, all on an unassuming Lenovo IdeaPad Pro 5. There was no need for dedicated graphics, just the Intel Core Ultra X9 388H's built-in Arc B390 GPU. There's a catch, of course: Intel's XeSS3 AI upscaling and 4X frame generation is the big reason why I was able to see such high fps figures. I was playing Battlefield 6 on a controller, with the Lenovo laptop connected to a TV, and I was surprised by how smooth the gameplay felt. There wa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary HDD brand that created 3.5-inch format makes surprising comeback at CES 2026 &#8212; could illustrious names like Maxtor, Iomega or SyQuest be next?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/legendary-hdd-brand-that-created-3-5-inch-format-makes-surprising-comeback-at-ces-could-illustrious-names-like-maxtor-iomega-or-syquest-be-next</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iR2Qv8CdThSKKSwMavNRca</guid>
      <description>Once a pioneer of PC hard drives, Conner reappears at CES 2026 with a very different product focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Director of &#8216;Greenland 2: Migration&#8217; Explains the Enduring Appeal of Disaster Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-director-of-greenland-2-migration-explains-the-enduring-appeal-of-disaster-movies-2000703715</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703715</guid>
      <description>Ric Roman Waugh directs the sequel to his 2020 hit, with Gerard Butler returning to face the post-apocalypse on a comet-ravaged Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony Patent Would Unleash AI &#8216;Ghosts&#8217; to Beat Games for You When They Get Too Hard</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-patent-would-unleash-ai-ghosts-to-beat-games-for-you-when-they-get-too-hard-2000706270</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706270</guid>
      <description>Maybe one day, we'll get an AI that can watch the movies for us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWC debuts PCIe Gen4-class 8TB Thunderbolt 5 external SSD, the largest and fastest in its category &#8212; but it won't be cheap</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/owc-debuts-pcie-gen4-class-8tb-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-the-largest-and-fastest-in-its-category-but-it-wont-be-cheap</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ovqT6emoyzFhenfCuAyqGh</guid>
      <description>OWC introduces an 8TB Thunderbolt 5 SSD offering high transfer speeds, broad compatibility, rugged design claims, and pricing well above mainstream portable storage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#8217;s Jensen Huang wins engineering group&#8217;s top award</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467925/nvidia-jensen-huang-wins-iee-chips-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467925/nvidia-jensen-huang-wins-iee-chips-ai</guid>
      <description>Huang is awarded the IEEE Medal of Honor for pioneering work in GPU-accelerated computing.
Nvidia&#8217;s Jensen Huang is one of the tech industry&#8217;s longest-serving chief executives, leading the chipmaker since&#160;cofounding&#160;it in 1993. Now&#160;he&#8217;s&#160;the recipient of a long-standing technology award: the IEEE Medal of Honor,&#160;established&#160;by a predecessor of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers in 1917.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best Kindle deals right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21539047/best-amazon-kindle-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T16:26:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21539047/best-amazon-kindle-deals</guid>
      <description>When it comes to finding a device to read ebooks, you have a few options to choose from. You can always buy a tablet or use your phone, but those devices are multipurpose and can be used for a ton of things, like surfing the web or doomscrolling on X or Bluesky. If you are [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer content is fuel for an internet-obsessed administration</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856948/nick-shirley-minnesota-daycare-fraud-influencer-media-cycle</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T16:24:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856948</guid>
      <description>Just a day after publishing a 40-minute video alleging fraud at Minnesota daycare centers, Nick Shirley had the vice president's attention. In Shirley's video, he and another man identified only as "David" roam Minneapolis with cameras and microphones, demanding entrance to daycare centers they say are operated by members of the local Somali community. With [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobileye acquires humanoid robot startup Mentee Robotics for $900M</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/mobileye-acquires-humanoid-robot-startup-mentee-robotics-for-900m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080151</guid>
      <description>Mentee Robotics was co-founded by Mobileye president Amnon Shashua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think That Coffee&#8217;s Safe on a Plane? Think Again, Researchers Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/think-that-coffees-safe-on-a-plane-think-again-researchers-say-2000706308</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706308</guid>
      <description>A new report finds that many airlines have relatively poor quality drinking water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market surges on Big Tech gains, nearing records</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470120/stock-market-big-tech-amazon-sandisk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T21:04:24</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470120/stock-market-big-tech-amazon-sandisk</guid>
      <description>Sandisk surged 25.8% for the market&#8217;s biggest gain, driven by artificial intelligence and demand for data-storage hardware.
Stocks rose on Wall Street Tuesday afternoon and approached more all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Ahead in &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-2026-preview-mandalorian-and-grogu-starfighter-2000705592</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705592</guid>
      <description>2026 marks another major transitory period for the galaxy far, far away&#8212;as it tries to return to movie theaters for the first time in almost seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame's latest robot vacuum concept has slightly terrifying legs that can climb full-size stairs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/dreames-latest-robot-vacuum-concept-has-slightly-terrifying-legs-that-can-climb-full-size-stairs-210000399.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efe72a0d-8e7e-44a0-8cf7-e8910908c28b</guid>
      <description>Robot vacuum companies are once again trying to outdo each other at CES 2026. This year, Chinese appliance maker Dreame is showing off a prototype of a device that can climb up and down an entire flight of stairs.The concept, called the Cyber X, was previewed last year at IFA in Berlin. The vacuum sports a somewhat terrifying set of legs with rubber treads that allow it to autonomously navigate multi-story environments. While Dreame has previously shown off vacuums that can move up smaller steps, it says the Cyber X can climb stairs up to 25cm (9.8 inches) high and slopes up to 42 degrees. It ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame's robot vacuum with an arm is back at CES 2026 and it can do more than pick up shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/dreames-robot-vacuum-with-an-arm-is-back-at-ces-2026-and-it-can-do-more-than-pick-up-shoes-210000020.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48f39b83-a16b-4998-91b7-41d31eb4145a</guid>
      <description>Last year at CES, Dreame showed off a robot vacuum prototype with a mechanical arm. But while we were able to see the arm extend and retract, we didn&#8217;t see the device, which was described as a prototype at the time, actually grab anything, which was a bit disappointing.This year, though, the company has made its arm-enabled vacuum a reality with the Cyber 10 Ultra. Dreame previewed it recently at IFA in Berlin, but has now confirmed it will be on sale later this year.&#160;The vacuum has an extendable arm that looks pretty similar to the prototype version we saw last year. It extends from the top o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI says it raised $20B in Series E funding</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/xai-says-it-raised-20b-in-series-e-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080465</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is among the many investors, but xAI has not disclosed if these investments come in the form of equity or debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs&#8217; Plan for Atari &#8216;Astrochart&#8217; Among New Items Up for Auction</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/steve-jobs-plan-for-atari-astrochart-among-new-items-up-for-auction-2000706227</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706227</guid>
      <description>Take a peek at the stuff from the Apple founder's childhood bedroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 day 2: the 11 best gadgets we've seen today, from smart flashlights to new Dell XPS laptops</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/ces-2026-day-2-the-11-best-gadgets-weve-seen-today-from-smart-flashlights-to-new-dell-xps-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eAWzswHS8hQaWVyLAEyBkV</guid>
      <description>The gadgets and gizmos on show at CES 2026 are continuing to impress us, as we tour the Las Vegas show floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why culture is strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470133/why-culture-is-strategy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:42:14</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470133/why-culture-is-strategy</guid>
      <description>Every organization already has a culture&#8212;but does it reflect the strategy or contradict it?
We&#8217;ve grown strangely comfortable separating things that were never meant to be separated: leadership from management, vision from execution, and perhaps most damaging, culture from strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inevitable Rise of the Art TV</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/art-frame-tv-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695be40a363a90f378f4766f</guid>
      <description>New televisions from Amazon, Hisense, TCL, and others are designed to display fine art and look like a painting when they&#8217;re switched off. It&#8217;s all thanks to smaller living spaces and new screen tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI teamed with Microsoft to build a unique stylus that doubles as an AI microphone for Copilot &#8212; and you can fully charge it in just 30 seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/msi-teamed-with-microsoft-to-build-a-unique-stylus-that-doubles-as-an-ai-microphone-for-copilot-and-you-can-fully-charge-it-in-just-30-seconds</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">w2qmyFzZEGFwfxKQYMoktF</guid>
      <description>MSI Nano Pen for Prestige Flip laptops combines pressure-sensitive stylus input, tilt support, rapid charging, and built-in Copilot voice commands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 ways to build global teams in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470115/5-ways-to-build-global-teams-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:34:22</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470115/5-ways-to-build-global-teams-in-2026</guid>
      <description>In a complex world, companies should re-evaluate their infrastructure.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At CES, EVs take a backseat to robotaxis and AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856503/ces-2026-robotaxi-ai-ev-car-concepts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856503</guid>
      <description>It says a lot about the current moment when one of the world's largest EV sellers shows up at the world's biggest electronics show to announce not a new, more affordable model or a cool futuristic concept car, but a humanoid robot. And one we've seen already. Hyundai's decision to use its CES keynote to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the largest US broadband providers investigates breach</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/one-of-the-largest-us-broadband-providers-investigates-breach</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DLAa4wc5b56DE9zC7fkmCD</guid>
      <description>Brightspeed is looking into claims of a data breach, made earlier by threat actors Crimson Collective.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
