<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:27:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon-carbon is just the start: these battery technologies could make your phone last even longer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/silicon-carbon-is-just-the-start-these-battery-technologies-could-make-your-phone-last-even-longer</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jCxXvtpYVmja5rbEJFgyK</guid>
      <description>There are loads of exciting battery technologies under development, and one day some of them could make their way to phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can save over $1,500 on LG&#8217;s 65-inch C5 OLED TV</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/862989/lg-c5-oled-tv-ebay-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:23:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862989</guid>
      <description>LG might have just revealed its new C6 OLED TVs at CES 2026, but we still don't know when they'll actually hit stores. If you don't want to wait - or spend a couple thousand dollars on a brand new model - the current-gen LG C5 OLED is a fantastic option now the 65-inch model [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best alternatives to Spotify for listening to music</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22910685/music-listening-service-spotify-apple-youtube-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:19:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22910685/music-listening-service-spotify-apple-youtube-amazon</guid>
      <description>Spotify is probably one of the most well-known music services available (if not the most popular) around - and it seems that the company it taking advantage of that. As of this month, Spotify announced that it was raising its prices, the third time since 2023. If that concerns you (especially if you're a current [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble&#8217;s Plans for Circular Smartwatches Could Bring Me Back to Wearables</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pebbles-plans-for-circular-smartwatches-could-bring-me-back-to-wearables-2000710823</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710823</guid>
      <description>The Pebble Round 2 and Index 01 are reminders of when tech didn't take itself 'too seriously.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus says it&amp;#8217;s dropping the RTX 5070 Ti as the memory shortage squeezes supply</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863000/asus-nvidia-rtx-5070-ti-5060-ti-supply-rumors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:06:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863000</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, Hardware Unboxed reported that Asus is winding down production of its RTX 5070 Ti, saying, Asus "explicitly told us this model is currently facing a supply shortage and, as such, they have placed the model into end-of-life status." They added that the same applies to Asus's 16GB RTX 5060 Ti, and mentioned how [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI lab revolving door spins ever faster</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/the-ai-lab-revolving-door-spins-ever-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083248</guid>
      <description>AI labs just can't get their employees to stay put. Yesterday&#8217;s big AI news was the abrupt and seemingly acrimonious departure of three top executives at Mira Murati&#8217;s Thinking Machines lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;All You Need Is Kill&#8217; Spins a Trippy, Heart&#8209;Flecked Loop That Only Partially Lands</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/all-you-need-is-kill-spins-a-trippy-heart%e2%80%91flecked-loop-that-only-partially-lands-2000707828</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707828</guid>
      <description>Studio 4&#176;C's anime film of Hiroshi Sakurazaka's beloved light novel, which also inspired the Tom Cruise adaptation 'Edge of Tomorrow,' hits theaters on January 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't be a doomer' - Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang says no one currently has 'any reasonable ability to create god AI', so we should all just relax</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dont-be-a-doomer-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-no-one-currently-has-any-reasonable-ability-to-create-god-ai-so-we-should-all-just-relax</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LsqE5CEwyADJ9zxiySexrP</guid>
      <description>Jensen Huang dismisses god-level AI fears, stresses responsible use of AI tools to improve productivity and address real-world challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take an Extra $50 Off My Favorite Mattress With This Code</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/nolah-evolution-hybrid-mattress-sale-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69693f52053685ef2d2c1d7b</guid>
      <description>Nolah's Evolution is the mattress I personally sleep on as a certified sleep coach, and it's on sale pre-Presidents' Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Glasses for OnlyFans Live Streaming Have Arrived</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/smart-glasses-for-onlyfans-live-streaming-have-arrived-2000710780</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710780</guid>
      <description>It was only a matter of time, to be honest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump unveils a health care plan aimed at lowering costs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475918/trump-great-health-care-plan-aca</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T21:34:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475918/trump-great-health-care-plan-aca</guid>
      <description>The cornerstone is his proposal to send money directly to Americans for health savings accounts so they can handle insurance and health costs as they see fit. 
President Donald Trump&#160;on Thursday announced the outlines of a health care plan he wants Congress to take up as&#160;Republicans have faced increasing pressure to address rising health costs&#160;after lawmakers let&#160;subsidies expire....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Need to Check Your Wireless Headphones for Updates, Right Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-need-to-check-your-wireless-headphones-for-updates-right-now-2000710714</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710714</guid>
      <description>Hackers can abuse a loophole to spy on conversations and track your location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside OpenAI&#8217;s Raid on Thinking Machines Lab</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-openai-raid-on-thinking-machines-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967d917aac0bb6ef1ecddf9</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is planning to bring over more researchers from Thinking Machines Lab after nabbing two cofounders, a source familiar with the situation says. Plus, the latest efforts to automate jobs with AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US claims it just strongarmed Taiwan into spending $250 billion on American chip manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862938/us-taiwan-chipmaking-deal-250-billion-investment-tsmc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T16:12:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862938</guid>
      <description>The US just lowered Taiwan's tariffs in exchange for a massive domestic chipmaking promise, the Commerce Department announced on Thursday. Under the deal, tariffs on goods from Taiwan will decrease from 20 to 15 percent, while Taiwanese technology companies will invest $250 billion into building and expanding chipmaking facilities in the US, supported by at [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Years Later, Has the MCU&#8217;s TV Excursion Worked?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/five-years-later-has-the-mcus-tv-excursion-worked-2000709110</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709110</guid>
      <description>'WandaVision' put the MCU on a journey into television that took time for the megafranchise to fully adjust to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got a Nespresso machine? These 5 tricks and tips will help you make the most of it, and enjoy better-tasting coffee every morning</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/got-a-nespresso-machine-these-5-tricks-and-tips-will-help-you-make-the-most-of-it-and-enjoy-better-tasting-coffee-every-morning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">C2xdaxzpLPGrFfJKTqvVAV</guid>
      <description>Are you getting the best possible flavor from your Nespresso capsules? This quick guide will help ensure that you do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offshore wind industry secures a major legal win in the battle against Trump&#8217;s freeze</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475881/new-york-offshore-wind-industry-legal-win-battle-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475881/new-york-offshore-wind-industry-legal-win-battle-trump</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration froze five big offshore wind projects&#160;on the East Coast days before Christmas, citing national security concerns. 
A federal judge on Thursday cleared the way for a New York offshore wind project to resume construction, a victory for the developer who said a Trump administration order to pause it would likely kill the project in a matter of days....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Help Ghouls Are Charging People Absurd Prices to Talk to Impersonator Chatbots</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/self-help-ghouls-are-charging-people-absurd-prices-to-talk-to-impersonator-chatbots-2000710744</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710744</guid>
      <description>Sure, it's exploitative, but it's also profitable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's New World: Aeternum MMO will go offline January 31, 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/amazons-new-world-aeternum-mmo-will-go-offline-january-31-2027-205449407.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">059941ce-c823-44f9-862e-c054624d3c17</guid>
      <description>Today, Amazon shared more details about the final chapter of its game New World: Aeternum. The company announced in October that it would wind down support for the MMO, with the Nighthaven season to be its last. New World will be delisted and no longer available for purchase starting today, but the game's servers will not be taken offline until January 31, 2027. People who own the game will be able to continue playing until that date. Nighthaven season will continue through to that end date.Players who had previously purchased New World: Aeternum will be able to re-download and continue playin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan to invest&#160;$250B in US semiconductor manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/taiwan-to-invest-250b-in-us-semiconductor-manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083221</guid>
      <description>The U.S. struck a trade deal with Taiwan as the country looks to help boost domestic semiconductor manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finally, Some Good News in the Fight Against Cancer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/finally-some-good-news-in-the-fight-against-cancer-2000710820</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710820</guid>
      <description>The American Cancer Society&#8217;s annual report found that 70% of patients now survive at least five years after diagnosis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krafton is trying to find its next PUBG</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862922/krafton-next-pubg-franchise</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T15:38:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862922</guid>
      <description>PUBG developer Krafton has 26 games in development, and in a recent town hall meeting, the company outlined a plan to "focus on its core gaming business while outlining a disciplined approach to building long-term Franchise IPs." "During the past year, KRAFTON has prepared for Franchise IP development by strengthening its creative leadership, as well [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the oldest phone you can still use in 2026?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/what-is-the-oldest-phone-you-can-still-use-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">paEMXJXmUa6LpDkb3az6jE</guid>
      <description>From iPhone to Galaxy to Google Pixel, these are the oldest phones you can still use day-to-day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our viewpoint is that we are trying to help consumers around the world': Micron finally breaks silence on claims it abandoned customers by dropping the Crucial memory brand</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/our-viewpoint-is-that-we-are-trying-to-help-consumers-around-the-world-micron-finally-breaks-silence-on-claims-it-abandoned-customers-by-dropping-the-crucial-memory-brand</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V66VKFTehydthjrQN98WXT</guid>
      <description>Micron confirms Crucial exit while emphasizing ongoing consumer support, highlighting enterprise DRAM growth and persistent shortages through at least 2028.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia inks new deals with AI companies to mark 25th anniversary</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475731/wikipedia-ai-deals-amazon-meta-microsoft-25th-anniversary</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:31:45</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475731/wikipedia-ai-deals-amazon-meta-microsoft-25th-anniversary</guid>
      <description>The new deals will help one of the world&#8217;s most popular websites monetize heavy traffic from AI companies.
Wikipedia unveiled new business deals with a slew of&#160;artificial intelligence&#160;companies on Thursday as it marked its 25th anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix's expanded Sony deal includes streaming rights to the Legend of Zelda movie</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/netflixs-expanded-sony-deal-includes-streaming-rights-to-the-legend-of-zelda-movie-203011384.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b09f0f28-9c05-4cb0-9720-961f235b1912</guid>
      <description>As part of a new agreement, films from Sony Pictures Entertainment will stream on Netflix first, the companies announced via a joint statement. The new deal expands on the exclusive rights Netflix had to Sony films in the US, and means the service will be the first place people will be able to stream upcoming projects like the live-action adaptation of The Legend of Zelda, and a quartet of biopics about The Beatles.Sony's films will stream worldwide on Netflix in what's called "Pay-1," the first window of availability after a movie's theatrical and VOD releases. As part of the deal, Netflix is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon is giving customers a $20 credit for the outage&#8212;but only if they claim it. Here&#8217;s how</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475876/verizon-outage-credit-for-customers-how-to-claim-redeem-on-app</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475876/verizon-outage-credit-for-customers-how-to-claim-redeem-on-app</guid>
      <description>The mobile giant experienced a massive nationwide service outage this week, and it&#8217;s offering a small refund that can be redeemed on the Verizon app.
If you are Verizon customer, like me, you&#8217;ve probably been scrambling to make phone calls, send texts, and get online since Wednesday, due to a massive, nationwide service outage. (I am writing this from my local food co-op outside Boston, where I am using the internet in their cafe.)...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
