<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 23:31:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Data centers in Oregon might be helping to drive an increase in cancer and miscarriages</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/834151/amazon-data-centers-oregon-cancer-miscarriage</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-30T18:17:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=834151</guid>
      <description>Morrow County, Oregon is home to mega farms and food processing plants. But it&#8217;s also home to several Amazon data centers. And now, some experts believe, that combination is leading to an alarmingly high concentration of nitrates in the drinking water that is driving up cancer and miscarriage rates in the area. Rolling Stone&#8217;s expos&#233; [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swatch MoonSwatch Mission To Earthphase Moonshine Gold Cold Moon: Price, Specs, Availability</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/every-model-of-this-new-snoopy-moonswatch-is-different-and-you-can-only-get-one-when-it-snows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692970a80a85a887a162c137</guid>
      <description>Swatch will laser unique gold snowflakes on every new "Cold Moon" MoonSwatch, but there&#8217;s a catch&#8212;you'll only be able to buy one when it's snowing in Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Avatar&#8217; director James Cameron says generative AI is &#8216;horrifying&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/30/avatar-director-james-cameron-says-generative-ai-is-horrifying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 22:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071222</guid>
      <description>James Cameron&#8217;s movies are often at the cutting edge of visual effects technology, but that doesn't make him a fan of generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus slashed $400 off one of the best gaming monitors it has &#8211; hurry to Amazon's Cyber Monday sale</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/monitors/asus-slashed-usd400-off-one-of-the-best-gaming-monitors-it-has-hurry-to-amazons-cyber-monday-sale</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 22:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zcEb66rJYEyR7ab4hgfDAf</guid>
      <description>High refresh rate, lowest-ever price - save big on the 32-inch 4K Asus ROG Swift</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Cyber Monday Mattress and Bedding Deals (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-cyber-monday-mattress-deals-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 22:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">691b76ae86e69565af2a4958</guid>
      <description>Some of the best sales of the year on mattresses, mattress toppers, and pillows are happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favorite Cyber Monday TV deals from Samsung, Sony, and others are up to 50% off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/829579/best-4k-tv-streaming-soundbar-blu-ray-player-deal-sale-black-friday</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-30T17:23:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=829579</guid>
      <description>Black Friday might have passed, but that doesn&#8217;t mean the holiday deals are gone. You can still find low prices on excellent TVs, streaming devices, and soundbars through Cyber Monday. I&#8217;ve found the best of these deals to level up your home theater setup, and make sure that your holiday season (and every day after) [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Plus, Hulu, and HBO Max are all over 60 percent off for Cyber Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/829306/best-black-friday-streaming-deals-hulu-disney-plus-paramount-hbo-max-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-30T16:54:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=829306</guid>
      <description>The holidays are a great time to see family, exchange gifts, and enjoy a good meal. It&#8217;s also the perfect time to gather around a TV and catch up on must-see shows and movies. Vince Gilligan&#8217;s Pluribus is a fantastic new series on Apple TV, while Hulu is the only place you can catch the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report examines how David Sacks might profit from Trump administration role</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/30/new-report-examines-how-david-sacks-might-profit-from-trump-administration-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 21:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3071216</guid>
      <description>David Sacks&#8217; role as President Donald Trump&#8217;s artificial intelligence and crypto czar could work out very well for his investments, according to a new report. However, Sacks fired back, calling the story a "nothing burger."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tor adds another layer to the onion with a new relay encryption algorithm - boosting resilience and security across the board</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/tor-adds-another-layer-to-the-onion-with-a-new-relay-encryption-algorithm-boosting-resilience-and-security-across-the-board</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MLJz4LtwzBQLz8N8CdU2BZ</guid>
      <description>Tor replaces its older tor1 relay encryption with CGO to strengthen privacy, block tagging attacks, and modernize authentication across circuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scared you'll delete important work files? This backup-focused cloud storage could ease your fears this Cyber Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/scared-youll-delete-important-work-files-this-backup-focused-cloud-storage-could-ease-your-fears-this-cyber-monday</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pUDzuAKheAYTLZGVFooEkD</guid>
      <description>Incorporate backups seamlessly into your cloud storage plans from BackBlaze</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
