<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:23:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MSI is the latest to join the Ryzen AI Max+ 395 bandwagon with the AI Edge mini PC &#8212; better late than never, but with more than 30 competitors out there, it might have a tough time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/msi-is-the-latest-to-join-the-ryzen-ai-max-395-bandwagon-with-the-ai-edge-mini-pc-better-late-than-never-but-with-more-than-30-mini-pcs-out-there-it-will-have-a-tough-time</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ye2reGPkwc6dN8WN2DAmW5</guid>
      <description>MSI&#8217;s AI Edge mini PC combines massive memory, local AI inference, RTX-class gaming, and a compact design for versatile desktop computing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Documentary Maker Weighs in on That ChatGPT Controversy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-duffer-brothers-chatgpt-netflix-2000709898</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709898</guid>
      <description>Eagle-eyed Netflix viewers glimpsed *something* on a computer screen in Martina Radwan's 'One Last Adventure: The Making of Stranger Things 5.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iLife and iWork strike back &#8212; Apple&#8217;s putting all of its creative and productivity apps under one subscription, Apple Creator Studio, and it&#8217;s multiplatform across macOS, iOS, and iPadOS</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/ilife-and-iwork-strike-back-apples-putting-all-of-its-creative-and-productivity-apps-under-one-subscription-apple-creator-studio-and-its-multiplatform-across-macos-ios-and-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wfxXZH9kiQadvNxekQgCo</guid>
      <description>Similar to iLife and iWork in years past, Apple is once again bundling its creative and productivity apps under one roof. Apple Creator Studio offers access to its premium apps at a single price and introduces new AI-powered features across the suite. It also marks the arrival of Pixelmator Pro on iPad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeatherTech founder might be the newest US consumer protection official</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861560/weathertech-founder-david-macneil-federal-trade-commission</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T17:28:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861560</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump made an unconventional pick for his nomination to the Federal Trade Commission: WeatherTech founder and CEO David MacNeil. MacNeil founded the company, which makes weather-resistant car floor mats, in 1989, according to its website, and he owns 100 percent of the company. WeatherTech has made it a mission to keep its manufacturing [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta has closed three VR studios as part of its metaverse cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/meta-has-closed-three-vr-studios-as-part-of-its-metaverse-cuts-202720670.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7129ad-5b4d-4ae8-b8a4-80cc0b970d30</guid>
      <description>Several of Meta's VR studios have been affected by the company's metaverse-focused layoffs. The company has shuttered three of its VR studios, including Armature, Sanzaru and Twisted Pixel. VR fitness app Supernatural will no longer be updated with fresh content.Employees at Twisted Pixel, which released Marvel's Deadpool VR in November, and Sanzaru, known for Asgard's Wrath, posted on social media about the closures. Bloomberg reported that Armature, which brought Resident Evil 4 to Quest back in 2021 has also closed and that the popular VR fitness app Supernatural will no longer be updated w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York governor clears path for robotaxis everywhere, with one notable exception</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/13/new-york-governor-clears-path-for-robotaxis-everywhere-with-one-notable-exception/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082486</guid>
      <description>New York City will be a notable exclusion from proposed legislation to legalize commercial robotaxis across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roblox's age verification system is reportedly a trainwreck</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/robloxs-age-verification-system-is-reportedly-a-trainwreck-220320016.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3895f3-ad9b-4a47-85b4-2dd2f09073a1</guid>
      <description>Roblox's age-verification system was designed as a response to allegations it has a child predator problem. Less than a week in, how's it going? Well, Wired reported on Tuesday that, in some cases, it's classifying children as adults and adults as children. So, not so great!Last week, Roblox made age verification mandatory for anyone using the platform's chat feature. That process involves either submitting a facial age estimate via selfie or (optionally for anyone 13 or older) uploading a government ID check. After verifying, you can only chat with groups of players around your age.The move c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is an Absolute Triumph</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-review-game-of-thrones-2000705180</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705180</guid>
      <description>The casting is perfect, and so is the tone: HBO&#8217;s latest journey to George R.R. Martin&#8217;s Westeros brings a smaller-scaled but no less epic adventure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Ear Audio Is Having a Huge Moment Right Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/open-ear-audio-is-having-a-huge-moment-right-now-2000709804</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709804</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, one audio trend was more audible than the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched all of A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms &#8212; and the new HBO Max show is the triumphant underdog tale that HBO's Game of Thrones franchise needs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dzfcwzPKmRd8tfiY5D6wC</guid>
      <description>A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms is a near-medieval masterpiece that stands tall among its Game of Thrones peers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms review: Game of Thrones prequel is a surprising comfort watch</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-review-game-of-thrones</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06WQLtkqWOu1lw51ohBPChG</guid>
      <description>HBO's "A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms," starring Peter Claffey and Dexter Sol Ansell, proves a surprising balm for the soul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram wants you to personalize your Reels algorithm for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/instagram-wants-you-to-personalize-your-reels-algorithm-for-2026-215252736.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d16159ac-55d0-4b30-9176-6632d84df1ab</guid>
      <description>Last month, Instagram began rolling out a new set of controls that allowed users to personalize the topics recommended to them by the Reels algorithm. Now, Meta is making that feature available to all English users of the app globally, along with the ability to highlight their top topics for the coming year.&#160;The feature begins with a selection of topics Meta's AI thinks you're interested in based on your recent activity, and has controls to remove them or add new categories. There's also a separate field for identifying what you want to see less of, and a new "build your 2026 algorithm" that a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s Solix E10 Battery Backup System Can Power Your Home for Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ankers-solix-e10-battery-backup-system-can-power-your-home-for-days-2000709853</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709853</guid>
      <description>Anker gets into the whole home backup game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is either the world's fastest laptop or someone made a massive typo: Obscure Chinese vendor Mechrevo unannounced Core Ultra 300HX CPU at CES, and apparently almost no one noticed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-is-either-the-worlds-fastest-laptop-or-someone-made-a-massive-typo-obscure-chinese-vendor-mechrevo-unannounced-core-ultra-300hx-cpu-at-ces-and-almost-no-one-noticed</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QeiXri2hMmKfSUdQY4YDBm</guid>
      <description>Mechrevo quietly unveiled the Yaoshi 18 Pro at CES 2026, featuring an unannounced Intel processor and powerful Nvidia graphics, which attracted minimal attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal&#8217;s Founder Turns His Attention to AI&#8217;s Privacy Problem</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/signals-founder-turns-his-attention-to-ais-privacy-problem-2000709897</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709897</guid>
      <description>Confer, an open source chatbot, encrypts both prompts and responses so companies and advertisers can&#8217;t access user data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested several cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T16:25:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Sure, it can take away from the slick design. But using a case relieves me of the worry that the console will accumulate tons of little scratches, or worse. I&#8217;ve tested several types of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
