<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:38:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo&#8217;s new Virtual Boy is more fun to look at than to play</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/873755/nintendo-switch-virtual-boy-impressions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T16:37:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873755</guid>
      <description>Though the Virtual Boy was both a commercial and critical failure, the console's infamy is part of what has made it such a fascinating piece of Nintendo's history. Original units are still going for hundreds of dollars on bidding sites, and hobbyists have spent years keeping the Virtual Boy alive through emulation and homebrew games. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigantic Headphone Speakers Are the Goofiest Thing I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gigantic-headphone-speakers-are-the-goofiest-thing-ive-ever-seen-2000718047</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718047</guid>
      <description>JLab's Blue XL are making my brain hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon to begin testing AI tools for film and TV production next month</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/04/amazon-to-begin-testing-ai-tools-for-film-and-tv-production-next-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089604</guid>
      <description>Amazon MGM Studios will reportedly begin a closed beta program in March to test its AI tools to help with film and TV production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even McDonald's thinks you need to change your passwords - especially if they're burger-related</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/even-mcdonalds-thinks-you-need-to-change-your-passwords-especially-if-theyre-burger-related</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">keh2JADsDxbgWFvavwRrH3</guid>
      <description>McDonald warns common passwords like 'bigmac' and 'happymeal' remain highly vulnerable, urging stronger, randomized credentials for all users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Is Causing Brain Swelling in Children in South Carolina</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/measles-is-causing-brain-swelling-in-children-in-south-carolina/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69838e38627fba3400739269</guid>
      <description>In the ongoing measles outbreak in South Carolina that has infected more than 800 people, some children have developed a rare but serious complication called encephalitis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will an Nvidia Laptop Even Matter?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/will-an-nvidia-laptop-even-matter-2000718055</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718055</guid>
      <description>Who is going to save Nvidia&#8217;s first CPU from Nvidia?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan SCAM Act would require online platforms to crack down on fraudulent ads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/bipartisan-scam-act-would-require-online-platforms-to-crack-down-on-fraudulent-ads-210316594.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a6fc10-dcf2-4949-8e6e-2bb33526fe98</guid>
      <description>Without meaningful deterrents, Big Tech companies will do what's profitable, regardless of the cost to consumers. But a new bipartisan bill could add a check that would make them think twice, at least in one area. On Wednesday, Senators Ruben Gallego (D-AZ) and Bernie Moreno (R-OH) introduced legislation that would require social platforms to crack down on scam ads.The Safeguarding Consumers from Advertising Misconduct (SCAM) Act would require platforms to take reasonable steps to prevent fraudulent or deceptive ads that they profit from. If they don't, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman responds to Anthropic&#8217;s &#8216;funny&#8217; Super Bowl ads</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/874084/ai-chatgpt-claude-super-bowl-ads-openai-anthropic</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T16:03:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874084</guid>
      <description>Sam Altman responded to Anthropic's new Super Bowl ad in an X post on Wednesday, saying the OpenAI competitor's campaign is "clearly dishonest," and called it "on brand" for Anthropic to "doublespeak." "We would obviously never run ads in the way Anthropic depicts them," he wrote. "We are not stupid and we know our users [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Overwatch 2&#8217; Rebrands, and Its Messy Arc Is Complete</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/overwatch-2-rebrands-and-its-messy-arc-is-complete-2000717981</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717981</guid>
      <description>Blizzard has become its own Infinity Gauntlet as it's tried to evolve and expand 'Overwatch' in interesting, often compromised ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Western US Is in a Snow Drought. What Comes Next Is Even Scarier</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-western-us-is-in-a-snow-drought-what-comes-next-is-even-scarier-2000718095</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718095</guid>
      <description>Major snowpack deficits could set the stage for widespread water scarcity and heightened wildfire risk across the American West this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Epstein Files Are Reviving a Conspiracy Theory About Wayfair and Human Trafficking</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jeffrey-epstein-files-wayfair-ashley-woody-allen-2000717900</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717900</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a receipt for furniture is just a receipt for furniture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral drops Voxtral Transcribe 2, an open-source speech model that runs on-device for pennies</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/mistral-drops-voxtral-transcribe-2-an-open-source-speech-model-that-runs-on</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6vzBtpWvGxAJ0mf6yEJUy</guid>
      <description>Mistral AI, the Paris-based startup positioning itself as Europe's answer to OpenAI, released a pair of speech-to-text models on Wednesday that the company says can transcribe audio faster, more accurately, and far more cheaply than anything else on the market &#8212; all while running entirely on a smartphone or laptop.The announcement marks the latest salvo in an increasingly competitive battle over voice AI, a technology that enterprise customers see as essential for everything from automated customer service to real-time translation. But unlike offerings from American tech giants, Mistral's new ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A16z just raised $1.7B for AI infrastructure. Here&#8217;s where it&#8217;s going.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/a16z-just-raised-1-7b-for-ai-infrastructure-heres-where-its-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3089607</guid>
      <description>Andreessen Horowitz just raised&#160;a whopping&#160;&#8288;new&#160;$15 billion&#160;in funding&#8288;.&#160;And a&#160;$1.7 billion&#160;chunk&#160;of that is going to&#160;its&#160;&#8288;infrastructure&#160;team&#8288;,&#160;the one responsible for some of its biggest, most prominent&#160;AI investments including&#160;Black Forrest Labs, Cursor, OpenAI,&#160;&#8288;ElevenLabs&#8288;, Ideogram,&#160;&#8288;Fal&#8288;&#160;and dozens of others.&#160;&#160; A16z&#160;&#8288;general partner&#160;with the infra team Jennifer Li&#8288;&#160;(who oversees such&#160;investments&#160;as&#160;ElevenLabs&#160;&#8211; just valued at&#160;$11 billion);&#160;Ideagram&#160;and Fal, has a clear thesis on where&#160;the team is looking [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Town, 2.0</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/874050/regulator-shutdown-averted-crypto</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T15:20:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/874050/the-crypto-bill-is-falling-apart-in-congress</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers about the most ambitious crossover event of all time: the infinity war between technology and politics. Not subscribed yet? Come on, do it! Washington might seem slower than Silicon Valley. But that's because it's more turbulent. In order to achieve anything, one has to navigate [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Crown&#8217; Star Claire Foy Quit Caffeine After Living With Gut Parasite for Half a Decade</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/crown-star-claire-foy-quit-caffeine-after-living-with-a-gut-parasite-for-years-2000717999</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717999</guid>
      <description>The British actor claims to have struggled with gut parasites for at least five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post Lays Off Its Amazon Beat Reporter as Bezos Brings the Hammer Down</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/washington-post-lays-off-its-amazon-beat-reporter-as-bezos-brings-the-hammer-down-2000718027</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718027</guid>
      <description>The paper is reportedly cutting roughly a third of its staff while its billionaire owner sits on a $261 billion fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doritos, Lays, Cheetos, and more popular snacks are getting a major discount ahead of the Super Bowl</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486830/doritos-lays-cheetos-super-bowl-snacks-get-major-price-cut-discount-deal-pepsi-co</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T20:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486830/doritos-lays-cheetos-super-bowl-snacks-get-major-price-cut-discount-deal-pepsi-co</guid>
      <description>PepsiCo is slashing prices on chips and other products by up to 15% after customer complaints about rising costs.
Just in time for the Super Bowl, PepsiCo is cutting the price of Doritos, Cheetos, Lay&#8217;s, Tostitos, and other snacks by up to 15%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some renters should be wary of &#8216;rent now, pay later&#8217; services. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486966/rent-now-pay-later-paycheck</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T20:08:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486966/rent-now-pay-later-paycheck</guid>
      <description>Economists and renters&#8217; advocates argue that none of these financing options address the fundamental issue of affordability in the rental market. 
Rent can eat up an entire paycheck at the start of the month, so a growing number of renters are turning to a financial product that promises relief by letting them split the bill &#8212; for a price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8217;What will people do in the year 2050, given the enormous intellectual power computers are likely to have?&#8217;: The man Google calls the spiritual father of AI asked big questions in 1991 &#8212; 35 years later, we&#8217;re still wrestling with the answers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-will-people-do-in-the-year-2050-given-the-enormous-intellectual-power-computers-are-likely-to-have-the-man-google-calls-the-spiritual-father-of-ai-asked-big-questions-in-1991-35-years-later-were-still-wrestling-with-the-answers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7H57F2P3hLcHFFJm5BNVdH</guid>
      <description>Ray Kurzweil&#8217;s 1991 AI predictions feel strikingly familiar today, revealing how progress advanced faster than our understanding of intelligence and purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best digital frames for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/best-digital-frame-120046051.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c6bd8ad-dfb7-4195-af8b-c278a7b1c8d7</guid>
      <description>A digital photo frame shouldn&#8217;t be complicated. At its best, it&#8217;s just a good-looking screen that can be set up quickly that reliably shows the photos you care about. Unfortunately, that&#8217;s not always how things play out. The market is flooded with cheap digital frames that promise simplicity but end up delivering washed-out displays, clunky apps and a frustrating experience &#8212; leading you to abandon it after a week.That&#8217;s a shame, because a good digital frame can be really enjoyable. Most of us have thousands of photos sitting on our phones that never make it beyond the camera roll, even though...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Bridgerton! It's Medieval Dynasty! No, it's The Sims 4 Royalty and Legacy, and I think it&#8217;s the best of both worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/its-bridgerton-its-medieval-dynasty-no-its-the-sims-4-royalty-and-legacy-and-i-think-its-the-best-of-both-worlds</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XT4Kri4NShf7FYzFFWYVSK</guid>
      <description>Scandals, dynasties and swordfighting make The Sims 4 Royalty and Legacy one of the most exciting storytelling packs in a while</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Season 2 Ends Pointing at the Big Bad You Already Knew Was Coming</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-season-2-ending-explained-colorado-liberty-prime-enclave-2000717889</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717889</guid>
      <description>Amazon's video game adaptation wraps up its sophomore season with plenty of nods to the 'Fallout' lore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch: all the news about Blizzard&#8217;s hit hero shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2022/6/14/23167853/overwatch-2-activision-blizzard-news</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T14:53:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/2022/6/14/603/overwatch-2-activision-blizzard-news</guid>
      <description>Overwatch 2, the sequel to Activision Blizzard&#8217;s hit hero shooter Overwatch, was announced in 2019 but didn&#8217;t arrive for another three years, eventually bringing a shift to five-on-five matches in PVP, and a few new characters, including Overwatch&#8217;s first Black female hero. After canceling planned PvE content and unlocking its hero pool, the game&#8217;s developers [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notepad++ Users, You May Have Been Hacked by China</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/notepad-plus-plus-china-hackers-update-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69836805afde988bb6796bae</guid>
      <description>Suspected Chinese state-backed hackers hijacked the Notepadd++ update infrastructure to deliver a backdoored version of the popular free source code editor and note-taking app for Windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Market in Shambles as Bitcoin Price Down 40% Since October High</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/crypto-market-in-shambles-as-bitcoin-price-down-40-since-october-high-2000717957</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717957</guid>
      <description>All muh apes, gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon wants Alexa+ to be the reason you keep Prime</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486821/amazon-wants-alexa-to-be-the-reason-you-keep-prime</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486821/amazon-wants-alexa-to-be-the-reason-you-keep-prime</guid>
      <description>The next-gen virtual assistant costs $19.99 a month, but Amazon is bundling it into Prime at no extra charge, giving members a powerful new perk.
Amazon is rolling out a new feature in hopes of retaining&#8212;or perhaps attracting&#8212;new Prime members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games Done Quick's Back to Black 2026 event kicks off tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/games-done-quicks-back-to-black-2026-event-kicks-off-tomorrow-194147068.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02d88d9-a76b-4f41-9cab-c50afe458869</guid>
      <description>Hot on the heels of AGDQ in January, Games Done Quick is hosting its second speedrunning event of the year, Back to Black 2026, starting tomorrow, February 5. The four-day event is organized by Black in a Flash and is raising money for Race Forward, a nonprofit that works across communities to address systemic racism.Back to Black is timed to the start of Black History Month and highlights the deep bench of talent in the Black speedrunning community. A few runs, like ones for Hades II, Donkey Kong Country and Silent Hill 4, were teased when Back to Black 2026 was announced last year. The full ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
