<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 23:23:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Did You Get an Instagram Password Reset Email Recently? This Might Be the Very Unpleasant Reason</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/did-you-get-an-instagram-password-reset-email-recently-this-might-be-the-very-unpleasant-reason-2000708667</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708667</guid>
      <description>Your info might be for sale on the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk says X's new algorithm will be made open source next week</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/elon-musk-says-xs-new-algorithm-will-be-made-open-source-next-week-225721656.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">122935f7-59c5-40ba-8091-8b77103b6d6b</guid>
      <description>X may soon provide more insight into how its algorithm works. On Saturday, Elon Musk posted on the platform to say that the company "will make the new X algorithm, including all code used to determine what organic and advertising posts are recommended to users, open source in 7 days."&#160;X's recommendation algorithm has been the subject of investigations by France and the European Commission, the latter of which recently extended through 2026 a retention order that it sent to the company at the beginning of last year. And scrutiny into the platform, along with demands for accountability, have onl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX gets FCC approval to launch 7,500 more Starlink satellites</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/10/spacex-gets-fcc-approval-to-launch-7500-more-starlink-satellites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081714</guid>
      <description>The Federal Communications Commission has given SpaceX approval to launch another 7,500 of its second generation Starlink satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says he&amp;#8217;s going to open-source the new X algorithm next week</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860294/elon-musk-open-source-x-algorithm</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T16:57:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860294</guid>
      <description>In 2023, what was then still called Twitter, open-sourced at least portions of the code that decided what it served up in your feed. But that GitHub repository is hopelessly out of date, with the vast majority of the files appearing to be from the initial upload three years ago. Elon Musk says that in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These&#160;are the smart home&#160;gadgets that impressed me at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/860241/best-smart-home-devices-ces-2026-matter-ikea-aqara-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T16:30:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860241</guid>
      <description>I picked Aqara's Smart Lock U400 and Roborock's Saros Rover robot vacuum as the overall best smart home gadgets from CES 2026, but there were gazillions of other great gadgets on the show floor. It was a banner year for smart home products, but the big trends I saw weren't about new product categories; they [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
