<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:40:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon and to commit $35bn into AI in India</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amazon-and-to-commit-usd35bn-into-ai-in-india</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vmbQQZohyj9uNxfeJsCiB</guid>
      <description>Amazon's $35 billion commitment is more than what Google and Microsoft have pledged, combined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big DJI Pocket 4 and Avata 360 leaks show a defiant DJI is planning on ending 2025 with a bang</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/drones/big-dji-pocket-4-and-avata-360-leaks-show-a-defiant-dji-is-planning-on-ending-2025-with-a-bang</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jqG9Ey5MEd6bbeKvQxxME8</guid>
      <description>DJI looks set to push out a couple more products before a US ban is expected to come into effect on 23 December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>01net Awards&#160;: le meilleur smartphone abordable de 2025 est&#8230;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/01net-awards-le-meilleur-smartphone-abordable-de-2025-est.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314591</guid>
      <description>La r&#233;daction de 01net.com d&#233;signe les meilleurs produits de l&#8217;ann&#233;e. D&#233;couvrez tous les jours les vainqueurs de chaque cat&#233;gorie jusqu&#8217;&#224; la remise des prix le 10 d&#233;cembre, en live s&#8217;il vous plait !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much suction do you need on a robovac? Here's what I look for as a professional reviewer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/how-much-suction-should-my-robot-vacuum-have</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YaxnKiUTU4wermy5pXop8m</guid>
      <description>When it comes to cleaning clout, it's not all about the suction specs &#8211; but there's still a minimum level you should look for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic! At the disc-o: Quad's retro CD transport makes me want to spend all my money on CDs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/panic-at-the-disc-o-quads-retro-cd-transport-makes-me-want-to-spend-all-my-money-on-cds</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gG7xBZmzNBPHA6wEMSx7Wf</guid>
      <description>The Quad 3CDT is "dedicated to discs" and looks stunning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google launches sub-$5 AI Plus plan in India to compete with ChatGPT Go</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/google-launches-sub-5-ai-plus-plan-in-india-to-compete-with-chatgpt-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074598</guid>
      <description>For new users in India, Google is offering an AI Plus subscription for &#8377;199 ($2.21) for the first six months, after which you'll have to pay &#8377;399 ($4.44).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freebox Ultra Essentiel VS SFR Fibre Premium&#160;: laquelle de ces box internet haut de gamme et Wi-Fi 7 est la meilleure ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/box-internet/2462292_sfr-fibre-premium-vs-freebox-ultra-essentiel-laquelle-de-ces-box-internet-a-8-gb-s-symetrique-est-la-meilleure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/box-internet/2462292_sfr-fibre-premium-vs-freebox-ultra-essentiel-laquelle-de-ces-box-internet-a-8-gb-s-symetrique-est-la-meilleure</guid>
      <description>
Pourquoi opposer la Freebox Ultra Essentiel &#224; la SFR Box 10+ de l'offre SFR Fibre Premium ? Ces deux routeurs partagent comme points communs leur fiche technique premium (d&#233;bit 8 Gb/s sym&#233;trique, Wi-Fi 7...) mais aussi d'appartenir aux forfaits les plus abordables dans la tranche haut de gamme. Voyons ici laquelle m&#233;rite votre attention.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram will let you control which topics its algorithm recommends</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/instagram-will-let-you-control-which-topics-its-algorithm-recommends-133002612.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a4e6c6e-c106-419d-9792-dc8084476f1d</guid>
      <description>For the first time, Instagram will start letting you control the topics its algorithm recommends, much as you now can on TikTok. The new feature is starting with the Reels tab but will eventually come to Explore and other areas of the app. Like much of what Meta is doing right now (for better or worse), the "Your Algorithm" feature will be powered by AI.&#160;
"As your interests evolve over time, we want to give you more meaningful ways to control what you see," Instagram wrote on its blog post. "Using AI, you can now more easily view and personalize the topics that shape your Reels, making recomme...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Will Start Letting You Pick What Shows Up in Your Reels</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/instagram-lets-you-pick-what-shows-up-in-reels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693857fa9c1b464c168a5d48</guid>
      <description>In the battle for your attention, Instagram is betting that more control over the algorithm could keep you scrolling on Reels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram gives you more control over your Reels algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841399/instagram-reels-tune-algorithm-feature</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841399</guid>
      <description>Instagram is launching a new AI-powered feature for fine-tuning which videos appear in your Reels tab. The "Your Algorithm" update allows you to see which topics Instagram already thinks you're interested in based on your previous activity, and then remove some, or add new topics, to better direct what kind of videos you actually want [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram&#8217;s new &#8216;Your Algorithm&#8217; tool gives you more control over the Reels you see</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/instagrams-new-your-algorithm-tool-gives-you-more-control-over-the-reels-you-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074201</guid>
      <description>You can select which topics you want to see more or less of, and your recommendations will adapt accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe and YouTube love-in delivers new tools for content creators &#8212; and resolves the biggest issue we had with Adobe's free video editing app</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/adobe-and-youtube-love-in-delivers-new-tools-for-content-creators-and-resolves-the-biggest-issue-we-had-with-adobes-free-video-editing-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JPmbcLF2NvqX5NwjYPn4Da</guid>
      <description>Content creators now get more tools as Adobe and YouTube join forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Spartacus: House of Ashur episode 3 on Starz?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/spartacus-house-of-ashur-episode-3-release-date-time-starz</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vE3TVQmbCZ5BcUYGCXVd68</guid>
      <description>The gladiator drama is only getting more fraught, but when we can watch Spartacus: House of Ashur episode 3 on Starz?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan v&#233;lo 2026 : le S&#233;nat sauve in extremis un budget de 50 millions d&#8217;euros, mais rej&#232;te deux aides v&#233;los pourtant primordiales</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2904747_plan-velo-2026-le-senat-sauve-in-extremis-un-budget-de-50-millions-deuros-mais-rejete-deux-aides-velos-pourtant-primordiales</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2904747_plan-velo-2026-le-senat-sauve-in-extremis-un-budget-de-50-millions-deuros-mais-rejete-deux-aides-velos-pourtant-primordiales</guid>
      <description>
Un amendement adopt&#233; de justesse par le S&#233;nat vient d'inclure un plan v&#233;lo de 50 millions d'euros au budget 2026, qui doit &#234;tre encore vot&#233; et promulgu&#233;, tandis que le bonus et les aides &#224; l&#8217;achat ont &#233;t&#233; rejet&#233;s.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art TVs Are Getting Smaller and I&#8217;m Here for It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/art-tvs-are-getting-smaller-and-im-here-for-it-2000697588</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697588</guid>
      <description>I can&#8217;t make room for a massive, expensive Frame TV, but I have space for an art monitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed rate cut announcement today: Probability, live stream, date, time, and how to watch</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457937/fed-rate-cut-today-live-stream-time-probability-watch-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T13:21:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457937/fed-rate-cut-today-live-stream-time-probability-watch-announcement</guid>
      <description>Markets are on edge as the Federal Open Market Committee prepares to announce its decision on interest rates. Here&#8217;s everything to know.
The economy has had a volatile year marked by ongoing headwinds and uncertainties. Persistent inflation, unpredictability around tariffs, and a stock market that many fear is in the midst of an AI-fueled bubble are among the factors impacting consumers&#8217; spending power....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe brings Photoshop, Express and Acrobat features to ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/adobe-brings-photoshop-express-and-acrobat-features-to-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074586</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT's 800 million plus userbase can now use Adobe's apps to modify images and PDFs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's AirPods Pro 3 are back on sale for an all-time-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-airpods-pro-3-are-back-on-sale-for-an-all-time-low-price-222806313.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42f7f263-d7c8-4a21-ad07-9121207a6244</guid>
      <description>If you haven't yet upgraded to Apple's AirPods Pro 3, you can pick up the company's latest model at a discount through a deal on Amazon right now. The AirPods Pro 3, which came out in September, are currently down from $249 to $220 &#8212; their Cyber Monday all-time low price. With the new AirPods Pro, Apple made some big improvements, including better battery life and sound quality, and introduced useful new features, such as Live Translation.


The AirPods Pro 3 are the best AirPods available today, with Apple's H2 chip, and earned a score of 90 out of 100 in Engadget's review this fall. Active n...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESTA&#160;: avant d&#8217;entrer aux &#201;tats-Unis, il faudra peut-&#234;tre montrer vos r&#233;seaux sociaux</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/esta-avant-dentrer-aux-etats-unis-il-faudra-peut-etre-montrer-vos-reseaux-sociaux.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314765</guid>
      <description>Les touristes fran&#231;ais qui souhaitent voyager aux &#201;tats-Unis pourraient bien &#234;tre oblig&#233;s de soumettre aux autorit&#233;s am&#233;ricaines les identifiants de leurs r&#233;seaux sociaux utilis&#233;s au cours des cinq derni&#232;res ann&#233;es. Une mesure qui vise &#224; mieux identifier les menaces potentielles contre le pays, mais qui dans les faits pourrait se transformer en vrai repoussoir pour des millions de voyageurs potentiels....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best last-minute Christmas gifts for the 2025 holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-10-best-last-minute-christmas-gifts-for-the-2025-holiday-season-140037254.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f10f3474-8a9f-4844-b943-494ef9bdc916</guid>
      <description>The holidays are nearly here and if you&#8217;re a bit behind on your gift shopping, you&#8217;re not alone. The holidays can truly sneak up on you, and this year that&#8217;s been more true than ever. Between wrapping things up at work before some well-deserved time off and making sure you have everything you need to host family and friends, it can be hard to find the time to go to a store to pick out presents. And when you do finally get there, you may be met with half-empty shelves. But this is where the internet comes in handy: you still have time to buy holiday gifts online.At this point, we recommend pick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Base Layers (2025): Ibex, Smartwool, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-base-layers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68d15ae35d8de5f8ba324367</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re layering up for winter cold or looking for an ultralight summer system, we&#8217;ve tested and found the best base layers for all your outdoor adventures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT can now use Adobe apps to edit your photos and PDFs for free</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841369/chatgpt-apps-adobe-photoshop-acrobat-express</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841369</guid>
      <description>Adobe is giving ChatGPT users some new capabilities for designing and editing their work without having to switch apps. New apps for Photoshop, Acrobat, and Adobe Express are launching today directly in ChatGPT, allowing users to create designs or adjust photos and PDFs by describing what they want. The Adobe apps are free to use, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best things Engadget editors bought in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-things-engadget-editors-bought-in-2025-130000576.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">667db3a4-97af-4068-a60c-f9abe0ddc383</guid>
      <description>For many of us at Engadget, a big part of our jobs is testing out new tech on a regular basis. Our desks are cluttered with new smartphones, power banks, gaming accessories and more pretty much all the time, and there are plenty of winners and losers amongst them. Similarly, there are winners and losers in the things we buy for ourselves throughout the year, and we like to sing their praises just as much as we do for the best new tech that (professionally) comes across our desks. These are the best things Engadget staffers purchased in 2025 that will continue to get lots of use in the new year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe brings Photoshop, Acrobat and Adobe Express to ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/adobe-brings-photoshop-acrobat-and-adobe-express-to-chatgpt-130000389.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8ff444c-3f7a-46c4-aa0f-2535e1a91697</guid>
      <description>Back in October, OpenAI announced apps like Spotify and Canva would be accessible in ChatGPT. At the time, the company said more software was on the way, and now one of the most popular professional applications is available through the chatbot.&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Starting today, you can access Photoshop, Acrobat and Adobe Express inside of ChatGPT. All the apps are free to use through OpenAI&#8217;s website, though before you can begin generating PDFs and illustrations using Acrobat and Adobe Express, you'll need to sign into your Adobe account.&#160;To use any of the apps in ChatGPT, either name them in your prompt or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the private space company building satellites&#8212;cheaper, faster, and better&#8212;in an old San Francisco shipyard</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456505/astranis-microgeo-satellites-john-gedmark</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456505/astranis-microgeo-satellites-john-gedmark</guid>
      <description>Astranis is modernizing an essential piece of modern communications infrastructure&#8212;and doing it in its own urban factory.
Once upon a time, San Francisco was a manufacturing town. For decades, the Union Iron Works built ships&#8212;such as the U.S. Navy&#8217;s U.S.S. Oregon (1893) and U.S.S. Wisconsin (1898)&#8212;in its plant on Pier 70 in the neighborhood now known as Dogpatch. In recent years, that sprawling, long-abandoned complex has been rehabbed and filled with office space, housing, retail, and art studios. Among its tenants are startup accelerator Y Combinator and HR platform Gusto, neither of which h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vie num&#233;rique | Vivre &#224; l&#8217;&#232;re du quettaoctet</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-10/vie-numerique/vivre-a-l-ere-du-quettaoctet.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06e3d42ca0b03d38b5161baf69b8d626</guid>
      <description>On manque de chiffres. Pis encore&#160;: on manque de mots&#8230; pour nommer ces chiffres. L&#8217;humanit&#233;, ou, en tout cas, ses machines, g&#233;n&#232;re tellement d&#8217;information que le vocabulaire peine &#224; suivre. Et si on parle aujourd&#8217;hui tr&#232;s couramment de gigaoctets et de t&#233;raoctets, pr&#233;parez-vous &#224; entendre parler de quettaoctets et de zettaoctets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe s&#8217;incruste dans ChatGPT pour vous aider &#224; retoucher gratuitement vos images, PDF et designs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/photo/2902459_adobe-sincruste-dans-chatgpt-pour-vous-aider-a-retoucher-gratuitement-vos-images-pdf-et-designs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/photo/2902459_adobe-sincruste-dans-chatgpt-pour-vous-aider-a-retoucher-gratuitement-vos-images-pdf-et-designs</guid>
      <description>
Adobe a annonc&#233; l'arriv&#233;e de ses agents au sein de ChatGPT. Il est d&#233;sormais possible de modifier des images ou des PDF directement dans l'outil d'OpenAI. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un colossal sursaut gamma long stup&#233;fie les astronomes, il a dur&#233; des heures au lieu de quelques minutes !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sursaut-gamma-colossal-sursaut-gamma-long-stupefie-astronomes-il-dure-heures-lieu-quelques-minutes-128389/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 13:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sursaut-gamma-colossal-sursaut-gamma-long-stupefie-astronomes-il-dure-heures-lieu-quelques-minutes-128389/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Quand le secret de leur d&#233;couverte par des militaires a &#233;t&#233; supprim&#233;, les sursauts gamma ont stup&#233;fi&#233; les astrophysiciens qui avaient du mal &#224; comprendre d'o&#249; ils pouvaient tirer leur formidable luminosit&#233;. L'un d'entre eux, r&#233;cemment d&#233;tect&#233;, questionne les th&#233;ories qui avaient &#233;t&#233; propos&#233;es &#224;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's for anybody who's ever been wronged' &#8212; Spartacus: House of Ashur star on excruciating death in episode 2</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/its-for-anybody-whos-ever-been-wronged-spartacus-house-of-ashur-star-on-excruciating-death-in-episode-2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xkyBUguCtucDhKTW9twkXS</guid>
      <description>I knew Spartacus: House of Ashur would be violent, but nothing prepared me for the vomit-worthy 'revenge' scene at the end of episode 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of Amazon is here &#8211; Alexa+ can now cut you out of the loop and order products for you when the price drops</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/the-future-of-amazon-is-here-alexa-can-now-cut-you-out-of-the-loop-and-order-products-for-you-when-the-price-drops</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KXHXa64ozTFWDSSZFUdzzA</guid>
      <description>Tell Alexa+ what you want and how much you're prepared to pay for it, and the AI will take care of the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le MacBook Air M2 devient le laptop Apple avec le meilleur rapport qualit&#233;/prix gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre de No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2904513_le-macbook-air-m2-devient-le-laptop-apple-avec-le-meilleur-rapport-qualite-prix-grace-a-cette-offre-de-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2904513_le-macbook-air-m2-devient-le-laptop-apple-avec-le-meilleur-rapport-qualite-prix-grace-a-cette-offre-de-noel</guid>
      <description>
Le MacBook Air M2 poss&#232;de toutes les qualit&#233;s demand&#233;es &#224; un laptop. Il est l&#233;ger, rapide, puissant et surtout silencieux. Que demander de plus ? Une baisse de prix ? C'est le cas chez Cdiscount o&#249; il tombe &#224; 750 euros contre 1 099 euros sur le site d'Apple.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon to invest additional $35B in India by 2030, taking total planned spending to $75B</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/amazon-to-invest-additional-35b-in-india-by-2030-taking-total-planned-spending-to-75b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074591</guid>
      <description>The e-commerce giant said the new investment will support its efforts to digitize small businesses and strengthen its logistics and operations footprint in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's not just about the games &#8212; 2025's PlayStation Wrap-Up will even give you info on accessories you used</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/playstation/its-not-just-about-the-games-2025s-playstation-wrap-up-will-even-give-you-info-on-accessories-you-used</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JktbacyZ56WpyijhEHUSr4</guid>
      <description>PlayStation's 2025 Wrap-Up will even give you info on accessories you used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurry &#8212; get 24GB of SIM-only data for the price of 8GB at Smarty</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/network-providers/hurry-get-24gb-of-sim-only-data-for-the-price-of-8gb-at-smarty</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46j5miVA7pkMnUoiooTg76</guid>
      <description>Smarty are tripling the data on the 8GB package - That's 24GB of data for just &#163;7 per month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Photos lance 5 nouveaux outils pour vos montages vid&#233;os</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/google-photos-lance-5-nouveaux-outils-pour-vos-montages-videos.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314755</guid>
      <description>Google vient de d&#233;voiler l&#8217;arriv&#233;e de cinq nouvelles fonctions d&#8217;&#233;dition vid&#233;o dans Google Photos sur iOS et Android. Avec ces nouveaux outils de montage, l&#8217;application se rapproche un peu plus de CapCut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wix sale is back for a limited time - save a massive 50% on select Wix plans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-building/the-wix-sale-is-back-for-a-limited-time-save-a-massive-50-percent-on-select-wix-plans</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nxAq5eL5jx4tLfroBf7PHf</guid>
      <description>Get your business ready for 2026 for less with 50% off Wix plans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone Fold is tipped to be the biggest smartphone launch of 2026 &#8211; but these 3 things would be deal-breakers for me</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/the-iphone-fold-is-tipped-to-be-the-biggest-smartphone-launch-of-2026-but-these-3-things-would-be-deal-breakers-for-me</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">s5SDhXpMVVWwsru9bEEoGj</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s foldable iPhone will need to overcome three main challenges when it launches in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cantata Haptique RS90 Universal Remote Review: Not Yet Great</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/review/cantata-rs90-universal-remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6938550e904c15561e765f51</guid>
      <description>One day, this remote might control all of our gadgets. That day is not today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pok&#233;mon TCG Mega Venusaur ex Premium Collection Box is finally under $70 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-10-pokemon-tcg-mega-venusaur-ex-premium-collection-box-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07d7UPBsHNEpujRUdd96YEl</guid>
      <description>Find the best Pok&#233;mon deal at Amazon. The Pok&#233;mon TCG Mega Venusaur ex Premium Collection Box is on sale for $69.81 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activision ditches back-to-back Modern Warfare or Black Ops releases after a weak Black Ops 7 launch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/activision-ditches-back-to-back-modern-warfare-or-black-ops-releases-after-a-weak-black-ops-7-launch</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KY5szC5RPMMUEfDiNnG5Q3</guid>
      <description>Activision is making some big changes to how it releases Call of Duty games going forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The impact of age verification: VPN use doubles, porn traffic plummets</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/age-verification-porn-uk-vpn-traffic</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02js778JWy7vKvsnqoV7fZA</guid>
      <description>The Online Safety law brought mandatory age verification into effect in the UK in 2025, and Ofcom reports that traffic to Pornhub decreased, while VPN usage increased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung va piquer un des meilleurs avantages de l&#8217;iPhone en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/samsung-va-piquer-un-des-meilleurs-avantages-de-liphone-en-2026.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314701</guid>
      <description>Samsung rendrait ses Galaxy S26 compatibles avec le standard Qi 2. En cons&#233;quence, la marque cor&#233;enne commercialiserait une gamme d'accessoires magn&#233;tiques bien pratiques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Directors of &#8216;Elio&#8217; and &#8216;KPop Demon Hunters&#8217; Talk About the Reality of Selling Diverse Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-directors-of-elio-and-kpop-demon-hunters-talk-about-the-reality-of-selling-diverse-movies-2000697468</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697468</guid>
      <description>Domee Shi and Maggie Kang look back on the inverse reactions to 'Elio' and 'KPop Demon Hunters' and their shared desires to center original stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Villarreal vs. Copenhagen online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/villarreal-copenhagen-champions-league-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00jRgAKMvzx4iw9eftNaWOR</guid>
      <description>How to watch Champions League for free. Live stream Villarreal vs. Copenhagen in the Champions League for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google invests in Fervo&#8217;s $462M round to unlock even more geothermal energy</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/google-invests-in-fervos-462m-round-to-unlock-even-more-geothermal-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074401</guid>
      <description>Fervo Energy's Series E round will help the company build additional phases of its Cape Station power plant while beginning development on new sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meesho&#8217;s $606M IPO pops as enthusiasm for India&#8217;s e-commerce startups rises</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/meeshos-606m-ipo-pops-as-enthusiasm-for-indias-e-commerce-startups-rises/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074585</guid>
      <description>Meesho had a good first day as a public company, with its shares climbing as much as 46% from its issue price as investors jumped to grab a piece of the company built around small merchants and value-conscious consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear Fusion Took Big Leaps in 2025. Here&#8217;s What Mattered Most</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nuclear-fusion-took-big-leaps-in-2025-heres-what-mattered-most-2000696767</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696767</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s to another year of waiting for fusion to come ten years later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naya Create Review: A Split Keyboard That Just Doesn&#8217;t Work</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/review/naya-create-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693836d9b6d6d2e18a794aec</guid>
      <description>A beautifully designed split keyboard that seems utterly determined not to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertility startup Inito wants to use AI-designed antibodies to expand at-home health tests</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/fertility-startup-inito-wants-to-use-ai-designed-antibodies-to-expand-at-home-health-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074232</guid>
      <description>Inito has raised $29 million in new funding to invest in and develop AI-engineered antibodies that will help it offer new types of tests and improve the accuracy of existing ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;m a professional photographer and the Manfrotto One is the greatest tripod I&#8217;ve ever used</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-accessories/manfrotto-one-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Cs5rUfebe2wvNR7bA9JNpY</guid>
      <description>The Manfrotto One aims to combine the best features of a photo and video tripod into a single model, and may just be the best pro tripod ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>he PlayStation DualSense Edge controller is still marked down to its best-ever price at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-10-playstation-dualsense-edge-wireless-controller-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02wWzOezqsnEL5Kf5vLltNM</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 10, the PlayStation DualSense Edge wireless controller is still on sale at its best price of $169 at Amazon. This is 15% off its list price of $199.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Show slams the White Houses plan to improve airports with workout spaces</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/daily-show-ronny-chieng-airports-sean-duffy-rfk-jr</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02Xm1TtBb3Ln368neQj4OkT</guid>
      <description>"The Daily Show" host Ronny Chieng unpicked transportation secretary Sean Duffy's $1 billion airport plan.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
