<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:23:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Congress removes right to repair language from 2026 defense bill</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/congress-removes-right-to-repair-language-from-2026-defense-bill-231708835.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ee53ef1-3d4e-49d4-aa28-7a78c73c95ab</guid>
      <description>According to a statement from the Public Interest Research Group, the National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2026 has removed language that would have granted the US military the right to repair its own equipment rather than requiring it to use official defense contractors for maintenance. This bill is still being considered by Congress, but it is uncertain whether the right to repair language is likely to be re-introduced once it has been removed.&#160;"Despite support from Republicans, Democrats, the White House and key military leaders, troops will keep waiting for repairs they could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best robot vacuum and mop to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/625409/best-robot-vacuum-mops</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T18:15:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=625409</guid>
      <description>Robot vacuums that can both mop and sweep your floors have improved significantly in recent years. While they are still not as effective as good ol&#8217; manual labor, if you run them regularly, they will help keep your floors cleaner with much less effort on your part. The difference is that newer &#8220;combo&#8221; robot vacuum [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Ils ont enfin fait ce qu&#8217;ils auraient d&#251; faire &#187; : le verdict de MKBHD pour le smartphone de l&#8217;ann&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2902793_ils-ont-enfin-fait-ce-quils-auraient-du-faire-le-verdict-de-mkbhd-pour-le-smartphone-de-lannee</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2902793_ils-ont-enfin-fait-ce-quils-auraient-du-faire-le-verdict-de-mkbhd-pour-le-smartphone-de-lannee</guid>
      <description>
C'est le rituel incontournable de d&#233;cembre. Marques Brownlee (MKBHD) vient de l&#226;cher ses Smartphone Awards 2025. Entre un iPhone 17 enfin complet et une technologie de batterie qui change tout, le youtubeur aux 20 millions d'abonn&#233;s a tranch&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC upholds ban on stalkerware founder Scott Zuckerman</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/ftc-upholds-ban-on-stalkerware-founder-scott-zuckerman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073988</guid>
      <description>Zuckerman, who used to run the stalkerware apps SpyFone and SpyTrac, claimed the ban is hurting his unrelated business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a trouv&#233; et test&#233; l&#8217;anti-ChatGPT : Euria est suisse, gratuit et chauffe des appartements</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2902773_on-a-trouve-et-teste-lanti-chatgpt-euria-est-suisse-gratuit-et-chauffe-des-appartements</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2902773_on-a-trouve-et-teste-lanti-chatgpt-euria-est-suisse-gratuit-et-chauffe-des-appartements</guid>
      <description>
Vous en avez marre que vos conversations avec les chatbots servent &#224; entra&#238;ner les futurs mod&#232;les de la Silicon Valley ? Regardez du c&#244;t&#233; de la Suisse. Infomaniak lance Euria, une IA g&#233;n&#233;rative gratuite qui joue la carte de la confidentialit&#233; absolue. Pas de profilage, pas d'entra&#238;nement sur vos datas, et une infrastructure 100 % renouvelable. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katsuhiro Harada is leaving Bandai Namco after 30 years</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/katsuhiro-harada-is-leaving-bandai-namco-after-30-years-223156258.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">883045ba-ee37-43ef-8161-335217827090</guid>
      <description>Katsuhiro Harada is departing Bandai Namco at the end of 2025. He announced the news both with a farewell note shared on X and, in possibly the coolest exit ever, with an hour-long DJ mix. Harada's 30-year career has most closely been involved with Tekken and he's a familiar face in the fighting game community.He began as a voice actor in the original Tekken game and continued to do so even as he became a director for the series. He has worked on other Bandai Namco titles as a producer, both in and out of the fighting genre. "Each project was full of new discoveries and learning, and every one...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftBank and Nvidia reportedly in talks to fund Skild AI at $14B, nearly tripling its value</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/softbank-and-nvidia-reportedly-in-talks-to-fund-skildai-at-14b-nearly-tripling-its-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073981</guid>
      <description>Skild AI is developing a hardware-agnostic foundation model for robots that can be customized for various uses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subaru joins controversial list of carmakers experimenting with infotainment system pop-up ads</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/subaru-joins-controversial-list-of-carmakers-experimenting-with-infotainment-system-pop-up-ads</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XjhETdYXx3YSsCz4VaA4Rc</guid>
      <description>Pop-up ads in Subarus have been driving customers around the bend, but they aren't the only manufacturer keen on exploiting the rich revenue stream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPad deals you can get right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21280354/best-ipad-deals-apple</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T17:25:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21280354/best-ipad-deals-apple</guid>
      <description>While the best iPad deals usually land during major sale events like Black Friday and Amazon Prime Day,&#160;many great iPad deals are available outside of those times. The day-to-day discounts come and go like changing winds, so there&#8217;s often some amount to be saved, particularly on Apple&#8217;s most affordable iPad, the iPad Mini, and the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every business is a snowflake</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455546/every-business-is-a-snowflake</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T22:07:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455546/every-business-is-a-snowflake</guid>
      <description>Increasingly, so are their security threats
Each business has its unique challenges, but one commonality today is that AI is poised to disrupt almost every business everywhere. Organizations aren&#8217;t the only ones rapidly shifting to adopt AI&#8212;attackers are too, and they&#8217;re doing it faster. The implications of this AI arms race are alarming for legitimate businesses around the world....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now buy groceries in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/chatgpt-grocery-delivery-instacart</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04hoJy4fQlTET4okVlsyfjP</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's chatbot will now allow you to buy groceries via Instacart right in the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget the &#8216;Knights of the Old Republic&#8217; Remake, There Might Be a &#8216;KOTOR II&#8217; Remake Too</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kotor-ii-remake-aspyr-lucasfilm-star-wars-2000697000</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697000</guid>
      <description>The *other* One of the Best 'Star Wars' Games of All Time was planned to get the remake treatment&#8212;but whether it still is remains to be seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See the Skies at Their Most Magical With the Best Aurora Photos of 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/see-the-skies-at-their-most-magical-with-the-best-aurora-photos-of-2025-2000696877</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696877</guid>
      <description>Missed the auroras? These photographers have got you covered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI copycat of King Gizzard &amp; the Lizard Wizard went unnoticed on Spotify for weeks</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/an-ai-copycat-of-king-gizzard--the-lizard-wizard-went-unnoticed-on-spotify-for-weeks-220018144.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b075d36-50e4-4d66-bd46-82b5185a68c0</guid>
      <description>Despite making some moves to address the proliferation of AI-generated audio on its platform, Spotify failed to catch a copycat making imitations of music by King Gizzard &amp; the Lizard Wizard. The long-running experimental rock band from Australia, has been a vocal critic of Spotify and was one of several artists that took their music off the platform in the summer. The move was in response to the discovery that outgoing CEO Daniel Ek was a leading investor in an AI-focused weapons and military company. Today, a poster on Reddit was recommended what appeared to be an AI-generated copy of one of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A CIO&#8217;s playbook for AI investment</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91454162/a-cios-playbook-for-ai-investment</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91454162/a-cios-playbook-for-ai-investment</guid>
      <description>The former Slack CIO and current CIO at Samsara, a leading Internet of Things firm that works in transportation and construction, has tips on managing the change AI brings.
CIOs are grappling with how to leverage AI, but most are asking the wrong question. It&#8217;s not about an &#8220;AI strategy.&#8221; It&#8217;s about a business strategy powered by AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investor letter reveals skyrocketing growth of Waymo&#8217;s robotaxi rides</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/investor-letter-reveals-skyrocketing-growth-of-waymos-robotaxi-rides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073936</guid>
      <description>Six months ago, Waymo disclosed it was providing 250,000 robotaxi rides. But it's grown significantly since, a leaked letter says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Optimus robot falls over, goes viral</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tesla-optimus-robot-falls-appears-teleoperated-at-event</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03hq473Zyk5LcKqFbVSnDrL</guid>
      <description>Watch Tesla's Optimus robot tip over while removing a phantom headset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of farming depends on supporting young farmers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91449645/the-future-of-farming-depends-on-supporting-young-farmers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T21:50:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91449645/the-future-of-farming-depends-on-supporting-young-farmers</guid>
      <description>As a new generation steps forward, regenerative organic agriculture offers a blueprint for a more resilient, hopeful food system. 
Across America, a new generation of farmers is reimagining what it means to work the land. They are engineers, ecologists, and entrepreneurs&#8212;people who see farming not only as a way to grow food, but as a form of innovation. In fields across the country, these farmers are harnessing soil science, biodiversity, and technology to restore what decades of extractive agriculture have depleted....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globe nominations are out: &#8216;One Battle After Another&#8217; leads the way</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456727/golden-globe-nominations-one-battle-after-another</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T21:48:52</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456727/golden-globe-nominations-one-battle-after-another</guid>
      <description>The movie knocked out &#8216;Wicked: For Good&#8217; from the best comedy or musical category.
Paul Thomas Anderson&#8217;s&#160;&#8220;One Battle After Another&#8221;&#160;scored a leading nine nominations to the 83rd Golden Globe Awards on Monday, adding to the&#160;Oscar favorite&#8217;s momentum&#160;and handing Warner Bros. a victory amid&#160;Netflix&#8217;s acquisition deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petco reveals a hack exposed customer data in these states</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/petco-breach-customer-data</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03VrseJWeuYFbdJkMZBDn6K</guid>
      <description>Petco breach exposed sensitive customer data, including SSNs and driver&#8217;s licenses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Department of Commerce approves Nvidia H200 chip exports to China</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/department-of-commerce-may-approve-nvidia-h200-chip-exports-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073906</guid>
      <description>This news comes as a bill was introduced in Congress last week to prevent these exact kinds of chip exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switching between Android and iOS is about to get easier</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/android-ios-apple-google-data-switching-transfer-easier</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Py9gwknO5EYycXhf0jTmO</guid>
      <description>You'll soon have an easier time moving from Android to iOS, or vice versa, thanks to a future software update for both platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 34 best gifts that your teen will actually use</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/785418/best-teen-gift-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T16:30:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=785418</guid>
      <description>Between keeping up with TikTok trends and whatever new gadget just dropped, it's tough to know exactly what teens are into these days. Luckily, we can help. We may be older than teenagers, but many of us here at The Verge are kids at heart. Plus, we've also got a few staffers with older kids. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;StableChain&#8217; Launch Shows How Far Crypto Has Strayed From Bitcoin&#8217;s Original Promise</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stablechain-launch-shows-how-far-crypto-has-strayed-from-bitcoins-original-promise-2000696959</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696959</guid>
      <description>The centralization will continue until morale improves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE location app developer sues government, not Apple, for app store removal</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456819/ice-location-app-apple-bondi-trump-immigration</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456819/ice-location-app-apple-bondi-trump-immigration</guid>
      <description>The case could reshape how tech platforms handle government requests, especially those without formal warrants or court orders.
Joshua Aaron, the developer of the ICE agent tracking app ICEBlock, filed a lawsuit against the&#160;Department of Justice and ICE for unconstitutionally pressuring Apple to remove the app from its App Store.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s AI try-on app Doppl adds a shoppable discovery feed</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/googles-ai-try-on-app-doppl-adds-a-shoppable-discovery-feed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073919</guid>
      <description>The tech giant says the idea behind the new feed is to display recommendations so users can discover and virtually try on items. Nearly everything in the feed is shoppable, with direct links to merchants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Skydance launches a hostile takeover bid in last-ditch effort to acquire Warner Bros. Discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91456587/paramount-skydance-launches-a-hostile-takeover-bid-in-last-ditch-effort-to-acquire-warner-bros-discovery</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-08T21:26:04</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91456587/paramount-skydance-launches-a-hostile-takeover-bid-in-last-ditch-effort-to-acquire-warner-bros-discovery</guid>
      <description>Paramount Skydance&#8217;s move escalates a monthslong bidding war over one of the most valuable IP libraries in entertainment history.
On December 5, the entertainment world was rocked when Netflix and Warner Bros. announced a massive deal that set Netflix up to purchase the legendary Hollywood studio, creating one of the largest media entities of all time. Today, Paramount Skydance&#8212;which has been vying for Warner Bros. for months&#8212;appears to be saying, &#8220;Not so fast.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
