<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:27:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai test&#233; &#224; Paris le Tesla FSD : pourquoi j&#8217;ai h&#226;te que ce syst&#232;me encore interdit soit autoris&#233; en Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2902551_jai-teste-a-paris-le-tesla-fsd-pourquoi-jai-hate-que-ce-systeme-encore-interdit-soit-autorise-en-europe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2902551_jai-teste-a-paris-le-tesla-fsd-pourquoi-jai-hate-que-ce-systeme-encore-interdit-soit-autorise-en-europe</guid>
      <description>
Encore interdit en Europe, nous avons pu tester le syst&#232;me FSD (Full Self-Drive) de Tesla &#224; Paris en avant-premi&#232;re. De quoi d&#233;couvrir un syst&#232;me de conduite autonome &#233;tonnant de maturit&#233;&#8230; et faire le point sur ce qui emp&#234;che son arriv&#233;e dans nos contr&#233;es.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 27 best gifts for travelers who are always on the move</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/799419/best-gifts-for-travelers-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T12:22:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=799419</guid>
      <description>I'm convinced that whoever said it's about the journey, not the destination, has never traveled. Try sitting on a plane for 16 hours - plus delays, airport security, and a snoring seat neighbor - and then get back to me. While getting from point A to point B can feel like a test of endurance, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is RAM so expensive right now? It's more complicated than you think</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/why-is-ram-so-expensive-right-now-its-more-complicated-than-you-think</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YGefuaPVVVsssjjcQuL8Na</guid>
      <description>The global DRAM crunch explained: shortages, soaring prices, and what comes next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Supergirl artwork reveals fresh look at Milly Alcock's rebellious hero as DCU movie trailer's release date and time confirmed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/new-supergirl-artwork-reveals-fresh-look-at-milly-alcocks-rebellious-hero-as-dcu-movie-trailers-release-date-and-time-confirmed</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wvYDJGKAWXueog89BcQKSj</guid>
      <description>DC Studios has announced when Supergirl's first trailer will take flight &#8211; and revealed its story synopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton Pass just made it even easier for developers to retrieve secrets &#8212; and that's a win for everyone involved</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/proton-pass-just-made-it-even-easier-for-developers-to-retrieve-secrets-and-thats-a-win-for-everyone-involved</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RGhFvrxUNExJeXrJmcseuA</guid>
      <description>A command-line interface is just what users wanted, and now Proton Pass have added it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation Plus Extra et Premium en d&#233;cembre 2025 : on se refait un Assassin&#8217;s Creed avant que Black Flag Resynced ne soit d&#233;voil&#233; ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2905485_playstation-plus-extra-et-premium-en-decembre-2025-on-se-refait-un-assassins-creed-avant-que-black-flag-resynced-ne-soit-devoile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2905485_playstation-plus-extra-et-premium-en-decembre-2025-on-se-refait-un-assassins-creed-avant-que-black-flag-resynced-ne-soit-devoile</guid>
      <description>
Pour sa derni&#232;re s&#233;lection de l'ann&#233;e, Sony met le paquet sur son catalogue PlayStation Plus Extra et Premium. Deux excellents titres sont &#224; l'honneur : Assassin's Creed Mirage dont le DLC Vall&#233;e des souvenirs est r&#233;cemment sorti et Wo Long Fallen Dynasty, un souls-like souvent compar&#233; &#224; Nioh.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctica&#8217;s Only Bug Is Eating Something It Really Shouldn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/antarcticas-only-bug-is-eating-something-it-really-shouldnt-2000697908</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697908</guid>
      <description>The findings hint at the creeping presence of microplastics near the South Pole, researchers suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Switch Online additions are N64 games Rayman 2: The Great Escape and Tonic Trouble</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/the-next-switch-online-additions-are-n64-games-rayman-2-the-great-escape-and-tonic-trouble-171500122.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">500d0d1d-838c-462f-a5de-d9b981d843ba</guid>
      <description>Nintendo has announced its Nintendo Switch Online additions for December, which are for all the N64-era 3D platformer fans out there. On December 17, Rayman 2: The Great Escape and Tonic Trouble are joining the Switch&#8217;s Nintendo Classics library. As a reminder, N64 games are exclusive to Switch Online + Expansion Pack subscribers, along with the emulators for the Game Boy Advance, Sega Genesis and GameCube.
For retro gaming completionsists, Tonic Trouble might actually be the more interesting get for NSO, despite being far less well known than the Rayman series. It was Ubisoft&#8217;s first 3D platf...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures liseuses couleur en 2025&#160;? La s&#233;lection</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2583405_meilleures-liseuses-couleur</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2583405_meilleures-liseuses-couleur</guid>
      <description>
Vous cherchez une bonne liseuse &#233;lectronique capable d'afficher de la couleur ? Il existe un certain nombre de r&#233;f&#233;rences sur le march&#233; en 2025 : voici notre s&#233;lection de celles que nous vous recommandons.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TunnelBear reshapes its free VPN model amid rising infrastructure costs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/tunnelbear-reshapes-its-free-vpn-model-amid-rising-infrastructure-costs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36Y2KFtgTmm7RGXMD8K6X6</guid>
      <description>TunnelBear has just announced several changes to its free VPN, including dropping custom server selection and split tunneling. Here&#8217;s all you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android users can now share a live video on 911 calls</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841503/android-emergency-live-video</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T12:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841503</guid>
      <description>A new feature coming to Android will allow users to get more support during emergencies by sharing a live video feed from their phone with 911 responders. For instance, if someone calls 911 for a medical emergency, the 911 responder can use the live video feed to walk the caller through CPR or first aid [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 16 Favorite Holiday Genre Movies, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/holiday-movies-ranked-horror-scifi-fantasy-2000696724</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696724</guid>
      <description>From 'Elf' and 'Gremlins' to 'Polar Express' and the Grinch, here's our ranking of holiday movies with a genre twist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the 19 best tech gadget gifts under $50 &#8212; Apple, Ring, Echo, and Sony from $9</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/here-are-the-19-best-tech-gadget-gifts-under-usd50-apple-ring-echo-and-sony-from-usd9</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PV96NwKTTZiiVHvDcDkjC4</guid>
      <description>I'm rounding up my favorite tech gadget gifts under $50, including headphones, speakers, and smart home gadgets from Apple, Sony, Amazon, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Men Linked to China&#8217;s Salt Typhoon Hacker Group Likely Trained in a Cisco &#8216;Academy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/2-men-linked-to-chinas-salt-typhoon-hacker-group-likely-trained-in-a-cisco-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692735021d6586ddd6c4134e</guid>
      <description>The names of two partial owners of firms linked to the Salt Typhoon hacker group also appeared in records for a Cisco training program&#8212;years before the group targeted Cisco&#8217;s devices in a spy campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google says it will link to more sources in AI Mode</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841603/google-ai-mode-source-links-web-guide</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841603</guid>
      <description>Google is planning to update its AI-powered search feature, AI Mode, to include more in-line links to the sources it's pulling information from. The company included the update as part of a broader change to the way it interacts with sources, saying it will also introduce the links embedded inside AI Mode with an AI-generated [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best doorbell cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22954554/best-video-doorbell-camera</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22954554/best-video-doorbell-camera</guid>
      <description>With a smart video doorbell, your front door's communication skills go from 1980s landline to a modern smartphone. Combining a motion-activated camera with a microphone, speaker, and buzzer, a doorbell camera sends alerts to your phone, allowing you to see who's at the door without needing to open it or even be at home. Whether [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is testing AI-powered article overviews on select publications&#8217; Google News pages</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/google-is-testing-ai-powered-article-overviews-on-select-publications-google-news-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074730</guid>
      <description>Google is testing AI-powered article overviews on participating publications&#8217; Google News pages as part of a new pilot program, the search giant announced on Wednesday. News publishers participating in the pilot program include Der Spiegel, El Pa&#237;s, Folha, Infobae, Kompas, The Guardian, The Times of India, The Washington Examiner, and The Washington Post, among others. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Max is streaming an incredible music documentary &#8211;and a slightly less great music mockumentary, too</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/hbo-max-is-streaming-an-incredible-music-documentary-and-a-slightly-less-great-music-mockumentary-too</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbUh2pgkgArA4uwZgYq4uk</guid>
      <description>Some of HBO Max's December 2025 additions are hit and miss &#8211; but its Jeff Buckley documentary is must-see TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit is starting to verify public figures</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/reddit-is-starting-to-verify-public-figures-170000833.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc4332b8-c59c-4012-be05-d35ff61562a7</guid>
      <description>Like it or not, the checkmark has become an almost universal symbol on most social platforms, even though its exact meaning can vary significantly between services. Now, Reddit, which historically hasn't cared that much about its users' identity, is joining the club and starting to test verification for public figures on its platform.The company is beginning "a limited alpha test" of the feature with a small "curated" group of accounts that includes journalists from major media outlets like NBC News and the Boston Globe. Businesses that are already using an "official" badge, which Reddit start...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's house of cards seems primed to collapse</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openais-house-of-cards-seems-primed-to-collapse-170000900.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfe1ecb3-3eec-4be0-ab44-9c420b863a73</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is in a far less commanding position than it was following the public release of ChatGPT a few short years ago.&#160;Back in 2022, the sudden popularity of ChatGPT sent Google into a panic. The company was so worried about the possibility of the upstart chatbot disrupting its Search business, executives sounded a "code red" alert inside of the company and called Sergey Brin and Larry Page out of retirement to help it formulate a response to OpenAI. It then rushed out Bard, announcing its first commercial chatbot on February 6, 2023. Google's stock tanked days later when the AI incorrectly an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici la meilleure enceinte de soir&#233;e de l&#8217;ann&#233;e &#8211; Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2899633_voici-la-meilleure-enceinte-de-soiree-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2899633_voici-la-meilleure-enceinte-de-soiree-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
La meilleure enceinte de soir&#233;e test&#233;e par Frandroid est la JBL PartyBox 520. D&#233;couvrez pourquoi ce produit a re&#231;u le Frandroid Awards avec Delos de sa cat&#233;gorie. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibri is too woke for the State Department</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841664/calibri-is-too-woke-for-the-state-department</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T11:54:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841664</guid>
      <description>The US State Department is turning back to an old typeface in its latest quest to tear up anything related to diversity or accessibility. In an internal document seen by Reuters and The New York Times, US Secretary of State Marco Rubio said that the Biden-era decision to switch to Calibri typeface in official department [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kobo Clara BW : &#224; -20 %, c&#8217;est l&#8217;une des meilleures liseuses &#224; offrir pour No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2905027_kobo-clara-bw-a-20-cest-lune-des-meilleures-liseuses-a-offrir-pour-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2905027_kobo-clara-bw-a-20-cest-lune-des-meilleures-liseuses-a-offrir-pour-noel</guid>
      <description>
Envie d&#8217;une liseuse pour No&#235;l ? La Kobo Clara BW tombe &#224; 119 euros au lieu de 149 euros, une belle ristourne pour s&#8217;offrir (ou offrir) une liseuse compacte, endurante et confortable pour les yeux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petco accidentally exposed heaps of customer information</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/petco-accidentally-exposed-heaps-of-customer-information-163825302.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3afc80ac-2ee1-4e7b-a2d4-e3fb9d4b62e7</guid>
      <description>Petco has accidentally exposed a whole lot of customer data and personal information, according to a report by TechCrunch. This is thanks to a security lapse involving its Vetco clinics website, forcing the company to take a portion of that site offline.
Petco has confirmed the leak and TechCrunch noted that the security lapse allowed anyone to download customer records without login information. The exposed data includes customer names, driver's license numbers, dates of birth, Social Security numbers and even financial information. It also includes customer records from visits to Vetco, like...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need AI training? CEOs think you should train yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/need-ai-training-ceos-think-you-should-train-yourself</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YW47KnLuBCTRxaZwkSBUYD</guid>
      <description>Employees say employers should provide AI training, CEOs say staff should be responsible for upskilling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This tiny chip could single-handedly solve the RAM shortage by allowing hyperscalers to reuse old DDR4 memory via CXL &#8212; and it comes with an extraordinary feature</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-tiny-chip-could-singlehandedly-solve-the-ram-shortage-by-allowing-hyperscalers-to-reuse-old-ddr4-memory-via-cxl-and-it-even-comes-with-an-extraordinary-feature</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BA9qGVHySQUnL7dyYbGpt9</guid>
      <description>Structera X 2404 enables hyperscalers to reuse DDR4 modules with compression, but latency remains untested under real workloads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chatbots are struggling with suicide hotline numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/841610/ai-chatbot-suicide-safety-failure</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T11:32:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841610</guid>
      <description>Last week, I told multiple AI chatbots I was struggling, considering self-harm, and in need of someone to talk to. Fortunately, I didn't feel this way, nor did I need someone to talk to, but of the millions of people turning to AI with mental health challenges, some are struggling and need support. Chatbot companies [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Taylor Swift Is a Nazi&#8217; Claims Were Spurred by a Coordinated Bot Attack, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/taylor-swift-is-a-nazi-claims-were-spurred-by-a-coordinated-bot-attack-study-finds-2000697793</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697793</guid>
      <description>Bots manipulated online discourse to convince people that Taylor Swift was MAGA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Echo Spot is just $45, beating its Black Friday price</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/841593/amazon-echo-spot-nintendo-joy-con-2-wheel-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T11:26:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841593</guid>
      <description>If you want a cheap gift that feels expensive, the Echo Spot is a great pick. The versatile smart display can handle dozens of everyday tasks, and right now it&#8217;s back at its all-time low of $44.99 ($35 off) at Amazon, Target, and Best Buy. That actually beats its Black Friday and Cyber Monday pricing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon changes how copyright protection is applied to Kindle Direct&#8217;s self-published ebooks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/amazon-changes-how-copyright-protection-is-applied-to-kindle-directs-self-published-ebooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074447</guid>
      <description>Amazon says its Kindle Direct DRM-free titles will be available as PDFs and EPUB files going forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marre de voir n&#8217;importe quoi dans vos Reels&#160;? Instagram pr&#233;pare un changement majeur</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/marre-voir-nimporte-quoi-dans-reels-instagram-prepare-changement-majeur.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314860</guid>
      <description>Instagram ajoute un nouvel outil pour vous aider &#224; reprendre la main sur les vid&#233;os propos&#233;es dans l&#8217;onglet Reels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu la voiture &#233;lectrique chinoise &#224; 25 000 &#8364; en version rallye pour inqui&#233;ter Renault et Alpine : la Nio Firefly Rally Concept</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nio/2892759_on-a-vu-la-voiture-electrique-chinoise-a-25-000-e-en-version-rallye-pour-inquieter-renault-et-alpine-la-nio-firefly-rally-concept</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nio/2892759_on-a-vu-la-voiture-electrique-chinoise-a-25-000-e-en-version-rallye-pour-inquieter-renault-et-alpine-la-nio-firefly-rally-concept</guid>
      <description>
On a vu en Chine la nouvelle voiture &#233;lectrique de Nio &#224; bas prix, en version rallye. La Firefly, qui arrive en Europe, donne encore plus envie avec cette version. Voici tout ce qu'il faut savoir.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 inspired gift ideas for the music lover in your life, hand-picked by an audio expert</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/9-inspired-gift-ideas-for-the-music-lover-in-your-life-hand-picked-by-an-audio-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">G2RYFWvisPAysPsXvn4ePS</guid>
      <description>Know a music-lover and looking for inspiration on what to buy them? Have a look at this little lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't afford to build your PC? This Alienware Aurora with an RTX 5080 is just $1,849 today</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/cant-afford-to-build-your-pc-this-alienware-aurora-with-an-rtx-5080-is-just-usd1-849-today</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FRxPqwZtg5R3u2iGk9RT7g</guid>
      <description>RAM prices getting you down? A massive $630 price cut on this Alienware Aurora with an RTX 5080 makes it a compelling option.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Si j&#8217;avais su&#8230;&#160;&#187; : la douche froide pour ces propri&#233;taires de Renault 5 &#233;lectrique qui d&#233;couvrent une erreur majeure apr&#232;s l&#8217;achat</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/renault/2905257_si-javais-su-la-douche-froide-pour-ces-proprietaires-de-renault-5-electrique-qui-decouvrent-une-erreur-majeure-apres-lachat</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/renault/2905257_si-javais-su-la-douche-froide-pour-ces-proprietaires-de-renault-5-electrique-qui-decouvrent-une-erreur-majeure-apres-lachat</guid>
      <description>
Des propri&#233;taires de la Renault 5 E-Tech d&#233;couvrent apr&#232;s livraison qu'ils ne peuvent pas utiliser les bornes de recharge rapide. Un d&#233;faut de conseil qui expose les limites de la finition Five, pens&#233;e pour les flottes d'entreprises, et r&#233;v&#232;le un probl&#232;me plus large : la formation insuffisante des commerciaux sur la voiture &#233;lectrique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate leaders and investors enthusiastic about AI - but the public isn't so convinced</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/corporate-leaders-and-investors-enthusiastic-about-ai-but-the-public-isnt-so-convinced</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HCu9XEaVVHDZKJ54DWVEpR</guid>
      <description>Investors are largely optimistic about AI, but they share some of the same concerns as the general public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger n&#8217;h&#233;site pas &#224; baisser le prix des AirPods Pro 3 avec un code promo sp&#233;cial No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2862267_boulanger-nhesite-pas-a-baisser-le-prix-des-airpods-pro-3-avec-un-code-promo-special-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2862267_boulanger-nhesite-pas-a-baisser-le-prix-des-airpods-pro-3-avec-un-code-promo-special-noel</guid>
      <description>
Les AirPods Pro 3 cumulent les qualit&#233;s : performance acoustique, r&#233;duction de bruit active, autonomie, int&#233;gration dans l'&#233;cosyst&#232;me Apple... Ils cochent toutes les cases. En ce moment, vous trouverez ces AirPods Pro 3 &#224; 229 euros au lieu de 249 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le flop monumental des manuels scolaires g&#233;n&#233;r&#233;s par IA en Cor&#233;e du Sud</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-flop-monumental-des-manuels-scolaires-generes-par-ia-en-coree-du-sud.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1314870</guid>
      <description>Cela avait tout de la fausse bonne id&#233;e. Le gouvernement cor&#233;en a investi plus de 800 millions de dollars dans un programme visant &#224; produire des manuels scolaires et des documents &#233;ducatifs avec l&#8217;aide de l&#8217;IA g&#233;n&#233;rative. L&#8217;id&#233;e partait d&#8217;une bonne intention : personnaliser l&#8217;apprentissage en fonction des &#233;l&#232;ves, all&#233;ger la charge des enseignants et pr&#233;venir les risques de d&#233;crochage. Mais tout ne s&#8217;est pas pass&#233; comme esp&#233;r&#233;....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 400,000-Year-Old Campfire Could Rewrite Human History</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-400000-year-old-campfire-could-rewrite-human-history-2000697601</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697601</guid>
      <description>Humans likely harvested their first flames from wildfire. When they learned to make it themselves, it changed everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best board games to gift for the 2025 holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-board-games-to-gift-for-the-2025-holiday-season-125529024.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b67d713-c1e1-4ea2-a3a8-ab47cde9ad9f</guid>
      <description>It's become cliche to say that we live in a golden age of board games, but to paraphrase the great stoic philosopher Andy Bernard, it's great to know you're in the good old days before you've left them. Great titles are still coming out by the thousands every year, from crowd-pleasing party games to genre-bending, theme-heavy Euros. Whether the gamer in your life is looking for a mind-warping challenge, a fun evening with friends or something in-between, we've got new releases or old favorites they'll love.
The best board games to gift (and play)




























Check out the rest ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Champion Has Already Filmed &#8216;More Than a Little&#8217; of &#8216;Avatar 4&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jack-champion-avatar-4-scenes-spider-2000697806</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697806</guid>
      <description>The 'Avatar: Fire and Ash' star gives us an update on how the next 'Avatar' is progressing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DHS Data Grab Is Putting US Citizens at Risk</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/dhs-data-grab-putting-us-citizens-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6937097183201b0c458b699f</guid>
      <description>As the US government rapidly merges data from across agencies in service of draconian immigration policies, citizens increasingly risk being caught up as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No one knows what to call these things</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/841536/smart-glasses-ai-glasses-xr-ar-headsets-terminology-wearables</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841536</guid>
      <description>I asked a simple question at Google's Project Aura demo last week. What do you call these things? To my surprise, multiple people launched into a vigorous discussion on the taxonomy of glasses-shaped face computers. It turns out "smart glasses" is out as a term. The term "AI glasses" is in. Kind of. Actually, it [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are no good outcomes for the Warner Bros. sale</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/841581/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-skydance-ellison-hostile-bid</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841581</guid>
      <description>Netflix is the frontrunner to become Warner Bros.' new owner, but the war for control of the legacy studio isn't over just yet. Paramount Skydance has made its own outsize offer for the company that would give CEO David Ellison even more control over the news and entertainment landscape. And while Warner Bros. Discovery has [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Real Madrid vs Man City: free streams, TV details for Champions League 2025/26 game</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/real-madrid-vs-manchester-city-champions-league-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ShEndfWVdTii4BreCUYzvA</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Real Madrid vs Man City live streams online, with Kylian Mbappe set to target Josko Guardiol and Ruben Dias again at the Bernabeu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pixel Watch 4 is getting new one-handed gestures and better smart replies</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841514/pixel-watch-4-gestures-pinch-control-wrist-turn-dismiss-enhaced-smart-replies</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T10:53:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841514</guid>
      <description>Google has started to roll out the first update for the Pixel Watch 4 since the wearable launched last August. WearOS 6.1 is available for the Pixel Watch 2, 3, and 4 models, but only the Pixel Watch 4 will be getting a pair of new one-handed gestures, while improvements made to smart replies are [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Max subscriber sues Netflix in dramatic class-action lawsuit, claiming the Warner Bros deal will cause 'irreparable antitrust injury'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/hbo-max-subscriber-sues-netflix-in-dramatic-class-action-lawsuit-claiming-the-warner-bros-deal-will-cause-irreparable-antitrust-injury</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FbpX3YrWYD3zZdu6mjBsp3</guid>
      <description>HBO Max member Michelle Fendelander has sued Netflix in a bid to prevent it from merging with Warner Bros Discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop comes to ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/chatgpt-adds-adobe-photoshop</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02ElFxYZGStPK0l8sAEgVPx</guid>
      <description>Adobe launches apps for ChatGPT that let users photoshop, make PDFs, and customize other content with the help from OpenAI's popular chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Can Now Use Photoshop and Other Adobe Apps for Editing</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chatgpt-can-now-use-photoshop-and-other-adobe-apps-for-editing-2000697834</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697834</guid>
      <description>OpenAI&#8217;s chatbot just added new integrations with Photoshop, Express, and Acrobat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;application iFixit d&#233;barque sur Android et iOS avec une IA qui vous aide &#224; r&#233;parer vos appareils</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/2905051_lapplication-ifixit-debarque-sur-android-et-ios-avec-une-ia-qui-vous-aide-a-reparer-vos-appareils</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/2905051_lapplication-ifixit-debarque-sur-android-et-ios-avec-une-ia-qui-vous-aide-a-reparer-vos-appareils</guid>
      <description>
iFixit, c&#233;l&#232;bre sp&#233;cialiste de la r&#233;paration d'appareils en tout genre, se dote enfin d'une application mobile. Au programme : des tutoriels, une boutique en ligne et un assistant IA capable de vous guider.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Was a Banner Year for Audio Nostalgia</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/2025-was-a-banner-year-for-audio-nostalgia-2000697474</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697474</guid>
      <description>Never thought I'd say this, but CD players are so back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CloverPit, a Balatro-style game with a grungy slot machine, hits iOS and Android on December 17</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/cloverpit-a-balatro-style-game-with-a-grungy-slot-machine-hits-ios-and-android-on-december-17-154500028.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0d915fa-80f4-4783-bb7d-cdba2cef139a</guid>
      <description>CloverPit is one of my favorite games of the year so far. Developer Panik Arcade took the formula that helped make Balatro so successful &#8212; using various tools to bend the rules of the game to help you rack up obscenely high scores &#8212; and based it around a slot machine rather than poker. It&#8217;s been a hit so far on PC, where it has sold more than a million copies since September, and on Xbox. CloverPit has been among the top 20 most-played titles on Game Pass since its surprise debut there last month. Now, the horror-tinged roguelite is venturing into new territory, as it&#8217;s coming to iOS and Andro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugreen copie le design de Nvidia pour son dock eGPU et c&#8217;est magnifique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/pc-fixes/mini-pc/2905217_ugreen-copie-le-design-de-nvidia-pour-son-dock-egpu-et-cest-magnifique</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/pc-fixes/mini-pc/2905217_ugreen-copie-le-design-de-nvidia-pour-son-dock-egpu-et-cest-magnifique</guid>
      <description>
On va finir par croire que je suis monomaniaque eGPU, mais regardez-moi &#231;a. Ugreen vient de l&#226;cher un dock eGPU qui a tout compris. Son nom ? La LinkStation. Son look ? Un clone assum&#233; des cartes &#171; Founders Edition &#187; de Nvidia. Mais le plus beau, c'est ce qu'il a dans le ventre : il refuse de choisir entre la performance de l'OCuLink et la simplicit&#233; de l'USB4.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Ring 2 shelved? An Oura patent dispute and reported 'underwhelming' sales casts doubt on the smart ring's future</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/samsung-galaxy-ring-2-shelved-an-oura-patent-dispute-and-reported-underwhelming-sales-casts-doubt-on-the-smart-rings-future</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YUPVfyp4xe2ajXhoBd7EtF</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Ring 2 could be on ice, with no planned 2026 Unpacked appearance and a legal spat with Oura hampering the sequel's chances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Lego poinsettia is the ultimate holiday centerpiece, and its under $40</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-10-lego-icons-poinsettia-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00j3lCdsaWErVjJKcnI1tUs</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 10, the Lego Icons Poinsettia (10370) building set is on sale for $39.35, down from $49.99. That's a 21% discount or a $10.64 price cut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 Best Gifts for Mom (2025): LED Masks, E-Readers, Blow-Dry Brushes</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/gifts-for-moms-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5de808cca4136b0008e27b5c</guid>
      <description>From high-tech skin care to cool accessories, these are our favorite picks for the WIRED mom in your life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracker Barrel reveals revenue forecast after 2025&#8217;s logo debacle</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457968/cracker-barrel-reveals-revenue-forecast-after-2025s-logo-debacle</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T15:32:53</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457968/cracker-barrel-reveals-revenue-forecast-after-2025s-logo-debacle</guid>
      <description>The Tennessee-based chain announced its revenue fell 5.7% to $797.2 million in the three months ending Oct. 31.
Cracker Barrel posted lower-than-expected sales in its fiscal first quarter and trimmed its revenue forecast for the year as it continued to feel the fallout from a botched plan to revamp its logo and restaurants.The Lebanon, Tennessee-based restaurant chain said Tuesday its revenue fell 5.7% to $797.2 million in the three months ending Oct. 31. That was lower than the $800 million Wall Street anticipated, according to analysts polled by FactSet.Cracker Barrel said its same-store res...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing markets where power is shifting the most toward buyers heading into 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458003/housing-market-where-power-is-shifting-the-most-toward-buyers-heading-into-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T15:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458003/housing-market-where-power-is-shifting-the-most-toward-buyers-heading-into-2026</guid>
      <description>These 18 states are back above pre-pandemic 2019 housing inventory levels.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La plus haute instance scientifique am&#233;ricaine l&#226;che sa bombe : la priorit&#233; absolue de la Nasa doit &#234;tre&#8230; la vie sur Mars !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/exploration-spatiale-plus-haute-instance-scientifique-americaine-lache-bombe-priorite-absolue-nasa-doit-etre-vie-mars-128427/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:29:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/exploration-spatiale-plus-haute-instance-scientifique-americaine-lache-bombe-priorite-absolue-nasa-doit-etre-vie-mars-128427/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Alors que le secteur spatial am&#233;ricain est chaque jour plus incertain et mouvant, un rapport pr&#233;conise d'&#233;tablir une liste des priorit&#233;s. Et s'il y a une question qui passe avant toutes les autres, c'est celle-ci : comment trouver de la vie sur Mars ?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
