<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:37:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Probe Instacart&#8217;s Al-Fueled Pricing Experiments on Groceries</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/feds-probe-instacarts-al-fueled-pricing-experiments-on-groceries-2000701379</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701379</guid>
      <description>The price is wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A massive new DDoS botnet has already snared 1.8 million devices - here's what we know about Kimwolf</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-massive-new-ddos-botnet-has-already-snared-1-8-million-devices-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CBcFwUGAxbxjPiYdt8BxqE</guid>
      <description>Researchers discovered a new botnet called Kimwolf, allegedly built by the same brain behind AISURU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was &#8216;The Force Awakens&#8217; the Savior of &#8216;Star Wars,&#8217; or a Sacrifice?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/was-the-force-awakens-the-savior-of-star-wars-or-a-sacrifice-2000699725</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699725</guid>
      <description>It's hard to separate 'The Force Awakens' from everything that happened in its wake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Teaser Is Online, But It&#8217;s Not the One You Want</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avengers-doomsday-teaser-online-countdown-russo-brothers-2000701364</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701364</guid>
      <description>The Russo Brothers released a short clip that isn't the more substantial video that should be in theaters soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palona goes vertical, launching Vision, Workflow features: 4 key lessons for AI builders</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/palona-goes-vertical-launching-vision-workflow-features-4-key-lessons-for-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4IfdwhflTGOhmR4uWSifIg</guid>
      <description>Building an enterprise AI company on a "foundation of shifting sand" is the central challenge for founders today, according to the leadership at Palona AI. Today, the Palo Alto-based startup&#8212;led by former Google and Meta engineering veterans&#8212;is making a decisive vertical push into the restaurant and hospitality space with today's launch of Palona Vision and Palona Workflow. The new offerings transform the company&#8217;s multimodal agent suite into a real-time operating system for restaurant operations &#8212; spanning cameras, calls, conversations, and coordinated task execution.The news marks a strategi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media is merging with a Google-backed fusion energy company in a deal worth $6 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/trump-media-is-merging-with-a-google-backed-fusion-energy-company-in-a-deal-worth-6-billion-180910779.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62c70882-77ce-4d7b-8404-4a9ed93f1c27</guid>
      <description>Trump media, the company behind the president's personal social media platform Truth Social, is inexplicably merging with a Google-backed fusion energy company called TAE Technologies. The deal is worth $6 billion, according to reporting by Financial Times.
Why is an entity known for publishing frenzied hot takes by the president at 3AM combining with a fusion energy company? Who the heck really knows, but a statement says the two organizations will join together to build the "world's first utility-scale fusion power plant." This would be huge, if true, as there are currently no operational co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 21-year-old dropouts raised $2M to build Givefront, a fintech for nonprofits</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/these-21-year-old-dropouts-raised-2m-to-build-givefront-a-fintech-for-nonprofits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077076</guid>
      <description>YC-backed Givefront is building a fintech designed specifically for nonprofits, including food banks, churches, and homeowner associations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot Games found a motherboard security flaw that helps PC cheaters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847539/riot-games-motherboard-security-flaw-pc-cheaters-anti-cheat</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T13:01:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847539</guid>
      <description>Riot Games says a security flaw in many recent motherboards could be exploited by cheaters undetected, and now companies including Asrock, Asus, Gigabyte, and MSI have released BIOS updates to address the issue. According to Riot, "had this issue gone unnoticed, it would have completely nullified all existing DMA detection and prevention tech currently on [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 best gifts under $25 for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-11-best-gifts-under-25-for-2025-140042203.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed1a9e09-5eb8-4f57-9f1c-a7a202af8266</guid>
      <description>The most hyped tech is often also the most expensive: flagship smartphones, ultra-powerful gaming laptops, immersive VR headsets and the like. But it would be wrong to assume that those are the only pieces of technology worth gifting. You don&#8217;t have to drain your wallet to get someone a cool gadget that will both be useful and make their lives easier. There are more solid, affordable gadgets out there now more than ever, but that also means you&#8217;ll discover some junk along the way. We&#8217;ve collected our favorite pieces of tech under $25 that make great gifts and help you to stick to a budget.
Bes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Wear OS features you're probably not using, but should be</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/3-wear-os-features-youre-probably-not-using-but-should-be</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wXT2gUWnrXnkz5BwT2pR5n</guid>
      <description>Smartwatches are more feature-filled than ever, but that can make it difficult to know where to start to make the most out of your tech. Here are some features you might have missed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A lot of people cry using the app &#8212; we&#8217;ve had users say it put into words things they&#8217;d been struggling with for years' : Mark Manson on the problem with self-help and why his AI app is different</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/a-lot-of-people-cry-using-the-app-weve-had-users-say-it-put-into-words-things-theyd-been-struggling-with-for-years-mark-manson-on-the-problem-with-self-help-and-why-his-ai-app-is-different</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xdAgWCcyCG9VMijdca7Gre</guid>
      <description>Mark Manson explains why he&#8217;s betting on an AI mentor over another self-help book &#8212; and how personalization may be reshaping the future of self-improvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondhand shopping is bigger than ever in 2025. Here&#8217;s how to thrift your holiday gifts the right way</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462858/thrifting-second-hand-shopping-tips-holiday-trend-2025-christmas-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462858/thrifting-second-hand-shopping-tips-holiday-trend-2025-christmas-gift-ideas</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Thriftmas&#8217; is surging in popularity this year as more Americans facing affordability issues look to buy vintage.
Christmas is coming, and our bank accounts are getting, well, obliterated. But luckily, it&#8217;s no longer just your quirky aunt who appreciates a good secondhand store: Shopping for gently used items, especially during the holidays, is now on trend. And if you get on board, you might be able to save a bundle by swapping your mall run for a day of thrifting.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FrandroidOffreMoi une cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/anker/2915625_frandroidoffremoi-une-camera-de-securite</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/anker/2915625_frandroidoffremoi-une-camera-de-securite</guid>
      <description>
On se tourne du c&#244;t&#233; de la s&#233;curit&#233; pour le jour 18 de notre calendrier de l'Avent. Tentez de gagner la cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; Eufy Solocam E42 avec notre concours #FrandroidOffreMoi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple opens up iOS in Japan in response to new regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/apple-opens-up-ios-in-japan-in-response-to-new-regulations-174854950.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e3fd528-9ae3-4fa5-b524-acc88551b9d7</guid>
      <description>You can add Japan to the list of regions where Apple has been forced to do something it would rather not: open up the App Store. On Thursday, the company announced changes to iOS in Japan to comply with the nation's Mobile Software Competition Act (MSCA). The tighter regulations for Apple and Google, which overlap with Europe's, took effect today. Users in the US and elsewhere won't see any of these changes.Apple's changes in iOS 26.2 in Japan revolve around alternative app stores, payments outside the App Store and browser choice. The company worked with Japanese regulators on new protections...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The JBL Flip 7 Bluetooth speaker is under $100 for the first time</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-jbl-flip-7-speaker-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03P2dBHTt7ytTbNSt7l38MR</guid>
      <description>The JBL Flip 7 portable Bluetooth speaker is on sale at Amazon for only $99.95. That's 33% off and its lowest price on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultra-Realistic AI Face Swapping Platform Driving Romance Scams</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-ultra-realistic-ai-face-swapping-platform-driving-romance-scams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67d9b883d699e181128c195e</guid>
      <description>Capable of creating &#8220;nearly perfect&#8221; face swaps during live video chats, Hoatian has made millions, mainly via Telegram. But its main channel vanished after WIRED's inquiry into scammers using the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay prepared with $70 off the DJI Power 1000 V2 portable power station</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-dji-power-1000-v2-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ZyKGfiuzHFRyX3FwZy28Z</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, save $70 on the DJI Power 1000 V2 portable power station at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Il n&#8217;y a pas eu de nouveau piratage massif de Bouygues Telecom, c&#8217;est un coup de bluff</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2915175_il-ny-a-pas-eu-de-nouveau-piratage-massif-de-bouygues-telecom-cest-un-coup-de-bluff</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2915175_il-ny-a-pas-eu-de-nouveau-piratage-massif-de-bouygues-telecom-cest-un-coup-de-bluff</guid>
      <description>
Sur le Dark Web, un pirate affirme avoir d&#233;rob&#233; plus de 6 millions de donn&#233;es clients Bouygues Telecom. Heureusement, c'est faux, m&#234;me si en soi il y a bien eu une fuite.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidy up your home with the Ecovacs Deebot X11 for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-ecovacs-deebot-x11-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00rHw3HcR9kohHQB3lZJhuN</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, get the Ecovacs Deebot X11 for its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media Wants to Become a Nuclear Fusion Company</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-media-wants-to-become-a-nuclear-fusion-company-2000701354</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701354</guid>
      <description>Trump Media just announced a $6 billion deal with an Alphabet-backed outfit that would create one of the first publicly traded fusion companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Shark AI Ultra robot vacuum clean your floors for under $250</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-shark-ai-ultra-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07hHQnUHziDzjpJFQkje12V</guid>
      <description>The Shark AI Ultra robot vacuum is on sale at Amazon for $249.99, down from the normal price of $549.99. That's a 55% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurry! Claim your free ByteSim for your next trip to Japan exclusively on TechRadar</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hurry-claim-your-free-bytesim-for-your-next-trip-to-japan-exclusively-on-techradar</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KA3Avqro5LsHQe2qpzFRzJ</guid>
      <description>TechRadar readers can grab a limited free eSIM + ongoing savings for future trips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus puissante sans Windows ? La Lenovo Legion Go 2 s&#8217;offre une transformation surprise d&#233;s le mois prochain</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lenovo/2915567_plus-puissante-sans-windows-la-lenovo-legion-go-2-soffre-une-transformation-surprise-des-le-mois-prochain</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lenovo/2915567_plus-puissante-sans-windows-la-lenovo-legion-go-2-soffre-une-transformation-surprise-des-le-mois-prochain</guid>
      <description>
La Lenovo Legion Go 2 pourrait s'offrir une version sans Windows, mais avec SteamOS, et ce d&#232;s le mois prochain.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels Apple AirPods choisir : le comparatif</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1995260_quels-modele-dairpods-choisir-notre-selection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1995260_quels-modele-dairpods-choisir-notre-selection</guid>
      <description>
Souvent imit&#233;s, mais jamais &#233;gal&#233;s, les &#233;couteurs AirPods d'Apple ne sont pas si nombreux. Toutefois, il existe plusieurs appareils audio Apple diff&#233;rents portant cette nomenclature. Vous ne savez pas quels AirPods choisir ? Suivez notre guide !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is our favorite instant camera &#8212; and it's now down to a record-low price on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/instant-cameras/the-fujifilm-instax-mini-12-is-our-favorite-instant-camera-and-its-now-down-to-a-record-low-price-on-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CYa7TqVxkdZsLXMQB2Rm6X</guid>
      <description>The beginner-friendly Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is now only $85.95 at Amazon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For a relatively cheap device, the I found the Alldocube IWork GT Ultra is an impressively specified Intel 2-in-1 tablet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/alldocube-iwork-gt-ultra-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EU4sMABkim9XnbPgVAmN5h</guid>
      <description>The Alldocube IWork GT Ultra is an Intel-based tablet that, with a flexible keyboard, can be used as a highly mobile laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone&#160;: Apple s&#8217;ouvre au Japon et en profite pour mettre la pression sur l&#8217;Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/iphone-apple-souvre-au-japon-et-en-profite-pour-mettre-la-pression-sur-leurope.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316162</guid>
      <description>L'iPhone s'ouvre au Japon sous la contrainte d'une nouvelle loi mais contre toute attente, Apple ne boude pas son plaisir. La firme californienne encense le mod&#232;le japonais pour mieux d&#233;noncer la r&#233;gulation europ&#233;enne, jug&#233;e dangereuse et bureaucratique.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesmate CRM review 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/software-services/salesmate-crm-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CHuhfbZ829QgAxmR2Hwk7T</guid>
      <description>Salesmate stands out with its modern interface, robust automation features, and comprehensive sales tools. While it may be pricier than some competitors, its time-saving capabilities and in-depth analytics make it a valuable investment for businesses seeking to optimize their sales operations and customer relationships. That said, the lack of enterprise-level features may be a deterrent for larger businesses with complex needs....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda reportedly held a secret Starfield event to showcase an upcoming update that will add faster loading times and technical improvements to the Creation Engine, along with a PS5 port that will be announced in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/bethesda-reportedly-held-a-secret-starfield-event-to-showcase-an-upcoming-update-that-will-add-faster-loading-times-and-technical-improvements-to-the-creation-engine-along-with-a-ps5-port-that-will-be-announced-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6GRzMPxkPrzi6jQ4qNRH8Q</guid>
      <description>Starfield is reportedly getting a major update in early 2026 that will improve space flight loading screens and the game's Creation Engine, as well as announcements for the PlayStation 5 and Nintendo Switch 2 ports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple M4 Mac Mini is back down to Black Friday price &#8212; order now and save $120</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-apple-m4-mac-mini-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">061Oev5vXafjqyCPCjTIQbe</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 18, shop the Apple Mac Mini with M4 chip for just $479. That saves you $120 off its list price, bringing it back down to its Black Friday price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save on Crunchyroll annual subscriptions this holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/save-on-crunchyroll-annual-subscriptions-this-holiday-season-194345431.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4b4dd4d-8f13-4ef2-9537-58b9ba035b39</guid>
      <description>If you're struggling to find your next binge-watch, you can't go wrong with anime. For the holidays, you can save on a Crunchyroll subscription, giving you access to its vast library of anime series to watch. Through December 29, you can sign up for an annual Fan subscription for $67, down from the usual $80, or a Mega Fan subscription for $100, down from $120.
While both the Fan and Mega Fan plans are ad-free, you do get some different benefits depending on which you decide to pay for. Fan subscribers get full access to Crunchyroll's library, new episodes "shortly after they air in Japan" and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media is merging with fusion power company TAE Technologies in $6B+ deal</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/trump-media-is-merging-with-fusion-power-company-tae-technologies-in-6b-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077322</guid>
      <description>The merger would broaden Trump Media&#8217;s holdings into the nascent fusion power space while data centers clamor for more electricity amid the ongoing AI boom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best streaming deals this week: ESPN Unlimited bundle, Paramount+, Spotify, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-best-streaming-deals-this-week</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05RJwGQJ0qOPFKQySCKdOGA</guid>
      <description>The best streaming deals this week (Dec. 18, 2025) include the ESPN Unlimited, Hulu, and Disney+ bundle, Paramount+, Spotify, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Live as Interstellar Comet 3I/ATLAS Makes Its Closest Approach to Earth</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/watch-live-as-interstellar-comet-3i-atlas-makes-its-closest-approach-to-earth-2000701321</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701321</guid>
      <description>This will be your best chance to see 3I/ATLAS in the night sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 practical smart home gifts that make everyday life a little easier</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/800449/best-practical-smart-home-gift-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800449</guid>
      <description>Smart home products are all about making everyday life a little easier, which is why they're some of the best and most thoughtful gifts you can give. Some people go all out building a multi-gadget IoT kingdom (like our resident smart home expert, Jen Pattison Tuohy), but a smart home is whatever your recipient wants [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix snags Elle Duncan from ESPN to host live events</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847394/netflix-espn-elle-duncan-live-tv-ambitions</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847394</guid>
      <description>Netflix is bringing ESPN host Elle Duncan onboard to become the voice of its growing roster of live events. Duncan, who has appeared on SportsCenter, College GameDay, and WNBA Countdown, will make her debut on Netflix with next year's Skyscraper Live broadcast. During the livestream, free solo climber Alex Honnold will attempt to ascend the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tin Can has reinvented the house phone for today&#8217;s families</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461659/tin-can-phone-kids-luddite</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461659/tin-can-phone-kids-luddite</guid>
      <description>The throwback phone has no screen, no apps, and no texting&#8212;and&#160;that&#8217;s&#160;how its users want it.&#160;
One hot new phone of 2025 has no screen,&#160;can&#8217;t&#160;send a text, and needs to be plugged into the wall. But to buyers of&#160;the Tin Can,&#160;that&#8217;s&#160;a definite plus.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is &#8216;artificial general intelligence&#8217; an illusion? Yann LeCun thinks so</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462273/yann-lecun-artificial-general-intelligence-databricks-google-gemini-3-flash</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462273/yann-lecun-artificial-general-intelligence-databricks-google-gemini-3-flash</guid>
      <description>Meta&#8217;s chief AI scientist says one of Big AI&#8217;s dearest narratives may be a mere distraction. AI labs should focus on tasks that are specific, valuable, and achievable.&#160;
Welcome to AI Decoded, Fast Company&#8217;s weekly newsletter that breaks down the most important news in the world of AI. I&#8217;m Mark Sullivan, a senior writer at Fast Company, covering emerging tech, AI, and tech policy....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Motorola Edge 70 : ultrafin et moins cher qu&#8217;un iPhone Air, a-t-il trouv&#233; la recette ultime ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2859201_test-motorola-edge-70-de-trop-gros-sacrifices-pour-quelques-millimetres-et-quelques-grammes-de-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2859201_test-motorola-edge-70-de-trop-gros-sacrifices-pour-quelques-millimetres-et-quelques-grammes-de-moins</guid>
      <description>
Le nouveau smartphone de Motorola mise tout sur son &#233;paisseur r&#233;duite et son poids minimal, au risque de frustrer certains utilisateurs, en qu&#234;te de performances, d'une grande autonomie ou encore d'une certaine polyvalence photographique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le meilleur vid&#233;oprojecteur compact de l&#8217;ann&#233;e &#8211; Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2906549_voici-quel-est-le-meilleur-videoprojecteur-compact-de-2025-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2906549_voici-quel-est-le-meilleur-videoprojecteur-compact-de-2025-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
Parmi les diff&#233;rents mod&#232;les de vid&#233;oprojecteurs test&#233;s, le LG CineBeam Q remporte la palme du mod&#232;le compact. D&#233;couvrez pourquoi il a remport&#233; le Frandroid Awards de sa cat&#233;gorie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Chromebooks - this Windows 11 laptop with an Intel i3 just dropped to under &#163;200 at Currys</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/forget-chromebooks-this-windows-11-laptop-with-an-intel-i3-just-dropped-to-under-gbp200-at-currys</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CCi93oxMqiWGa5b9MNHaRU</guid>
      <description>Asus Vivobook 15 is 43% off its usual price right now and it'll arrive before Christmas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go big with this 57-inch Samsung Odyssey Neo G9 curved gaming monitor while its nearly 40% off at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-18-samsung-odyssey-neo-g9-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07lcJjuAbuRSupxoXLoqWcN</guid>
      <description>The 57-inch Samsung Odyssey Neo G9 curved gaming monitor is on sale at Amazon for $1,449.99, down from the list price of $2,299.99. That's a 37% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is bringing back Black Friday prices on its best-selling devices &#8212; 50% off Kindle, Echo, Fire TVs and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/amazon-is-bringing-back-black-friday-prices-on-its-best-selling-devices-50-percent-off-kindle-echo-fire-tvs-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MXfuArSjziZ5muRz54tqhf</guid>
      <description>Amazon is bringing back Black Friday prices on its best-selling devices, including up to 50% off Kindle, Echo, Ring Doorbells, Fire TVs, and more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;De vraies passoires&#160;&#187;: les douanes fran&#231;aises incapables de faire face &#224; l&#8217;afflux de colis chinois</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/de-vraies-passoires-les-douanes-francaises-incapables-de-faire-face-a-lafflux-de-colis-chinois.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316106</guid>
      <description>Absence de contr&#244;le, insuffisance des effectifs : les services douaniers fran&#231;ais sont totalement d&#233;pass&#233;s par la vague de petits colis provenant de Chine, estiment des parlementaires fran&#231;ais dans un rapport. Les &#233;lus listent une s&#233;rie de recommandations pour am&#233;liorer la situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free d&#233;bloque une fonction bien pratique sur ces Pixel de Google</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2915459_free-debloque-une-fonction-bien-pratique-sur-ces-pixel-de-google</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2915459_free-debloque-une-fonction-bien-pratique-sur-ces-pixel-de-google</guid>
      <description>
Free &#233;tend la compatibilit&#233; de la VoNR &#224; plusieurs mod&#232;les de smartphones Pixel. Voici lesquels et comment en profiter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Phone Delivers on Its Promise of Being Complete and Utter Bullshit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-trump-phone-delivers-on-its-promise-of-being-complete-and-utter-bullshit-2000701261</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701261</guid>
      <description>Trump Mobile insists you have a little refurbished phone as an appetizer to the T1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kia and Hyundai will spend millions fixing old cars to stop &amp;#8216;Kia Boyz&amp;#8217; thefts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847454/kia-boyz-settlement-kia-hyundai-fix-ignition-cylinder</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T11:44:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847454</guid>
      <description>Kia and Hyundai will offer free repairs for millions of cars that lack anti-theft technology as part of a settlement with dozens of US states. The automakers agreed to outfit the roughly nine million eligible cars sold between 2011 and 2022 with a zinc sleeve installed around the ignition cylinder to prevent the viral "Kia [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Cheap Phones (2025), Tested and Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-cheap-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a8f727d213ac83aca7f0a36</guid>
      <description>There&#8217;s little reason to pay top dollar for a smartphone. These iPhones and Android devices&#8212;ranging from $100 to $600&#8212;stood up to WIRED&#8217;s testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT calls this mini PC "a steal" while Gemini says it's "insane" value for money &#8212; Meet the $379 AMD Ryzen 7 8745HS powerhouse that AI is raving about</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/chatgpt-calls-this-mini-pc-a-steal-while-gemini-says-its-insane-value-for-money-meet-the-usd379-amd-ryzen-7-8745hs-powerhouse-that-ai-is-raving-about</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yiNEfiKdBSVUCdJ6bDgopG</guid>
      <description>No other deal touches this Machenike AI mini PC for value - and it boasts an AMD Ryzen 7 8745HS with 16GB of high-speed RAM and a 512GB M.2 SSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larian Studios CEO says RAM crisis will affect game development &#8211; but I think it's actually a blessing in disguise</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/larian-studios-ceo-says-ram-crisis-will-affect-game-development-but-i-think-its-actually-a-blessing-in-disguise</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VmkAwQJ9gx8CCfgUkQgEtn</guid>
      <description>Baldur's Gate 3 maker suggests RAM crisis will impact game development, but I don't think that's a bad thing at all.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
