<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:29:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking "5D memory crystal" storage could last until the end of the universe - but will it be able to hold all of your pet photos?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/groundbreaking-5d-memory-crystal-storage-could-last-until-the-end-of-the-universe-but-will-it-be-able-to-hold-all-of-your-pet-photos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rtMpR73hCFUQxufikVqTCQ</guid>
      <description>SPhotonix&#8217;s 5D memory crystal stores 360 TB per disc and lasts billions of years, designed for cold data in data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Streaming Bundles and Streaming Deals of December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-streaming-deals-and-streaming-bundles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">694074197656a254331c40ba</guid>
      <description>The best streaming deals right now are ad-free. Maybe the best streaming deals are always ad-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larian&#8217;s CEO says the studio isn&#8217;t &#8216;trimming down teams to replace them with AI&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845713/larian-ceo-divinity-ai-swen-vincke</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T15:15:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845713</guid>
      <description>The CEO of Baldur's Gate 3 studio Larian has inadvertently stirred up some controversy over the use of AI in the developer's next game. Based on an interview with Larian CEO Swen Vincke, Bloomberg reported that the studio uses AI tools for things like developing concept art and writing placeholder text. But following some initial [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sues five TV manufacturers over predatory ad-targeting spyware</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/texas-sues-five-tv-manufacturers-over-predatory-ad-targeting-spyware-201500248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3454b67-1222-4515-a718-38f90599dc47</guid>
      <description>Behold: Ken Paxton will now demonstrate that broken clocks are indeed right twice a day. The Texas Attorney General is notorious for, well, a very long list of reasons. But in this case, he at least appears to be doing consumers a solid: He sued five television companies for using ad-targeting spyware on their TVs.Texas sued Sony, Samsung, LG, Hisense and TCL for allegedly recording what viewers watch without their consent. The predatory technology, Automated Content Recognition (ACR), identifies the content being played on a device by matching short content fingerprints to a database.ACR is e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slate crosses 150,000 reservations despite waning EV truck enthusiasm</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/slate-crosses-150000-reservations-despite-waning-ev-truck-enthusiasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076618</guid>
      <description>It took Slate Auto about seven months to grow its customer list by 50%, but new reservations appear to be outpacing any cancelations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Burning Questions We Have After the &#8216;It: Welcome to Derry&#8217; Finale</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/7-burning-questions-we-have-after-the-it-welcome-to-derry-finale-2000699510</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699510</guid>
      <description>HBO&#8217;s Stephen King adaptation delivered plenty of Pennywise, but we have some lingering thoughts about what happened and what&#8217;s next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 Best Shows on Apple TV, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (December 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63cf1b483f042fa5827033d7</guid>
      <description>Down Cemetery Road, Pluribus, and The Morning Show are among the best shows on Apple TV this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump&#8217;s anti-DEI policies are hurting Black workers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460876/how-trumps-anti-dei-policies-are-hurting-black-workers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460876/how-trumps-anti-dei-policies-are-hurting-black-workers</guid>
      <description>If you want to understand how the DEI backlash is impacting workers, look no further than the Black unemployment rate. 
When the government shutdown came to an end last month, the much-delayed jobs report for September was finally released, revealing that the unemployment rate had inched up to 4.4%&#8212;the highest it had been in four years. Amid a tough job market and economic uncertainty, it&#8217;s little surprise that unemployment is on the rise again: In the latest jobs dispatch that was published today, unemployment had ticked up to 4.6% for the month of November.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These &#8216;historical tours&#8217; of modern offices capture just how banal work is</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461495/these-historical-tours-of-modern-offices-capture-just-how-banal-work-is</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461495/these-historical-tours-of-modern-offices-capture-just-how-banal-work-is</guid>
      <description>A viral TikTok series imagines how people in the future will talk about multiple monitors and &#8220;circling back by EOD.&#8221;
If you&#8217;ve ever been to a museum or on a school field trip, you may have had a tour guide walk you through a historical exhibit of 19th century households or of ancient Mesopotamian agricultural tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your TV is a &#8216;mass surveillance system&#8217; says Texas, and the state is suing LG, Samsung, Hisense, TCL, and more to stop it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/your-tv-is-a-mass-surveillance-system-says-texas-and-the-state-is-suing-lg-samsung-hisense-tcl-and-more-to-stop-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xdYav5qU5FRGZkEjMN7DyV</guid>
      <description>Texas's AG is suing Samsung, LG, TCL, Hisense, and Sony over their apparent use of ACR to deliver custom content and advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is letting creators make playable games with a Gemini 3 tool</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/youtube-is-letting-creators-make-playable-games-with-a-gemini-3-tool-195500318.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0365c187-d3d8-4a7f-9cfa-e50e11becd24</guid>
      <description>Google's at it again, once more insisting that AI is something people need or want more of in their lives. The latest move comes from YouTube Gaming, which announced an open beta for a project called Playables Builder. This allows select YouTube Creators to use a "prototype web app built using Gemini 3" to make bite-sized games, no coding required.&#160;YouTube is launching a closed Beta test for Playables Builder, a prototype web app built using Gemini 3 where users create games with short text, video or image prompts. we&#8217;ve partnered with YouTube Creators like @sambucha, @AyChristene, @goharsguid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sonos Arc Ultra is back down to its Black Friday price &#8212; don't miss out on this excellent Dolby Atmos soundbar deal</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/the-sonos-arc-ultra-is-back-down-to-its-black-friday-price-dont-miss-out-on-this-excellent-dolby-atmos-soundbar-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ayp6ozsfcHQHPYoY4KVcvN</guid>
      <description>Fancy upgrading your holiday movie soundtracks? There's a great deal on Sonos' superb Dolby Atmos soundbar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crunchyroll annual subscriptions are on sale for the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/crunchyroll-annual-subscriptions-are-on-sale-for-the-holidays-194345327.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4b4dd4d-8f13-4ef2-9537-58b9ba035b39</guid>
      <description>If you're looking for something to watch during a holiday break from work or school, you can't go wrong with anime, and right now you can sign-up for a year of Crunchyroll for as low as $65. Holiday discounts running through December 29 bring the anime streaming service's year-long Fan subscription from $80 down to $67 and its Mega Fan subscription from $120 down to $100. That's either $13 or $20 off access to one of the largest libraries of anime series and movies out there.
While both the Fan and Mega Fan plans are ad-free, you do get some different benefits depending on which you decide to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornhub cyberattack sees some Premium members data stolen - here's what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/pornhub-cyberattack-sees-some-premium-members-have-data-snatched</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zETBPQrSaov6TXTN7cypgX</guid>
      <description>ShinyHunters claims responsibility for the attack, saying they stole almost 100GB of sensitive Pornhub Premium user data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grindr Goes &#8216;AI-First&#8217; as It Strives to Be an &#8216;Everything App for the Gay Guy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/grindr-ai-first-era-everything-app-for-the-gay-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693c41e2199888f1c10473e1</guid>
      <description>After controlling shareholders failed to take Grindr private and controversies over data and the banning of the phrase &#8220;No Zionists,&#8221; Grindr&#8217;s CEO opens up about AI, privacy, and big expansion plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix will soon start airing video podcasts like The Breakfast Club</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/netflix-will-soon-start-airing-video-podcasts-like-the-breakfast-club-193112093.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">863ab051-7436-46a7-b15a-4539dbc82d73</guid>
      <description>Netflix has inked a deal with iHeartMedia to begin showing video podcasts, so the content will never, ever run out. The partnership covers new episodes from more than 15 popular podcasts, including The Breakfast Club, Dear Chelsea, My Favorite Murder and others. Customers will have access to video podcast episodes in early 2026.&#160;
In addition to new footage, the partnership includes a select library of archival episodes from each show. It's worth noting that YouTube already platforms video versions of many popular podcasts, including stuff like The Breakfast Club.
This follows a similar deal fr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold's best feature won't be its hardware &#8211; here's why I'm more excited for DeX</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-z-trifolds-best-feature-wont-be-its-hardware-heres-why-im-more-excited-for-dex</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VjpzcPyTo3SawWwXM2fCEJ</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold is due to merge the mobile and tablet experience like never before &#8211; and if Samsung plays its cards right, it could revolutionize on-the-go productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can pair a tiny wireless mic to this 4K webcam</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845499/hollyland-lyra-4k-uhd-webcam-wireless-receiver-lark-a1-microphone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T14:22:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845499</guid>
      <description>Hollyland, a company best known for affordable wireless microphones that are popular with creators, has announced its first webcam, the small 4K Lyra. While it lacks advanced features like the Insta360 Link's tracking gimbal, it's one of the first webcams we've seen that's designed to improve how you sound by connecting directly to one of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is rolling out Conversation Focus and AI-powered Spotify features to its smart glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/meta-is-rolling-out-conversation-focus-and-ai-powered-spotify-features-to-its-smart-glasses-192133928.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6acac9b7-a755-4ca3-a645-120540a726f4</guid>
      <description>Back in September during Meta Connect, the company previewed a new ability for its smart glasses lineup called Conversation Focus. The feature, which is able to amplify the voices of people around you, is now starting to roll out in the company's latest batch of software updates.When enabled, the feature is meant to make it easier to hear the people you're speaking with in a crowded or otherwise noisy environment. "You&#8217;ll hear the amplified voice sound slightly brighter, which will help you distinguish the conversation from ambient background noise,&#8221; Meta explains. It can be enabled either via...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Bringing Vertical Video to TVs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/instagram-bringing-vertical-video-to-tvs-2000700289</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700289</guid>
      <description>You don't even have to turn your TV sideways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Images s&#8217;am&#233;liore&#160;: OpenAI muscle son g&#233;n&#233;rateur pour r&#233;pondre &#224; Google et Nano Banana</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/chatgpt-images-ameliore-openai-muscle-son-generateur-pour-repondre-google-nano-banana.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315735</guid>
      <description>Face &#224; la mont&#233;e en puissance de Google Gemini, OpenAI continue de muscler ChatGPT. La start-up vient d'annoncer une nouvelle version de son g&#233;n&#233;rateur d'images. Il est d&#233;sormais anim&#233; par le mod&#232;le gpt-image-1.5, qui se veut plus rapide, et plus pr&#233;cis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karl Urban Says Johnny Cage Is the Most Physically Demanding Role He&#8217;s Ever Had</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/karl-urban-says-johnny-cage-is-the-most-physically-demanding-role-hes-ever-had-2000700290</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700290</guid>
      <description>He's been in 'Lord of the Rings,' 'Star Trek,' 'Dredd,' 'The Boys,' and many more, but 'Mortal Kombat II' really put the star to the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE leader at Treasury is looking to buy thousands of ChatGPT licenses</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461459/doge-treasury-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461459/doge-treasury-chatgpt</guid>
      <description>Federal spending records show a Treasury Department official appears to have approved the acquisition of up to 3,000 licenses for the OpenAI platform.&#160;
AI has now arrived at the Treasury Department.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les astronomes se pr&#233;parent : le 3e visiteur interstellaire connu passera au plus pr&#232;s de la Terre le 19 d&#233;cembre</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/3i-atlas-astronomes-preparent-3e-visiteur-interstellaire-connu-passera-plus-pres-terre-19-decembre-128638/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/3i-atlas-astronomes-preparent-3e-visiteur-interstellaire-connu-passera-plus-pres-terre-19-decembre-128638/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le visiteur interstellaire 3I/Atlas sera au plus proche de la Terre le 19 d&#233;cembre prochain. L'occasion de profiter de ce spectacle unique, concernant un astre myst&#233;rieux qui est encore loin d'avoir livr&#233; tous ses secrets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obscura VPN just aced its first independent audit</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/obscura-vpn-just-aced-its-first-independent-audit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uo9bLmqyhbwhwvZsfYNPJH</guid>
      <description>Obscura VPN, a relatively new VPN service for iOS and macOS, has just passed its first independent audit. The VPN prioritizes not just user security, but also complete browsing privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Image : OpenAI r&#233;pond enfin &#224; Google Nano Banana</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/openai-chatgpt/2912641_chatgpt-image-openai-repond-enfin-a-nano-banana</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/openai-chatgpt/2912641_chatgpt-image-openai-repond-enfin-a-nano-banana</guid>
      <description>
OpenAI annonce une nouvelle version majeure de ChatGPT pour la g&#233;n&#233;ration ou la modification d'images.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash rolls out Zesty, an AI social app for discovering new restaurants</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/doordash-rolls-out-zesty-an-ai-social-app-for-discovering-new-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076512</guid>
      <description>Users can view and share photos and comments about restaurants they&#8217;ve visited, discover content from others, and follow people just like on any social network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing market inventory is still rising&#8212;but the pace of growth is slowing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461436/housing-market-inventory-is-still-rising-but-the-pace-of-growth-is-slowing</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461436/housing-market-inventory-is-still-rising-but-the-pace-of-growth-is-slowing</guid>
      <description>In November 2024, there were 196,885 more U.S. homes for sale than in November 2023. In November 2025, there were 120,003 more U.S. homes for sale than in November 2024.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 preview: What we're expecting from tech's biggest conference in January</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-preview-what-were-expecting-from-techs-biggest-conference-in-january-120000768.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2645ab40-20b1-4cf0-bdcf-9e9656c79061</guid>
      <description>CES doesn't start until January, but whispers of the products and announcements that could be in store for tech's biggest annual conference have already started to take shape. The CES 2026 show floor is officially open from January 6 through 9, although the show kicks off with events on Sunday January 4 and a host of press conferences on Monday. As always, product demos, announcements and networking will be happening at the Las Vegas Convention Center and surrounding hotels all over the city. As usual, Engadget will be covering the event in-person and remotely, bringing you news and hands-ons ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundcloud confirms data breach - user info stolen, here's what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/soundcloud-confirms-data-breach-user-info-stolen-heres-what-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Q4zvSYPS6WmCMvbx6etdj</guid>
      <description>About a fifth of Soundcloud's user base had email details stolen, but banking and login information was unaffected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&amp;#8217;s&#160;Kindle&#160;is a great gift, and most models are on sale right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/845546/kindle-scribe-colorsoft-paperwhite-holidays-2025-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T13:32:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845546</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re shopping for a book lover, it&#8217;s hard to beat a Kindle, especially if your giftee already owns a library of Kindle books. Amazon&#8217;s latest sale makes them even easier to recommend: the last-gen Kindle Scribe with 32GB of storage and ads is matching its best price to date starting at $279.99 ($140 off) [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s AI glasses can now help you hear conversations better</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/metas-ai-glasses-can-now-help-you-hear-conversations-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076502</guid>
      <description>Conversation focus uses the AI glasses' open-ear speakers to amplify the voice of the person you're talking to, says Meta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VW Closes German Plant for First Time Ever. Plant Will Pivot to AI Research</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/vw-closes-german-plant-for-first-time-ever-plant-will-pivot-to-ai-research-2000700232</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700232</guid>
      <description>The auto industry continues its push into an AI-driven future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Ellison&amp;#8217;s big dumb gift to his large adult son</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/845532/larry-ellison-paramount-wb-netflix-takeover-oracle</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845532</guid>
      <description>Media is a business about dreams, and Larry Ellison's son is dreaming big. This might explain why the case for Paramount Skydance to buy Warner Bros. Discovery is so incoherent. In October, Warner Bros. put itself up for sale, leading to a number of bids. The two we are concerned with are a bid from [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
