<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:29:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Ross Takes Marvel to New Dimensions in New Graphic Novel</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alex-ross-takes-marvel-to-new-dimensions-in-new-graphic-novel-2000719285</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719285</guid>
      <description>Get ready to fall in love with Alex Ross' art all over again in the upcoming story, 'Marvel Dimensions.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam now lets developers display the exact date of when their game leaves Early Access</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/steam-now-lets-developers-display-the-exact-date-of-when-their-game-leaves-early-access-190413701.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4bb02f5-2700-4e7f-a876-069b3aeead4f</guid>
      <description>Steam is adding a little more transparency when it comes to Early Access games. Announced in a blog post, Steam introduced a new feature for game developers to add the exact date of when their game would leave Early Access and see a version 1.0 launch. According to Steam, this feature stems from developers who requested a way to display an official launch date.
While games still in Early Access give eager players a way to experience the early stages of a title and contribute towards the development, some games have been stalled in this phase for years. With this new feature, players can see a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Over, BigOven: MealBoard is my new kitchen essential</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/mealboard</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nuUCgqvcd3oenjV6WCckxc</guid>
      <description>Homescreen Heroes: MealBoard has taken all the stress out of meal planning and grocery shopping</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test de l&#8217;Amazon Echo Dot Max : la petite enceinte qui voulait devenir grande</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazon/2958305_test-de-lamazon-echo-dot-max-la-petite-enceinte-qui-voulait-devenir-grande</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazon/2958305_test-de-lamazon-echo-dot-max-la-petite-enceinte-qui-voulait-devenir-grande</guid>
      <description>
L'Echo Dot Max est la nouvelle enceinte connect&#233;e star d'Amazon. Elle vient muscler le jeu par rapport &#224; l'Echo Dot de 2022, avec une nouvelle architecture sonore et une puce plus puissante. Ces am&#233;liorations justifient-elles un prix en hausse ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to stream the 2026 Super Bowl for free tonight: Patriots vs. Seahawks time, where to watch Super Bowl LX, start time, halftime show and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-stream-the-2026-super-bowl-for-free-tonight-patriots-vs-seahawks-time-where-to-watch-super-bowl-lx-start-time-halftime-show-and-more-124512549.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b2b14-4380-47f2-9cb8-bd2dfe744915</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Super Bowl between the New England Patriots and the Seattle Seahawks will air on NBC today, Feb. 8, at 6:30PM ET/3:30PM PT. The Big Game will also stream live on Peacock. If you no longer subscribe to cable, don't have access to NBC over the air and aren't currently signed up for Peacock, there are still ways to watch Super Bowl LX &#8212; and Bad Bunny's history-making Super Bowl halftime show &#8212; for free. Here's how to tune in.&#160;
How to watch Super Bowl LX free:




Date: Sunday, Feb. 8
Time: 6:30 p.m. ET
Location: Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.
TV channel: NBC, Telemundo
Streaming: ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette ultra-polyvalente Ugreen de 145 W supporte m&#234;me la recharge sans fil pour un prix &#224; peine sup&#233;rieur &#224; 100 euros</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2968955_cette-ultra-polyvalente-ugreen-de-145-w-supporte-meme-la-recharge-sans-fil-pour-un-prix-a-peine-superieur-a-100-euros</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2968955_cette-ultra-polyvalente-ugreen-de-145-w-supporte-meme-la-recharge-sans-fil-pour-un-prix-a-peine-superieur-a-100-euros</guid>
      <description>
La Ugreen Nexode 145 W est une batterie externe compacte, mais tr&#232;s polyvalente gr&#226;ce &#224; ses nombreux ports de charge et son socle sans fil Qi2 qui vous permet de recharger quatre appareils en m&#234;me temps. Le tout tombe &#224; 107,97 euros chez Amazon au lieu de 179,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026: What time Seahawks vs Patriots starts, where to stream it</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/super-bowl-start-time-livestream-options-patriots-vs-seahawks</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07ov81pxt2frwkzGGXmsrci</guid>
      <description>Super Bowl 2026 between the Seahawks and Patriots is hours away. Here's when it starts and how to stream it live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Black Mirror&#8217; Episode Comes to Life in Alleged $66 Million Crypto Theft Attempt</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/black-mirror-episode-comes-to-life-in-alleged-66-million-crypto-theft-attempt-2000719314</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719314</guid>
      <description>Authorities believe the would-be alleged thieves were being extorted by mysterious figures named &#8220;Red&#8221; and &#8220;8&#8221; who communicated with them over signal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meilleurs aspirateurs-robots laveurs en f&#233;vrier 2026 : la s&#233;lection</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2037272_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-aspirateurs-robots-laveur-notre-selection</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2037272_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-aspirateurs-robots-laveur-notre-selection</guid>
      <description>
De plus en plus d'aspirateurs robots proposent une fonction de nettoyage humide pour s'occuper &#224; fond des sols. Certes, il s'agit souvent de mod&#232;les plus chers, mais aussi plus performants et polyvalents. Apr&#232;s tests, voici notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs aspirateurs robots laveurs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone 17e will reportedly bring some key upgrades without raising the price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/the-iphone-17e-will-reportedly-bring-some-key-upgrades-without-raising-the-price-174154577.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e373b7d1-d365-403e-b60a-4af153cd3866</guid>
      <description>Apple is keeping the entry level for iPhones at $599, according to Bloomberg's Mark Gurman. In the latest Power On report, Gurman said that the iPhone 17e is "due imminently" and will keep the same price as its predecessor.
Considering we&#8217;re about a year away from the iPhone 16e&#8217;s announcement, we&#8217;re due for a successor to Apple&#8217;s more affordable smartphone. According to Gurman, Apple upgraded the new budget-friendly iPhone with MagSafe charging and the A19 chip that's seen in the iPhone 17 base model. The iPhone 17e will also get Apple's latest in-house cellular and wireless chips, Gurman rep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook Reportedly Reassures Apple Employees That He Doesn&#8217;t Want His Friend Trump to Deport Them</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tim-cook-trump-immigration-disagreement-lobbying-2000718266</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718266</guid>
      <description>Cook and Trump seem to have a difference of opinion on immigration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You need to listen to the new Mandy, Indiana record: URGH</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/875469/mandy-indiana-urgh-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875469</guid>
      <description>Often, I focus on recommending older media that isn't currently getting a ton of attention. But this week, I can't stop listening to the new Mandy, Indiana album long enough to even think about anything else. It's early still, obviously, but URGH is my favorite release of 2026 so far. The band that I fell [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can&#8217;t escape the AI slop? Here are 3 handy ways to spot AI-generated music in Spotify, and what you can do to report it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/spotify/cant-escape-the-ai-slop-here-are-3-handy-ways-to-spot-ai-generated-music-in-spotify-and-what-you-can-do-to-report-it</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">S77SuoWiwDyT9ZPouiCjnY</guid>
      <description>AI-generated music is plaguing Spotify for some users, but there are things you can do to spot it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 LIVE: how to watch Patriots vs Seahawks online for free, halftime show, odds, live updates</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/live/super-bowl-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rwLng8rtzMFCSKuhEZqMzV</guid>
      <description>Here's where to watch Super Bowl 2026 online from anywhere as Patriots take on Seahawks at Levi's Stadium, Santa Clara.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
