<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:19:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman is hiring someone to worry about the dangers of AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850537/sam-altman-openai-head-of-preparedness</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-27T14:00:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850537</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is hiring a Head of Preparedness. Or, in other words, someone whose primary job is to think about all the ways AI could go horribly, horribly wrong. In a post on X, Sam Altman announced the position by acknowledging that the rapid improvement of AI models poses "some real challenges." The post goes on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors share what to remember while raising a Series A</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/27/investors-share-what-to-remember-while-raising-a-series-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078443</guid>
      <description>Investors share what founders should remember if looking to raise a Series A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Dolby Atmos FlexConnect to Marshall and KEF getting into the game, 2025 was a great year for soundbars</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/from-dolby-atmos-flexconnect-to-marshall-and-kef-getting-into-the-game-2025-was-a-great-year-for-soundbars</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JAdNisTJSZSCLrVBPiKytV</guid>
      <description>In 2025, we saw models arrive from new brands, stalwarts like Samsung and LG resting on their laurels, and a big change in the form of Dolby Atmos FlexConnect. All in all, it was an interesting year for soundbars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec une baisse de 60 % &#224; la Fnac, la Nacon Revolution X co&#251;te maintenant moins cher qu&#8217;une manette classique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2921395_avec-une-baisse-de-60-a-la-fnac-la-nacon-revolution-x-coute-maintenant-moins-cher-quune-manette-classique</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2921395_avec-une-baisse-de-60-a-la-fnac-la-nacon-revolution-x-coute-maintenant-moins-cher-quune-manette-classique</guid>
      <description>
La Nacon Revolution X offre de nombreuses options de personnalisation pour convenir &#224; tous les styles de jeu. Du c&#244;t&#233; de la Fnac, vous pouvez la retrouver pour 39,99 euros 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel est le meilleur casque &#224; conduction osseuse en 2025 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1368305_quel-casque-a-conduction-osseuse-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1368305_quel-casque-a-conduction-osseuse-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Les casques &#224; conduction osseuse d&#233;livrent le son directement via les os du cr&#226;ne au lieu des tympans. Ils permettent de rester conscients de ce qui se passe autour et sont donc particuli&#232;rement conseill&#233;s aux sportifs. On fait le point sur cette technologie et sur les meilleurs mod&#232;les disponibles sur le march&#233; !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the team that investigates when journalists and activists get hacked with government spyware</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/27/meet-the-team-that-investigates-when-journalists-and-activists-get-hacked-with-government-spyware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076051</guid>
      <description>For years, Access Now&#8217;s Digital Security Helpline has been aiding journalists and dissidents who have been targeted with government spyware. This is how they operate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s been a special year for JRPG remakes in 2025, but these 3 games really stood out</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/top-3-jrpgs-of-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NWpd8c3NkKghYV5EX7sLWb</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;ve played a ton of JRPG remakes in 2025, but these 3 are the absolute best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley players on the Nintendo Switch 2 get a free upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/stardew-valley-players-on-the-nintendo-switch-2-get-a-free-upgrade-174849697.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0feb51fe-1dfd-406f-beb8-c396eb63b87d</guid>
      <description>Stardew Valley is truly the gift that keeps on giving. Fans of the farm life simulator, specifically those who already own it for the Nintendo Switch 2, can download a free upgrade that introduces new features and multiplayer modes. However, fans have reported some bugs following the free release, and Eric Barone, the game's developer that's better known as ConcernedApe, is working on fixes.
If you have Stardew Valley on the Switch 2, you can download the Upgrade Pack that introduces mouse controls to make it easier to place furniture and organize your inventory. The upgrade also adds local sp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zack Snyder Reveals Henry Cavill in the Reeves Superman Suit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/zack-snyder-reveals-henry-cavill-in-the-reeves-superman-suit-2000703752</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703752</guid>
      <description>Merry Kryptonmas? This was apparently the right time for Snyder to show everyone what Cavill looked like in the classic Superman costume.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
