<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:25:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We set some pretty high ambition levels&#8217; &#8212; Lego on why Smart Bricks needed custom wireless charging</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/we-set-some-pretty-high-ambition-levels-lego-on-why-smart-bricks-needed-custom-wireless-charging</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uig5ohAtPzoCiA8wFBJY6U</guid>
      <description>We spoke with Lego about why Smart Play&#8217;s Smart Bricks rely on custom, non-Qi wireless charging &#8211; a system designed to power bricks through other bricks and hint at where the technology could go next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Cowork turns Claude from a chat tool into shared AI infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/claude-cowork-turns-claude-from-a-chat-tool-into-shared-ai-infrastructure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2oiqXhfIlzCRIGWhxJ6uAT</guid>
      <description>Claude Cowork is now available to more Claude users, alongside new updates aimed at team workflows.Anthropic made Claude Cowork accessible to users on Team and Enterprise plans, and it brings the platform closer to being a collaborative AI infrastructure.&#160;For enterprise teams, the change matters less as a feature update than as a shift in how Claude is meant to be used. Cowork reframes Claude as a shared, persistent workspace where context, files, and tasks live beyond a single user session. This aligns more closely with how teams actually operate than one-off chat interactions.Cowork, release...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Spider-Man&#8217; Director Sam Raimi Would Love to Take on Batman</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spider-man-director-sam-raimi-would-love-to-take-on-batman-2000713581</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713581</guid>
      <description>The 'Evil Dead' legend just loves making superhero movies, apparently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's a Ryzen rollercoaster, alright - new figures show Intel struggling to keep pace in the server market as AMD sees a huge surge</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/its-a-ryzen-rollercoaster-alright-new-figures-show-intel-struggling-to-keep-pace-in-the-server-market-as-amd-sees-a-huge-surge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rL9iQbYVQ4c2yKz9JRaCBT</guid>
      <description>AMD steadily gains desktop, server, and cloud market share while Intel loses ground due to performance, thermal, and architectural challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How childcare workers in Minnesota are protesting ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479506/how-childcare-workers-in-minnesota-are-protesting-ice</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T22:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479506/how-childcare-workers-in-minnesota-are-protesting-ice</guid>
      <description>They joined other companies that shut their doors on Friday as part of the economic blackout day in Minnesota.
Since the Trump administration deployed 2,000 immigration officers to Minneapolis a few weeks ago, childcare workers have been on high alert. Immigration officers have shown up at childcare centers across Minnesota, leaving many childcare workers scared to show up for work. Childcare providers, who have long faced funding challenges and staffing shortages, are now being forced to figure out how to protect their workers while continuing to provide an essential service to families.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Uncanny Valley&#8217;: Donald Trump&#8217;s Davos Drama, AI Midterms, and ChatGPT&#8217;s Last Resort</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-trump-davos-ice-ai-midterms-chatgpt-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69713a93fd4fefc4b1451036</guid>
      <description>On this episode of Uncanny Valley, our hosts unpack the news from Davos, where Trump and major AI companies shared the stage at the World Economic Forum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Judge Rules ICE Raids Require Judicial Warrants, Contradicting Secret ICE Memo</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/us-judge-rules-ice-raids-require-judicial-warrants-contradicting-secret-ice-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6973c859092d3a44d5792e04</guid>
      <description>The ruling in federal court in Minnesota lands as Immigration and Customs Enforcement faces scrutiny over an internal memo claiming judge-signed warrants aren&#8217;t needed to enter homes without consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung and Sandisk are set to integrate rival HBF technology into AI products from Nvidia, AMD, and Google within 24 months, and that's a huge deal</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/samsung-and-sandisk-are-set-to-integrate-rival-hbf-technology-into-ai-products-from-nvidia-amd-and-google-within-24-months-and-thats-a-huge-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WGHr9VHwSLPbf5B8LP9Cnc</guid>
      <description>HBF stacks multiple 3D NAND dies to provide high-capacity, high-bandwidth memory for AI accelerators, complementing HBM for GPUs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress doesn&#8217;t seem to know if the TikTok deal complies with its law</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866977/tiktok-deal-congress-china</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T17:08:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866977</guid>
      <description>TikTok finally closed a deal meant to bring it into compliance with the law that should have banned it a year ago, and the lawmakers who passed that law still don't seem to know what's going on. The company announced Tuesday that its US service is now part of the separate TikTok USDS Joint Venture [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Appears to Have Moved Its Robotaxi Safety Monitors to a More Sneaky Location</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-appears-to-have-moved-its-robotaxi-safety-monitors-to-a-more-sneaky-location-2000713566</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713566</guid>
      <description>Just what everyone wants, their own personal tail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audeze is upgrading its legendary LCD headphones range with its new SLAM tech for silky bass &#8212; these promise 'mastering-grade precision', with a price to match</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/headphones/audeze-lcd-5s-with-slam</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HCKwaMqnDzJ93FCvFFRdU8</guid>
      <description>Audeze makes its highly acclaimed planars even more desirable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babbel helps you travel beyond tourist mode</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-23-babbel-language-learning-lifetime-subscription-all-languages</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03xqBMBnGI1cADL2vxLOcKG</guid>
      <description>Babbel helps you learn 14 different languages, and a lifetime subscription is available now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo probed by National Transportation Safety Board over illegal school bus behavior</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/waymo-probed-by-national-transportation-safety-board-over-illegal-school-bus-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085535</guid>
      <description>The NTSB joins the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in investigating Waymo vehicles illegally passing stopped school buses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Photos can now turn you into a meme</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-photos-can-now-turn-you-into-a-meme-213930935.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84b0ee39-a76c-455a-881d-868a3836dde6</guid>
      <description>In Big Tech's never-ending quest to increase AI adoption, Google has unveiled a meme generator. The new Google Photos feature, Me Meme, lets you create personalized memes starring a synthetic version of you.Google describes Me Meme as "a simple way to explore with your photos and create content that's ready to share with friends and family." You can choose from a variety of templates or "upload your own funny picture" to use in their place.The feature isn't live for everyone yet, so you may not yet have access to it. (A Google representative told TechCrunch that the feature will roll out to An...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now That &#8216;Sinners&#8217; Broke Oscars Records, Warner Bros. Really Wants You to See It in Theaters Again</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sinners-oscars-record-imax-rerelease-2000713578</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713578</guid>
      <description>Ryan Coogler's extremely nominated vampire sensation will give audiences yet another chance to experience it in 70mm IMAX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Pepper used a TikTok creator&#8217;s jingle. Now everyone wants to get in on the act</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480175/dr-pepper-used-a-tiktok-creators-jingle-now-everyone-wants-to-get-in-on-the-act</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480175/dr-pepper-used-a-tiktok-creators-jingle-now-everyone-wants-to-get-in-on-the-act</guid>
      <description>TikTok creator Romeo Bingham made up a new jingle for Dr Pepper that was so catchy, the soda company used it in a TV ad. Now, other TikTokers are flooding the app with their own ditties in hopes of the same thing happening to them.
For the first time in Dr Pepper&#8217;s 140-year history, the brand is the second-most-popular soda in America. And now, it has a shiny new jingle to match.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Is Now Collecting Even More Data About Its Users. Here Are the 3 Biggest Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-new-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6973cbc9a24600323e658444</guid>
      <description>According to its new privacy policy, TikTok now collects more data on its users, including their precise location, after majority ownership officially switched to a group based in the US.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
