<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:59:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ten years after The Witness, Jonathan Blow's next massive puzzle game is almost ready for primetime</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ten-years-after-the-witness-jonathan-blows-next-massive-puzzle-game-is-almost-ready-for-primetime-015727378.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c002c8c-bd99-4424-aba9-7d2cf251554d</guid>
      <description>Many of the big announcements at The Game Awards are for completely new projects, some of which are total surprises (if you had an Okami sequel on your bingo card last year, you're either in the know or probably used up all your luck for the next few years). We'll often get updates on games that were previously announced too. The trailer for Order of the Sinking Star is something a little different, as it's a game that Braid designer Jonathan Blow has been working on fairly openly since releasing The Witness in 2016.&#160;The trailer revealed some new details, including confirmation of the expected...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Star Wars game is the spiritual successor to Knights of the Old Republic</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/843188/star-wars-fate-of-the-old-republic-casey-hudson</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T20:48:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843188</guid>
      <description>The next Star Wars game is coming from the director of Mass Effect and Knights of the Old Republic. Star Wars: Fate of the Old Republic was revealed during The Game Awards with a brief trailer that got Geoff Keighley so excited his voice started cracking. Like any announcement trailer, it was brief, featuring a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World launches its &#8216;super app,&#8217; including crypto pay and encrypted chat features</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/world-launches-its-super-app-including-crypto-pay-and-encrypted-chat-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074899</guid>
      <description>Tools for Humanity, the company behind the app, is seeking to expand its "real human network."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coven of the Chicken Foot is the debut game from Naughty Dog alum Bruce Straley's indie studio</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/coven-of-the-chicken-foot-is-the-debut-game-from-naughty-dog-alum-bruce-straleys-indie-studio-014004553.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eae4a882-5cbf-42b2-857c-75b244e87cb1</guid>
      <description>Coven of the Chicken Foot has a lot of things going for it already, in my book. It stars a hero rarely seen in video games, an elderly woman, and it has gorgeous storybook-style art in a lush fantasy setting. It&#8217;s a single-player puzzle platformer, it relies on wordless storytelling and the woman, a witch named Gertie, travels with a creepy-cute companion. Plus, Gertie has chicken feet. I love her little chicken feet.Coven of the Chicken Foot is the first game from Wildflower Interactive, the independent studio founded by Naughty Dog veteran Bruce Straley. The game is coming to Steam and it&#8217;s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: Fate of the Old Republic is a new action RPG from the director of Mass Effect and KOTOR</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/star-wars-fate-of-the-old-republic-is-a-new-action-rpg-from-the-director-of-mass-effect-and-kotor-012913046.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3b8d05-5074-490e-9753-14ed9811a7c5</guid>
      <description>The Game Awards kicked off with a bang, showing the world premiere of Star Wars: Fate of the Old Republic. It's a brand new action role-playing game that will be directed by Casey Hudson, who previously headed up several notable BioWare games you probably know like Mass Effect and&#160;Star Wars: Knight of the Old Republic.There&#8217;s not much to go on in the trailer, but the game simply existing is a pretty great surprise and this cinematic trailer sure looks shiny. Hudson is working with Arcanaut Studios on this project, which is described as &#8220;an epic interactive adventure across a galaxy on the brin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Old Republic Returns to &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Video Games</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-fate-of-the-old-republic-announcement-trailer-game-awards-2000698818</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698818</guid>
      <description>Expected to see the 'Knights of the Old Republic' remake at the Game Awards tonight? Too bad: have a *brand new* game instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs AI executive order pushing to ban state laws</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/841817/trump-signs-ai-executive-order-pushing-to-ban-state-laws</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T20:18:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841817</guid>
      <description>On Thursday evening, with White House AI and crypto czar David Sacks looking over his shoulder, Donald Trump signed an executive order aiming to grab unilateral power over regulating artificial intelligence for the federal government. The order can't by itself unilaterally override state AI laws, but it directs federal agencies to take steps to reduce [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capcom's Pragmata is coming your way on April 24</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/capcoms-pragmata-is-coming-your-way-on-april-24-010826258.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e9a4087-681a-41a3-8ae4-fa17099d82e1</guid>
      <description>Capcom&#8217;s long, long-delayed sci-fi shooter Pragmata finally has a release date. It&#8217;s headed your way on April 24, 2026 on Steam, PS5, Xbox Series X/S and &#8212; as Capcom confirmed in a trailer at The Game Awards &#8212; Nintendo Switch 2. You don&#8217;t have to wait another four months to try it out, though. A gameplay demo is out now on Steam. It will be available for consoles at a later date.Pragmata first emerged all the way back in 2020 and Capcom initially planned to release it in 2022. After multiple delays, the game will arrive four years later than the company anticipated. This is the first entry in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley the Badger looks like Wreck-It Ralph as a real video game</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/bradley-the-badger-looks-like-wreck-it-ralph-as-a-real-video-game-005634520.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d59164e-4745-4a11-a880-e34a7c131dd8</guid>
      <description>A lot of trailers drop during The Game Awards, but the comedy of Bradley the Badger stood out from the pack. The conceit is similar to Wreck-It Ralph. Bradley, the protagonist of a fictional platforming series, is suddenly transported into the worlds of other unfinished video games; the trailer shows a badger-ified Bloodborne, Cyberpunk 2077 and The Last of Us. He also has access to a kit of dev tools that let him modify these incomplete projects, getting a taste of making a game. As the trailer ends, Bradley briefly crosses into the real world and comes face to face with an actual game develo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Signs Executive Order That Threatens to Punish States for Passing AI Laws</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-signs-executive-order-ai-state-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693760d7532eea46faabbf95</guid>
      <description>The order creates a Justice Department task force to challenge state AI laws and directs the Commerce Department to pull future broadband funding from states that pass &#8220;onerous&#8221; legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stanford&#8217;s star reporter takes on Silicon Valley&#8217;s &#8216;money-soaked&#8217; startup culture</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/stanfords-star-reporter-takes-on-silicon-valleys-money-soaked-startup-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075465</guid>
      <description>His reporting on a Stanford University president put Theo Baker on the map, but his upcoming book may cement his reputation as the rare young journalist willing to challenge Silicon Valley's startup machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australie | Reddit attaque en justice l&#8217;interdiction des r&#233;seaux sociaux aux moins de 16&#160;ans</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-11/australie/reddit-attaque-en-justice-l-interdiction-des-reseaux-sociaux-aux-moins-de-16-ans.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:44:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c499b2d60c943e9eac782ac538740470</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;entreprise technologique Reddit a annonc&#233; avoir lanc&#233; vendredi une action en justice contre la r&#232;glementation australienne interdisant les r&#233;seaux sociaux aux moins de 16&#160;ans entr&#233;e en vigueur le 10&#160;d&#233;cembre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve tested the latest Switch 2 controllers, and this one is the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/791574/best-switch-2-controllers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T19:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=791574</guid>
      <description>If you choose to get an extra controller for your Nintendo Switch 2, you can spend a lot &#8212; and get a lot in return. Buying Nintendo&#8217;s own $89.99 Switch 2 Pro Controller, for instance, will net you the console&#8217;s only wireless controller with a 3.5mm headphone jack for private listening, not to mention great-feeling [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Game Awards 2025: all the news and announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/841973/the-game-awards-2025-annoucements-news-trailers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T19:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=841973</guid>
      <description>The Game Awards are back once again to showcase a metric ton of commercials, provide the gaming public with their monthly dose of Muppets, and validate gamers&#8217; opinions on which title should be named the Game of the Year. I don&#8217;t wanna say it&#8217;s a foregone conclusion what this year&#8217;s GOTY will be &#8212; Silksong [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5.2 vs Gemini 3 &#8212; How the two heavyweight models compare on benchmarks, price, and feature set</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/openai-gpt-5-2-vs-google-gemini-3-how-they-compare</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01UMwrVKhtDUZ08D5OoHNBS</guid>
      <description>The AI race between OpenAI and Google is heating up with the release of GPT-5.2. How does it compare to Gemini 3?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google launched its deepest AI research agent yet &#8212; on the same day OpenAI dropped GPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/google-launched-its-deepest-ai-research-agent-yet-on-the-same-day-openai-dropped-gpt-5-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075457</guid>
      <description>For the first time, developers can embed Google's Deep Research tool, based on Gemini 3 Pro, into their own apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#201;tats-Unis | Trump signe un d&#233;cret pour centraliser la r&#233;gulation de l&#8217;IA au niveau f&#233;d&#233;ral</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-11/etats-unis/trump-signe-un-decret-pour-centraliser-la-regulation-de-l-ia-au-niveau-federal.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:07:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0a6b95f97023ba8857bf7aeca0a2a9c</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump a sign&#233; jeudi un d&#233;cret visant &#224; centraliser la r&#233;gulation de l&#8217;intelligence artificielle (IA) au niveau f&#233;d&#233;ral, avec pour objectif d&#8217;emp&#234;cher les 50&#160;&#201;tats am&#233;ricains de le faire &#224; leur niveau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring home this 65-inch TCL 4K QLED TV for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-11-tcl-t7-4k-qled-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">066xD1rnjZmXgLxROaOk1XB</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 11, get the 65-inch TCL 4K QLED TV for its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
