<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:26:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Black Mirror&#8217; Will Bring More Dystopia to Our Dystopia With Season 8</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/black-mirror-will-bring-more-dystopia-to-our-dystopia-with-season-8-2000708106</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708106</guid>
      <description>Charlie Brooker's series will return to Netflix for another round of (inevitably) eerily timely episodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes Fnac Darty : les meilleures offres &#224; saisir avant le week-end</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_soldes-fnac-darty-les-meilleures-offres-a-saisir-avant-le-week-end</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_soldes-fnac-darty-les-meilleures-offres-a-saisir-avant-le-week-end</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 sont lanc&#233;s&#8239; ! Bien &#233;videmment, la Fnac et Darty y participent. Les deux e-commer&#231;ants proposent des nombreuses offres tr&#232;s int&#233;ressantes du c&#244;t&#233; Tech et nous vous avons list&#233; les meilleures d&#8217;entre elles pour vous aider dans vos recherches !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur&amp;#8217;s Gate 3 studio says it won&amp;#8217;t use AI for concept art or writing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/859551/baldurs-gate-3-larian-studios-gen-ai-concept-art-reddit-ama</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T12:20:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859551</guid>
      <description>Following some controversy, the developers at Baldur's Gate 3 creator Larian Studios have further clarified their use of generative AI. CEO Swen Vincke and other Larian developers held an AMA on Reddit where they answered users' questions about the team's next title, Divinity. They also fielded questions related to reports that the studio was using [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If your best ChatGPT replies keep getting lost, this pin trick will change your life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/if-your-best-chatgpt-replies-keep-getting-lost-this-pin-trick-will-change-your-life</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RBkgJUNX9B9bc2hUeUEKPL</guid>
      <description>A simple text-prompt workaround lets you pin, label, and save your best ChatGPT responses, stopping valuable AI insights from getting lost in long conversations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cdiscount met le paquet pour le week-end des soldes avec de belles promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933945_cdiscount-se-demarque-en-multipliant-les-codes-promos-pour-les-soldes-le-top-10-des-offres-a-retenir</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933945_cdiscount-se-demarque-en-multipliant-les-codes-promos-pour-les-soldes-le-top-10-des-offres-a-retenir</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver sont aussi chez Cdiscount, et c&#8217;est le moment id&#233;al pour craquer sur un nouveau produit Tech sans se ruiner. En plus des remises d&#233;j&#224; g&#233;n&#233;reuses, l&#8217;e-commer&#231;ant ajoute deux codes promo exclusifs pour faire encore baisser la note. On vous a s&#233;lectionn&#233; les meilleures offres &#224; ne surtout pas manquer.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record profits forecast for Samsung with dramatic increase in AI chip demand</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/record-profits-forecast-for-samsung-with-dramatic-increase-in-ai-chip-demand</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8K2ynNX7mXKEpUbD22LkJ</guid>
      <description>Samsung's profits could increase by 3x year-over-year thanks to a surge in demand for memory chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : voici les meilleurs deals &#224; saisir en DIRECT chez Amazon, Boulanger, Fnac, Darty&#8230;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931731_soldes-dhiver-2026-voici-les-meilleurs-deals-a-saisir-en-direct-chez-amazon-boulanger-fnac-darty</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931731_soldes-dhiver-2026-voici-les-meilleurs-deals-a-saisir-en-direct-chez-amazon-boulanger-fnac-darty</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver 2026 viennent de d&#233;buter et pour l'occasion Boulanger, Amazon, Fnac, Darty ou encore Cdiscount proposent une foule d'offres int&#233;ressantes. Smartphones, PC portables, t&#233;l&#233;viseurs, tablettes ou encore casques et &#233;couteurs sans fil&#8230; Voici les meilleures offres Tech s&#233;lectionn&#233;es par la r&#233;daction.&#160;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clicks co-founder explains who its tiny Communicator phone is for</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/the-clicks-co-founder-explains-who-its-tiny-communicator-phone-is-for-170000501.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b747fd19-ae32-4fad-ae62-84f9d8942106</guid>
      <description>Clicks is an apologetically gadgety company, making gear that feels charmingly out-of-place in a world where almost every smartphone out there is an all-screen slab. That was obviously two years ago when the company first revealed its keyboard case that brought tactile typing to the iPhone and eventually other Android devices. Rather than that being a one-off curiosity, the company had two new announcements at CES 2026: a magnetic keyboard accessory that also doubles as a battery bank and small, squat mobile phone with a keyboard. And while there isn&#8217;t a working prototype of the Clicks Communi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un myst&#232;re vieux de plusieurs d&#233;cennies : James-Webb &#233;claire ce qui bloque la formation d&#8217;&#233;toiles au c&#339;ur de la Voie lact&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-mystere-vieux-plusieurs-decennies-james-webb-eclaire-ce-bloque-formation-etoiles-coeur-voie-lactee-w2t8-129862/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-mystere-vieux-plusieurs-decennies-james-webb-eclaire-ce-bloque-formation-etoiles-coeur-voie-lactee-w2t8-129862/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>La r&#233;gion de formation d&#8217;&#233;toiles, nomm&#233;e Sagittarius C (Sgr C), se trouve &#224; environ 200 ann&#233;es-lumi&#232;re du trou noir supermassif central de la Voie lact&#233;e, Sagittarius A*. Curieusement, il s'y forme moins d'&#233;toiles que pr&#233;vu. Les observations conjointes du James-Webb et du MeerKAT sugg&#232;rent une...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Orders ISS Medical Evacuation&#8212;but Here&#8217;s the Real Surprise</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-orders-iss-medical-evacuation-but-heres-the-real-surprise-2000708096</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708096</guid>
      <description>The fact that Crew-11 is the first to leave the International Space Station early due to a medical issue is a testament to the safety of NASA&#8217;s human spaceflight program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats ask Apple and Google to remove X&#8217;s undressing bot from their app stores</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/859631/democrats-x-grok-apple-google-app-store</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T11:55:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859631</guid>
      <description>Apple and Google are being dragged into the uproar around X's AI chatbot that has continued to virtually undress women in images without their consent this week. In a letter to Apple CEO Tim Cook and Google CEO Sundar Pichai, Sens. Ron Wyden (D-OR), Ben Ray Lujan (D-NM), and Ed Markey (D-MA) wrote that "X's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon n&#8217;h&#233;site pas &#224; vendre au rabais de nombreux produits Tech lors des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-frappe-fort-pour-le-debut-des-soldes-dhiver-les-10-deals-tech-a-retenir</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-frappe-fort-pour-le-debut-des-soldes-dhiver-les-10-deals-tech-a-retenir</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver battent leur plein, et m&#234;me si Amazon ne communique pas officiellement sur sa participation, de nombreuses offres et remises sont en ligne pour le week-end. C&#8217;est le moment id&#233;al pour profiter de ces offres Tech &#224; prix r&#233;duit et bien commencer l&#8217;ann&#233;e 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta announces a slew of nuclear energy agreements</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/meta-announces-a-slew-of-nuclear-energy-agreements-165337159.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e68a0765-be33-4a81-9d5f-add709032e20</guid>
      <description>Meta has announced three new agreements to purchase nuclear power for its AI infrastructure as well as the Prometheus supercluster, a 1-gigawatt data center being built in Ohio. The social media giant is partnering with power companies Vistra, TerraPower and Oklo to deliver an expected 6.6 gigawatts of generation to its projects by 2035.
The company's agreement with TerraPower will fund the development of two new reactors capable of delivering up to 690 megawatts of power as early as 2032. The deal also gives Meta rights to energy from six other reactors that could deliver an additional 2.1 gi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Americans should be concerned"  &#8211; digital rights experts respond to the US withdrawal from internet freedom organization</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/americans-should-be-concerned-digital-rights-experts-respond-to-the-us-withdrawal-from-internet-freedom-organization</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FexRucGtDowS6e5eXvrecZ</guid>
      <description>Digital rights experts criticize the Trump administration's decision to withdraw from key international internet freedom organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM's AI 'Bob' could be manipulated to download and execute malware</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/ibms-ai-bob-could-be-manipulated-to-download-and-execute-malware</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AN6voXVdBQNAaDg79zpZAj</guid>
      <description>Bob is also susceptible to indirect prompt injection, but only under specific conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un prix sal&#233; pour la Steam Machine&#160;? Un revendeur a peut-&#234;tre vendu la m&#232;che</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/un-prix-sale-pour-la-steam-machine-un-revendeur-a-peut-etre-vendu-la-meche.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319226</guid>
      <description>Combien co&#251;tera la Steam Machine ? Depuis la pr&#233;sentation de la nouvelle console de salon de Valve en fin d'ann&#233;e derni&#232;re, la question est sur toutes les l&#232;vres, et le constructeur ne pipe mot malgr&#233; un lancement programm&#233; ce premier trimestre. Un revendeur vient peut-&#234;tre de griller la surprise&#8230; et elle n'est pas tr&#232;s bonne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre top des meilleurs PC portables en 2026 : ultraportables, gaming et rapport qualit&#233;/prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/638058_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-pc-portables-haut-de-gamme-de-2019</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/638058_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-pc-portables-haut-de-gamme-de-2019</guid>
      <description>
Vous &#234;tes &#224; la recherche d'un nouvel ordinateur portable ? Entre les MacBook, Zenbook, Dell XPS, Galaxy Book&#8230; il y a de quoi faire. Nous avons test&#233; et compar&#233; de nombreux mod&#232;les pour vous aider &#224; trouver le meilleur PC portable, selon vos crit&#232;res et budget. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Moves to Monetize Grok Deepfake Abuse, UK Calls It Insulting</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-moves-to-monetize-grok-deepfake-abuse-uk-calls-it-insulting-2000708064</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708064</guid>
      <description>It's a smokescreen solution to a problem that isn't going away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the tech and gadgets announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/all-the-tech-and-gadgets-announced-at-ces-2026-130124023.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is upon us. All manner of companies descended on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew were on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we kept tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, LG showed off a wide array of TVs and Lego unveil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin's closest Apple Watch Ultra rival is getting a soft gold revamp</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/garmins-closest-apple-watch-ultra-rival-is-getting-a-soft-gold-revamp</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gVhBdXrBaCXy65V4p3qGwJ</guid>
      <description>Sick of chunky, black Garmins? The sleek Venu X1 is going for gold in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petro-states vs. electro-states: What to watch for the global energy transition in&#160;2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469864/global-energy-transition-2026-fossil-fuels-fight</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T16:36:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469864/global-energy-transition-2026-fossil-fuels-fight</guid>
      <description>Some inspiration for helping fossil-fuel-producing countries transition to cleaner energy could come from Brazil and Norway.
Two years ago, countries around the world set a goal of &#8220;transitioning away from fossil fuels in energy systems in a just, orderly and equitable manner.&#8221; The plan included tripling renewable energy capacity and doubling energy efficiency gains by 2030&#8212;important steps for slowing climate change since the energy sector makes up about 75% of the global carbon dioxide emissions that are heating up the planet....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike acquires continuous identity firm SGNL for $740m in push for next-gen security</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/crowdstrike-acquires-continuous-identity-firm-sgnl-for-usd740m-in-push-for-next-gen-security</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">o9K2NQYC7Aty7J2CcNGKrV</guid>
      <description>SGNL to be snatched up by CrowdStrike in a $740 million mostly-cash deal, and the small team will keep their jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS announces little-known trick to get your 2026 tax returns accepted early</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91472107/taxes-2026-refund-filing-tax-returns-irs-free-file</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T16:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91472107/taxes-2026-refund-filing-tax-returns-irs-free-file</guid>
      <description>Can&#8217;t wait to file for a refund? Qualified taxpayers can start today, says the Internal Revenue Service. Using Free File can help.
A new year brings a new tax filing season. With many cash-strapped Americans worried about their finances, many can&#8217;t wait to file their returns. The sooner you file, the sooner your chances of getting your refund, after all. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the 2026 Grammy Awards see K-pop artists win for the first time?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471935/will-2026-grammy-awards-see-k-pop-win-first-time</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T16:26:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471935/will-2026-grammy-awards-see-k-pop-win-first-time</guid>
      <description>K-pop artists have performed at the Grammys, but have yet to win a trophy.
Two things can be true at once. K-pop is an inextricable force in global pop culture, and it has long been undercelebrated at institutions like the Grammys &#8212; where K-pop artists have performed but have never taken home a trophy.That could change at next month&#8217;s 2026 Grammy Awards ceremony. Songs released by K-pop artists &#8212; or K-pop-adjacent artists, more on that later &#8212; have received nominations in the big four categories for the first time. Ros&#233;, perhaps best known as one-fourth of the juggernaut girl group Blackpink, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Visits the Gal&#225;pagos and All She Got Was This Exotic Eye Parasite</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/woman-visits-the-galapagos-and-all-she-got-was-this-exotic-eye-parasite-2000708043</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708043</guid>
      <description>These flatworms are known to infect mammals like sea lions, but documented human cases are incredibly rare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 coolest TVs at CES 2026 are from Samsung, LG, and TCL and feature wildly different tech</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-best-tvs-samsung-lg-tcl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07F2dcVYJItfHlbNHDI8fDy</guid>
      <description>The best TV brands like Samsung, LG, TCL, and more debuted stunning new TVs at CES 2026, and there's more variety than we expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-blog-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03weFCUbfFvR5jPHEa0V0Ce</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI isn't the only drone maker hit by new US laws &#8211; the world's first waterproof selfie drone could be next</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/drones/dji-isnt-the-only-drone-maker-hit-by-new-us-laws-the-worlds-first-waterproof-selfie-drone-could-be-next</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RHL7BzNdRhErx9v3A9T2YH</guid>
      <description>It's not just DJI that's targeted by the US government's new rules on foreign-made drones &#8211; they look likely to send the promising HoverAir Aqua drone to Davey Jones' locker too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#192; -40 %, ce puissant laptop 2-en-1 (&#233;cran OLED 120 Hz et Ryzen 7) est le super deal des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2759261_a-40-ce-puissant-laptop-2-en-1-ecran-oled-120-hz-et-ryzen-7-est-le-super-deal-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2759261_a-40-ce-puissant-laptop-2-en-1-ecran-oled-120-hz-et-ryzen-7-est-le-super-deal-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
L&#233;ger et convertible en tablette, le HP Envy x360 14 combine &#233;l&#233;gance et performance pour accompagner toutes vos t&#226;ches du quotidien. &#192; l&#8217;occasion des soldes d&#8217;hiver, cet ultraportable complet voit son prix chuter &#224; 782,39&#8239;&#8364;, au lieu de 1&#8239;299&#8239;&#8364;, chez Darty. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes PC portables : voici les meilleures configurations gaming et bureautiques &#224; prix sold&#233;s pendant la premi&#232;re d&#233;marque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935325_soldes-pc-portables-voici-les-meilleures-configurations-gaming-et-bureautiques-a-prix-soldes-pendant-la-premiere-demarque</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935325_soldes-pc-portables-voici-les-meilleures-configurations-gaming-et-bureautiques-a-prix-soldes-pendant-la-premiere-demarque</guid>
      <description>
Bureautique, gaming, AMD, Intel, Qualcomm, IPS-LCD, OLED... Les PC portables sont incontournables dans nos quotidiens, mais cela ne justifie pas de d&#233;penser des mille et des cents pour ces appareils. Pendant les soldes d'hiver, voici les meilleures offres pour faire de r&#233;elles &#233;conomies.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filming on your phone? This DJI Mobile 7P Gimbal Stabilizer gets you the perfect shot &#8212; and its now 20% off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-dji-osmo-mobile-7p-gimbal-stabilizer-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05x8b7K2nNctjkvwwL11qT2</guid>
      <description>As of Jan 9. get the DJI Mobile 7P Gimbal Stabilizer for just $103 at Amazon. That saves you $26 and makes filming on-the-go a breeze.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudways in 60 minutes: The ultimate in simplified cloud hosting</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/cloudways-in-60-minutes-the-ultimate-in-simplified-cloud-hosting</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2kwX6CzYWpQWf4LEyjfoZ5</guid>
      <description>One hour with Cloudways: 60 minutes with a top managed cloud hosting provider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab the Google Pixel Watch 4 LTE for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-google-pixel-watch-4-lte-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07FJDM9C8YI3E5NzKYJmR9G</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 9, get the Google Pixel Watch 4 LTE for 50% off at Amazon, which is its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car tech at CES 2026: Utter AI domination</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/car-tech-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00JS0Yt7pqbRMln581WVSGu</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, automakers focused on showing us the future of cars, but not the cars themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s new AeroFit Pro 2 earbuds are already $30 off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/859486/anker-aerofit-pro-2-earbuds-donkey-kong-bananza-elgato-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T11:04:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859486</guid>
      <description>We saw a ton of cool new products at CES 2026, but not all of them made the cut when it came to deciding what was best of show. One of those products that we nevertheless think holds promise is Anker&#8217;s AeroFit Pro 2, which are wireless earbuds that can double as open-ear headphones. You [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score the Magic: The Gathering Innistrad Remastered Play Booster Box for $181.89</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-magic-the-gathering-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ag9ibWEMnJTd3X4Fa3V6g</guid>
      <description>Score the Magic: The Gathering Innistrad Remastered Play Booster Box for $181.89 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Ahead in Horror</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/horror-movies-tv-shows-2026-preview-2000705076</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705076</guid>
      <description>If you hunger for monsters and thirst for blood, 2026 is going to be an excellently gruesome year on screens both big and small.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Billionaires Panic Over California&#8217;s Proposed Wealth Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/backchannel-silicon-valley-billionaires-california-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695c1dbfb8d433ee584443c2</guid>
      <description>Larry Page&#8217;s apparent Florida move highlights how seriously the ultra-rich are taking a one-time tax aimed at extreme wealth inequality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cameroon vs Morocco Free Streams: How to watch AFCON 2025 quarter-final online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/cameroon-vs-morocco-afcon-2025-quarter-final-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JKfmgYonu27R9JgjaX6iXg</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Cameroon vs Morocco live streams for FREE from anywhere, as Man United's Bryan Mbeumo aims to knockout the host nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 offered a lonely vision of the future</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ces-2026-offered-a-lonely-vision-of-the-future-160000993.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db084e83-b5f0-4086-9ec4-4805e8c05b13</guid>
      <description>LG opened CES 2026 by outlining its vision to reduce the physical effort and mental burden of life. Buy enough of the devices it&#8217;s presently working on and you&#8217;ll exist in an environment of &#8220;ambient care,&#8221; coddled by the machinery in your home. It sounds positively utopian: When the sensors in your bed know you&#8217;ve not slept well and are getting a cold, a robot will wake you with a glass of freshly squeezed orange juice. When you&#8217;re in a rush to get to work, the robot will make you a sandwich for you to eat on the go, sparing you the effort of making it yourself. The more I roamed the halls of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Cameroon vs. Morocco online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/cameroon-morocco-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07t5r4JguQG0uxUo1ZyuBcB</guid>
      <description>How to watch AFCON for free. Live stream Cameroon vs. Morocco in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#8217;s next-generation RTX 60 series GPUs rumored to be on track to launch next year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/nvidias-next-generation-rtx-60-series-gpus-rumored-to-be-on-track-to-launch-next-year</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vBCBkKXmU6pUFcDopSka2J</guid>
      <description>Nvidia&#8217;s next gen RTX 60 GPUs could arrive just in time for GTA 6&#8217;s PC port &#8211; but could the RAM apocalypse cause problems?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget's best of CES 2026: All the new tech that caught our eye in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/engadgets-best-of-ces-2026-all-the-new-tech-that-caught-our-eye-in-las-vegas-200057123.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">289bf078-4351-4457-b4ba-74ba94fb78b6</guid>
      <description>Over 4,000 exhibitors flocked to Las Vegas, Nevada this week to showcase their wares at CES 2026. The Engadget team, as usual, was out in full force covering the show.  The week began with press conferences from huge companies at the show, mostly filled with AI buzzwords, vague promises and quite little in the way of hard news.More than one company even decided to forgo announcing things during their conferences to make way for more AI chatter, only to publish press releases later quietly admitting that, yes, actually, they did make some consumer technology. It's appropriate, I guess, that as ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just traded in my Polar running watch for a Garmin after learning a rather expensive lesson</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/i-just-traded-in-my-polar-running-watch-for-a-garmin-after-learning-a-rather-expensive-lesson</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CzfmVv5Lz7PDKnFqay6qfC</guid>
      <description>Just because two devices should be compatible in theory, that doesn't necessarily mean they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk&#8217;s Grok chatbot is now restricting image generation after wave of sexualized deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471945/musks-grok-chatbot-now-restricting-image-generation-after-wave-sexualized-deepfakes</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T15:52:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471945/musks-grok-chatbot-now-restricting-image-generation-after-wave-sexualized-deepfakes</guid>
      <description>The sexualized deepfakes, some of which appeared to show children, caused global backlash.
Elon Musk&#8217;s AI chatbot Grok is preventing most users from generating or editing any images after a global backlash that erupted after it started spewing sexualized deepfakes of people.The chatbot, which is accessed through Musk&#8217;s social media platform X, has in the past few weeks been granting a wave of what researchers say are malicious user requests to modify images, including putting women in bikinis or in sexually explicit positions.Researchers have warned that in a few cases, some images appeared to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Joy-Con de la Nintendo Switch 2 gagnent des nouvelles couleurs, mais un petit souci saute imm&#233;diatement aux yeux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nintendo/2937329_les-joy-con-de-la-nintendo-switch-2-gagnent-des-nouvelles-couleurs-mais-un-petit-souci-saute-immediatement-aux-yeux</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nintendo/2937329_les-joy-con-de-la-nintendo-switch-2-gagnent-des-nouvelles-couleurs-mais-un-petit-souci-saute-immediatement-aux-yeux</guid>
      <description>
Environ 6 mois apr&#232;s la sortie de la Switch 2, Nintendo annonce l'arriv&#233;e de deux nouvelles couleurs pour les Joy-Con de la console. Mais un souci saute imm&#233;diatement aux yeux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. government is punting on Grok&#8217;s undressing issue</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471550/grok-undressing-xai-trump-elon-musk-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T15:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471550/grok-undressing-xai-trump-elon-musk-ai</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration&#8217;s numerous ties with Elon Musk and efforts to bring Grok into the federal government raise troubling questions about safety guardrails.
Grok&#8217;s digital undressing scandal is horrifying. In recent days, countless women, including the mother of one of Elon Musk&#8217;s children, have found AI-generated and nonconsensual sexual images of themselves propagating across the web. According to one analysis, Grok was, at least as of early January, generating thousands of sexually suggestive, or undressed, images of people per hour. (Elon Musk now says that image generation will only b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slash $100 off the most portable iPad in Apples lineup</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-apple-ipad-mini-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01fyCrgDxQ9e6w1FIWod2uf</guid>
      <description>The Apple iPad Mini 7 is on sale for $399 at Amazon and Best Buy, saving shoppers $100 or 20% off the list price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consoles portables&#160;: Intel veut revenir dans le jeu, mais part de tr&#232;s loin</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/consoles-portables-intel-veut-revenir-dans-le-jeu-mais-part-de-tres-loin.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319205</guid>
      <description>Intel ne manque pas de culot. &#192; l'occasion de la pr&#233;sentation des puces Core Ultra Series 3 durant le CES, le g&#233;ant am&#233;ricain assure pouvoir reprendre &#224; AMD la couronne des processeurs pour consoles portables. C'est audacieux, car Intel a absolument tout &#224; prouver dans ce domaine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of Bank of England's Oracle migration set to triple</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/cost-of-bank-of-englands-oracle-migration-set-to-triple</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WqQWGiYXWLj2tdtciDZaJj</guid>
      <description>The Bank of England initially advertised a &#163;7 million contract to help with its Oracle cloud migration &#8211; that's now up to &#163;21.5 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu le Mazda CX-6e : le plus beau SUV &#233;lectrique est peut-&#234;tre l&#224;, et il cache un secret chinois</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mazda/2937581_on-a-vu-le-mazda-cx-6e-le-plus-beau-suv-electrique-est-peut-etre-la-et-il-cache-un-secret-chinois</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mazda/2937581_on-a-vu-le-mazda-cx-6e-le-plus-beau-suv-electrique-est-peut-etre-la-et-il-cache-un-secret-chinois</guid>
      <description>
Pour survivre dans l'&#233;lectrique, Mazda a d&#251; &#234;tre pragmatique. Ce nouveau CX-6e repose sur une base technique chinoise, mais le design est pur jus japonais. Le r&#233;sultat ? Un SUV imposant, une batterie LFP rassurante, et une gueule d'enfer. Reste &#224; savoir si l'&#226;me de Mazda a surv&#233;cu &#224; la greffe.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can break apart and share this 10K power bank like a KitKat bar</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859493/nimble-champ-stack-10k-power-bank-shareable</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T10:32:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859493</guid>
      <description>Accessory maker Nimble announced a new power bank at CES 2026 that will appeal to anyone who's had to reluctantly share or loan their portable charger to someone else. The Champ Stack 10K looks like a typical 10,000mAh power bank that's jumped on the built-in charging cable bandwagon, but it has one interesting difference: you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illicit Crypto Flows Climbed to $154 Billion in 2025 as Nation States Evade Sanctions, Report Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/illicit-crypto-flows-climbed-to-154-billion-in-2025-as-nation-states-evade-sanctions-report-finds-2000708055</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708055</guid>
      <description>As the Trump administration is adding rocket fuel to sanction enforcement, it's also been legitimizing crypto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Je suis mont&#233; &#224; bord du Kia EV2, et j&#8217;ai trouv&#233; que cette voiture &#233;lectrique abordable pouvait battre la Renault 4 E-Tech</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/test/2937337_je-suis-monte-a-bord-du-kia-ev2-et-jai-trouve-que-cette-voiture-electrique-abordable-pouvait-battre-la-renault-4-e-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/test/2937337_je-suis-monte-a-bord-du-kia-ev2-et-jai-trouve-que-cette-voiture-electrique-abordable-pouvait-battre-la-renault-4-e-tech</guid>
      <description>
Kia s'attaque au march&#233; des petits SUV avec son EV2, une voiture &#233;lectrique calibr&#233;e pour se battre contre les Renault 4 E-Tech et Peugeot 2008. J'ai pu partir &#224; sa d&#233;couverte, voici mon premier avis.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the budget-priced Eufy 11S Max robot vacuum for 50% off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-eufy-11s-max-robot-vacuum-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01A4ewC3FP25pnC4f0xf7Ha</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 9, get the Eufy 11S Max robot vacuum for 50% off at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
