<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:22:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The mother of one of Elon Musk's children is suing xAI over nonconsensual deepfake images</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/the-mother-of-one-of-elon-musks-children-is-suing-xai-over-nonconsensual-deepfake-images-191451979.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6abfc3d7-f6bd-4d1e-85f9-358b68a74ceb</guid>
      <description>Although X removed Grok&#8217;s ability to create nonconsensual digitally undressed images on the social platform, the standalone Grok app is another story. It reportedly continues to produce &#8220;nudified&#8221; deepfakes of real people. And now, Ashley St. Clair, a conservative political strategist and mother of one of Elon Musk&#8217;s 14 children, has sued xAI for nonconsensual sexualized images of her that Grok allegedly produced.In the court filing, St. Clair accused xAI&#8217;s Grok chatbot of creating and disseminating deepfakes of her &#8220;as a child stripped down to a string bikini, and as an adult in sexually expl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover 2000-Year-Old Mummified Cheetah in an Unexpected Place</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-discover-2000-year-old-mummified-cheetah-in-an-unexpected-place-2000711079</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711079</guid>
      <description>The discovery marks the first time scientists have found mummified big cats in the Arabian Peninsula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's cut the nonsense: I've assessed and rated all the biggest iPhone 18 rumors so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/lets-cut-the-nonsense-ive-assessed-and-rated-all-the-biggest-iphone-18-rumors-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rZ5Ffra3nywX5cYDbscmLM</guid>
      <description>There are already loads of rumors about the iPhone 18 series, but some sound a lot more likely than others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Will Keep Warner Bros. Movies in Theaters for 45 Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/netflix-will-keep-warner-bros-movies-in-theaters-for-45-days-2000711122</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711122</guid>
      <description>Co-CEO Ted Sarandos committed to the theatrical window after looking at how much money could be made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI healthcare gold rush is here</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/the-ai-healthcare-gold-rush-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3083413</guid>
      <description>AI companies are clustering around healthcare and fast.&#160; In just the past week, OpenAI&#160;bought health startup Torch, Anthropic launched&#160;Claude for healthcare, and Sam Altman-backed&#160;MergeLabs closed a $250 million seed round&#160;at an $850 million valuation. The money and products are pouring into health&#160;and voice AI, but so are concerns about hallucination risks, inaccurate medical information, and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman Is Tearing Apart His Former Colleague&#8217;s Startup</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altman-is-tearing-apart-his-former-colleagues-startup-2000711135</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711135</guid>
      <description>OpenAI just rehired former employees who previously left the company to work at Thinking Machines Lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego's latest educational kit seeks to teach AI as part of computer science, not to build a chatbot</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/legos-latest-educational-kit-seeks-to-teach-ai-as-part-of-computer-science-not-to-build-a-chatbot-184636741.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55b2488e-c460-4d49-99ec-60dfa20ede3f</guid>
      <description>Last week at CES, Lego introduced its new Smart Play system, with a tech-packed Smart Brick that can recognize and interact with sets and minifigures. It was unexpected and delightful to see Lego come up with a way to modernize its bricks without the need for apps, screens or AI.&#160;So I was a little surprised this week when the Lego Education group announced its latest initiative is the Computer Science and AI Learning Solution. After all, generative AI feels like the antithesis of Lego&#8217;s creative values. But Andrew Silwinski, Lego Education&#8217;s head of product experience, was quick to defend Lego...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frigidaire recall: 964,000 minifridges sold at Target pose a serious risk</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476527/frigidaire-recall-964000-minifridges-sold-at-target-pose-serious-risk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476527/frigidaire-recall-964000-minifridges-sold-at-target-pose-serious-risk</guid>
      <description>Canada-based Curtis International is adding another 330,000 products to the unsafe list after reports that fridges caught fire. Here&#8217;s what to know.
Almost 1 million Frigidaire minifridges are being recalled because they pose the potential to catch fire, according to a notice&#160;from the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC) released on Thursday.&#160;The notice expands an earlier recall from 2024....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon-owned Visible is offering outage credits, too</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863554/visible-verizon-outage-credit-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:41:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863554</guid>
      <description>Customers of Visible Wireless, which is owned by Verizon, may be getting a $5 credit toward their next bill in response to a Verizon cell service outage earlier this week. Verizon customers were offered a $20 credit after the outage. As spotted by 9to5Google, a message sent to Visible customers explains: "Yesterday we let you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about the botched launch of Eric Adams&#8217; new crypto token</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476321/what-to-know-about-the-botched-launch-of-eric-adams-new-crypto-token</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:32:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476321/what-to-know-about-the-botched-launch-of-eric-adams-new-crypto-token</guid>
      <description>Despite claims of transparency, Adams has so far declined to reveal his partners in the token.
For a moment, Eric Adams was riding high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructors at this boutique yoga studio may go on strike</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471697/instructors-at-this-boutique-yoga-studio-may-go-on-strike</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471697/instructors-at-this-boutique-yoga-studio-may-go-on-strike</guid>
      <description>Social media suggests that some yoga teachers at buzzy, trendy gyms make small wages after having paid large sums for training.
Rumors are circulating of potential strike action next month from CorePower Yoga instructors, who say they are paid less per hour than the cost of a single class drop-in fee.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is facing increasing demands to do more for Iranian protestors</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476162/apple-is-facing-increasing-demands-to-do-more-for-iranian-protestors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476162/apple-is-facing-increasing-demands-to-do-more-for-iranian-protestors</guid>
      <description>As Starlink becomes a lifeline to Iranian protestors, some are calling on Apple to expand access to satellite-based texting.
As protests in Iran intensify, satellite technology has become one of the only ways for people in the country to circumvent a total internet blackout and heavy restrictions on phone service. Now, as a number of people in the country turn to SpaceX&#8212;the company now providing free access to Starlink&#8212;there are growing calls for Apple to get involved, too....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel your inner Leon S Kennedy with this slick limited edition Resident Evil Requiem watch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/channel-your-inner-leon-s-kennedy-with-this-slick-limited-edition-resident-evil-requiem-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saXNZLieLyiL3VzMz7fAMn</guid>
      <description>$2,000+ might be a lot for a limited edition watch, but this Resi timepiece is pure quality with some great detail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD CPU users beware - this security flaw could spill all your secrets</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/amd-cpu-users-beware-this-security-flaw-could-spill-all-your-secrets</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3aDSsafWNj2e5LJQNyAKHT</guid>
      <description>AMD gave the bug a low severity score and released a fix, so update now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another fast food franchisee files for Chapter 11 bankruptcy. Will any of its restaurants close?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476442/another-fast-food-franchisee-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-will-any-of-its-restaurants-close</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:25:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476442/another-fast-food-franchisee-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-will-any-of-its-restaurants-close</guid>
      <description>Recent years have seen a number of bankruptcy filings from franchisees of major QSR brands, with many citing similar reasons.
A major fast food franchisee has filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection. The franchisee, Sailormen Inc., operates 130 Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen locations in Florida, and like the franchisees of other big-name fast food chains in recent years, has faced numerous economic headwinds. Here&#8217;s what you need to know....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Sarandos says Netflix will commit to 45-day theatrical releases</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/863511/ted-sarandos-netflix-theatrical-movie-release-windows</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:24:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863511</guid>
      <description>Though Netflix's plan to buy Warner Bros. Discovery has prompted concerns about how the deal might hurt the movie theater business, the streamer's co-CEO says that there is nothing to worry about. In a new interview with The New York Times, Netflix co-CEO Ted Sarandos said that, should the WBD acquisition go through, the streamer [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Creator on Working With George R.R. Martin</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-creator-on-working-with-george-r-r-martin-2000710370</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710370</guid>
      <description>Ira Parker says that collaborating with the 'Game of Thrones' author on their new HBO series has been a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads Are Coming to ChatGPT. Here&#8217;s How They&#8217;ll Work</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-testing-ads-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6969b129d6ddbc660392573b</guid>
      <description>OpenAI says ads will not influence ChatGPT&#8217;s responses, and that it won&#8217;t sell user data to advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads are coming soon to ChatGPT, starting with shopping links</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863428/openai-chatgpt-shopping-ads-test</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863428</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT will soon start showing you sponsored products or services if they're related to your conversation. In an announcement on Friday, OpenAI says it will start testing ads in the coming weeks for logged-in users in the US who use the app for free or have a ChatGPT Go subscription. The "clearly labeled" ads will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases a cheaper ChatGPT subscription</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863466/openai-chatgpt-go-global-release</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863466</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is expanding a low-cost subscription tier called ChatGPT Go to the US and the rest of the world. Go was released in India in August and later became available in another 170 countries prior to Friday's global release. "In markets where Go has been available, we've seen strong adoption and regular everyday use for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PlayStation Portal was my gaming savior over an extended holiday break &#8212; but this one flaw still grinds my thumbsticks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/ps5/the-playstation-portal-was-my-gaming-savior-over-an-extended-holiday-break-but-this-one-flaw-still-grinds-my-thumbsticks</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qHa3WUX8uArasXALNUjzAi</guid>
      <description>I have always enjoyed the PlayStation Portal and sung its praises as often as I can, but its slow-charging battery is a real drawback and became apparent when relying on the device over the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye cheap OLED TVs &#8212; you had a good run, but RGB mini-LED and &#8216;wallpaper&#8217; OLEDs will soon make you irrelevant</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/goodbye-cheap-oled-tvs-you-had-a-good-run-but-rgb-mini-led-and-wallpaper-oleds-will-soon-make-you-irrelevant</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fueC9ULzRtBgJtbw9ESUgE</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, it was clear that OLED TV makers are shifting focus to higher-end, design-forward models. Meanwhile, RGB mini-LED is coming to smaller screen sizes to challenge OLED's dominance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many words per minute can you read? Find out now</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476036/how-many-words-per-minute-can-you-read-find-out-now</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476036/how-many-words-per-minute-can-you-read-find-out-now</guid>
      <description>Your brain slips into a different mode when taking on this viral speed-reading challenge on X.
Put down Wordle. New brain-exercise-for-the-day just dropped.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Reddit, TikTok, and AI are changing the game for substance&#160;use researchers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474911/reddit-tiktok-ai-changing-the-game-substance-use-researchers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:59:58</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474911/reddit-tiktok-ai-changing-the-game-substance-use-researchers</guid>
      <description>Advances in artificial intelligence are helping make sense of these conversations at a scale that wasn&#8217;t possible before.
When you think of tools for studying substance use and addiction, a social media site like Reddit, TikTok, or YouTube probably isn&#8217;t the first thing that comes to mind. Yet the stories shared on social media platforms are offering unprecedented insights into the world of substance use....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z travelers want destinations that haven&#8217;t been spoiled by Instagram. These cities are topping the list</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475874/gen-z-travelers-want-destinations-that-havent-been-spoiled-by-instagram-these-cities-are-topping-the-list</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:55:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475874/gen-z-travelers-want-destinations-that-havent-been-spoiled-by-instagram-these-cities-are-topping-the-list</guid>
      <description>Vacation goals are changing for younger generations as travel-related content has flooded social media and worsened an overtourism crisis. 
Big city or small town? Tourist trap or undiscovered sights? Following an itinerary or spontaneous exploring?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mova Rover Master : j&#8217;ai vu le robot de piscine du futur qui a un bras articul&#233; pour servir l&#8217;ap&#233;ro</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mova/2946081_mova-rover-master-jai-vu-le-robot-de-piscine-du-futur-qui-a-un-bras-articule-pour-servir-lapero</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mova/2946081_mova-rover-master-jai-vu-le-robot-de-piscine-du-futur-qui-a-un-bras-articule-pour-servir-lapero</guid>
      <description>
Mova ne s'arr&#234;te plus. Apr&#232;s son robot aspirateur volant, la spin-off de Dreame profite du CES 2026 pour d&#233;voiler un prototype de robot de piscine pour le moins audacieux. &#201;quip&#233; d'un bras bionique articul&#233;, il ramasse jouets &#233;gar&#233;s et peut m&#234;me transporter vos boissons dans la piscine.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh No, Meta Just Killed Off Working in VR</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oh-no-meta-just-killed-off-working-in-vr-2000711072</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711072</guid>
      <description>The VR dream is dead, but AR glasses may still force us to work two inches from our screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada cuts tariffs on Chinese EVs as part of new deal</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/canada-cuts-tariffs-on-chinese-evs-as-part-of-new-deal-174241990.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95e68105-d4e2-4897-ac41-f9408ab08251</guid>
      <description>Canada has agreed to drastically reduce its tariffs on imported Chinese EVs from 100 percent to 6.1 percent as part of a new deal between the two countries. In return, China will be reducing tariffs on Canadian canola seeds from 84 percent to about 15 percent.
The move is a break from the United States, which maintains a 100 percent tariff on EVs from China, effectively banning them in the country. Mexico currently tariffs the vehicles at 50 percent after increasing its rate last year.
Under the agreement, which Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney called "preliminary," Canada will allow up to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want more people to use public transit? Make it safer</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469963/want-more-people-to-use-public-transit-make-it-safer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:36:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469963/want-more-people-to-use-public-transit-make-it-safer</guid>
      <description>When people don&#8217;t feel secure, they opt out.
If a City is going to operate a multimodal transportation system, then it helps to understand the motivations of people who continue to choose personal cars for their short trips.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Ask SEC to Explain Lack of Enforcement on Trump-Linked Crypto Entities</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/democrats-ask-sec-to-explain-lack-of-enforcement-on-trump-linked-crypto-entities-2000711123</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711123</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Given the industry&#8217;s history of investor-harm... this turn raises troubling questions about the SEC&#8217;s priorities and effectiveness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Huawei Pura 80 Ultra : ses incroyables aptitudes en photo compensent-elles ses nombreuses faiblesses ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/huawei/2859125_test-huawei-pura-80-ultra-ses-incroyables-aptitudes-en-photo-compensent-elles-ses-nombreuses-faiblesses</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/huawei/2859125_test-huawei-pura-80-ultra-ses-incroyables-aptitudes-en-photo-compensent-elles-ses-nombreuses-faiblesses</guid>
      <description>
Avec son capteur de 1 pouce et ses deux t&#233;l&#233;objectifs, ce nouveau Pura Ultra peut-il faire oublier le fait que Huawei ne puisse pas avoir acc&#232;s &#224; une puce Qualcomm, &#224; la 5G et aux applications et services Google ? Pas s&#251;r, compte tenu de son prix tr&#232;s &#233;lev&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X has been down for most of the morning</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/x-has-been-down-for-most-of-the-morning-171843527.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">814237b9-63ca-4ae5-9c95-a454783a5e0b</guid>
      <description>X is still struggling with an outage that has intermittently taken the service offline and made it slow to load for much of the morning. According to X&#8217;s developer platform page,  there is an ongoing incident related to streaming endpoints that&#8217;s caused increased errors. The incident started at 7:39AM PT, according to the page.That roughly coincides with a spike in reports at Down Detector. The issues seems to be somewhat intermittent. At some points, X&#8217;s website has loaded partially and only shown older posts. At other times, the app and website have failed to load at all. As of 9:30AM PT, X&#8217;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After today&#8217;s big memory upgrade, ChatGPT can now remember conversations from a year ago, and link you directly to them</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/after-todays-big-memory-upgrade-chatgpt-can-now-remember-conversations-from-a-year-ago-and-link-you-directly-to-them</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5WAGZJ45crKWBdyiUT9Xxg</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT&#8217;s new memory upgrade lets Plus and Pro users instantly revisit conversations from a year ago &#8212; complete with direct links to the original chats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Soundcores C30i open earbuds while theyre down to their best price ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-16-soundcore-c30i-open-earbuds-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00REpn2EXCFmx7kkFz7bLUX</guid>
      <description>The Soundcore C30i open earbuds are on sale for only $34.99 at Amazon. That's 50% off their usual price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get a leg up on the competition with the Alienware AW3423DWF QD-OLED gaming monitor for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-16-alienware-gaming-monitor-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05U9ronKdomF4TC3NcxcTOY</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 16, get the Alienware AW3423DWF QD-OLED gaming monitor for its lowest price yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quand Google cesse d&#8217;envoyer des lecteurs aux sites web</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/quand-google-cesse-denvoyer-des-lecteurs-aux-sites-web.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320788</guid>
      <description>Google a beau s&#8217;en d&#233;fendre, le constat est sans appel : le moteur de recherche renvoie de moins en moins de trafic vers les sites web. En cause, notamment, ses r&#233;sum&#233;s g&#233;n&#233;r&#233;s par intelligence artificielle, qui fournissent des r&#233;ponses sans n&#233;cessiter le moindre clic. En coulisses, les &#233;diteurs prennent acte de cette &#233;rosion et tentent, tant bien que mal, de pr&#233;parer un avenir o&#249; Google ne sera plus un passage oblig&#233;....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
