<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:50:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>'Super-fast dryers often dry hair quickly but without smoothness' &#8212; a GHD exec on how the brand created a hair dryer that combines power and control</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/hair-care/super-fast-dryers-often-dry-hair-quickly-but-without-smoothness-a-ghd-exec-on-how-the-brand-managed-to-create-a-hair-dryer-that-combines-power-and-control</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sQTqZ7vk3exis7QsnPQQ4k</guid>
      <description>The GHD Speed has an intriguing 'halo' feature designed to deliver extra control and prevent heat damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon cans a major warehouse robotics project &#8212; but Blue Jay will live on, with new robots set to come soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amazon-cans-a-major-warehouse-robotics-project-but-blue-jay-will-live-on-with-new-robots-set-to-come-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hVCnRCHGQBQ2jsFCskT2va</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#8217;s Blue Jay robotics project ended quickly, but Vulcan demonstrates advanced dual-arm AI handling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webb Just Spent 17 Hours Staring at Uranus&#8212;and Found Its Auroras Are Even Weirder Than We Thought</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/webb-just-spent-17-hours-staring-at-uranus-and-found-its-auroras-are-even-weirder-than-we-thought-2000724794</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724794</guid>
      <description>The telescope observed the ice giant for a full rotation, revealing how temperature and charged particles vary with altitude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America desperately needs new privacy laws</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/882516/privacy-laws-america</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882516</guid>
      <description>This is The Stepback, a weekly newsletter breaking down one essential story from the tech world. For more on the dire state of tech regulation, follow Adi Robertson. The Stepback arrives in our subscribers' inboxes at 8AM ET. Opt in for The Stepback here. How it started In 1973, long before the modern digital era, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe camera shootout: Camp Snap Pro vs. Flashback One35 V2</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/882641/camp-snap-pro-flashback-one35-v2-digicam-camera-comparison-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882641</guid>
      <description>There's been a surge of interest over the last few years in inexpensive digital cameras. Younger folks are snapping up old point-and-shoots because they view the aesthetic as more authentic and more appealing than smartphone images. Companies are even rereleasing old tech at new prices. And there are cameras like the original Camp Snap: a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Tottenham vs Arsenal: Free Streams, TV Guide, Preview for North London derby</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/tottenham-vs-arsenal-premier-league-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2EjYBMyK4MW6KiZax7hDLk</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Tottenham vs Arsenal live streams online and from anywhere, as the title-chasing Gunners take on their bitter rivals in the North London derby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromancer is just the thing I needed to give me a dark, sci-fi hit while I wait for Cyberpunk 2</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/neuromancer-is-just-the-thing-i-needed-to-give-me-a-dark-sci-fi-hit-while-i-wait-for-cyberpunk-2</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rFvSuNa9wZVqFfHRJ9tTV6</guid>
      <description>Meet Neuromancer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to send a message via satellite on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/how-to-send-a-message-via-satellite-on-iphone-130000418.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cf8bae0-8869-4c98-830a-b2eebb48d4bf</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s satellite features were originally designed for emergencies, allowing iPhone users to contact emergency services when cellular and Wi-Fi coverage is unavailable. With recent versions of iOS, Apple has expanded those capabilities to include sending and receiving messages via satellite. This makes it possible to stay in touch with friends and family from remote locations where traditional networks do not reach, such as hiking trails, rural areas or offshore locations.Messaging via satellite is built directly into the iPhone and works automatically when no cellular or Wi-Fi signal is avai...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du F2-I516-N05 d&#8217;Altyk&#160;: le mini-PC made in France passe la seconde</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2983305_test-du-f2-i516-n05-daltyk-le-mini-pc-made-in-france-passe-la-seconde</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2983305_test-du-f2-i516-n05-daltyk-le-mini-pc-made-in-france-passe-la-seconde</guid>
      <description>
Un peu plus d&#8217;un an apr&#232;s le lancement de sa gamme de mini-PC, le fabricant fran&#231;ais Altyk a donc d&#233;cid&#233; de monter en puissance. La gamme originelle est toujours d&#8217;actualit&#233;, mais une seconde vague voit le jour avec des am&#233;liorations &#224; tous les niveaux. On ne va pas bouder notre plaisir.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony LinkBuds Clip : les nouveaux &#233;couteurs ouverts sont d&#233;j&#224; en promotion chez Boulanger</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2984779_sony-linkbuds-clip-les-nouveaux-ecouteurs-ouverts-sont-deja-en-promotion-chez-boulanger</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2984779_sony-linkbuds-clip-les-nouveaux-ecouteurs-ouverts-sont-deja-en-promotion-chez-boulanger</guid>
      <description>
Sony vient de pr&#233;senter ses LinkBuds Clip, des &#233;couteurs sans fil ouverts qui ne p&#233;n&#232;trent pas dans le conduit auditif, ce qui permet de rester attentif &#224; ce qui nous entoure. Actuellement, Boulanger les propose &#224; 179,99 euros au lieu de 199,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Olympics closing ceremony live</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495937/olympics-closing-ceremony-2026-live-stream-watch-free-on-nbc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T12:01:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495937/olympics-closing-ceremony-2026-live-stream-watch-free-on-nbc</guid>
      <description>The Winter Games are already coming to a close, with a closing event themed &#8216;Beauty in Action&#8217; set to take place today. Here&#8217;s how to catch it.
The fleeting nature of the Olympic Winter Games makes them all the more alluring. The scarcity is almost sacred. Competitors work their whole lifetimes for one shot at glory that takes place over a period of just a few weeks....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France vs Italy Free Streams: TV Channels, Kick-Off time, Team News, Preview for Six Nations 2026 match</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/rugby/france-vs-italy-six-nations-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">epbEUSuYyLjCoGmyvURQ3d</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch France vs Italy live streams online &#8211; including for FREE &#8211; in the 2026 Six Nations Round 3 clash at Stade Pierre-Mauroy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Know About At-Home STI Tests: Pros, Cons, and Recommendations (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/at-home-sti-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697ce61e9aebf0e1ecc3cf23</guid>
      <description>It's easier than ever to test for sexually transmitted infections at home. We break down whether or not you should.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 Olympics: How to watch the Winter Games Closing Ceremony today</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/2026-olympics-how-to-watch-the-winter-games-closing-ceremony-today-115500771.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e156bc4-b7b0-4f0c-ac61-df9773b0106b</guid>
      <description>


  The Closing Ceremony for the 2026 Winter Games is this Sunday. (Li Jing/Xinhua via Getty Images)
 

  Xinhua News Agency via Getty Images
 

The 2026 Winter Olympics come to an end this weekend. This year's Closing Ceremony theme is "Beauty in Action." The event will feature appearances from musician and DJ Gabry Ponte, actress Benedetta Porcaroli, and ballet dancer Roberto Bolle. Alfredo Accatino, the ceremony's artistic director, has promised the ceremony will "begin with lots of colors and end with a party."
The ceremony will kick off today at 2:30PM ET on NBC and Peacock. An encore br...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
