<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:24:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX gets FCC approval to launch 7,500 more Starlink satellites</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/10/spacex-gets-fcc-approval-to-launch-7500-more-starlink-satellites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081714</guid>
      <description>The Federal Communications Commission has given SpaceX approval to launch another 7,500 of its second generation Starlink satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says he&amp;#8217;s going to open-source the new X algorithm next week</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860294/elon-musk-open-source-x-algorithm</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T16:57:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860294</guid>
      <description>In 2023, what was then still called Twitter, open-sourced at least portions of the code that decided what it served up in your feed. But that GitHub repository is hopelessly out of date, with the vast majority of the files appearing to be from the initial upload three years ago. Elon Musk says that in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These&#160;are the smart home&#160;gadgets that impressed me at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/860241/best-smart-home-devices-ces-2026-matter-ikea-aqara-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T16:30:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860241</guid>
      <description>I picked Aqara's Smart Lock U400 and Roborock's Saros Rover robot vacuum as the overall best smart home gadgets from CES 2026, but there were gazillions of other great gadgets on the show floor. It was a banner year for smart home products, but the big trends I saw weren't about new product categories; they [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is reportedly asking contractors to upload real work from past jobs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/10/openai-is-reportedly-asking-contractors-to-upload-real-work-from-past-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081712</guid>
      <description>An intellectual property lawyer says OpenAI is "putting itself at great risk" with this approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAG-AFTRA Is Keeping an Eye on the Disney/OpenAI Deal</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sag-aftra-is-keeping-an-eye-on-the-disney-openai-deal-2000708414</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708414</guid>
      <description>Not everyone liked hearing Disney got into bed with OpenAI, but SAG-AFTRA thinks it could be good for transparency and progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameStop reportedly shuts down more than 400 US stores</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/gamestop-reportedly-shuts-down-more-than-400-us-stores-210632743.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7bbe15a-4721-4b9d-9bc6-a8f532c9fe34</guid>
      <description>Your neighborhood GameStop might be on the chopping block, along with more than 400 other retail locations across the US. As first reported by Polygon, the retailer is pursuing a severe cost-saving measure by closing up several hundred physical locations. According to a blog that keeps track of GameStop closures, there are 410 locations that are confirmed to be closing or are already closed, along with another 11 that are reportedly also on their way, as of January 10.&#160;
As Polygon indicated, these closings aren't much of a surprise considering GameStop's SEC filing for December 2025 indicated ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FCC is letting SpaceX launch 7,500 more Starlink satellites</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860210/fcc-spacex-7500-more-starlink-satellites</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T16:06:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860210</guid>
      <description>The FCC approved SpaceX's plan to launch an additional 7,500 Gen2 Starlink satellites on Friday. That brings the total number of satellites the company will have in orbit to around 15,000 worldwide. As part of the approval, the government is also waiving previous requirements that prevented overlapping coverage and enhanced capacity. SpaceX originally sought approval [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Says In One Week He Will Fully Reveal Why Your X Timeline Is&#8230; Like That</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-says-in-one-week-he-will-fully-reveal-why-your-x-timeline-is-like-that-2000708652</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708652</guid>
      <description>He&#8217;s been claiming he would make the algorithm open source since 2022.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
