<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:30:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>These New &#8216;Super Mario Galaxy Movie&#8217; Posters Go Galactic</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/these-new-super-mario-galaxy-movie-posters-go-galactic-2000722148</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722148</guid>
      <description>Get some new, cosmic looks at the heroes and villains of 'The Super Mario Galaxy Movie.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1 second in tens of billions of years': China's ultra-precise optical lattice clock gets international recognition as it challenges US hegemony on time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/1-second-in-tens-of-billions-of-years-chinas-ultra-precision-optical-lattice-clock-gets-international-recognition-as-it-challenges-us-hegemony-on-time</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zp7oumH8fnFa8TvpcP7nu9</guid>
      <description>China&#8217;s optical lattice clock now contributes to global time, achieving unprecedented precision and challenging traditional caesium-based measurement systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MasterClass deal: It's the last day to get 50 percent off subscriptions</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/masterclass-deal-its-the-last-day-to-get-50-percent-off-subscriptions-130500234.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c284a7e-f983-403b-b08f-04f40f53adb8</guid>
      <description>MasterClass has dropped the price of its annual memberships by 50 percent, making it a more affordable way to explore its full library of courses across cooking, business, photography, writing and more. With the discount applied, you&#8217;ll spend $10 per month when billed annually for the Premium tier, with lower-cost Standard and Plus options available depending on how many devices you want to use at once and whether you need offline viewing.
There are more than 200 classes on MasterClass now, and many are led by big names at the top of their fields. Depending on your interests, you might pick up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Shutter : tout comprendre sur l&#8217;effet qui d&#233;forme vos photos et vid&#233;os</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/comment-faire/2926157_rolling-shutter-tout-comprendre-sur-leffet-qui-deforme-vos-photos-et-videos</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/comment-faire/2926157_rolling-shutter-tout-comprendre-sur-leffet-qui-deforme-vos-photos-et-videos</guid>
      <description>
Poteaux qui penchent quand vous filmez depuis un train, ventilateur de plafond aux pales &#171; liqu&#233;fi&#233;es &#187;, photo de concert z&#233;br&#233;e de bandes sombres&#8230; Ces bizarreries visuelles ont toutes la m&#234;me origine : le rolling shutter. Ce ph&#233;nom&#232;ne technique touche la quasi-totalit&#233; des smartphones et cam&#233;ras modernes. On vous explique tout.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iBuyPower&#8217;s gaming desktops are discounted for Presidents Day</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/878927/ibuypower-gaming-desktop-pc-presidents-day-sale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878927</guid>
      <description>Buying a pre-assembled gaming desktop makes sense for some. It can save you time and money, too, compared to buying PC components piecemeal. If you&#8217;re weighing your options, consider some Presidents Day offers on iBuyPower&#8217;s pre-built desktops, including the $1,899 RDY Element 9 Pro R07 and the $2,099.99 Slate &#8212; both of which are stocked [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favorite League of Legends spin-off since Arcane just got even better &#8211; but the upgrade only amplifies my stock availability woes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/my-favorite-league-of-legends-spin-off-since-arcane-just-got-even-better-but-the-upgrade-only-amplifies-my-stock-availability-woes</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">inmtJWmhw34xMz8dboe4Dn</guid>
      <description>My favorite Arcane and League of Legends spin-off just got better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland security pushes social media giants to dox anonymous accounts critical of ICE</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/homeland-security-issues-subpeonas-to-dox-social-media-users</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04rx5P6HXTTB2QXVcqM7A3X</guid>
      <description>Four whistleblowers reveal the extent to which the Department of Homeland Security is pressuring social media companies to identify users critical of government policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Tech announced the finalists in its wild musical instrument competition</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/879482/georgia-techs-musical-instrument-competition-fiddle-henge</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T11:42:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879482</guid>
      <description>Georgia Tech has announced the finalists in its annual Guthman Musical Instrument Competition. Every year, for the last 28 years, the school invites inventors from around the world to submit new instruments of their own design to compete for $10,000 in prizes. Past finalists have included founding members of Teenage Engineering, Artiphon, and Roli. And [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ and Hulu deal: Get the bundle for $10 for one month</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/disney-and-hulu-deal-get-the-bundle-for-10-for-one-month-192814789.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b6e8a2-981f-4fc9-b476-d49dcaeed4ba</guid>
      <description>The peak time for deals on streaming services &#8212; the holiday shopping season &#8212; has come and gone, but Disney is back with a fresh offer for the new year. New and eligible returning subscribers can get one month of the ad-supported Disney+ Hulu bundle for just $10. That's $3 off the usual monthly rate for the bundle, and more than 58 percent off if you consider the prices for each service individually (Disney+ at $12 per month and, separately, Hulu also at $12 per month).
We'd be remiss if we didn't mention that this isn't quite as good as the Black Friday deal we saw last year, which offered th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce Lenovo Yoga Slim 7 boost&#233; avec 32 Go de RAM et un Intel Core Ultra 7 se d&#233;charge de 500 &#8364; chez Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2972149_ce-lenovo-yoga-slim-7-booste-avec-32-go-de-ram-et-un-intel-core-ultra-7-se-decharge-de-500-e-chez-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2972149_ce-lenovo-yoga-slim-7-booste-avec-32-go-de-ram-et-un-intel-core-ultra-7-se-decharge-de-500-e-chez-amazon</guid>
      <description>
Pour laisser libre cours &#224; votre imagination, rendez-vous chez Amazon avec cette version du Yoga Slim 7 &#233;quip&#233;e d'un Intel Core Ultra 7 pour 949,99 euros au lieu de 1 499 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India doubles down on state-backed venture capital, approving $1.1B fund</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/14/india-doubles-down-on-state-backed-venture-capital-approving-1-1b-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093154</guid>
      <description>India&#8217;s $1.1B fund-of-funds will invest through private VCs to support deep-tech and manufacturing startups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab our favorite wireless headphones while they're on sale for an all-time-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/grab-our-favorite-wireless-headphones-while-theyre-on-sale-for-an-all-time-low-price-175038719.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4519507c-493c-4bae-a537-e3800e375935</guid>
      <description>Sony's wireless WH-1000XM6 headphones are on sale for $398 via Amazon. This is a record-low price, as it drops $62 from the price tag. The sale applies to all three colorways.
These easily topped our list of the best wireless headphones. They are, in a word, fantastic. The headphones are packed with premium features, like advanced ANC. There are a whopping 12 ANC microphones throughout and a brand-new chip to power the feature. The end result? It successfully blocks background noise at medium and high frequencies, including the human voice. 


The sound quality is extremely pleasing to the ear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi-Yah! &#8216;The Muppet Show&#8217; Was a Smash Hit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hi-yah-the-muppet-show-was-a-smash-hit-2000722178</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722178</guid>
      <description>Disney's given everyone more Muppets with 'The Muppet Show,' and people love it. But is there more on the horizon?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
