<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:24:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s 2026 &#8216;focus&#8217; is &#8216;practical adoption&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864229/openai-focus-practical-adoption-sarah-friar</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T16:05:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864229</guid>
      <description>OpenAI plans to focus on "practical adoption" of AI in 2026, according to a blog post from CFO Sarah Friar. As the company spends a huge amount of money on infrastructure, OpenAI is working on "closing the gap" on what AI can do and how people actually use it. "The opportunity is large and immediate, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK agency questions Meta's policies for illegal gambling site ads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/uk-agency-questions-metas-policies-for-illegal-gambling-site-ads-210500714.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffc49933-c6b0-4df4-92f7-55ecc8fe6659</guid>
      <description>The UK Gambling Commission has raised concerns that Meta is ignoring advertisements by illegal gambling websites on its platforms. At a conference in Barcelona, the commission's Executive Director Tim Miller criticized Meta's behavior towards advertisements for online gambling on its Facebook and Instagram social networks."Companies like Meta will tell you that they don&#8217;t tolerate the advertising of illegal sites and will remove them if they are notified about them," Miller's speech transcript reads. "But that approach suggests that they don&#8217;t know about those ads unless alerted. That is simpl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Couldn&#8217;t Even Kill the Original &#8216;Galaxy&#8217;s Edge&#8217; Right</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-galaxys-edge-changes-disney-lucasfilm-2000711222</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711222</guid>
      <description>The 'Star Wars' sequels are out, and the original trilogy is in at Disneyland&#8212;but just as the parks failed to commit to what made 'Galaxy's Edge' so interesting in the first place, now they can't even commit to erasing that dream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much can a city take?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/864195/minneapolis-ice-invasion-organizing-immigration</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864195</guid>
      <description>I live in Minneapolis. I grew up not far from here, in a suburb of St. Paul; after stints on both coasts, my wife and I settled here to raise our daughters in a freezing state that had always welcomed us warmly. As the ongoing occupation by over 3,000 ICE agents stretches into its third [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TurboTax Deluxe is on sale for $45 ahead of tax season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/turbotax-deluxe-is-on-sale-for-45-ahead-of-tax-season-204848571.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d4b28c6-34f1-44bb-800a-eec732a96ded</guid>
      <description>With the spring approaching, it's time to start thinking about how you'll file your taxes. Unfortunately, with the recent demise of Direct File, there isn't a free, government-provided alternative to TurboTax in 2026, and you'll need to look to other federal programs, including IRS Free File, to file your paperwork. If you don't qualify for Free File, chances are you'll need to dish out cash for Intuit's software. And while we hate to suggest you give money to a company that has spent decades lobbying to ensure America's tax system remains a nightmare, we can at least save you some money if Tu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid robots are 'stepping out of the lab and into the real world' to take the jobs we don't want - so get ready for the rise of the robot coworkers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/get-ready-for-the-rise-of-the-robot-coworkers-new-report-claims-humanoid-robots-are-stepping-out-of-the-lab-and-into-the-real-world-to-take-the-jobs-we-dont-want</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Mh9RBGBYkP5apZSU2sNGyB</guid>
      <description>Humanoid robots are entering real workplaces due to labor shortages, falling costs, and technical progress, though large-scale adoption remains uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Bitcoin Glitch Fixed When &#8216;Decentralized&#8217; Crypto Exchange Uses Centralized Rollback</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/free-bitcoin-glitch-fixed-when-decentralized-crypto-exchange-uses-centralized-rollback-2000711734</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711734</guid>
      <description>Situations that expose centralization in supposedly decentralized exchanges have become par for the course in crypto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Football Playoff National Championship 2026 Free Streams: Watch Miami vs Indiana, TV Channels, Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/college-football-playoff-national-championship-2026-miami-hurricanes-vs-indiana-hoosiers-free</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ovaqXEYNaVgcJjaiUGqHPN</guid>
      <description>As the Miami Hurricanes and Indiana Hoosiers go for the big one, here's how to watch College Football Playoff National Championship 2026 for free and from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie's Marathon arrives on March 5</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/bungies-marathon-arrives-on-march-5-193808588.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d281aa64-5e04-427a-9e18-b315e83b7df3</guid>
      <description>Marathon, Bungie's long-awaited extraction shooter, will arrive on March 5, the studio announced today. Alongside a definitive release date, Bungie shared a new gameplay trailer, in addition to details about the game's forthcoming deluxe edition, which fans can pre-order today on Steam, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S. All versions of the game will support crossplay, meaning you'll be able to play with your friends, no matter where they decide to buy Marathon.&#160;&#160;Sony, Bungie's parent company, had previously committed to a March release for Marathon, but stopped short of sharing an exact date....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A second US Sphere could come to Maryland</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/864192/sphere-entertainment-mini-venue-maryland-national-harbor</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T14:35:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864192</guid>
      <description>Sphere Entertainment, the company behind the eye-catching interactive venue in Las Vegas, has announced its "intent to develop" another Sphere in Maryland that will be located 15 minutes south of Washington, DC. A timeline and exact location haven't been finalized, but the Maryland Sphere would be the company's second venue in the US, following plans [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungies Marathon gets March release date</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/bungie-marathon-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06lYt8yCPejExBK6nwuU3yR</guid>
      <description>Bungie's 'Marathon' gets March release date</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
