<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:32:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>If you live in the UK, you probably won&#8217;t be able to visit Pornhub anymore</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/if-you-live-in-the-uk-you-probably-wont-be-able-to-visit-pornhub-anymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086598</guid>
      <description>Pornhub parent company Aylo will restrict access from U.K. users, rather than comply with age verification mandates, which the company said it believes have not succeeded in promoting online safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Swears It Didn&#8217;t Ban Sharing the Name &#8216;Epstein,&#8217; as Gavin Newsom Announces Investigation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tiktok-swears-it-didnt-ban-sharing-the-name-epstein-as-gavin-newsom-announces-investigation-2000714521</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714521</guid>
      <description>The scrutiny follows a rocky first week under new U.S. ownership./</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says it&#8217;s still working to recover its U.S. infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/tiktok-says-its-still-working-to-recover-its-u-s-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086628</guid>
      <description>TikTok says some of the glitches continue but it's making "significant progress" in recovering its U.S. infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo is adding generative AI to its search engine</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/yahoo-is-adding-generative-ai-to-its-search-engine-172706249.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db692d13-1bbb-488e-a6c6-ce1e27414497</guid>
      <description>Yahoo has announced a new AI-powered "answer engine", dubbed Yahoo Scout. The new tool is available now in beta and is powered by Anthropic's Claude.
The company says Scout "synthesizes" info from the web, as well as Yahoo's own data and content when constructing responses to user's natural-language search queries. Yahoo says the interface will include interactive digital media, structured lists and tables and visible source links aimed at making answers easier to verify. (Disclosure: Yahoo is the parent company of Engadget.)
Alongside Scout, Yahoo is announcing an "intelligence platform" acro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp is rolling out a new stricter security setting to protect users from cyber attacts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/whatsapp-is-rolling-out-a-new-stricter-security-setting-to-protect-users-from-cyber-attacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086615</guid>
      <description>Days after Meta was sued by over alleged false privacy claims by its chat app WhatsApp, the company has rolled out a new setting to protect users against cyber attacks. The feature, called Strict&#160;Account&#160;Settings, adds restrictions like automatically blocking media and attachments from unknown senders, and silencing calls from unknown numbers. Under this setting, link [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oppo Reno 15 : quatre nouveaux smartphones et toujours plus de 6000 mAh</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/oppo/2956623_oppo-reno-15-quatre-nouveaux-smartphones-et-toujours-plus-de-6000-mah</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/oppo/2956623_oppo-reno-15-quatre-nouveaux-smartphones-et-toujours-plus-de-6000-mah</guid>
      <description>
Les quatre nouveaux Oppo Reno 15, Reno 15 Pro, Reno 15 F et Reno 15 FS sont officialis&#233;s en France avec, en argument choc, des batteries au dessus des 6000 mAh.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worrying Microsoft Office security flaw patched - update now or risk hackers accessing your files</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/worrying-microsoft-office-security-flaw-patched-update-now-or-risk-hackers-accessing-your-files</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Jof4ywzbk2Pg3RfLhCjbf</guid>
      <description>Microsoft forced to issue an emergency patch to fix an Office zero-day being actively exploited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung confirme le prix du Galaxy Z TriFold, et &#231;a pique</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-son-prix-et-sa-date-de-sortie-fuitent-et-ca-pique.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322645</guid>
      <description>Le puzzle se compl&#232;te enfin pour le Galaxy Z TriFold. Apr&#232;s notre prise en main de ce monstre de technologie, de nouvelles indiscr&#233;tions viennent d&#233;voiler l'addition et le calendrier de lancement. Pr&#233;parez-vous, la facture s'annonce particuli&#232;rement sal&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmes addictifs des r&#233;seaux sociaux | TikTok conclut un accord avant l&#8217;ouverture du proc&#232;s</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-27/algorithmes-addictifs-des-reseaux-sociaux/tiktok-conclut-un-accord-avant-l-ouverture-du-proces.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:13:07 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d9d445691353168996ee97536f9f253</guid>
      <description>Une semaine apr&#232;s Snapchat, TikTok a &#224; son tour conclu un accord pour clore des poursuites juste avant l&#8217;ouverture mardi d&#8217;un proc&#232;s test pour les g&#233;ants des r&#233;seaux sociaux, accus&#233;s d&#8217;avoir con&#231;u leurs applications pour rendre les jeunes utilisateurs accros, selon des avocats joints par l&#8217;AFP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consommation, recharge, s&#233;curit&#233; : pourquoi la nouvelle Dacia Spring &#233;lectrique devrait &#234;tre plus &#224; l&#8217;aise sur autoroute</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2956989_consommation-recharge-securite-pourquoi-la-nouvelle-dacia-spring-electrique-devrait-etre-plus-a-laise-sur-autoroute</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2956989_consommation-recharge-securite-pourquoi-la-nouvelle-dacia-spring-electrique-devrait-etre-plus-a-laise-sur-autoroute</guid>
      <description>
La Dacia Spring vient de recevoir des moteurs plus puissants. Cela devrait lui faire du bien sur autoroute : outre de meilleures performances, la consommation en baisse &#224; haute vitesse et la recharge plus rapide devraient faire progresser la polyvalence de la voiture &#233;lectrique la moins ch&#232;re du march&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN kills legacy apps &#8211; you have time until March 31 to update yours</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-kills-legacy-apps-you-have-time-until-march-31-to-update-yours</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9YqLaiLK3MBd8buhzovGbK</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN says older app versions will stop connecting after March 31, 2026, as part of a major security update. Check your version, update now, and stay protected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok US is mostly back up and running</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868679/tiktok-down-outage-us-usds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T12:05:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868679</guid>
      <description>As we moved into the third day of the TikTokalypse, the app appears to have finally stabilized in the US, as we verified that it's possible to consistently publish new videos and even have other people watch them. That hasn't been a simple task since the service started having problems early Sunday morning, but on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp renforce la s&#233;curit&#233; des comptes les plus expos&#233;s aux attaques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/whatsapp-renforce-la-securite-des-comptes-les-plus-exposes-aux-attaques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322818</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp propose depuis toujours le chiffrement de bout en bout par d&#233;faut des discussions, ce qui offre un bon niveau de confidentialit&#233; aux &#233;changes. Mais certains utilisateurs peuvent en vouloir davantage, c'est pourquoi la messagerie de Meta propose une nouvelle option de s&#233;curit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel Redmi Note 15 choisir&#160;? Le guide ultime pour s&#8217;y retrouver</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/quel-redmi-note-15-choisir-le-guide-ultime-pour-sy-retrouver.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320592</guid>
      <description>&#192; chaque g&#233;n&#233;ration, les Redmi Note reviennent occuper le terrain du smartphone abordable, au point de devenir un passage quasi oblig&#233; pour les petits budgets. Avec les Redmi Note 15, Xiaomi reconduit la recette, mais la prolif&#233;ration de versions (4G, 5G, Pro et Pro+) brouille s&#233;rieusement les pistes pour le grand public. Ce dossier d&#233;cortique les cinq mod&#232;les, du ticket d&#8217;entr&#233;e &#224; 200 euros jusqu&#8217;au Pro+ &#224; 500 euros, afin de vous aider &#224; comprendre ce que vous gagnez, ou perdez, &#224; chaque palier de prix et &#224; choisir en connaissance de cause....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For some reason, Bethesda has teamed up with Pringles to launch a Fallout 76 Mystery Flavour</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/for-some-reason-bethesda-has-teamed-up-with-pringles-to-launch-a-fallout-76-mystery-flavour</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pjPaeTWHfWjjcY6buhynqf</guid>
      <description>Pringles has launched a new Fallout 76 Mystery Flavour, and to celebrate, fans can submit their guess to win a special prize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: Everything we think the company will unveil</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-everything-we-think-the-company-will-unveil-130000218.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hands-on coverage of Samsung's new smartphones soon after they're announced. While we wait for an official invite, here's everything we expect Samsung will introduce at the first Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026.Galaxy S26, S26+ and S26 UltraSamsung ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following its major restructuring announcement, Ubisoft begins 'a collective, voluntary mutual termination agreement' at its Paris HQ, with 200 jobs on the line</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-industry/following-its-major-restructuring-announcement-ubisoft-begins-a-collective-voluntary-mutual-termination-agreement-at-its-paris-hq-with-200-jobs-on-the-line</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gcKrcgVjUnniC8KcDPhW6T</guid>
      <description>After announcing major restructuring plans at Ubisoft and the cancellation of several games, the company has now begun a voluntary redundancy process at its Paris, France headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Raimi Movies, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-raimi-movies-ranked-2000713699</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713699</guid>
      <description>His new one, 'Send Help,' is out this week, but where does it rank against 'Evil Dead,' 'Spider-Man,' and others?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : il reste un peu plus d&#8217;une semaine pour faire de bonnes affaires, les meilleures offres en DIRECT</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949895_soldes-dhiver-2026-il-reste-un-peu-plus-dune-semaine-pour-faire-de-bonnes-affaires-les-meilleures-offres-en-direct</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949895_soldes-dhiver-2026-il-reste-un-peu-plus-dune-semaine-pour-faire-de-bonnes-affaires-les-meilleures-offres-en-direct</guid>
      <description>
C'est d&#233;j&#224; bient&#244;t la fin des soldes d'hiver. En effet, dans un peu plus d'une semaine, les e-commer&#231;ants tels qu'Amazon, Fnac, Darty, Boulanger ou encore Cdiscount vont arr&#234;ter de partager des offres en ce sens. C'est bient&#244;t la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque, l&#224; o&#249; il y a les meilleures offres &#224; saisir. Tenez-vous pr&#234;t(e)s !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google DeepMind Staffers Ask Leaders to Keep Them &#8216;Physically Safe&#8217; From ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-deepmind-staffers-ice-office-questions-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69783fc373242c9937907204</guid>
      <description>A federal agent allegedly tried to enter Google&#8217;s Cambridge campus in the fall, WIRED has learned. Now, staffers want policies that protect them from immigration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Search now lets you ask AI Overviews follow-up questions</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868497/google-ai-search-follow-up-questions-gemini-3</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868497</guid>
      <description>Google is making Search less about links and more about AI. The company is upgrading its AI-powered search features, adding Gemini 3 to AI Overviews and letting users ask follow-up questions "seamlessly" to make sure Search can answer "whatever's on your mind," a move that feels closer to using an AI chatbot than a search [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The promise and peril of a new online shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/868558/highguard-online-shooters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868558</guid>
      <description>The routine is familiar by now. A new online shooter with bright, colorful graphics launches and rockets up the charts despite the fact that you maybe haven't even heard of it. Or maybe it just has a really forgettable name. But everyone seems to be talking about it, and it's free, so you figure you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google now lets users jump from AI Overviews into AI Mode conversations</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/google-now-lets-users-jump-from-ai-overviews-into-ai-mode-conversations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086581</guid>
      <description>The tech giant also announced that it's making Gemini 3 the new default model for AI Overviews globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android phones are getting more anti-theft features</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/android-phones-are-getting-more-anti-theft-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086593</guid>
      <description>Google says Android devices will get new security features, like stronger authentication safeguards and enhanced recovery tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Search gets smarter AI Overviews with Gemini 3 &#8212; and adds follow&#8209;up chats to your search results</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/gemini/google-search-gets-smarter-ai-overviews-with-gemini-3-and-adds-follow-up-chats-to-your-search-results</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bTsTc3SskNt6ftyH7eRjd8</guid>
      <description>Google Search upgrades AI Overviews with Gemini 3 and a connection to AI Mode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 is now Google's default model for AI Overviews</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/gemini-3-is-now-googles-default-model-for-ai-overviews-170000302.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf9ab5ff-6d05-4bdb-aa4d-dd7c4bafa410</guid>
      <description>Google has begun rolling out two upgrades for Search. Starting today, Gemini 3 is the default model powering AI Overviews. When the company debuted its new family of AI systems last November, it first deployed Gemini 3 in AI Overviews through a router that was programmed to direct the most difficult questions to the new system. Now Google is making Gemini 3 the standard for all users globally. In practice, Gemini 3 should prove better at generating more credible and relevant summaries.&#160;As for that second upgrade, now you can jump into AI Mode conversation directly from an AI Overview. Google f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual AI launches Agent Composer to turn enterprise RAG into production-ready AI agents</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/contextual-ai-launches-agent-composer-to-turn-enterprise-rag-into-production</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7A4OWvyUV01VqTlSX81exc</guid>
      <description>In the race to bring artificial intelligence into the enterprise, a small but well-funded startup is making a bold claim: The problem holding back AI adoption in complex industries has never been the models themselves.Contextual AI, a two-and-a-half-year-old company backed by investors including Bezos Expeditions and Bain Capital Ventures, on Monday unveiled Agent Composer, a platform designed to help engineers in aerospace, semiconductor manufacturing, and other technically demanding fields build AI agents that can automate the kind of knowledge-intensive work that has long resisted automatio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette galaxie contredit tout ce qu&#8217;on pensait savoir sur l&#8217;Univers primitif</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/univers-cette-galaxie-contredit-tout-ce-quon-pensait-savoir-univers-primitif-w2t8-130489/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/univers-cette-galaxie-contredit-tout-ce-quon-pensait-savoir-univers-primitif-w2t8-130489/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Les galaxies satellites de notre Voie lact&#233;e ont appris beaucoup de choses aux astronomes sur l&#8217;&#233;volution de notre Univers. C&#8217;est du moins ce dont ils &#233;taient convaincus. Mais la d&#233;couverte d&#8217;une toute petite galaxie dans le voisinage d&#8217;Androm&#232;de remet pas mal de choses en question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian states weigh Australia-style ban on social media for children</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/indian-states-weigh-australia-style-ban-on-social-media-for-children/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086579</guid>
      <description>Goa and Andhra Pradesh are among Indian states mulling Australia-like social media ban for under-16s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Pediatricians Give Middle Finger to RFK Jr., Issue Their Own Vaccine Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/us-pediatricians-give-middle-finger-to-rfk-jr-issue-their-own-vaccine-recommendations-2000714459</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714459</guid>
      <description>The American Academy of Pediatrics and 12 other medical groups are recommending the same childhood shots once endorsed by the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel smartphone Oppo choisir en 2026&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/smartphones/709865_guide-smartphones-oppo</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/smartphones/709865_guide-smartphones-oppo</guid>
      <description>
Oppo fait son retour en France et plus largement en Europe. La marque chinoise est revenue sur le march&#233; avec un nouveau t&#233;l&#233;phone haut de gamme.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon se montre bien g&#233;n&#233;reux pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes avec une myriade d&#8217;offres</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-multiplie-les-offres-a-lapproche-de-la-derniere-demarque-les-17-meilleurs-deals-a-saisir</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-multiplie-les-offres-a-lapproche-de-la-derniere-demarque-les-17-meilleurs-deals-a-saisir</guid>
      <description>
La derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver d&#233;marre d&#232;s demain, et Amazon en profite pour proposer des offres toujours plus int&#233;ressantes avant la fin de l&#8217;&#233;v&#233;nement. Smartphones pliants, vid&#233;oprojecteurs &#224; prix cass&#233; et bien d&#8217;autres produits tech sont &#224; saisir d&#232;s maintenant&#8239;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This iPhone offer from AT&amp;T might just be one of the best deals I've seen at the carrier in months - and it's easy to miss</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/this-iphone-offer-from-at-and-t-might-just-be-one-of-the-best-deals-ive-seen-at-the-carrier-in-months-and-its-easy-to-miss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">J3iJ2Vv8Kax7Ed5HNHM5TD</guid>
      <description>This deal on the iPhone Air beats the iPhone 17, 17 Pro, and others</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel 10 users are reporting broken Wi-Fi and Bluetooth with the latest update &#8211; and there&#8217;s no fix in sight</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/google-pixel-phones/google-pixel-10-users-are-reporting-broken-wi-fi-and-bluetooth-with-the-latest-update-and-theres-no-fix-in-sight</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hwbsS25syQTp3uZkyXoTrX</guid>
      <description>The latest Pixel patch fixes bugs but also seems to introduce some, rendering certain Pixel 10 series phones almost unusable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I stock up on these viral Amazon pillows every January &#8212; they have 200,000+ five-star reviews and are just $41.98 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/i-stock-up-on-these-viral-amazon-pillows-every-january-they-have-200-000-five-star-reviews-and-are-just-usd41-98-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LQwYBGcsJxoYUPYUvy5YfR</guid>
      <description>If you're like me and stock up on new pillows every January, then I can't recommend the viral Beckham Hotel Collection pillows, which are on sale for $41.98 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les AirPods 4 avec ANC sont quasiment au m&#234;me prix que la version sans ANC pendant les soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2956903_les-airpods-4-avec-anc-sont-quasiment-au-meme-prix-que-la-version-sans-anc-pendant-les-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2956903_les-airpods-4-avec-anc-sont-quasiment-au-meme-prix-que-la-version-sans-anc-pendant-les-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Les AirPods 4 ont beau &#234;tre des &#233;couteurs sans fil ouverts, ils parviennent tout de m&#234;me &#224; offrir une r&#233;duction de bruit active efficace. S'ils vous int&#233;ressent, sachez qu'ils sont, pendant les soldes d'hiver 2026, affich&#233;s &#224; 154,99 euros au lieu de 199,99 euros chez Rakuten. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I grew up with Alex Pretti</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/868567/alex-pretti-minneapolis-childhood-friend</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T11:39:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868567</guid>
      <description>The day Alex Pretti was shot 10 times in the street by federal agents, I was delivering a eulogy for my grandfather, who died the way we're supposed to: old, asleep, surrounded by family. Because it's my job to coordinate visuals for this website, I locked myself in a bathroom stall, watched a video of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get NBC without Fubo ahead of the 2026 Winter Olympics</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-get-nbc-without-fubo-ahead-of-the-2026-winter-olympics-163805696.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c64dbaf8-5340-4d6b-b78b-690a010272ac</guid>
      <description>After more than two months of contract disputes, NBCUniversal's lineup of channels are still not being carried by Fubo, which is a bummer for anyone hoping to watch the 2026 Winter Olympics. Once again, NBC will be the primary place to watch the Winter Games, but Fubo subscribers will need to find alternate viewing methods if they want to watch events like figure skating, ice hockey, luge or skiing this year. The Olympics will also be broadcast on the USA Network and CNBC, and those channels are similarly blacked out on Fubo.
While the two media companies continue their negotiations, subscribe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C&#8217;est le grand d&#233;stockage chez Boulanger : voici les 20 meilleures offres &#224; saisir avant la fin des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-degaine-de-belles-offres-mais-voici-celles-qui-meritent-vraiment-votre-argent-avant-la-derniere-demarque</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-degaine-de-belles-offres-mais-voici-celles-qui-meritent-vraiment-votre-argent-avant-la-derniere-demarque</guid>
      <description>
La derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes commence d&#232;s demain&#8239;! Avant la fin de l&#8217;&#233;v&#233;nement, les amateurs de bons plans peuvent encore profiter d&#8217;offres particuli&#232;rement attractives sur une large s&#233;lection de produits Tech chez Boulanger.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornhub will block new users in the UK next month</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868640/pornhub-uk-block-age-verification-online-safety-act</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T11:35:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868640</guid>
      <description>Pornhub will soon begin restricting UK users from accessing its website in response to the country's "failed" online safety regulations, according to an announcement on Tuesday. The site's owner, Aylo, says it will block users who haven't already verified their age on the platform starting February 2nd, 2026, as reported earlier by 404 Media. As [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus besoin d&#8217;une carte graphique &#224; 1000&#8364; ? Forza Horizon 6 mise sur une optimisation record</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2956841_plus-besoin-dune-carte-graphique-a-1000e-forza-horizon-6-mise-sur-une-optimisation-record</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2956841_plus-besoin-dune-carte-graphique-a-1000e-forza-horizon-6-mise-sur-une-optimisation-record</guid>
      <description>
Forza Horizon 6 devrait tourner sur une tr&#232;s large gamme de cartes graphiques, y compris sur les GPU int&#233;gr&#233;s de certains PC portables.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new malware service promises to skip Google's review process and get your malware straight onto the Chrome Store</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-new-malware-service-promises-to-skip-googles-review-process-and-get-your-malware-straight-onto-the-chrome-store</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5gLyfqLPNKjxtEARJuYht9</guid>
      <description>The malware spoofs entire websites, while keeping the address bar intact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest is conducting a massive round of layoffs to prioritize 'AI-powered products and capabilities'</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/pinterest-is-conducting-a-massive-round-of-layoffs-to-prioritize-ai-powered-products-and-capabilities-163440004.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8be0fc93-7bc0-4709-8164-f4efb5e16a64</guid>
      <description>Pinterest is planning on laying off up to 15 percent of its workforce, according to a report by CNBC. The company has been posting stellar earnings reports these past few quarters, so why punish employees? You already know the answer. It's AI.
The company said it's "reallocating resources" to AI projects and prioritizing "AI-powered products and capabilities." It's also cutting down on office space, presumably because AI algorithms don't require cubicles and the occasional low-grade snack.
Pinterest noted in a recent security filing that it expects these cuts to the workforce will be complete ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fin de l&#8217;ADSL&#160;: l&#8217;&#201;tat peut verser jusqu&#8217;&#224; 1&#160;200&#160;&#8364; pour financer un raccordement &#224; la fibre</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fin-de-ladsl-letat-peut-verser-jusqua-1-200-e-pour-financer-un-raccordement-a-la-fibre.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322810</guid>
      <description>Le r&#233;seau cuivre est en sursis. &#192; l'horizon 2030, il sera remplac&#233; par la fibre sur tout le territoire, mais une &#233;ch&#233;ance va tomber tr&#232;s vite : &#224; compter du 31 janvier, des milliers de foyers et d'entreprises ne pourront plus souscrire &#224; de nouveaux abonnements ADSL. Une aide financi&#232;re de l'&#201;tat est disponible sous certaines conditions pour financer des travaux de raccordement chez les usagers concern&#233;s....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of nudify apps found on Google and Apple&#8217;s app stores</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868614/nudify-apps-ttp-report-google-apple-app-stores</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T11:26:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868614</guid>
      <description>Removing or restricting access to Grok's AI image editor might not be enough to stop the flood of nonconsensual sexualized images being generated by AI. A report from the Tech Transparency Project (TTP) released on Tuesday found dozens of AI "nudify" apps similar to Grok on Google and Apple's platforms, as previously reported by CNBC. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A TikTok US power outage caused a 'cascading systems failure' leading to multiple bugs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/a-tiktok-us-power-outage-caused-a-cascading-systems-failure-leading-to-multiple-bugs-173426490.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c92f4e5-a484-40cc-b29f-ef5732fb73d6</guid>
      <description>If your TikTok feed has felt a little off lately, it's not just you. TikTok says is still working to fix its service in the US following a power outage at one of its data centers that's caused &#8220;multiple bugs&#8221; in the app. TikTok users have reported problems logging in and uploading videos, as well as strange behavior from the "for you" algorithm. Creators have also noticed that new uploads are seemingly getting o views or likes and that in-app earnings have disappeared."Since yesterday we&#8217;ve been working to restore our services following a power outage at a U.S. data center impacting TikTok and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Agenda : fini le casse-t&#234;te pour organiser des r&#233;unions, cette nouveaut&#233; de Gemini va vous sauver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2956771_google-agenda-fini-le-casse-tete-pour-organiser-des-reunions-cette-nouveaute-de-gemini-va-vous-sauver</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2956771_google-agenda-fini-le-casse-tete-pour-organiser-des-reunions-cette-nouveaute-de-gemini-va-vous-sauver</guid>
      <description>
L'IA Gemini de Google se dote d'une fonctionnalit&#233; bien pratique dans l'application Agenda. Elle permet d'organiser des rendez-vous &#224; plusieurs tr&#232;s facilement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is closing its physical Amazon Go and Amazon Fresh stores</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/amazon-is-closing-its-physical-amazon-go-and-amazon-fresh-stores/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086577</guid>
      <description>These retail closures will not impact customers who use Amazon for grocery delivery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turntable legend Pro-Ject has a weird but wonderful new hi-fi box &#8211; it's a phono stage, streaming hub, DAC, TV HDMI connector, and headphone amp all in one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/hi-fi/turntable-legend-pro-ject-has-a-weird-but-wonderful-new-hi-fi-box-its-a-phono-stage-streaming-hub-dac-tv-hdmi-connector-and-headphone-amp-all-in-one</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3DgtENZxs5DDUvv2xCNeGg</guid>
      <description>The Pro-Ject Pre Box S3 brings all your audio sources together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grosse puissance et autonomie : le pionnier de la moto &#233;lectrique lance son tout premier scooter &#233;lectrique &#224; un prix attractif</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/scooters-electriques/2956919_grosse-puissance-et-autonomie-le-pionnier-de-la-moto-electrique-lance-son-tout-premier-scooter-electrique-a-un-prix-attractif</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/scooters-electriques/2956919_grosse-puissance-et-autonomie-le-pionnier-de-la-moto-electrique-lance-son-tout-premier-scooter-electrique-a-un-prix-attractif</guid>
      <description>
Zero Motorcycles, le pionnier californien de la moto &#233;lectrique, franchit une &#233;tape symbolique pour son vingti&#232;me anniversaire. La marque s'attaque pour la premi&#232;re fois au march&#233; du scooter urbain avec le LS1, un mod&#232;le &#233;quivalent 125 cm&#179; qui mise sur une autonomie record et une technologie h&#233;rit&#233;e de ses mod&#232;les hautes performances.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fnac et Darty d&#233;voilent leurs meilleures offres juste avant la fin des soldes : voici les 20 deals &#224; saisir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-lachent-une-nouvelle-vague-de-promotion-a-lapproche-de-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-lachent-une-nouvelle-vague-de-promotion-a-lapproche-de-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
D&#232;s demain, la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver d&#233;bute chez Fnac et Darty. C&#8217;est votre ultime chance de profiter de r&#233;ductions exceptionnelles sur une large s&#233;lection Tech &#8212; smartphones, tablettes, ordinateurs et bien plus encore &#8212; avant la fin de l&#8217;&#233;v&#232;nement&#8239;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornhub Will Block New UK Users Starting Next Week to Protest &#8216;Flawed&#8217; ID Law</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/pornhub-will-block-new-uk-users-starting-next-week-to-protest-flawed-id-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6973e8feb56ba9c4db51237d</guid>
      <description>Only users who have already registered and completed age verification will be able to access the world's largest porn site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Web vs InMotion Hosting: VPS hosting compared</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/liquid-web-vs-inmotion-hosting-vps-hosting-compared</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WGXGASh5GSxSwKNwH2zD5P</guid>
      <description>Liquid Web vs InMotion Hosting: VPS hosting compared</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego&#8217;s Newest &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Smart Play Sets Are Cheaper, With a Huge Catch</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lego-star-wars-smart-play-sets-price-release-date-2000714464</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714464</guid>
      <description>Lego's push for smart bricks in the galaxy far, far away is continuing, and things are only getting weirder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Return of Nintendo&#8217;s Worst-Selling Console Could Be More Glorious Than We Thought</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/virtual-boy-switch-2-could-be-more-glorious-than-we-thought-2000714470</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714470</guid>
      <description>Get ready to return to the neck-straining magic of red and black gaming with several never-released games for the Virtual Boy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've had this compact B&amp;O speaker for 4 months now &#8211; here are 3 reasons it's better than the JBL Charge 6</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/speakers/ive-had-this-compact-b-o-speaker-for-4-months-now-here-are-3-reasons-its-better-than-the-jbl-charge-6</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5sS8zjZtLHm4abi4WSmCD</guid>
      <description>The last few months with B&amp;O&#8217;s audiophile-friendly Bluetooth speaker have been so amazing, I&#8217;d pick it over JBL&#8217;s Bluetooth speakers &#8211; for these 3 reasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi la France ne va pas vraiment pouvoir interdire les r&#233;seaux sociaux aux ados</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/politique/2957025_pourquoi-la-france-ne-va-pas-vraiment-pouvoir-interdire-les-reseaux-sociaux-aux-ados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/politique/2957025_pourquoi-la-france-ne-va-pas-vraiment-pouvoir-interdire-les-reseaux-sociaux-aux-ados</guid>
      <description>
Malgr&#233; une premi&#232;re adoption de la loi sur l&#8217;interdiction des r&#233;seaux sociaux aux moins de 15&#160;ans en France, l'&#201;tat ne pourra jamais vraiment la faire appliquer. Ce n'est pas son r&#244;le.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le prix de l&#8217;aspirateur balai Dyson V12 Origin est en chute libre pendant les soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2458874_le-prix-de-laspirateur-balai-dyson-v12-origin-est-en-chute-libre-pendant-les-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2458874_le-prix-de-laspirateur-balai-dyson-v12-origin-est-en-chute-libre-pendant-les-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Dyson est devenu, avec le temps, la r&#233;f&#233;rence des aspirateurs-balais haut de gamme. En t&#233;moigne le mod&#232;le V12 Origin que Cdiscount rend bien plus abordable avec cette r&#233;duction de pr&#232;s de 200 euros pour les soldes d'hiver. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowmageddon Continues: Another Major Storm Could Slam the East Coast This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/snowmageddon-continues-another-major-storm-could-slam-the-east-coast-this-weekend-2000714510</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714510</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s looking increasingly likely that a coastal storm could bring more snow to the East Coast this weekend&#8212;and potentially strengthen into a bomb cyclone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Votre op&#233;rateur sait o&#249; vous &#234;tes : Apple met fin &#224; ce pistage (mais pas pour tous)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2956815_votre-operateur-sait-ou-vous-etes-apple-met-fin-a-ce-pistage-mais-pas-pour-tous</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2956815_votre-operateur-sait-ou-vous-etes-apple-met-fin-a-ce-pistage-mais-pas-pour-tous</guid>
      <description>
Votre op&#233;rateur mobile sait exactement o&#249; vous &#234;tes, &#224; la seconde pr&#232;s, gr&#226;ce aux antennes relais. C'est un fait &#233;tabli depuis des ann&#233;es, mais Apple a d&#233;cid&#233; de siffler la fin de la r&#233;cr&#233;ation avec iOS 26.3. Une nouvelle option de confidentialit&#233; va brouiller les pistes, mais attention : il faudra montrer patte blanche pour en profiter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I think, ultimately, we could have made a different trailer' &#8212; Wildlight Entertainment CEO wishes 'Highguard had been received better' amidst the game's negative review score on Steam</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/i-think-ultimately-we-could-have-made-a-different-trailer-wildlight-entertainment-ceo-wishes-highguard-had-been-received-better-amidst-the-games-negative-review-score-on-steam</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">em6Jr2hsS8SVMFmH6tr3cm</guid>
      <description>Wildlight Entertainment's CEO has admitted the studio could have marketed Highguard better following radio silence leading up to its launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France just approved a social media ban for kids under 15</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481705/france-just-approved-social-media-ban-for-kids-under-15</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T15:46:12</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481705/france-just-approved-social-media-ban-for-kids-under-15</guid>
      <description>Legislators approved the bill, which also bans the use of mobile phones in high schools.
French lawmakers approved a bill banning social media for children under 15, paving the way for the measure to enter into force at the start of the next school year in September, as the idea of setting a minimum age for use of the platforms gains momentum across Europe.The bill, which also bans the use of mobile phones in high schools, was adopted by a 130-21 vote late Monday. French President Emmanuel Macron has requested that the legislation be fast-tracked and it will now be discussed by the Senate in t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest layoffs today: 15% of jobs cut as social media giant is latest to cite shift to AI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481805/pinterest-stock-price-pins-layoffs-today-2026-job-cuts-latest-to-cite-shift-to-ai-artificial-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T15:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481805/pinterest-stock-price-pins-layoffs-today-2026-job-cuts-latest-to-cite-shift-to-ai-artificial-intelligence</guid>
      <description>The platform&#8217;s stock price plummeted by more than 8% after news of the reduction in workforce.
Nike isn&#8217;t the only household corporate name to announce significant layoffs this week. Just a day after the sporting goods giant announced layoffs, citing a further embrace of automation, social media giant Pinterest has announced it will cut jobs. The driving factor here? Artificial intelligence....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU tells Google to give external AI assistants the same access to Android as Gemini has</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/the-eu-tells-google-to-give-external-ai-assistants-the-same-access-to-android-as-gemini-has-154157081.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66e23734-a757-441a-9f94-aac0bcea05fa</guid>
      <description>The European Commission has started proceedings to ensure Google complies with the Digital Markets Act (DMA) in certain ways. Specifically, the European Union&#8217;s executive arm has told Google to grant third-party AI services the same level of access to Android that Gemini has. "The aim is to ensure that third-party providers have an equal opportunity to innovate and compete in the rapidly evolving AI landscape on smart mobile devices," the Commission said in a statement.&#160;The company will also have to hand over "anonymized ranking, query, click and view data held by Google Search" to rival searc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 512GB Samsung P9 microSD Express card is 33 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/this-512gb-samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-is-33-percent-off-143849630.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7c1c9b1-8762-4b3b-bd34-558e13eba66f</guid>
      <description>MicroSD Express cards are still a little hard to find, considering they're pretty new and only really started becoming popular last year once the Switch 2 came out. These upgraded versions of microSD cards are the only ones compatible with the Switch 2 for expanding its storage, os if you're already starting to feel the crunch on your console, it's worth picking one up. Samsung's P9 microSD Express card is on sale right now &#8212; you can grab the 512GB version of $80, which is 33 percent off and one of the best prices we've seen.


The P9 boasts transfer speeds of up to 800MB/s, making moving game...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I thought Virtual Boy on Nintendo Switch Online was laughable, but now that we're getting two unreleased games and a color change option I'm happy to be proven wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/i-thought-virtual-boy-on-nintendo-switch-online-was-laughable-but-now-that-were-getting-two-unreleased-games-and-a-color-change-option-im-happy-to-be-proven-wrong</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tF9HwKCKmp45YeCFTGgt3o</guid>
      <description>Nintendo Switch Online's Virtual Boy lineup includes two games no one has ever played before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 stylish home office payday finds under $50 at IKEA that finally fix clutter</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/15-stylish-home-office-payday-finds-under-usd50-at-ikea-that-finally-fix-clutter</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wxqWHGZQ8A7Q3aiUgqatrk</guid>
      <description>I went searching IKEA for the cheapest home office gear to keep your workspace organized, and this is what I found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirPods 4 with ANC drop to $119</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airpods-4-with-anc-drop-to-119-153239093.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">309c48af-1160-4213-97d7-a89957a5882f</guid>
      <description>Every time Apple's AirPods 4 with active noise cancelation go on sale I have the same thought: maybe I made a mistake. Don't get me wrong, I love my regular AirPods 4, but the noise canceling aspect makes their sister pair very enticing.
Take now, for instance, when the AirPods 4 with ANC are on sale for $119, down from $179. The 34 percent discount brings them to only $4 more than the standard AirPods 4 current sale price and below their usual $129. While we've seen the ANC model as low as $99, the $119 price tag is the best deal we've seen so far this year.&#160; 


Apple released its fourth-gene...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Minneapolis shooting of Alex Pretti is impacting gun rights politics for Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481794/how-minneapolis-shooting-alex-pretti-impacting-gun-rights-politics-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T15:32:27</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481794/how-minneapolis-shooting-alex-pretti-impacting-gun-rights-politics-trump</guid>
      <description>Prominent Trump supporters have called for a probe into Pretti&#8217;s death.
Prominent Republicans and gun rights advocates helped elicit a White House turnabout this week after bristling over the administration&#8217;s characterization of Alex Pretti, the second person killed this month by a federal officer in Minneapolis, as responsible for his own death because he lawfully possessed a weapon.The death produced no clear shifts in U.S. gun politics or policies, even as President Donald Trump shuffles the lieutenants in charge of his militarized immigration crackdown. But important voices in Trump&#8217;s coal...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
