<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:32:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg says a future without smart glasses is &#8216;hard to imagine&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/mark-zuckerberg-future-smart-glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087229</guid>
      <description>Take Zuckerberg's outlook with a grain of salt. After all, he thought we'd all be hanging out in the metaverse by now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg says Reality Labs will (eventually) stop losing so much money</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/mark-zuckerberg-says-reality-labs-will-eventually-stop-losing-so-much-money-222900157.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">476967e0-b23c-4a75-9f3a-20c86b890732</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg says there's an end in sight to Reality Labs' years of multibillion-dollar losses following the company's layoffs to the metaverse division earlier this year. The CEO said he expects to "gradually reduce" how much money the company is losing as it doubles down on AI glasses and shifts away from virtual reality.Speaking during Meta's fourth-quarter earnings call, Zuckerberg was clear that the changes won't happen soon, but sounded optimistic about the division that lost more than $19 billion in 2025 alone. "For Reality Labs, we are directing most of our investment towards glasse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patreon creators have to switch to subscription billing by November, thanks to Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/patreon-creators-have-to-switch-to-subscription-billing-by-november-thanks-to-apple-203759852.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05720d3d-ef66-4e85-b7fd-998ade177cb9</guid>
      <description>Patreon creators will need to make some changes soon, thanks to Apple. On Wednesday, Patreon said Apple has renewed its requirement that all Patreon creators must move to subscription billing. The deadline to do so is November 1, 2026.Patreon's blog post announcing the change made it clear that it had no other choice. "We strongly disagree with this decision," the company wrote. "Creators need consistency and clarity in order to build healthy, long-term businesses. Instead, creators using legacy billing will now have to endure the whiplash of another policy reversal &#8212; the third such change fro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Gunn Told You Once, He&#8217;s Told You Again: Robert Pattinson Is Not the DCU&#8217;s Batman</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/james-gunn-told-you-once-hes-told-you-again-robert-pattinson-is-not-the-dcus-batman-2000715159</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715159</guid>
      <description>Pattinson's Caped Crusader will stay in the Matt Reeves universe, and the DCU's version will be played by someone else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doom Has Come for Nvidia&#8217;s Graphics Cards, After All</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doom-has-come-for-nvidias-graphics-cards-after-all-2000715184</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715184</guid>
      <description>The latest RTX 50-series is hundreds or thousands of dollars more expensive than at launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audi declares war on &#8216;giant iPad&#8217; dashboards &#8211; as design boss signals return to the analog buttons everyone&#8217;s craving</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/audi-declares-war-on-giant-ipad-dashboards-as-design-boss-signals-return-to-the-analogue-buttons-everyones-craving</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wfZNc7ApFzpFHKVwjRzdMe</guid>
      <description>Audi's design boss sees a return to analog switches and dials for the brand, as massive screens aren't the answer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla invested $2B in Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tesla-invested-2b-in-elon-musks-xai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087539</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's AI company xAI  disclosed earlier this month it had raised $20 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Xbox controller to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23025443/best-xbox-controllers-one-series-x-s</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:46:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23025443/best-xbox-controllers-one-series-x-s</guid>
      <description>We live in a golden age of controllers. The gamepads on the market now are of higher quality, more versatile, and more customizable than anything from even one console generation ago. If you play games on an Xbox Series X or Series S (or a Windows PC), you have the unenviable task of choosing between [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk teases a new image-labeling system for X&#8230; we think?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/elon-musk-teases-a-new-image-labeling-system-for-xwe-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087446</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk says X will begin identifying "manipulated media" but doesn't share details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sea Urchin Apocalypse Is Real, and It Might Be Spreading Globally, Scientists Warn</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-sea-urchin-apocalypse-is-real-and-it-might-be-spreading-globally-scientists-warn-2000715108</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715108</guid>
      <description>New research has uncovered a mass die-off of sea urchins living in the Canary Islands&#8212;one that could signal an ongoing marine pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Is Using Palantir&#8217;s AI Tools to Sort Through Tips</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-is-using-palantirs-ai-tools-to-sort-through-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a474382e93380fc4f4913</guid>
      <description>ICE has been using an AI-powered Palantir system to summarize tips sent to its tip line since last spring, according to a newly released Homeland Security document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Really Needs to Pump the Brakes on That Viral Moltbot AI Agent</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/everyone-really-needs-to-pump-the-brakes-on-that-viral-moltbot-ai-agent-2000715154</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715154</guid>
      <description>It's all fun and games until every aspect of your life is splashed all over the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX is coming to the public markets, and secondaries are already on fire</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/spacex-is-coming-to-the-public-markets-and-secondaries-are-already-on-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3087562</guid>
      <description>paceX is&#160;reportedly lining&#160;up&#160;four major Wall Street banks&#160;for a&#160;2026 IPO&#160;that could provide the&#160;reset&#160;the market needs.&#160; The company just completed a tender offer at an&#160;$800 billion&#160;valuation, and secondary market demand is through the roof. If SpaceX goes public anywhere near its&#160;rumored&#160;$1.5 trillion&#160;valuation, it&#160;could trigger&#160;an IPO cascade for&#160;other&#160;late-stage unicorns like OpenAI, Stripe, and Databricks.&#160; Watch as&#160;Equity&#160;host Rebecca Bellan [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out: hackers are hijacking Microsoft Teams messages to try and get access to your emails - here's what you need to look out for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/watch-out-hackers-are-hijacking-microsoft-teams-messages-to-try-and-get-access-to-your-emails-heres-what-you-need-to-look-out-for</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uJpVATG5WR7knr4QSiXEx8</guid>
      <description>Hackers exploit Microsoft Teams by sending obfuscated invitations and fraudulent billing messages to access emails across multiple global industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers share new insights about the early universe via the Webb Space Telescope</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/astronomers-share-new-insights-about-the-early-universe-via-the-webb-space-telescope-213311848.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58200378-7754-452f-bc21-0d7679f974a9</guid>
      <description>Researchers using the James Webb Space Telescope have found a galaxy that is offering new data about the early stages of the universe's existence. The latest discovery shared by astronomers is about a bright galaxy dubbed MoM-z14. According to the team, this galaxy existed 280 million years after the Big Bang.&#160;The sounds like a long time, but in the context of the universe's estimated 13.8 billion years of existence, that's actually one of the closest examples astronomers have found to the Big Bang's occurrence. As a result, MoM-z14 can offer some insights and some surprises about what the ear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google adds Gemini AI-powered &#8216;auto browse&#8217; to Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869731/google-gemini-ai-chrome-auto-browse</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:32:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869731</guid>
      <description>Google is launching a new "auto browse" feature inside Chrome that can perform multi-step tasks on your behalf. The Gemini AI-powered capability is coming to Google AI Pro and Ultra subscribers in the US, and can do things like research hotel and flight costs, schedule appointments, fill out online forms, manage subscriptions, and more. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla says production-ready Optimus robot is coming soon</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/869746/tesla-optimus-gen-3-q1-2026-earnings</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:28:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869746</guid>
      <description>In its earnings report, Tesla says that the third-generation version of its Optimus humanoid robot "meant for mass production" will be unveiled in the first quarter of 2026. This new version of Optimus will include "major upgrades from version 2.5, including our latest hand design." And the company is making preparations for the first production [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why predictable AI will finally fix customer experience</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482953/why-predictable-ai-will-finally-fix-customer-experience</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T21:25:15</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482953/why-predictable-ai-will-finally-fix-customer-experience</guid>
      <description>Four shifts will define who succeeds in the CX reset.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft reports strong cloud earnings in Q2 as gaming declines</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869493/microsoft-q2-2026-earnings-revenue-profits-windows-xbox-gaming-surface</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:23:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869493</guid>
      <description>Microsoft just posted the second quarter of its 2026 fiscal financial results. The software maker made $81.3 billion in revenue and a net income of $30.9 billion during Q3. Revenue is up 17 percent, and net income has increased by 23 percent. The holiday quarter saw PC shipments grow unexpectedly amid an ongoing RAM shortage. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI security startup Outtake raises $40M from Iconiq, Satya Nadella, Bill Ackman, and other big names</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/ai-security-startup-outtake-raises-40m-from-iconiq-satya-nadella-bill-ackman-and-other-big-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087428</guid>
      <description>Outtake makes an agentic cybersecurity platform to help enterprises detect identity fraud. Its angel investors read like a who's who of tech industry names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla profit tanked 46% in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tesla-earnings-profit-q4-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087513</guid>
      <description>The company's sales fell for a second year in a row, as Tesla looks to AI and robotics, including a new $2 billion investment in CEO Elon Musk's company xAI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Arco&#8217; Is as Close to an Instant Animated Classic as It Gets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/arco-neon-natalie-portman-mark-ruffalo-animated-movie-review-2000705262</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705262</guid>
      <description>Neon's sci-fi animated feature features the voices of Natalie Portman and Mark Ruffalo and is playing in theaters now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow inks another AI partnership, this time with Anthropic</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/servicenow-inks-another-ai-partnership-this-time-with-anthropic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087398</guid>
      <description>ServiceNow partners with Anthropic just a week after announcing a partnership with OpenAI as the company takes a multi-model approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla hits a grim milestone: its second straight year of decline</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/869603/tesla-q4-2025-earnings-revenue-profit-musk-robotaxis</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:08:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869603</guid>
      <description>Tesla just reported its second consecutive year of declining revenue and profits, further complicating Elon Musk's $1 trillion effort to transform his company into a leader in AI and robotics. Meanwhile, the global EV market continues to grow, seemingly in spite of the pioneering company's setbacks. Tesla said it earned $840 million in net income [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy TriFold is coming to America: Price, release date confirmed</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-everything-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03aXLP36c4KEfAdH65EPOMB</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy TriFold is available in South Korea, but U.S. shoppers finally have a release date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina Measles Outbreak Becomes America&#8217;s Largest in 25 Years</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/south-carolina-measles-outbreak-becomes-americas-largest-in-25-years-2000715084</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715084</guid>
      <description>Thanks, anti-vaxxers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February&#8217;s PS Plus Monthly Games include Undisputed and Subnautica: Below Zero</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/februarys-ps-plus-monthly-games-include-undisputed-and-subnautica-below-zero-205100847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d778183-4789-433b-a1e9-27b44e3900e0</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;ve somehow almost reached the end of January already, which means it&#8217;s time for Sony to divulge the list of PlayStation Plus Monthly Games for February. They are Undisputed, Subnautica: Below Zero, Ultros and Ace Combat 7: Skies Unknown. If you have a PS Plus subscription on any tier, you can claim these starting on February 3. After claiming them, these games will stay in your library as long as your PS Plus plan remains active.&#160;Undisputed (PS5) is a 2024 boxing game with dozens of licensed fighters across several weight classes. They include legendary figures like Muhammad Ali and Sugar R...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube&amp;#8217;s top AI slop channels are disappearing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869684/youtube-top-ai-channels-removed-kapwing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T15:47:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869684</guid>
      <description>YouTube appears to have taken down two of the most popular AI slop channels on its platform, along with several others. A report from Kapwing found that a channel called CuentosFacianantes no longer exists on the platform after amassing more than 5.9 million subscribers and over 1.2 billion total views. In a November 2025 report, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Wonderful DIY Lego Typewriter Does What Lego Couldn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-wonderful-diy-lego-typewriter-does-what-lego-couldnt-2000715081</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715081</guid>
      <description>When you absolutely have to type a letter using Lego, accept no substitutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now that's a team-up: Samsung and Nvidia expected to join forces to feature 'revolutionary' HBM4 memory modules in upcoming Vera Rubin hardware</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/now-thats-a-team-up-samsung-and-nvidia-expected-to-join-forces-to-feature-revolutionary-nbm4-memory-modules-in-upcoming-vera-rubin-hardware</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qMCVftVxRXZwysLE5dzN6n</guid>
      <description>Samsung and Nvidia coordinate HBM4 memory and Rubin accelerators, emphasizing integration, production timing, and memory bandwidth for AI infrastructure deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luminar sale approved despite last-minute mystery bid</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/luminar-sale-approved-despite-last-minute-mystery-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087141</guid>
      <description>An unidentified bidder submitted a Hail Mary offer that was "substantially higher" than the winning bid at auction. Founder Austin Russell has been circling a bid, but it's not clear he was behind it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
