<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:32:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Starlink Is About to Enter a New Conflict Zone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starlink-is-about-to-enter-a-new-conflict-zone-2000705523</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705523</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s satellite megaconstellation will provide free broadband internet access to Venezuela following the U.S. incursion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Air, Gravity EVs Get a Much-Needed Map Update</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lucid-air-gravity-evs-get-a-much-needed-map-update-2000705467</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705467</guid>
      <description>Lucid&#8217;s EVs will use HERE location data to improve EV routing and advanced driving features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin could be gearing up for an exciting but overdue Health Status upgrade &#8211; here&#8217;s what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-trackers/garmin-could-be-gearing-up-for-an-exciting-but-overdue-health-status-upgrade-heres-what-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfBFGrdL6tpozMgearTBQH</guid>
      <description>Garmin's Health Status feature has one small setback, but this new upgrade could allow you to keep tabs on health trends over longer time periods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep your home warm with the Google Nest Learning Thermostat, now only $230</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/854979/google-nest-thermometer-8bitdo-everboom-deals-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:14:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854979</guid>
      <description>While everyone is paying attention to the cool new stuff being exhibited at CES at this very moment, there are some good deals to be had on devices that are already available but equally cool. For example, the 4th-gen Google Nest Learning Thermostat, which our reviewer called &#8220;a stunner,&#8221; is now available for $229.99 at [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Knight confirms 35% of A Thousand Blows season 2 is based on real-life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/steven-knight-confirms-35-percent-of-a-thousand-blows-season-2-is-based-on-real-life</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WRaLyQFxgYQ6NkgSAvRHgW</guid>
      <description>What&#8217;s true in A Thousand Blows season 2? Steven Knight breaks down the real-life events that inspired the next chapter of the historical crime drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec les OpenWear Stereo Pro, Xiaomi propose des &#233;couteurs ouverts et pas chers gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2928883_avec-les-openwear-stereo-pro-xiaomi-propose-des-ecouteurs-ouverts-et-pas-chers-grace-a-cette-offre</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2928883_avec-les-openwear-stereo-pro-xiaomi-propose-des-ecouteurs-ouverts-et-pas-chers-grace-a-cette-offre</guid>
      <description>
Les Xiaomi OpenWear Stereo Pro sont des &#233;couteurs ouverts sans-fil dans un &#233;crin premium, qui se posent autour de l'oreille comme des bijoux, disponibles &#224; 115,31 euros au lieu de 149,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une cyberattaque a frapp&#233; l&#8217;Office fran&#231;ais de l&#8217;immigration et de l&#8217;int&#233;gration, des millions de donn&#233;es vol&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/cyberattaque-frappe-office-francais-immigration-integration.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318175</guid>
      <description>Les donn&#233;es personnelles de centaines de milliers d&#8217;&#233;trangers en France se retrouvent en vente sur le dark web. L&#8217;Office fran&#231;ais de l&#8217;immigration et de l&#8217;int&#233;gration a en effet &#233;t&#233; pirat&#233; par le biais d'un prestataire tiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's new 45W charger from CES is already $10 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/ankers-new-45w-charger-from-ces-is-already-10-off-160707324.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker introduced a nifty little charger at CES 2026, which is a refresh of the pre-existing Nano Charger. It's already on sale for $30, which is a discount of $10. These are preorders, however, with shipments officially going out on January 20.
The 45W charger includes a screen that displays real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to ensure a longer battery lifespan. 


To that end, it works with just about everything. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $20 smart scale is the easiest way to track your 2026 health wins</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-renpho-smart-scale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">061e6gvYlICMvHg8HPWJcHT</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 5, you can get the Renpho Smart Scale for $19.99, down from $34.99, at Amazon. That's a 43% discount or $15 in savings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundcore Is Trying to Fix the Worst Problem With Open Wireless Earbuds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/soundcore-is-trying-to-fix-the-worst-problem-with-open-wireless-earbuds-2000705179</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705179</guid>
      <description>The AeroFit 2 Pro wireless earbuds can shapeshift into open-ear and ANC modes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon veut r&#233;duire le temps perdu &#224; choisir quelque chose &#224; la t&#233;l&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/amazon-veut-reduire-le-temps-perdu-a-choisir-quelque-chose-a-la-tele.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318194</guid>
      <description>Amazon rafra&#238;chit et surtout acc&#233;l&#232;re son interface Fire TV, en se donnant pour mission de r&#233;duire le temps pass&#233; &#224; scroller pour trouver quelque chose &#224; regarder. Et dans la foul&#233;e, le g&#233;ant du commerce en ligne lance une nouvelle gamme de t&#233;l&#233;s connect&#233;es &#224; afficher au mur fa&#231;on tableau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing the Alliwava U58 mini PC, I realized I&#8217;d seen this platform before - and with a little effort, this could have been great</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/alliwava-u58-mini-pc-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Udxk3CiSZGTye5SmjUZWAo</guid>
      <description>The Alliwava U58 offers plenty of functionality, but lacks the performance of mini PCs with more modern chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Is Still Killing a Disturbing Number of Americans, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/covid-19-is-still-killing-a-disturbing-number-of-americans-study-finds-2000705483</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705483</guid>
      <description>Between 2022 and 2024, covid-19 killed roughly 100,000 Americans annually, new research by CDC scientists shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's Soundcore Work AI voice recorder offers transcription in an ultra-compact form factor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/ankers-soundcore-work-ai-voice-recorder-offers-transcription-in-an-ultra-compact-form-factor-160030844.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">584da5c1-6cf1-4105-a4b2-9a4950e76dd1</guid>
      <description>Anker's sub-brand Soundcore just announced a new AI voice recorder at CES 2026. The appropriately-named Work voice recorder is primarily intended for professionals, but also seems useful for students and anyone else who wants an AI to transcribe conversations.
To that end, the company promises 97-percent transcription accuracy via the AI algorithm. The affiliated app will also provide summaries of conversations, like many modern AI tools. Users can double-tap the gadget during important parts of a conversation to ensure it gets preferential treatment.
Anker/Soundcore 
None of this is really th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker unveils a new lineup of chargers and docks at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/anker-unveils-a-new-lineup-of-chargers-and-docks-at-ces-2026-160021195.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a59925-1c86-46f9-b8b4-44c46f9069f6</guid>
      <description>Anker, one of the leaders in third-party chargers, has unveiled a new portfolio of "smart" chargers and docks at CES 2026. The company says the lineup adds improved visual interfaces, faster Qi2 wireless charging and "upgraded ecosystems" for the latest line of iPhone models.
First up is the Anker Nano Charger, which features a smart display, 180-degree foldable prongs and provides up to 45W of power. The plug can identify the exact iPhone model connected and then deliver the right amount of power for your phone. Anker says the Nano uses three-stage power delivery and a "Care Mode" that the co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eufy just revealed a tech-heavy baby bottle washer at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/eufy-just-revealed-a-tech-heavy-baby-bottle-washer-at-ces-160021666.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe2ebe3-51a1-4f7f-8139-4f32f7b3e51d</guid>
      <description>Anker's sub-brand Eufy just revealed a high-tech baby bottle washer at CES 2026. The Bottle Washer S1 is filled to the brim with nifty features that should please frazzled parents.
It's been designed to clean deeper than rival models. The Bottle Washer S1 features a built-in water softener, a first in the product category, which should help remove stubborn minerals. It also includes proprietary HydroBlast technology that cleans baby bottles from every angle. This is assisted by the inclusion of a multi-layer rotating spray.
It sterilizes up to 212 degrees Fahrenheit and dries in just 40 minute...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundcore's Nebula P1i portable projector launches in early 2026 for $369</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/soundcores-nebula-p1i-portable-projector-launches-in-early-2026-for-369-160020321.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e0b60a4-b5e9-4bb0-9f39-456659e13820</guid>
      <description>If you had your eye on Nebula P1 projector but $799 is too rich for your blood, Soundcore has a new option at CES 2026. The Anker affiliate just unveiled the 1080p Nebula P1i portable projector that's less than half the price and even more portable, albeit with less brightness.&#160;
Instead of detachable speakers like the Nebula P1, the P1i's speakers are embedded in the projector and can be flipped open and tilted through 180 degrees. It also lacks the P1's tilting projector body and instead offers a stand that can incline the projector from zero to 12 degrees.&#160;
Though it offers the same 1080p ma...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's new AeroFit 2 earbuds can switch between open-ear and ANC form factors</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/ankers-new-aerofit-2-earbuds-can-switch-between-open-ear-and-anc-form-factors-160014977.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39d9829e-e044-4b85-a493-4fe2cd29ec83</guid>
      <description>Open-ear wireless earbuds are great for running, when keeping some awareness of the world around you is necessary, but not so good when you want premium audio features that require a good seal, like active noise cancellation. At CES 2026, Anker is trying to change that with the Soundcore AeroFit 2 Pro, the company's first open-ear earbuds that offer ANC.
The Soundcore AeroFit 2 Pro features a similar adjustable ear-hook design to Anker's previous AeroFit 2 and AeroFit, but with one extra level of adjustment to help the earbuds create more of a seal in your ear. That change, plus tweaks to the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo's Ultimate 3E gamepad for Xbox offers swappable button modules and joysticks</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/8bitdos-ultimate-3e-gamepad-for-xbox-offers-swappable-button-modules-and-joysticks-160011248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b17f40-a1c7-4317-ac2c-b0ac8a06d512</guid>
      <description>8BitDo just revealed a new gamepad at CES and it's a doozy. The Ultimate 3E Controller for XBox is a modular marvel that should suit just about any configuration preference. That's because many elements are swappable.
There are two different button modules, each with a different feel when pressing down. There are several joystick options, including standard, tall and thick-neck designs. The controller even ships with a pair of D-pad options. One is intended for precision and the other for "smooth, directional rolls."
8BitDo
There are other bells and whistles here. The Ultimate 3E offers a 1000...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Course &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; Has Made a Billion Dollars Already</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avatar-fire-and-ash-box-off-2000705494</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705494</guid>
      <description>The future's bright and full of box office records on Pandora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker Teases a New Whole Home Hybrid Battery Backup System</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anker-teases-a-new-whole-home-hybrid-battery-backup-system-2000705254</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705254</guid>
      <description>The company says it&#8217;s the first of its kind, but remains mum on the specifics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo&#8217;s new wireless Xbox controller has swappable ABXY button switches</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/848331/8bitdo-ultimate-3e-controller-xbox-wireless-tmr-swappable-joysticks</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848331</guid>
      <description>8BitDo's second officially licensed wireless Xbox controller is also its most expensive gamepad to date. The 8BitDo Ultimate 3E Controller for Xbox follows last August's Ultimate 3-mode Controller for Xbox - Rare 40th Anniversary Edition with some excellent upgrades, less branding, and a big price hike. It's got tunneling magnetoresistance (TMR) joysticks, Hall effect triggers [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s powerful new Eufy S2 robot vacuum doubles as an aromatherapy diffuser</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/850483/eufy-robot-vacuum-omni-s2-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850483</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Anker debuted the Eufy S2, a powerful robot vacuum and mop hybrid that cleans your floors while also perfuming your home. According to the company, the robovac features a built-in "aromatherapy system" with scent options that include bamboo, sage, bergamot, lychee, citrus, and basil. The idea is to perfume your space while [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker adds features and style to its smart home security</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851341/anker-eufy-doorbell-smart-lock-wall-light-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851341</guid>
      <description>Anker is introducing a number of new devices for the new year as part of its Eufy line of smart home appliances, including the Eufy Video Doorbell S4, the Eufy Smart Lock E40, and the Eufy Solar Wall Light Cam S4. New designs and upgraded features are some of the main attractions of this year's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker put a screen on its smallest 45W charger</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852742/anker-nano-charger-prime-wireless-charging-station-power-strip</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852742</guid>
      <description>Anker has announced three new charging solutions at CES 2026 including an update to its compact Nano Charger. For the first time it now features a small screen on the front providing details on power delivery and your connected phone's charge level. The new Anker Nano Charger is comparable in size to the 45W single-port [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s AeroFit 2 Pro can be worn as open-ear headphones or ANC earbuds</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852887/anker-soundcore-aerofit-2-pro-sleep-a30-special-boom-go-3i-bluetooth-headphones-earbuds-speaker</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852887</guid>
      <description>Anker announced a new version of its AeroFit Pro headphones at CES 2026 that give you the option to hear the world around you, or block it out using ANC. The traditional design of open-ear headphones leave your ears wide open, but Anker's new Soundcore AeroFit 2 Pro have an adjustable ear hook design that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker Soundcore unveils open earbuds that can adapt to be ear-sealing ANC buds too &#8212; is this the best of both audio worlds?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/anker-soundcore-unveils-open-earbuds-that-can-adapt-to-be-ear-sealing-anc-buds-too-is-this-the-best-of-both-audio-worlds</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4xSj39y5TDFXTKfWEqNa79</guid>
      <description>Anker's new adaptable earbuds are tiny transformers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 5 days in, the best fitness headphones of 2026 have already been announced &#8212; if they&#8217;ll stick the landing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/only-5-days-in-the-best-fitness-headphones-of-2026-have-already-been-announced-if-theyll-stick-the-landing</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6XS9yRqV3b4ohmdaqUH4nf</guid>
      <description>The Anker Soundcore Aerofit 2 Pro are open earbuds that can switch over to become standard fitness 'phones, fixing problems with the form factor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Max sticks with its tried and tested formula for The Pitt season 2 &#8212; and it&#8217;s the best medicine possible</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/the-pitt-season-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LFP3p5QLsUdk3Udxfg5ieD</guid>
      <description>I've been counting down the days until the return of hit HBO Max show The Pitt season 2, and I'm pleased so say I wasn't disappointed &#8211; and you won't be either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's CES smart home lineup includes a $1,600 Eufy robovac</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/ankers-ces-smart-home-lineup-includes-a-1600-eufy-robovac-160000133.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d15ea7-428b-47b4-a860-f46048114046</guid>
      <description>It seems like only a few years ago that Anker made nothing more than batteries and chargers. But 15 years into its history, the company's CES portfolio continues to illustrate how much it's expanded. Among other announcements, the company has a new robot vacuum, video doorbell, outdoor light and smart lock. They're all rolling out under Anker's Eufy smart home brand.The company hopes its Eufy Clean Robot Vacuum Omni S2 will be your next robovac. The $1,600 device vacuums with 100 AW suction, and it mops, too. Anker claims the vac works on shag carpets up to about 2 inches (5 cm) in pile height...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab expands its gaming lineup at CES with keyboards, mice and headsets</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/jlab-expands-its-gaming-lineup-at-ces-with-keyboards-mice-and-headsets-160000419.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71e227ca-776e-415e-9cbc-9a90ddc7245a</guid>
      <description>JLab, known for quality consumer audio that doesn't break the bank, is diving further into gaming. At CES 2026, the company has new keyboards, mice and headsets aimed at gamers. Sticking with the brand's "bang for your buck" angle, they're available in three reasonably priced tiers.The entry-level tier adopts the Nightfall brand name, which JLab already used on its 2023 gaming headphones. (They're still available and now come in pink and white colors, alongside the preexisting black.) Joining them is a $40 "ultra-light" mouse that weighs 53g. Also costing $40 is a Nightfall keyboard that the c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab adds ANC to its tiny wireless  earbuds for CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/jlab-adds-anc-to-its-tiny-wireless-earbuds-for-ces-2026-160000342.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c005e93b-7857-49e8-b831-a47b62090bec</guid>
      <description>JLab is following up its ultra-affordable JBuds Mini from 2023 with a new model that supports active noise cancellation at CES 2026. The JBuds Mini ANC are still as tiny as the company's previous wireless earbuds, but now offer customizable ANC for the same $40 price.In comparison to the company's JLab Go POP+, which is only $30, JLab says its new model features a 50 percent smaller charging case, and 30 percent smaller earbuds. The JBuds Mini ANC comes in gray, dark blue, red and pink, and is IP55-rated for dust and sweat resistance. JLab says the Mini ANC get 6.5 hours of battery life per ea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Teens spend hour-plus on their phones at school</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/teens-spend-an-hour-on-phones-at-school</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06SUnKzhxmt0EftVkEqiInX</guid>
      <description>Teens are on Instagram, TikTok, Snapchat, and YouTube while at school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pitt Season 2 review: Big changes ahead for Noah Wyles stellar medical drama</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/the-pitt-season-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03c9euQAhw3vczOCFxoQxiz</guid>
      <description>Emmy-winning drama "The Pitt" remains captivating in Season 2, with new characters upsetting the balance in just the right way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Soundcore introduces new open earbuds with active noise cancellation</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-soundcore-sleep-a30-special-aerofit-2-pro-release</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00bbDCSHTOM7OMPIv9CbueR</guid>
      <description>The Soundcore Sleep A30 Special earbuds will be available as of Jan. 6, with the AeroFit Pro 2 earbuds following shortly after.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le syst&#232;me Tizen des TV et vid&#233;oprojecteurs Samsung &#233;volue avec encore plus d&#8217;IA</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2929151_le-systeme-tizen-des-tv-et-videoprojecteurs-samsung-evolue-avec-encore-plus-dia</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2929151_le-systeme-tizen-des-tv-et-videoprojecteurs-samsung-evolue-avec-encore-plus-dia</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES 2026 de Las Vegas, Samsung a pr&#233;sent&#233; plusieurs &#233;volutions int&#233;ressantes pour son syst&#232;me Tizen qui anime les TV et les vid&#233;oprojecteurs de la marque.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: The latest news, surprises, strange tech, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is here. See the latest news on bleeding-edge tech, EV advancements, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fantastic SteelSeries Arctis GameBuds have returned to their lowest ever price at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-fantastic-steelseries-arctis-gamebuds-have-returned-to-their-lowest-ever-price-at-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">h6TFnuYQ26nyxenHiSMi5o</guid>
      <description>The SteelSeries Arctis GameBuds are a fantastic earbud option for gamers, and right now we're highlighting them selling at a lowest-ever Amazon price in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Govee lamps light up CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-govee-lights-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ph2VEXc6Q83imoYSj5P6o</guid>
      <description>Three new Govee flagship lamps and lighting options were announced at CES 2026, as well as tech advancements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Razr Fold leak suggests Samsung Galaxy Z Fold has major compeition</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/motorola-razr-fold-leak-samsung-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05iFtmwbqhS0eC5rBzvzqX6</guid>
      <description>Motorola's rumored book-style foldable device might have what it takes to stand up to Samsung's Galaxy Z Fold line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi vous ne devriez plus vous faire filmer par les webcams des lieux touristiques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/pourquoi-vous-ne-devriez-plus-vous-faire-filmer-par-les-webcams-des-lieux-touristiques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318163</guid>
      <description>Les cam&#233;ras qui filment et diffusent en permanence un lieu touristique doivent aussi respecter le r&#232;glement europ&#233;en sur les donn&#233;es personnelles. Elles ne sont pas cens&#233;es collecter des donn&#233;es personnelles et donc filmer des personnes dans leur quotidien, a rappel&#233; la CNIL, qui a proc&#233;d&#233; &#224; plusieurs contr&#244;les.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular debloating tool now has fresh powers to strip out Windows 11's AI features &#8211; but I'd proceed with caution</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/a-popular-debloating-tool-now-has-fresh-powers-to-strip-out-windows-11s-ai-features-but-id-proceed-with-caution</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UzLiZUScTVNAABceyRhPpC</guid>
      <description>Hate AI in Windows 11? You're not alone judging by the popularity of AI debloating tools, and this one just got a major update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Egypt vs Benin for *FREE* &#8212; live stream AFCON 2025/26 knockout tie, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/egypt-vs-benin-afcon-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wdfoh9VHVuBNg4A6A2LYe9</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Egypt vs Benin live streams for FREE from anywhere, as Salah and Marmoush aim to find their range in the AFCON last 16 clash in Agadir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 will be smarter, safer and with a much better soundtrack. Here's why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/phone-accessories/2026-will-be-smarter-safer-and-with-a-much-better-soundtrack-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EmLrJUQfPTDFvi3fT4hn8S</guid>
      <description>Baseus raises the bar in mobile digital, smart audio and smart security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix drops emotional trailer for Stranger Things Season 5 documentary</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/netflix-stranger-things-5-making-of-documentary-trailer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04zGO9dxw7S0bQBsRRMPSVq</guid>
      <description>Netflix has dropped a trailer for "One Last Adventure: The Making of Stranger Things 5", a behind-the-scenes documentary for the final season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Series 11 is at the lowest price we've ever seen</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/the-apple-watch-series-11-is-at-the-lowest-price-weve-ever-seen-154609747.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9398dfc3-7cc2-4fa1-ba51-8f9fa52c78af</guid>
      <description>The Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for the lowest price we've ever seen. You can pick up the smartwatch for $300, which is 25 percent off its regular price, a discount of $100. Discounts tend to increase as we get closer to September, when the next generation of Apple Watch is typically announced.
The Series 11 is our best overall smartwatch pick, and we gave it a score of 90 out of 100 in our hands-on review. We were impressed with the battery life, which lasted longer than the 24 hours it's rated for in our testing. We also liked how lightweight and thin the watch is. The 9.7mm thick case ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DS va bient&#244;t lancer une voiture &#233;lectrique et hybride cruciale pour la marque : voici les premi&#232;res images du DS N&#176;7</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ds-automobiles/2928655_ds-va-bientot-lancer-une-voiture-electrique-et-hybride-cruciale-pour-la-marque-voici-les-premieres-images-du-ds-n7</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ds-automobiles/2928655_ds-va-bientot-lancer-une-voiture-electrique-et-hybride-cruciale-pour-la-marque-voici-les-premieres-images-du-ds-n7</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s le succ&#232;s du DS 7 Crossback, le fleuron fran&#231;ais de Stellantis, DS, s'appr&#234;te &#224; offrir une deuxi&#232;me g&#233;n&#233;ration &#224; son SUV best-seller. Ce mod&#232;le, probablement d&#233;nomm&#233; DS N&#176;7, partagera de nombreux &#233;l&#233;ments techniques avec le 3008 &#233;lectrique de chez Peugeot.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Withings Body Scan 2 smart scale promises to be your &#8216;longevity station&#8217; &#8211; thanks to over 60 biomarkers that predict your future health</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/the-withings-body-scan-2-smart-scale-promises-to-be-your-longevity-station-thanks-to-over-60-biomarkers-that-predict-your-future-health</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nieFbqCPsPkkeU7PBnxUXC</guid>
      <description>Withings&#8217; Body Scan 2 is a new smart scale that is packed with AI and advanced health-measuring tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Hisense CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-hisense-ces-2026-press-conference-live-190040504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9486b306-eae4-49da-a805-9b5cf78d2fb9</guid>
      <description>Xinhua News Agency via Getty Images
Hisense is typically best known for its affordable electronics and home appliances, from TVs to refrigerators. But at CES 2025, the China-based company showed off its premium side with a massive 136-inch micro LED TV &#8212; now available for a jaw-dropping $100,000. So what's in store for this year's show? New leadership, for starters.
The company has two new hires, including Chief Marketing Officer Sarah Larsen and Chief Commercial Officer James Fishler. In a press release, Hisense said Fishler's experience in home entertainment, appliances and HVAC is important...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette bague connect&#233;e ajoute des fonctions bien utiles et encore trop rares sur le march&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2929065_cette-bague-connectee-ajoute-des-fonctions-bien-utiles-et-encore-trop-rares-sur-le-marche</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2929065_cette-bague-connectee-ajoute-des-fonctions-bien-utiles-et-encore-trop-rares-sur-le-marche</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES de Las Vegas, RingConn a lev&#233; le voile sur sa troisi&#232;me g&#233;n&#233;ration de bague connect&#233;e. La nouvelle RingConn Gen 3 profite notamment de deux nouveaut&#233;s particuli&#232;rement commodes. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les 10 smartphones les plus populaires de la semaine sur Frandroid : l&#8217;ann&#233;e commence comme elle a termin&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2491986_les-10-smartphones-les-plus-populaires-de-la-semaine-sur-frandroid-lannee-commence-comme-elle-a-terminee</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2491986_les-10-smartphones-les-plus-populaires-de-la-semaine-sur-frandroid-lannee-commence-comme-elle-a-terminee</guid>
      <description>
Pour notre top 10 des smartphones les plus populaires de la semaine sur Frandroid, certaines marques prennent le dessus. Sur ce classement, nous retrouvons Samsung, Xiaomi et OnePlus.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsair annulerait des commandes de m&#233;moire RAM pour une raison qui enflamme Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/corsair/2928801_corsair-annulerait-des-commandes-de-memoire-ram-pour-une-raison-qui-enflamme-internet</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/corsair/2928801_corsair-annulerait-des-commandes-de-memoire-ram-pour-une-raison-qui-enflamme-internet</guid>
      <description>
La marque Corsair subit les foudres des internautes apr&#232;s plusieurs annulations de commande impliquant des barrettes de m&#233;moire RAM DDR5.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch today's Bosch CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/how-to-watch-todays-bosch-ces-2026-press-conference-live-130020554.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9086383-b545-4c70-a9ca-34644261e45c</guid>
      <description>You might think of Bosch as the modern European equivalent to what the GE brand once was in America. It's a home appliance name (thanks to its partnership with Siemens), but the German multinational brand's core business is really about providing the underlying technology and engineering that powers cars, homes and factories around the world. That focus is reflected at CES 2026, where much of what Bosch is unveiling is intended to be licensed to other companies rather than sold as Bosch-branded products on store shelves.
Case in point is Bosch's automotive plans at CES. The company is showcasi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 could be the year we move beyond smartphones &#8212; led by a Sam Altman and Jony Ive-designed AI device</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/2026-could-be-the-year-we-move-beyond-smartphones-led-by-a-sam-altman-and-jony-ive-designed-ai-device</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BxVARcp4mzFhDyPXRNTg4G</guid>
      <description>2026 could mark the beginning of the post-smartphone era, with OpenAI betting on a Jony Ive-designed, audio-first AI device to redefine how we interact with technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $90 Kindle deal is the best way to finally tackle your TBR list</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-kindle-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036dWGLKPwa3lZhqw6gKMt2</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 5, you can get Amazon's 2024 Kindle (16GB RAM) in Matcha or Black for just $89.99, down from $109.99, at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung unveiled AI-powered products at CES 2026: Everything announced from the year's first press conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/samsung-unveiled-ai-powered-products-at-ces-2026-everything-announced-from-the-years-first-press-conference-230059247.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f895c55-a52d-430d-945c-f98a90fd611d</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 kicked off with a big press conference from one of the biggest companies at the show: Samsung. The tech giant held its "first look" presentation to show off new home products and make a plethora of AI-infused announcements. New TVs, speakers, projectors and more were among the headliners, along with updated gaming monitors and soundbars.
Many of the products announced on stage were not actually new, but instead had been dripped out by Samsung recently. Like its minimalist Music Studio speakers or new Micro RGB TVs. We did get a closer look a previously undisclosed set, a flagship 130-...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 kicks off in Las Vegas this week, showcasing AI, robotics, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468992/ces-2026-kicks-off-las-vegas-this-week-showcasing-ai-robotics-more</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T15:25:24</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468992/ces-2026-kicks-off-las-vegas-this-week-showcasing-ai-robotics-more</guid>
      <description>The Consumer Technology Association&#8217;s trade show launches this week in Las Vegas.
With the start of the New Year squarely behind us, it&#8217;s once again time for the annual CES trade show to shine a spotlight on the latest tech that companies plan to offer in 2026.The multiday event, organized by the Consumer Technology Association, kicks off this week in Las Vegas, where advances across industries like robotics, healthcare, vehicles, wearables, gaming and more are set to be on display.Artificial intelligence will be anchored in nearly everything, again, as the tech industry explores offerings con...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch: We smashed Pluto TVs holiday rage room</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/pluto-tv-rage-room</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07MkrJ2XnyeQvCklD6w1wbO</guid>
      <description>We went wild at Pluto TV's holiday rage room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 grammes pour tout retenir : SwitchBot s&#8217;attaque au march&#233; de l&#8217;assistant vocal portable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2926717_18-grammes-pour-tout-retenir-switchbot-sattaque-au-marche-de-lassistant-vocal-portable</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2926717_18-grammes-pour-tout-retenir-switchbot-sattaque-au-marche-de-lassistant-vocal-portable</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s l'&#233;chec cuisant du Humane AI Pin, on pensait le march&#233; des "badges IA" mort et enterr&#233;. Mais SwitchBot n'est pas d'accord. Au CES 2026, ils d&#233;gainent le MindClip, un assistant vocal discret con&#231;u pour &#234;tre votre "second cerveau". La promesse est belle : transformer vos conversations en to-do lists. La r&#233;alit&#233; ? Elle d&#233;pendra de l'abonnement.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versant stock price sinks on Nasdaq trading debut as Comcast spinoff tests investor appetite for legacy cable TV</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469058/versant-stock-price-today-comcast-spinoff-sinks-nasdaq-debut</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T15:14:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469058/versant-stock-price-today-comcast-spinoff-sinks-nasdaq-debut</guid>
      <description>The newly separate company owns well-known channels like CNBC and MS NOW, but it lacks the distribution power of streaming and cable giants.
Is cable television truly dead? The markets are about to test the hypothesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickstart your 2026 resolutions while the NordicTrack T Series 5 treadmill is on sale for $479</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-nordictrack-t-series-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04rEZVjNpRIQ2Bi72hL8nRH</guid>
      <description>The NordicTrack T Series 5 treadmill is on sale at Amazon for $479 at Amazon, down from the normal price of $599. That's a 20% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic LastPass breach enabling cryptocurrency theft, investigation reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/historic-lastpass-breach-enabling-cryptocurrency-theft-investigation-reveals</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CnfBYNHNNPWnec82inqVp5</guid>
      <description>Tens of millions of dollars are being stolen through cracked LastPass vaults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the RugOne Xever 7 Pro - a lightweight rugged phone with removeable battery that&#8217;s dragged down by its processor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/phone-communications/rugone-xever-7-pro-rugged-phone-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aCYeKBwafbYcj92ypneZW9</guid>
      <description>The RugOne Xever 7 Pro is a lightweight, rugged design that uses swapable batteries to extend its operating life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>281 trillions de couleurs ? Le chiffre totalement absurde (mais dr&#244;le) de la nouvelle lampe Govee</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927355_govee-devoile-3-nouvelles-lampes-matter-au-ces-2026-dont-un-puit-de-lumiere-artificiel</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927355_govee-devoile-3-nouvelles-lampes-matter-au-ces-2026-dont-un-puit-de-lumiere-artificiel</guid>
      <description>
Vous trouviez qu'il manquait de l'intelligence artificielle dans votre plafonnier ? Non ? Govee l'a fait quand m&#234;me. Le fabricant chinois profite du CES pour d&#233;voiler sa nouvelle gamme, dont la Floor Lamp 3 et ses promesses colorim&#233;triques absurdes. Mais le produit qui nous pla&#238;t, c'est peut-&#234;tre ce faux puit de lumi&#232;re ultra-lumineux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is rolling out Alexa+ for the web so you can use its assistant without a dedicated device</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazon-is-rolling-out-alexa-for-the-web-so-you-can-use-its-assistant-without-a-dedicated-device-150053826.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48cb763b-0931-4cb1-967d-46f5e4086fd8</guid>
      <description>You no longer need an Amazon device to summon Alexa since the AI assistant will be available on the Alexa.com website. Amazon will roll out the web client to its Alexa+ Early Access customers first, still featuring the company's new and improved AI assistant that was announced in February.
The web model won't be much different from the existing Alexa+ that's already available on Echo devices, Fire TV and Fire tablets. However, instead of buying into the Amazon ecosystem, Early Access customers can use any web browser to get Alexa+'s help with everything from basic questions to complex tasks, l...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. Abrams&#8217; Mysterious Next Movie May Have Found Its Title</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jj-abrams-new-movie-great-beyond-2000705331</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705331</guid>
      <description>Plus, is it really time for next Doctor rumors on 'Doctor Who' already?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bee has been busy since its acquisition by Amazon last year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/bee-has-been-busy-since-its-acquisition-by-amazon-last-year-150025311.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d1d6a66-084e-4cfc-9d45-8f198a4a756f</guid>
      <description>Bee, the company behind an always-listening AI wearable that Amazon acquired last year, has announced new features in a status update. The device is designed to run in the background of daily life and captures conversations or thoughts spoken aloud. Recording can be started or stopped with the push of a button.
Co-founder of Bee, Maria de Lourdes Zollo, says the company has shipped four major updates that will run on the existing Bee Pioneer hardware. The first is &#8220;Actions,&#8221; which connects Bee to a user's email and calendar and works to turn spoken commitments into actions. The company says th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ember Artline is Amazon's answer to Samsung's The Frame</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/ember-artline-is-amazons-answer-to-samsungs-the-frame-150015104.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d28ecd7-00a9-482c-b109-80bf177a66d4</guid>
      <description>Amazon just revealed the Ember Artline TV at CES 2026. This is a lifestyle TV that displays art, putting it in direct competition with Samsung's The Frame. The 4K QLED screen is extremely thin, at 1.5-inches, so it'll likely fit just about anywhere.
It also features a glare-reducing matte screen that has been "designed to make your art and photos look great." The Artline integrates with Amazon Photos and offers access to 2,000 pieces of free art to display. For those worried about electricity usage, the TV includes proprietary technology that senses when someone has entered or left the room an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ces lunettes remplacent votre TV : XREAL d&#233;voile les 1S au CES 2026 qui int&#232;grent une compatibilit&#233; native avec la Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/lunettes-intelligentes/2927175_ces-lunettes-remplacent-votre-tv-xreal-devoile-les-1s-au-ces-2026-qui-integrent-une-compatibilite-native-avec-la-switch-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/lunettes-intelligentes/2927175_ces-lunettes-remplacent-votre-tv-xreal-devoile-les-1s-au-ces-2026-qui-integrent-une-compatibilite-native-avec-la-switch-2</guid>
      <description>
C'est devenu une tradition au CES : XREAL sort une nouvelle paire de lunettes. Cette ann&#233;e, place aux XREAL 1S. Ne cherchez pas la r&#233;volution, c'est une &#233;volution chirurgicale : 1200p, plus de luminosit&#233; et une compatibilit&#233; native avec la Switch 2.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This egg-shaped gadget aims to demystify hormones&#8230; with pee</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852942/mira-ultra4-wand-hormone-testing-ces-2026-health</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852942</guid>
      <description>Your urine can tell you a lot about your reproductive health hormones. Unfortunately, at-home testing can be cumbersome, involving collecting samples that are then mailed out to labs. That's what health startup Mira is trying to simplify with its $249 Ultra4 Hormone Monitor. The pitch is to make highly accurate, readily available hormone testing for [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon adds to the lifestyle TV landscape with the Ember Artline TV</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853508/amazon-ember-artline-tv-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853508</guid>
      <description>Joining Samsung's The Frame, Hisense CanvasTV, TCL Nxtvision, and newly announced LG Gallery TV, is Amazon's very first art TV. The Amazon Ember Artline is a 4K edge-lit LED TV with a matte screen to reduce ambient light glare and is only 1.5 inches thick. At purchase, customers will be able to include their choice [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alexa Plus website is now available to everyone in early access</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853535/alexa-plus-website-now-available</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853535</guid>
      <description>Alexa Plus was already popping up online for some users earlier this month, and now it's officially available to everyone through an early access program. Anyone can go sign up at Alexa.com and start playing with the new web interface for Amazon's new AI chatbot. Alexa Plus was already available on all new Echo devices [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Fire TV OS gets a much-needed revamp</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853550/amazon-fire-tv-os-revamp-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853550</guid>
      <description>Amazon Fire TV has been a bit long in the tooth for a while now. Its design isn't as intuitive to navigate as Google TV, Roku, or Apple TV, and its responsiveness is frustrating. I've found it to be the weak link in Amazon's portfolio for a while now, and the only major drawback to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon revamps Fire TV, launches its own &#8216;Artline&#8217; televisions with frames at CES</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/amazon-revamps-fire-tv-launches-its-own-artline-televisions-with-frames/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079300</guid>
      <description>Fire TV's new interface focuses on your content and offers easier, speedier navigation, Amazon says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s AI assistant comes to the web with Alexa.com</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/alexa-without-an-echo-amazons-ai-chatbot-comes-to-the-web-and-a-revamped-alexa-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079547</guid>
      <description>Amazon is bringing Alexa+ to the web with a new Alexa.com site, expanding its AI assistant beyond devices and positioning it as a family-focused, agent-style chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Tuesday, January 6 (game #1443)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-6-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Lm6EoH5DUL2tMJxmoQM3LB</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Tuesday, January 6 (game #940)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-6-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fo6mgN5QchUgZ3v8MvDEPG</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Tuesday, January 6 (game #674)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-6-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WU6kqBcjaogqaTsyNhzT2E</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Ember Artline is its answer to Samsung&#8217;s Frame &#8212; with a focus on value and AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/embargo-7am-pt-10am-et-1-5-2026-amazons-ember-artline-is-its-answer-to-samsungs-frame-with-a-focus-on-value-and-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HdsTU8jFwgGD6UhQqgWTyA</guid>
      <description>Amazon is taking on Samsung&#8217;s Frame with the Ember Artline Fire TV, a lifestyle TV that combines art display with ambient AI features and a likely lower starting price that includes the frame in the box.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is redesigning its Fire TV UI for streaming sticks and TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/amazon-is-redesigning-its-fire-tv-ui-for-streaming-sticks-and-tvs-150000622.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33981978-2d4d-4beb-832b-696efdf62538</guid>
      <description>Amazon is kicking off the new year by announcing a redesign of its Fire TV UI at CES 2026. The new UI is designed to make finding things to watch on the platform faster, while making it easier to access more of Fire TV's features straight from the home screen.On first blush, the biggest difference in the new Fire TV UI is that everything is rounder. Shows, movies and apps have rounded corners, and Amazon's changed the spacing in the interface to give everything more room to breathe. Tweaks to typography and color gradients also give the UI a more modern feel, and Amazon says it's rebuilt the c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The culture solution CEOs are missing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467608/the-culture-solution-ceos-are-missing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T15:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467608/the-culture-solution-ceos-are-missing</guid>
      <description>Skills-based volunteering is catalyzing the workforce of the future.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini la prise de notes : ce bo&#238;tier &#171;&#160;Fran&#231;ais&#160;&#187; de g&#233;nie r&#233;sume vos r&#233;unions avec ChatGPT, Claude et Gemini</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2928199_ce-boitier-ia-compatible-chatgpt-et-claude-enregistre-et-resume-vos-reunions</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2928199_ce-boitier-ia-compatible-chatgpt-et-claude-enregistre-et-resume-vos-reunions</guid>
      <description>
En 2015, Facebook promettait un assistant humain nomm&#233; Moneypenny. Dix ans plus tard, le nom revient au CES 2026, mais chez Oxtak. C'est un dictaphone dop&#233; aux st&#233;ro&#239;des et &#224; l'IA qui promet de r&#233;sumer votre vie pro.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z Trifold Hands On: This Is the Phone-Tablet Hybrid You're Looking For</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6957fa77f93229aa3801734f</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, we went hands-on with the three-panel Samsung tablet that folds up to the size of a (large) phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plier le linge et vider le lave-vaisselle : SwitchBot nous vend du r&#234;ve avec son robot Onero H1</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/robots/2926533_switchbot-se-lance-dans-la-robotique-humanoide-avec-lonero-h1-cest-soit-une-revolution-soit-une-vaste-blague</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/robots/2926533_switchbot-se-lance-dans-la-robotique-humanoide-avec-lonero-h1-cest-soit-une-revolution-soit-une-vaste-blague</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu la vid&#233;o de d&#233;mo du SwitchBot Onero H1 ? C'est impressionnant : il plie le linge, vide le lave-vaisselle, sert &#224; manger. Trop beau pour &#234;tre vrai ? Probablement. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordVPN denies data breach after hackers claim Salesforce leak &#8212; here's everything we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/nordvpn-denies-data-breach-after-hackers-claim-salesforce-leak-heres-everything-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R5AE9mhNREhUHjvFVKTU3B</guid>
      <description>Reports have surfaced of a potential data breach involving NordVPN's Salesforce tools. Here is what the hackers are claiming, and why NordVPN says your data remains secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une feuille OLED de 9 mm pour jouer en 165 Hz : LG n&#8217;a pas fait les choses &#224; moiti&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2927107_lg-w6-le-retour-du-wallpaper-oled-une-feuille-de-9-mm-qui-cache-une-bete-de-course</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2927107_lg-w6-le-retour-du-wallpaper-oled-une-feuille-de-9-mm-qui-cache-une-bete-de-course</guid>
      <description>
C'est probablement le t&#233;l&#233;viseur le plus impressionnant visuellement de ce CES 2026. La LG OLED evo W6 reprend le concept du &#171; papier peint &#187; abandonn&#233; en 2020. En gros, c'est un &#233;cran de 77 ou 83 pouces coll&#233; au mur, sans aucun c&#226;ble visible, pilot&#233; par un bo&#238;tier sans fil.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia pourrait remettre en vente une de ses cartes graphiques les plus populaires</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/nvidia-pourrait-remettre-en-vente-une-de-ses-cartes-graphiques-les-plus-populaires.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318170</guid>
      <description>Cette bonne vieille RTX 3060 pourrait revenir dans les rayons des magasins d'&#233;lectronique dans le courant du premier trimestre. Nvidia semble en effet pr&#233;parer le retour de sa carte graphique toujours tr&#232;s populaire malgr&#233; son &#226;ge. Il faut dire que la situation actuelle au niveau de la RAM plaide en faveur de ce mod&#232;le.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La B&amp;YOU Pure Fibre est d&#233;sormais plus ch&#232;re : l&#8217;offre vaut-elle toujours le coup ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2928563_la-byou-pure-fibre-est-desormais-plus-chere-loffre-vaut-elle-toujours-le-coup</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/bouygues-telecom/2928563_la-byou-pure-fibre-est-desormais-plus-chere-loffre-vaut-elle-toujours-le-coup</guid>
      <description>
Bouygues Telecom l'avait annonc&#233; et c'est chose faite. &#192; partir du 5 janvier 2026, l'abonnement B&amp;YOU Pure Fibre voit son tarif augmenter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personne n&#8217;en a besoin, tout le monde la veut : voici l&#8217;objet d&#233;co le plus cool du CES</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927995_switchbot-obboto-une-lampe-globe-avec-2900-leds-pour-le-pixel-art</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2927995_switchbot-obboto-une-lampe-globe-avec-2900-leds-pour-le-pixel-art</guid>
      <description>
Il faut qu'on parle de l'obsession de mettre de l'IA partout. M&#234;me dans une lampe. SwitchBot d&#233;voile l'Obboto, un globe lumineux capable de g&#233;n&#233;rer des "animations d'ambiance contr&#244;l&#233;es par l'IA". Au-del&#224; du buzzword, c'est surtout un tr&#232;s joli afficheur pixel art qui pourrait bien faire de l'ombre au c&#233;l&#232;bre LaMetric Time.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bient&#244;t en Europe, le Tesla Model Y L &#224; 6 places se d&#233;couvre dans ces images in&#233;dites</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2928501_bientot-en-europe-le-tesla-model-y-l-a-6-places-se-decouvre-dans-ces-images-inedites</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2928501_bientot-en-europe-le-tesla-model-y-l-a-6-places-se-decouvre-dans-ces-images-inedites</guid>
      <description>
Jusqu'ici r&#233;serv&#233;e au march&#233; chinois, le Tesla Model Y L dot&#233;e de six places devrait bient&#244;t arriver en Europe, o&#249; il rejoindra la version Performance. L'occasion de d&#233;couvrir les croquis des designers.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft supprime l&#8217;activation des licences de Windows et d&#8217;Office par t&#233;l&#233;phone</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/microsoft-supprime-lactivation-des-licences-de-windows-et-doffice-par-telephone.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318166</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;activation des licences du syst&#232;me d&#8217;exploitation de Microsoft et de sa suite bureautique par t&#233;l&#233;phone n&#8217;est plus possible. La firme de Redmond a mis son serveur vocal d&#233;di&#233; hors service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cameron&#8217;s &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; crosses the $1B mark at the box office</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469008/james-camerons-avatar-fire-ash-crosses-1b-mark-box-office</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:38:37</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469008/james-camerons-avatar-fire-ash-crosses-1b-mark-box-office</guid>
      <description>The sci-fi epic is Hollywood&#8217;s No. 1 movie for the third straight week.
Hollywood kicked off 2026 with &#8220;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8221; atop the box office for the third straight week and with hopes for a blockbuster-filled year after a disappointing 2025.In three weeks of release, &#8220;Fire and Ash&#8221; has cleared $1 billion worldwide. The third chapter in James Cameron&#8217;s Pandora epic collected $40 million over its third weekend in North American theaters, according to studio estimates Sunday.&#8220;Fire and Ash&#8221; is doing its biggest business overseas; it&#8217;s grossed $777.1 million internationally thus far. The Walt ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick up Amazon's latest Kindle on sale for $20 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/pick-up-amazons-latest-kindle-on-sale-for-20-off-183302556.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9865d5d-82c0-47b4-858f-2d61df88bf8c</guid>
      <description>If you're one of the many who made a New Year's resolution to read more, an ereader can help by putting your whole library (and more) at your fingertips wherever you are. While not as expensive as an iPad or another flagship tablet, these e-paper devices can be more expensive than you think, but right now you can save on one of our favorites. Amazon's base Kindle is on sale for $90 &#8212; that's $20 less than usual and only $10 more than its record-low price.
This made our list of the best ereaders, and for good reason. It's an iconic device that gets the job done. It doesn't have much by way of mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J. Crew&#8217;s new Olympic skiing capsule gives sportswear a &#8217;70s vibe shift</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465832/jcrew-olympic-skiing-collection-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:33:44</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465832/jcrew-olympic-skiing-collection-2026</guid>
      <description>J. Crew creative director Olympia Gayot on how the new collection was inspired by the Olympic archives, vintage design details, and winter gear with panache.
J. Crew just revealed its apparel collection with the U.S. Ski &amp; Snowboard teams for the 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympics. It&#8217;s an ode to retro ski aesthetics that even the most amateur athlete (or viewer) can get behind.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
