<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:56:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#8216;Incognito&amp;#8217; operator sentenced to 30 years for running a dark web drug market</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/873825/incognito-market-dark-web-drug-sales-sentencing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T11:51:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873825</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Rui-Siang Lin was sentenced to 30 years in prison for running "Incognito Market," a dark web platform that prosecutors say "sold more than $105 million of narcotics-including more than 1,000 kilograms of cocaine, over 1,000 kilograms of methamphetamines, hundreds of kilograms of other narcotics, and more than 4 kilograms of purported 'oxycodone'," between [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: Everything we're expecting from the S26 launch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-everything-were-expecting-from-the-s26-launch-130000556.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup. Official invites have yet to be shared, but the date is widely expected to be near the end of the month, probably on February 25 But as usual, we know a lot about what&#8217;s expected when Samsung does hold its next event.Whenever it does happen, Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A bet for the future of cybersecurity' &#8211; Nord Security hits 400 patents as race for solutions against next-gen threats heats up</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/a-bet-for-the-future-of-cybersecurity-nord-security-hits-400-patents-as-race-for-solutions-against-next-gen-threats-heats-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V9cx4JpQitZSZ2EzewWq36</guid>
      <description>Nord Security has quadrupled its patent count since 2023, signaling a massive shift towards post-quantum encryption and AI-driven threat detection to future-proof its privacy tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EE is down for many &#8211;here's what we know about the outage</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/ee-down-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UwfvHPHwcedEBGnmkRi8iD</guid>
      <description>The EE network appears to be down for many in the UK &#8211;here's everything we know about the outage so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest Reportedly Fires Employees Who Built a Tool to Track Layoffs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pinterest-reportedly-fires-employees-who-built-a-tool-to-track-layoffs-2000717884</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717884</guid>
      <description>Pinterest says the internal layoff-tracking tool built by company engineers violated company policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A violation of fundamental rights' &#8211; Civil society calls on Switzerland to abandon data retention proposals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/a-violation-of-fundamental-rights-civil-society-calls-on-switzerland-to-abandon-data-retention-proposals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ze9HSzzVFAN4EzebpnVD3</guid>
      <description>Switzerland wants to expand its surveillance law and require VPNs, messaging apps, social media platforms, and other online services to collect data to help identify their users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone Fold rumors: Everything we know so far, including the leaked foldable design</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/iphone-fold-rumors-everything-we-know-so-far-including-the-leaked-foldable-design-130000349.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0490e267-519c-4446-8600-db194c77de1f</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s long-rumored foldable iPhone hasn&#8217;t been announced yet, but after years of speculation, it seems like this device could finally be coming out soon(ish). Multiple sources claim that Apple could be targeting a late-2026 launch for its first foldable phone, and new rumors suggest the company is even already thinking about its second model, which could be a clamshell-style foldable iPhone.But of course, nothing is official yet. Plans can change, features can be dropped and timelines can slip. Still, recent reports paint the clearest picture yet of how Apple might approach a foldable iPhone...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super deal du jour : -30% sur ce TV Mini LED Philips Ambilight de 65&#8243; (144 Hz), taill&#233; pour l&#8217;immersion</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2966301_super-deal-du-jour-30-sur-ce-tv-mini-led-philips-ambilight-de-65-144-hz-taille-pour-limmersion</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2966301_super-deal-du-jour-30-sur-ce-tv-mini-led-philips-ambilight-de-65-144-hz-taille-pour-limmersion</guid>
      <description>
&#192; la recherche d'un nouveau TV offrant une belle qualit&#233; d'image&#160;? Le Philips 65PML9059/12 propose un &#233;cran Mini LED avec de l&#8217;Ambilight pour sublimer le tout, avec un prix plus avantageux qu&#8217;&#224; son lancement&#160;: 699 euros contre 999 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cozey Neptune Sofa Bed Review: Firm but Flexible</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/review/cozey-neptune-sofa-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697923e82a25347a226ac7cc</guid>
      <description>This modular sleeper sofa allows buyers to design any seating configuration they want, if they don&#8217;t mind a solid surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day sales 2026: The best tech deals from Apple, Sony, Roku and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/presidents-day-sales-2026-the-best-tech-deals-from-apple-sony-roku-and-others-163000379.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba4f502-86ba-4c79-a2ff-b27b6e52c38b</guid>
      <description>You can find a lot of good deals for Presidents&#8217; Day, but to say it&#8217;s a tech-deal boon would be an overstatement. The best Presidents&#8217; Day deals are usually on mattresses, appliances and furniture, but you can find some decent tech sales thrown in as well. This year, Presidents&#8217; Day comes right after Valentine&#8217;s Day and Super Bowl 2026, which means there are even more chances to save as sales and discounts overlap. If you&#8217;re looking for a new streaming device, a fresh iPad or an upgraded vacuum so you can enter the spring-cleaning season properly, we have you covered. These are the best Presid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Stuck 2 Mummies in a CT Scanner. Here&#8217;s What They Saw</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/experts-stuck-two-mummies-in-a-ct-scanner-heres-what-they-saw-2000717867</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717867</guid>
      <description>This is probably not how the ancient Egyptian priests thought their afterlife would go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt to block Roblox for all users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/egypt-to-block-roblox-for-all-users-161343443.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3120133e-ad23-43f9-8329-6ea796a7c6c9</guid>
      <description>Egyptian regulators have banned Roblox, a popular children's video game, Bloomberg&#160;reports. The nation's Supreme Council for Media Regulation is coordinating with the National Telecommunications Regulatory Authority on the decision to ensure its enforcement.
The state-owned outlet reported that Senator Walaa Hermas Radwandid had proposed regulation of the platform to &#8220;protect children&#8217;s moral and educational values." The senator outlined his concerns with the nature of the Roblox platform, including the ability to communicate directly with strangers as well as "potential psychological and beha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide : quelles sont les meilleures liseuses Kobo en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/710365_guide-liseuse-kobo-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/710365_guide-liseuse-kobo-choisir</guid>
      <description>
La marque de liseuses Kobo vous int&#233;resse ? On vous explique tout pour vous aider &#224; bien choisir et &#224; profiter d'une exp&#233;rience de lecture au top. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft warns infostealer malware is 'rapidly expanding beyond traditional Windows-focused campaigns' and targeting Mac devices</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/microsoft-warns-infostealer-malware-is-rapidly-expanding-beyond-traditional-windows-focused-campaigns-and-targeting-mac-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GSHHg82RM3zcMauFzXe5Ci</guid>
      <description>Hackers are increasingly targeting macOS users with social engineering and infostealers, Microsoft warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase, le g&#233;ant des cryptos, est victime d&#8217;une nouvelle fuite de donn&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/coinbase-geant-cryptos-victime-nouvelle-fuite-donnees.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324136</guid>
      <description>Coinbase, le g&#233;ant am&#233;ricain des cryptomonnaies, a reconnu une nouvelle fuite de donn&#233;es. L&#8217;un de ses sous&#8209;traitants a abus&#233; de ses acc&#232;s &#224; l&#8217;outil interne de support pour consulter les donn&#233;es d'une partie des clients. Cet incident survient moins d&#8217;un an apr&#232;s une violation analogue. L&#224; encore, c'est un prestataire qui &#233;tait &#224; l'origine de la fuite....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Whistle&#8217; Puts a Pleasingly Freaky Spin on a Familiar Horror Tale</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/whistle-movie-review-dafne-keen-nick-frost-shudder-2000714790</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714790</guid>
      <description>Dafne Keen and Nick Frost star in Corin Hardy&#8217;s cursed-object chiller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s Galaxy S26 Might Have an Even More Ridiculous Camera Zoom</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/samsungs-galaxy-s26-might-have-an-even-more-ridiculous-camera-zoom-2000717834</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717834</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to zooooooom?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the ICE Forum Where Agents Complain About Their Jobs</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-the-ice-forum-where-agents-complain-about-their-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6982067a7c553e1f8e36ee8c</guid>
      <description>&#8220;I'm all for removing illegals, but snatching dudes off lawn mowers in Cali and leaving the truck and equipment just sitting there? Definitely not working smarter,&#8221; writes one forum user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can now fake the videos we trust most. How to tell the difference&#8212;and how newsrooms can respond</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485004/ai-can-now-fake-the-videos-we-trust-most</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485004/ai-can-now-fake-the-videos-we-trust-most</guid>
      <description>Real eyewitness footage contains the rough edges that come with real life. Those traits are now creeping into AI-generated video, too.
The footage was real, verified, and delightful: a security camera clip of a coyote bouncing on a backyard trampoline in Los Angeles. Days after the video went viral, near-identical kangaroos, bears, and rabbits began circulating too, all generated by AI. Millions shared them, believing they&#8217;d captured another glimpse of animals behaving hilariously. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE quietly scrambled for vaccine support after losing access through the VA</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485615/ice-quietly-scrambled-for-vaccine-support-after-losing-access-through-the-va</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485615/ice-quietly-scrambled-for-vaccine-support-after-losing-access-through-the-va</guid>
      <description>Records reveal that the VA cut off medical support used for detainees, forcing ICE into an emergency procurement amid mounting concerns about disease outbreaks and overcrowded facilities.
In procurement documents quietly published last month, Immigration and Customs revealed that the Veterans Affairs administration abruptly cut off its access to vaccines that the agency has historically provided to the people it detains. It was one of a series of medical support services that were suddenly halted, and comes amid long-standing and growing concerns about the health care provided at ICE facilitie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo&#238;te de r&#233;ception | Recharge optimis&#233;e, recel d&#8217;iPhone et web clandestin</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-04/boite-de-reception/recharge-optimisee-recel-d-iphone-et-web-clandestin.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd079c7341e933c8970c21685a5449f0</guid>
      <description>Chaque mercredi, notre journaliste r&#233;pond &#224; vos questions en lien avec le num&#233;rique et les nouvelles technologies. Cette semaine, on se demande s&#8217;il faut d&#233;brancher son iPhone de temps en temps, on devine pourquoi les voleurs aiment le t&#233;l&#233;phone d&#8217;Apple, et on revisite le web cach&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexa+ is now available nationwide, with a free text-based version for non-Prime members to try</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/alexa-is-now-available-nationwide-with-a-free-text-based-version-for-non-prime-members-to-try-155550342.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aea1b8ff-1af8-492d-9a11-fd9d4c4ff46b</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#8217;s next-generation AI assistant is now available to everyone in the US for $20 per month, or for free if you&#8217;re a Prime member. Amazon has also introduced a try-before-you-buy free tier for non-Prime members, but it&#8217;s limited to text-based chat.
Alexa+ has been in early access since last year, and Amazon says it&#8217;s listened to user insights ahead of rolling out the update nationwide today. If you&#8217;re a Prime member, you can start using the new assistant by saying "Alexa, upgrade to Alexa+" or by heading to Alexa.com and signing into your Amazon account. The Alexa website is also where you&#8217;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trail, cyclisme, Hyrox : cette montre de sport devient bien plus puissante gr&#226;ce &#224; cette mise &#224; jour</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazfit/2966287_trail-cyclisme-hyrox-cette-montre-de-sport-devient-bien-plus-puissante-grace-a-cette-mise-a-jour</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazfit/2966287_trail-cyclisme-hyrox-cette-montre-de-sport-devient-bien-plus-puissante-grace-a-cette-mise-a-jour</guid>
      <description>
Amazfit a annonc&#233; une mise &#224; jour cons&#233;quente pour sa T-Rex 3 Pro, avant l'arriv&#233;e attendue d'une T-Rex Ultra 2 plus haute en gamme. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 14-inch, ARM-based Asus Vivobook is half off today</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/873792/asus-vivobook-snapdragon-x-laptop-amd-ryzen-switch-2-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T10:55:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873792</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m typically reluctant to recommend budget-friendly laptops, particularly ones that run Windows, because they suck, more often than not. That&#8217;s beginning to change, thanks in part to last year&#8217;s introduction of the Snapdragon X-series processors that offer solid performance and good x86 and x64 app compatibility. If you&#8217;re in need of a compact 14-inch laptop [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s 2026 Valentine&#8217;s Day gift guide (for him)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/865396/valentines-day-2026-gift-ideas-for-him-boyfriend-husband-partner</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T10:48:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865396</guid>
      <description>Valentine's Day is often thought of as the quintessential Hallmark holiday - and why wouldn't it be? Most of the time, it's marketed to us with massive floral arrangements and heart-shaped chocolates, both of which can come off as borderline twee. But no one says you have to play by the rulebook when it comes [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, where to stream, start time, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-where-to-stream-start-time-and-more-175759112.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is less than a week away. This year's game will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA, and the Bay Area will be host to loads of other football events this week, too, including Thursday's NFL Honors, where we'll learn who this season's MVP is. (That event, which will be held in San Francisco, will air live on NBC and the NFL Network on Thursday at 9...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s Why You Should Care About the Next-Gen Xbox Launch</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/heres-why-you-should-care-about-the-next-gen-xbox-launch-2000717835</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717835</guid>
      <description>It's going to make a bad time for the gaming industry even worse if Xbox can't pull off a win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Direct February 2026 livestream: When is it, how to watch</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nintendo-direct-february-2026-livestream-how-to-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04FMLnWQd3RTkSLQ9FDfWIm</guid>
      <description>Nintendo is blessing us with 30 minutes of announcements for new Switch games on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPad deal: Get $100 off the latest iPad mini right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/ipad-deal-get-100-off-the-latest-ipad-mini-right-now-140900989.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19626799-ebb9-4821-a9ee-8598c32b4da3</guid>
      <description>Apple's smallest tablet is a great option for frequent travelers or anywho who prefers their slabs be the size of an ereader. The latest iPad mini with the A17 Pro chip is down to one of the best prices we've seen right now &#8212; $400, which is $100 off.
Apple released this iPad mini in late 2024 and it was a solid update. We gave it an 83 in our review thanks to the power of its A17 Pro chip and that it comes with a minimum of 128GB of storage. The model currently on sale comes with 128GB, Wi-Fi and all four color options: Blue, Purple, Space Gray and Starlight.&#160; 


We named the Apple iPad mini o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElevenLabs raises $500M from Sequoia at an $11 billion valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/04/elevenlabs-raises-500m-from-sequioia-at-a-11-billion-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089477</guid>
      <description>ElevenLabs' valuation has raised more than three times in the last 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD graphics card makers rumored to be looking at more price hikes &#8212; and they might abandon 16GB GPUs like Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/amd-graphics-card-makers-rumored-to-be-looking-at-more-price-hikes-and-they-might-abandon-16gb-gpus-like-nvidia</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V95pX7Jt9bna9Sde53d357</guid>
      <description>A shift towards more production of 8GB graphics cards won't go down well with PC gamers, that's for sure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral's New Ultra-Fast Translation Model Gives Big AI Labs a Run for Their Money</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/mistral-voxtral-real-time-ai-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69822a3948379122cdc58576</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Too many GPUs makes you lazy,&#8221; says the French startup's vice president of science operations, as the company carves out a different path than the major US AI companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score the Amzmerit smart scale for its best-ever price on Amazon &#8212; save $50 with this handy coupon code</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-4-amzmerit-smart-scale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">009ax8TCNMfMa8HB0rOs54j</guid>
      <description>The Amzmerit smart scale is on sale for just $49.99 when you enter the code TQXXS39F at checkout. That's an extra $50 off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to beat change fatigue</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485057/how-beat-change-fatigue</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T15:30:33</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485057/how-beat-change-fatigue</guid>
      <description>5 ways to find stability in chaos.
We live in a world of increasing change. The international order is shifting and political certainties are evaporating day by day. Technological shifts are changing how we experience the world and interact with others. And in the workplace, AI is poised to unleash what might be the most revolutionary set of changes humanity has experienced since the first hunter-gatherers settled down to grow crops and build cities....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Laptop Backpacks We&#8217;ve Tried and Tested (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/the-best-backpacks-for-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a871f32fe6ef84cd1052bf2</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re biking to the office or schlepping a camera to a shoot, a laptop bag is your constant companion. These WIRED-reviewed packs do the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DJI Mini 5 Pro Fly More Combo is down to an all-time low price &#8212; save $500 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-4-dji-mini-5-pro-combo-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06bDGsp3UDM67KcG3IB58y4</guid>
      <description>The DJI Mini 5 Pro Fly More Combo is on sale at Amazon for $1,099, down from the list price of $1,599. That's a 31% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonpig is giving away free greeting cards for Valentines Day &#8212; use this coupon code to qualify</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-4-moonpig-valentines-day-cards-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07LLCyaAvriajqlfQETIy8f</guid>
      <description>As of Feb. 4, Moonpig is giving away free greeting cards for Valentine's Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES is clear: People want tech to improve their everyday lives</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ces-is-clear-people-want-tech-to-improve-their-everyday-lives</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HkML3eFpY6ZqqLwdj2jwUP</guid>
      <description>Every year, CES showcases the limitless potential of our industry, but this year, we moved away from proof-of-concepts and towards real-world applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus d&#233;stocke sa tablette pas ch&#232;re et glisse 3 cadeaux dans le panier</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2966167_oneplus-destocke-sa-tablette-pas-chere-et-glisse-3-cadeaux-dans-le-panier</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2966167_oneplus-destocke-sa-tablette-pas-chere-et-glisse-3-cadeaux-dans-le-panier</guid>
      <description>
La OnePlus Pad Lite est une tablette abordable dont le prix chute de 30&#160;% sur le site officiel. Une aubaine pour celles et ceux &#224; la recherche d'une tablette efficace et pas ch&#232;re.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying a Mac Mini to run OpenClaw? Save $50 when you shop at Amazon.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-4-mac-mini-openclaw-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07p8FGi3G2yR9r40cC4Yxo8</guid>
      <description>As of Feb. 4, the Mac Mini is down to $549 at Amazon, saving you $50. So if you're looking to buy a Mac Mini to run OpenClaw, now is not a bad time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux users report Microsoft's Visual Studio Code Snap package isn't actually deleting files</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/linux-users-report-microsofts-visual-studio-code-snap-package-isnt-actually-deleting-files</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NHTnaQBk4ZFWteNZMUG26i</guid>
      <description>Many users have run out of disk space entirely, and a patch is nowhere in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Valve is on track to begin shipping its AMD-powered Steam Machine early this year': AMD's CEO says gaming PC remains on course &#8212; and I'm hopeful it could arrive in March</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/consoles-pc/valve-is-on-track-to-begin-shipping-its-amd-powered-steam-machine-early-this-year-amds-ceo-says-gaming-pc-remains-on-course-and-im-hopeful-it-could-arrive-in-march</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gasSWhcuVZzU6fwQy6XBE6</guid>
      <description>Valve has previously said the Steam Machine will debut early in 2026, and Lisa Su has underlined that this is still the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; On prend ma voix pour faire dire n&#8217;importe quoi &#187; : la voix fran&#231;aise d&#8217;Harrison Ford d&#233;clare la guerre &#224; l&#8217;IA</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2965991_on-prend-ma-voix-pour-faire-dire-nimporte-quoi-la-voix-francaise-dharrison-ford-declare-la-guerre-a-lia</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2965991_on-prend-ma-voix-pour-faire-dire-nimporte-quoi-la-voix-francaise-dharrison-ford-declare-la-guerre-a-lia</guid>
      <description>
Voix cultes du paysage francophone, Fran&#231;oise Cadol ou encore Richard Darbois ont annonc&#233; s&#8217;attaquer aux plateformes VoiceDub et Fish Audio afin que leurs voix exploit&#233;es ill&#233;galement soient retir&#233;es.  
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 TV deals: The best sales this week on OLEDs and other smart TVs ahead of the big game</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/super-bowl-2026-tv-deals-the-best-sales-this-week-on-oleds-and-other-smart-tvs-ahead-of-the-big-game-160000415.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19a8ed95-5057-4f9e-952b-502d925814e1</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re having people over to watch the Patriots and the Seahawks battle it out in Super Bowl 2026, or you&#8217;re more interested in the Bad Bunny halftime show, your TV will be an important part of the puzzle of putting together an excellent big-game party. If you&#8217;ve been thinking about upgrading your current TV, now&#8217;s a decent time to do it. The weeks leading up to the Super Bowl are typically awash with TV deals to consider.
Generally, TV prices steadily decrease after a new model comes out. Some 2026 TV models were announced at CES and are forthcoming things year, making now a good time...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLC : apr&#232;s des ann&#233;es d&#8217;attente, cette fonctionnalit&#233; indispensable d&#233;barque enfin sur Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2966267_vlc-apres-des-annees-dattente-cette-fonctionnalite-indispensable-debarque-enfin-sur-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2966267_vlc-apres-des-annees-dattente-cette-fonctionnalite-indispensable-debarque-enfin-sur-windows</guid>
      <description>
Il aura fallu attendre, mais cette fois, &#231;a y est. VLC se met &#224; jour et int&#232;gre enfin une option pr&#233;sente depuis tr&#232;s longtemps dans beaucoup de programmes similaires.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paylocity review</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/paylocity-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zot35u5J5Crtp5XRKGnCoY</guid>
      <description>A feature-packed HR and payroll platform with deep automation and employee experience tools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save up to 26% on Sonos Home Theater for the Super Bowl</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/save-up-to-26-percent-on-sonos-home-theater-for-the-super-bowl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MkgVhDYPhdRKbLxveEEgbk</guid>
      <description>The best Sonos sale of the year: Save 26% on our top-rated picks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.3&#160;: Apple teste une option pour limiter la localisation des op&#233;rateurs</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/ios-26-3-apple-teste-une-option-pour-limiter-la-localisation-transmise-aux-operateurs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324114</guid>
      <description>Avec la b&#234;ta de sa mise &#224; jour iOS 26.3, Apple introduit une nouvelle option de confidentialit&#233; destin&#233;e &#224; limiter la pr&#233;cision des donn&#233;es de localisation transmises aux op&#233;rateurs mobiles. Une nouvelle fonctionnalit&#233; r&#233;serv&#233;e &#224; certains appareils et r&#233;seaux.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin is having a bad year as price tumbles to fresh lows today: Why does crypto keep falling in 2026?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486633/bitcoin-price-falling-again-today-what-is-happening-with-crypto-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T15:11:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486633/bitcoin-price-falling-again-today-what-is-happening-with-crypto-2026</guid>
      <description>The world&#8217;s most popular cryptocurrency has seen its value shrink amid a confluence of vexing factors. Here&#8217;s what to know. 
Much to the chagrin of investors, the value of Bitcoin continues to slide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De 1000 Go &#224; 15 Go : la chute brutale du stockage gratuit chez Yahoo Mail</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2966129_de-1000-go-a-15-go-la-chute-brutale-du-stockage-gratuit-chez-yahoo-mail</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2966129_de-1000-go-a-15-go-la-chute-brutale-du-stockage-gratuit-chez-yahoo-mail</guid>
      <description>
Yahoo Mail, r&#233;put&#233; pour sa g&#233;n&#233;rosit&#233; en mati&#232;re de stockage, a d&#233;cid&#233; de drastiquement r&#233;duire l'espace offert gratuitement &#224; ses membres. Une d&#233;cision radicale qui r&#233;duit la fracture avec la  concurrence, mais qui risque surtout de bloquer de nombreuses bo&#238;tes de r&#233;ception.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I wanted to see if this old, affordable Shark vacuum could hold its own against the fanciest new models &#8211; I was amazed by the results</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/shark-stratos-iz400-cordless-vacuum-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q5osoJJNHRDhqHnrWLx3An</guid>
      <description>The Shark Stratos IZ400 is often overlooked, but it's one of the best-value cordless vacs you can buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s D.C. building boom includes a proposed arch, the &#8216;biggest one of all&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486558/trumps-d-c-building-boom-includes-proposal-for-an-arch-the-biggest-one-of-all</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T15:04:07</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486558/trumps-d-c-building-boom-includes-proposal-for-an-arch-the-biggest-one-of-all</guid>
      <description>It would be similar to Paris&#8217;s Arc de Triomphe.
President Donald Trump says history is on his side.He wants to build a towering arch near the Lincoln Memorial and argues that the nation&#8217;s capital first clamored for such a monument two centuries ago &#8212; even going so far as to erect four eagle statues as part of the project before being derailed by the attack on Fort Sumter.&#8220;It was interrupted by a thing called the Civil War, and so it never got built,&#8221; Trump said aboard Air Force One as he flew to Florida last weekend. &#8220;Then, they almost built something in 1902, but it never happened.&#8221;Trump&#8217;s hi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;KPop Demon Hunters&#8217; Adds Lego Sets to Its Pop Culture Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lego-kpop-demon-hunters-teaser-release-date-2000717836</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717836</guid>
      <description>The delayed realization that the Netflix film was going to be one of 2025's breakout hits means you'll have to wait a while, though.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I drove three Chinese cars &#8212; here&#8217;s why they would clean up in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/873408/geely-zeekr-lynk-co-test-drive-china</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873408</guid>
      <description>It only took a brief drive in a Zeekr 7X to convince me: Chinese cars are now competitive and could be sold in the US tomorrow. The compact battery-electric crossover, a bestseller in Europe, is aimed directly at the Tesla Model Y with its five seats, two rows, impressive road grip, energetic performance, and smooth [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Thursday, February 5 (game #704)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-5-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">T5jHzWQogxqauZnyk7oSWG</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Thursday, February 5 (game #1473)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-5-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3vrFYrjHUSBR39XBUrMWBB</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Thursday, February 5 (game #970)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-5-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z8Yh8YKiXysf2egxTioknN</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curling at Winter Olympics 2026 Free Streams: TV Channels, Medal Matches &amp; Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/curling-at-winter-olympics-2026-free-streams-milano-cortina</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qsLvkGfdoSf6m88ibL27gg</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Winter Olympics curling 2026 live streams for FREE, with Italy, Great Britain and Canada all bidding to defend their titles.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
