<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:25:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple AirPods Pro 3 Are $50 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/apple-airpods-pro-3-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695e9ae04e793bb818c7d36c</guid>
      <description>Snag a relatively rare discount on Apple's finest earbuds at Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget Podcast: CES 2026 and the rocky year ahead for the PC industry</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/engadget-podcast-ces-2026-and-the-rocky-year-ahead-for-the-pc-industry-221500019.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18e5fc2c-eb4a-471c-ad66-982d59bd2ee0</guid>
      <description>CES 2026: A rocky year ahead of the PC industryWe're halfway through CES 2026, and it&#8217;s clear that it's going to be a rough year for the PC industry. In this episode, Devindra chats with Engadget's Dan Cooper about Intel, AMD, NVIDIA and the sad state of the PC industry. We've got some new CPUs, but the volatile RAM market will likely make everything expensive this year. Also, they dive into Dell's revival of the XPS brand, as well as iPolish's smart nails and Subtle's AI-powered VoiceBuds.Subscribe!iTunesSpotifyPocket CastsStitcherGoogle PodcastsTopicsThe state of the PC industry in 2026 -- 0...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, LinkedIn banned AI agent startup Artisan, but now it&#8217;s back</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/yes-linkedin-banned-ai-agent-startup-artisan-but-now-its-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080944</guid>
      <description>Several viral posts noticed that Artisan was banned. But the CEO tells us it wasn't for the reasons many thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Display at CES 2026: Playful demos and mysterious prototypes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/samsung-display-ces-2026-playful-demos-and-mysterious-prototypes-220407696.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01743a0a-5f8c-4b31-957f-73ae08c4b1a6</guid>
      <description>Samsung Display is the part of its giant parent company that makes OLEDs, LCDs and other screens for both Samsung devices and anyone else that can afford them. This year, it&#8217;s going all-in on OLEDs of the future. And that meant things like foldable displays with invisible creases, robots hurling basketballs at supertough OLED panels, and OLED screens packed into baffling form factors for no good reason.
Creases
Samsung Display
The &#8220;seamless&#8221; foldable display that might be a part of a future foldable iPhone disappeared from the booth during our tour, reappearing when it was time to leave. (This...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Launches ChatGPT Health, Wants Access to Your Medical Records</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-launches-chatgpt-health-wants-access-to-your-medical-records-2000707024</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707024</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's biggest play into the burgeoning health AI market is here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#8217;s Live-Action &#8216;Tangled&#8217; Has Found Its Leads</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-live-action-tangled-casting-rapunzel-2000707051</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707051</guid>
      <description>Relative newcomers Teagan Croft and Milo Manheim will play Rapunzel and Flynn Rider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why AI feels generic: Replit CEO on slop, toys, and the missing ingredient of taste</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/why-ai-feels-generic-replit-ceo-on-slop-toys-and-the-missing-ingredient-of</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3NMK5V0Fqi6ozdebavd1fD</guid>
      <description>Right now in the AI world, there are a lot of percolating ideas and experimentation. But as far as Replit CEO Amjad Masad is concerned, the results are unreliable, marginally effective, and generic.&#160;&#8220;There's a lot of sameness out there,&#8221; Masad explains in a new VB Beyond the Pilot podcast. &#8220;Everything kind of looks the same, all the images, all the code, everything.&#8221;This "slop," as it&#8217;s come to be known, is not only the result of lazy one-shot prompting, but a lack of individual flavor.&#160;&#8220;The way to overcome slop is for the platform to expend more effort and for the developers of the platform t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok Is Generating Sexual Content Far More Graphic Than What's on X</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/grok-is-generating-sexual-content-far-more-graphic-than-whats-on-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d7fbcdbe489ef91435a3f</guid>
      <description>A WIRED review of outputs hosted on Grok&#8217;s official website shows it&#8217;s being used to create violent sexual images and videos, as well as content that includes apparent minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This haptic wristband pairs with Meta smart glasses to decode facial expressions</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/this-haptic-wristband-pairs-with-meta-smart-glasses-to-decode-facial-expressions-214305431.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc006348-e94a-4af9-91ae-7418b1334036</guid>
      <description>It's only been a few months since Meta announced that it would open its smart glasses platform to third-party developers. But one startup at CES is already showing off how the glasses can help power an intriguing set of accessibility features.Hapware has created Aleye, a haptic wristband that, when paired with Ray-Ban Meta smart glasses, can help people understand the facial expressions and other nonverbal cues of the people they are talking to. The company says the device could help people who are blind, low vision or neurodivergent unlock a type of communication that otherwise wouldn't be av...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 7% of Americans Want Their Next Car to Be Electric, Survey Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/only-7-of-americans-want-their-next-car-to-be-electric-survey-finds-2000707031</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707031</guid>
      <description>A new Deloitte survey finds price, driving range, and charging concerns are slowing EV adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roku&#8217;s $3 streaming service Howdy will be coming to other platforms, CEO says</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/rokus-3-streaming-service-howdy-will-be-coming-to-other-platforms-ceo-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080966</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Anthony Wood, Roku's founder, chairman, and CEO, offered a hint about the future of the company's newest streaming channel, Howdy, and its ambition to become a broader competitor in the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is RAM the new Bitcoin? DDR4 memory prices are rising so fast, some tracker graphs are running out of space - and I fear 2026 could well see a 10x price rise</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/is-ram-the-new-bitcoin-ddr4-memory-prices-are-rising-so-fast-some-tracker-graphs-are-running-out-of-space-and-i-fear-2026-could-well-see-a-10x-price-rise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5t7sDDso9v3rsigjMXEHm</guid>
      <description>Is RAM the new Bitcoin? DDR4 prices jump from under $100 to several hundred dollars in a matter of months and the worrying trend shows no signs of slowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Motorola Razr Fold could open up a new era for folding phones &#8211; if the price is right</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/motorola-phones/the-motorola-razr-fold-could-open-up-a-new-era-for-folding-phones-if-the-price-is-right</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YMTqm95HVmY2bGrpWrrite</guid>
      <description>Motorola could be the one to lead the charge on mid-range foldables by adding the Razr Fold to its lineup of existing flip phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning 25-Year Timelapse Shows a Supernova Tearing Through Deep Space</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stunning-25-year-timelapse-shows-a-supernova-tearing-through-deep-space-2000706993</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706993</guid>
      <description>Decades in the making, NASA's X-ray timelapse shows a stellar explosion expanding into space at up to 2% the speed of light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 2026 Be the Year That the AI Industry Stops Crowing About &#8216;AGI&#8217;?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/will-2026-be-the-year-that-the-ai-industry-stops-crowing-about-agi-2000707012</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707012</guid>
      <description>Surely it's not because AGI is simply unachievable with the current technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta's $2b Manus acquisition sparks concerns from Chinese regulators</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/metas-usd2b-manus-acquisition-sparks-concerns-from-chinese-regulators</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UaUt84PyjV4JwEMwzTJtdm</guid>
      <description>Chinese regulators are worried about Manus' move to Singapore, so new parent company Meta could be in trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazfit&#8217;s stylish budget tracker is nearly matching its best price to date</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/857877/amazfit-active-2-fitness-tracker-new-years-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T16:16:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857877</guid>
      <description>Amazfit might not have the name recognition of a company like Garmin or Fitbit, but its wearables consistently impress, with the Amazfit Active 2 being one of the best fitness trackers you can buy. And right now, it&#8217;s on sale for just $84.99 ($15 off) at Amazon, Best Buy, and Target, which is only $5 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X&#8217;s deepfake machine is infuriating policymakers around the globe</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/857924/x-grok-ai-chatbot-bikini-images-regulators-congress</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T16:09:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857924</guid>
      <description>X's Grok chatbot hasn't stopped accepting users' requests to strip down women and, in some cases, apparent minors to AI-generated bikinis. According to some reports, the flood of AI-generated images includes more extreme content that potentially violates laws against nonconsensual intimate imagery (NCII) and child sexual abuse material (CSAM). Even in the US, where X [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI unveils ChatGPT Health, says 230 million users ask about health each week</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/openai-unveils-chatgpt-health-says-230-million-users-ask-about-health-each-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080910</guid>
      <description>The feature, which is expected to roll out in the coming weeks, will offer a dedicated space for conversations with ChatGPT about health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer joins AI bandwagon with external AI accelerator backed by iconic AMD chip architect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/razer-joins-ai-bandwagon-with-external-ai-accelerator-backed-by-iconic-amd-chip-architect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2UT2NDRA3TmmR3Nxn8aQjV</guid>
      <description>Razer announces Forge AI Dev Workstation at CES 2026 alongside a compact Tenstorrent external AI accelerator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This phishing campaign spoofs internal messages - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-phishing-campaign-spoofs-internal-messages-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3EdEtU7wjfjrjNsuYjk8iF</guid>
      <description>Crooks are abusing misconfigurations to trick victims into thinking they received an email from their bosses and HRs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop chasing AI experts</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470855/stop-chasing-ai-experts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T21:02:24</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470855/stop-chasing-ai-experts</guid>
      <description>Start building the right AI skills in the right roles.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is launching a new dedicated Health portal</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/chatgpt-is-launching-a-new-dedicated-health-portal-210150083.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26accf7a-1d82-43aa-9be6-4b84d629c2d6</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is launching a new facet for its AI chatbot called ChatGPT Health. This new feature will allow users to connect medical records and wellness apps to ChatGPT in order to get more tailored responses to queries about their health. The company noted that there will be additional privacy safeguards for this separate space within ChatGPT, and said that it will not use conversations held in Health for training foundational models. ChatGPT Health is currently in a testing stage, and there are some regional restrictions on which health apps can be connected to the AI company's platform.The annou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Frankenstein&#8217; and &#8216;Sinners&#8217; Get Screen Actors Guild Awards Love&#8212;&#8217;Andor,&#8217; Not So Much</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/frankenstein-and-sinners-get-screen-actors-guild-awards-love-andor-not-so-much-2000706975</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706975</guid>
      <description>The Actor Awards (formerly known as the SAG Awards) will be presented March 1, with a ceremony streaming on Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Live as NASA Astronauts Conduct Spacewalk to Prep the ISS for its Demise</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/watch-live-as-nasa-astronauts-conduct-spacewalk-to-prep-the-iss-for-its-demise-2000706341</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706341</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, a pair of astronauts will venture outside the space station to prepare for the future installation of roll-out solar arrays that will help power its deorbit in 2030.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loads of free content is coming to The Elder Scrolls Online this year &#8212; here are the four biggest additions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/loads-of-free-content-is-coming-to-the-elder-scrolls-online-this-year-here-are-the-four-biggest-additions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9FL7hufYeHwy8FfdoNGcEW</guid>
      <description>We break down some of the biggest additions coming to The Elder Scrolls Online throughout 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Pitt season 2 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/the-pitt-season-2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eNkie2xgePBiLqsTmugr43</guid>
      <description>An intense 15 hour ER shift is covered in 15 real-time episodes. Here&#8217;s how you can watch The Pitt season 2 online and from anywhere including the UK, US, Australia and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firm overseeing FCC&#8217;s Cyber Trust Mark Program withdraws over ties to China</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/firm-overseeing-fccs-cyber-trust-mark-program-withdraws-over-ties-to-china</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mqFvNpSBLv2TBDBqQYEfUM</guid>
      <description>UL Solutions will no longer be the USCTM's Lead Administrator because of the company's ties with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify : vos amis peuvent d&#233;sormais voir ce que vous &#233;coutez en temps r&#233;el, voici comment activer cette fonction</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/2934347_spotify-vos-amis-peuvent-desormais-voir-ce-que-vous-ecoutez-en-temps-reel-voici-comment-activer-cette-fonction</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/2934347_spotify-vos-amis-peuvent-desormais-voir-ce-que-vous-ecoutez-en-temps-reel-voici-comment-activer-cette-fonction</guid>
      <description>
Spotify ne l&#226;che pas l'affaire. Apr&#232;s avoir lanc&#233; sa propre messagerie l'&#233;t&#233; dernier, le g&#233;ant su&#233;dois va plus loin. D&#232;s aujourd'hui, vos amis peuvent voir votre activit&#233; d'&#233;coute en temps r&#233;el directement dans vos discussions.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTV Is Officially Dead. It&#8217;s Time for Zombie MTV to Live in Your Browser</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mtv-is-officially-dead-its-time-for-zombie-mtv-to-live-in-your-browser-2000706831</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706831</guid>
      <description>MTV Rewind is the closest thing you can get to glory days of the boob tube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell admet que l&#8217;IA ne fait pas vendre de PC, c&#8217;est m&#234;me l&#8217;inverse</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926241_on-vend-plus-en-ne-le-disant-pas-dell-admet-que-lia-ne-fait-pas-vendre-de-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dell/2926241_on-vend-plus-en-ne-le-disant-pas-dell-admet-que-lia-ne-fait-pas-vendre-de-pc</guid>
      <description>
Vous en avez marre qu'on vous colle de l'IA &#224; toutes les sauces ? Vous n'&#234;tes pas seul. Dell s'est rendu compte d'une r&#233;alit&#233; brutale : le terme &#171; AI PC &#187; ne fait pas vendre. Pire, il embrouille tout le monde. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allez vous craquer pour l&#8217;un de ces t&#233;l&#233;viseurs lifestyle Hisense bient&#244;t disponibles ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hisense/2934373_allez-vous-craquer-pour-lun-de-ces-televiseurs-lifestyle-hisense-bientot-disponibles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hisense/2934373_allez-vous-craquer-pour-lun-de-ces-televiseurs-lifestyle-hisense-bientot-disponibles</guid>
      <description>
La marque Hisense a profit&#233; du CES de Las Vegas pour annoncer la prochaine commercialisation de plusieurs t&#233;l&#233;viseurs dits &#171;&#160;lifestyle&#160;&#187;. Comprenez qu&#8217;ils proposent des designs particuli&#232;rement originaux au d&#233;triment d&#8217;une fiche technique assez classique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>It's a new year, and a great time to fulfill your resolution to practice better cybersecurity. The early days of January are a great time to grab a last-minute subscription for yourself or a loved one. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart  online trackers.
Although we strongly recommend using a VPN, jumping on the first deal that comes along might get you stuck with a substandard app. Beyond that, even otherwise respectable VPNs sometimes frame their prices in misleading ways...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 gadgets from CES 2026 that you can buy right now: Dell, Xreal, Soundcore, more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-gadgets-you-can-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04ikMNmEkW7LNBvHL8IQEiy</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 just started, but a handful of new gadgets are already available to buy as of Jan. 7. Shop drops from Xreal, Anker, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
