<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:46:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok settles to avoid major social media addiction lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/tiktok-settles-to-avoid-major-social-media-addiction-lawsuit-183943927.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abcc6c37-37ca-4e5e-8875-a91aaac1cd59</guid>
      <description>TikTok has reached a settlement in a closely-watched lawsuit over social media addiction, narrowly avoiding a trial that's scheduled to begin jury selection Tuesday. Terms of the deal, which was reported by The New York Times, weren't disclosed.&#160;TikTok's settlement comes about one week after Snap reached a settlement in the same case. The trial is expected to move forward in Los Angeles with Meta and YouTube as the only defendants. Mark Lanier, a lawyer for the plaintiff, said in a statement to NYT that they were "pleased" with the settlement and that it was "a good resolution." TikTok didn't ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State-Led Crackdown on Grok and xAI Has Begun</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-state-led-crackdown-on-grok-and-xai-has-begun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965700bc9e9698ec20c258f</guid>
      <description>At least 37 attorneys general for US states and territories are taking action against xAI after Grok generated a flood of nonconsensual sexual images of women and minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;An issue that has gone unaddressed for too long': Major US city takes bold decision to ban single-use printer cartridges but will others follow suit?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/an-issue-that-has-gone-unaddressed-for-too-long-major-us-city-takes-bold-decision-to-ban-single-use-printer-cartridges-but-will-others-follow-suit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7PCKjmdvbXbe9hy4uz7vNH</guid>
      <description>A proposed ban on single-use ink cartridges in Los Angeles exposes the hidden environmental and financial cost of home printing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Data Shows Robotaxis Competing on Price&#8212;and Speed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-data-shows-robotaxis-competing-on-price-and-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977aa218ad4d08d0dc3c326</guid>
      <description>Research from the ride-hail aggregator Obi finds Waymo is starting to edge up on Uber and Lyft in San Francisco. Tesla, which operates a ride-hail service with human drivers, is winning the price wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A former Netflix game studio went indie to reach more players</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/868711/spry-fox-netflix-game-studio-indie-spirit-crossing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868711</guid>
      <description>When Netflix first acquired cozy game developer Spry Fox in 2022, it made a lot of sense. The studio had been around for over a decade and had several hits with mobile games like Triple Town and Alphabear. That approachable style of puzzle game seemed like a good fit for Netflix's mobile-first strategy, and, as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An app developer is suing Apple for Sherlocking it with Continuity Camera</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868740/apple-reincubate-lawsuit-camo-continuity-camera</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:25:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868740</guid>
      <description>Reincubate, which makes the Camo and Camo Studio apps for turning your iOS or Android phone into a webcam for your Mac or PC, is suing Apple, alleging anticompetitive conduct and patent infringement. Camo first launched in 2020, but two years after, Apple launched a similar feature called Continuity Camera, which works just with Apple [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic and OpenAI CEOs condemn ICE violence, praise Trump</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/anthropic-and-openai-ceos-condemn-ice-violence-praise-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086660</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's Dario Amodei and OpenAI's Sam Altman spoke out against ICE enforcement tactics following Minneapolis violence, with one addressing concerns publicly and the other in an internal message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Is Blocking Links To ICE List on Facebook, Instagram, and Threads</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/meta-is-blocking-links-to-ice-list-on-facebook-instagram-and-threads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6978dd298a2e73820b9b99b2</guid>
      <description>Users of Meta's social platforms can no longer share links to ICE List, a website listing what it claims are the names of thousands of DHS employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s foldable 3-in-1 charging station has hit a new low price of $50</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/868696/anker-maggo-wireless-charging-station-foldable-3-in-1-lego-roses-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:08:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868696</guid>
      <description>Buying separate chargers for your phone, watch, and earbuds adds up quickly. Anker&#8217;s MagGo Wireless Charging Station (Foldable 3-in-1) replaces all three, and now through January 30th it&#8217;s just $49.99 ($60 off) at Amazon-owned Woot. That&#8217;s the best price we&#8217;ve seen, and cheaper than many chargers designed for just one device. The charging station delivers [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Go and Fresh stores are closing as Amazon focuses on grocery delivery and Whole Foods</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/amazon-go-and-fresh-stores-are-closing-as-amazon-focuses-on-grocery-delivery-and-whole-foods-180448412.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd490677-0c7f-4d7b-a6bc-00afe8c1157b</guid>
      <description>Amazon is rethinking its grocery business, and as part of that, it will shut down all of its remaining Amazon Go and Amazon Fresh physical stores. The company will convert some locations into Whole Foods Market stores.&#160;"While we've seen encouraging signals in our Amazon-branded physical grocery stores, we haven't yet created a truly distinctive customer experience with the right economic model needed for large-scale expansion," the company wrote in a blog post. Amazon added that it would help workers at Go and Fresh stores to find positions elsewhere within the company.For now, Amazon is focus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp&amp;#8217;s new &amp;#8216;lockdown&amp;#8217; settings add another layer of protection against cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868722/whatsapp-strict-account-settings-cyberattacks</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:01:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868722</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is launching new "Strict Account Settings" that add even more protections against cyberattacks. The feature is built for people at a high-risk of attacks - such as journalists or public figures - and automatically blocks attachments and media from senders you don't know, while silencing calls from unknown contacts. The new setting limits other [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Sue the White House Over an AI Deepfake?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/can-you-sue-the-white-house-over-an-ai-deepfake-2000714219</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714219</guid>
      <description>The Trump regime's abuse of AI has opened up new legal questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s more affordable AI Plus plan rolls out to all markets, including the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/googles-ai-plus-plan-rolls-out-to-all-markets-including-the-u-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086571</guid>
      <description>Gemini 3 Pro and other AI tools are now available globally through the Google AI Plus plan, which is $7.99 per month in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These New &#8216;KPop Demon Hunter&#8217; Toys Will Takedown Your Wallet</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kpop-demon-hunters-toys-merchandise-dolls-release-date-hasbro-mattell-2000714461</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714461</guid>
      <description>Hasbro and Mattel are taking 'KPop Demon Hunters' to the stores with dolls, NERF weapons, and even UNO and Monopoly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI launches Prism, a new AI workspace for scientists</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/openai-launches-prism-a-new-ai-workspace-for-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086665</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has launched a new scientific workspace program called Prism, which integrates AI into existing standards for composing research papers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases Prism, a Claude Code-like app for scientific research</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-releases-prism-a-claude-code-like-app-for-scientific-research-180000454.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a96e543-e735-4e89-8c6c-db959c08a68c</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is releasing a new app called Prism today, and it hopes it does for science what coding agents like Claude Code and its own Codex platform have done for programming.&#160;Prism builds on Crixet, a cloud-based LaTeX platform the company is announcing it acquired today. For the uninitiated, LaTeX is a typesetting system for formatting scientific documents and journals. Nearly the entire scientific community relies on LaTeX, but it can make some tasks, such as drawing diagrams through TikZ commands, time-consuming to do. Beyond that, LaTeX is just one of the software tools a scientist might tur...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google AI Plus is now available in the US for $8 a month</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-ai-plus-is-now-available-in-the-us-for-8-a-month-180000175.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbd3aae1-4c4f-433c-abf9-d2d04959ae4e</guid>
      <description>Google AI Plus, the company&#8217;s most affordable AI subscription plan, is now rolling out in the US. It will cost you $8 a month for its features, though you can get it for $4 a month for the first two months for a limited time only. AI Plus gives you access to 200GB of storage, as well as access to the Gemini 3 Pro model, Deep Research and Nano Banana Pro inside the Gemini app. Nano Banana Pro generates images that look so realistic, they&#8217;re nearly indistinguishable from ordinary photos snapped on phones. Google even had to limit its usage due to high demand. A subscription to AI Plus also expan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid Trump attacks and weaponized sanctions, Europeans look to rely less on US tech</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/amid-trump-attacks-and-weaponized-sanctions-europeans-look-to-rely-less-on-us-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086633</guid>
      <description>European governments are looking to move away from U.S. tech and reclaim their digital sovereignty at a time of unpredictability and volatility in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert Insights</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tag/trpc</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GngCbbjotX4e9F6KRjvN3J</guid>
      <description>All TechRadar Pro stories tagged TRPC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 products that transformed my business trips from chaotic to super productive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/14-products-that-transformed-my-business-trips-from-chaotic-to-super-productive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gBgkEURSsuKjKNLSieZSie</guid>
      <description>From getting lost in the back streets of Paris to epic delays caused by volcanoes, I've had plenty of adventures whilst working away from home. Now, I have curated a list of the products I wouldn't leave home without.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos lance son premier nouveau produit depuis plus d&#8217;un an</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sonos/2957269_sonos-lance-son-premier-nouveau-produit-depuis-plus-dun-an</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sonos/2957269_sonos-lance-son-premier-nouveau-produit-depuis-plus-dun-an</guid>
      <description>
Vous vous souvenez de Sonos ? Apr&#232;s une ann&#233;e de silence radio et un fiasco logiciel qui a co&#251;t&#233; sa place au patron, la marque revient enfin aux affaires.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to add Freely's free streaming to your existing TV? This 4K HDR box might be the perfect upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/want-to-add-freelys-free-streaming-to-your-existing-tv-this-4k-hdr-box-might-be-the-perfect-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HGLSJ2uYeuFMDDKVmjHkPM</guid>
      <description>Free channels, regular streaming services, and TiVo's software &#8211; but should it be cheaper?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The price gap between Waymo and Uber is narrowing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/the-price-gap-between-waymo-and-uber-is-narrowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086568</guid>
      <description>Data collected and analyzed by Obi suggest a shift is underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This popular free YouTube function could be locked into its paid Premium plan &#8212; and I won't be happy if I have to sign up for another subscription service</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/this-popular-free-youtube-function-could-be-locked-into-its-paid-premium-plan-and-i-wont-be-happy-if-i-have-to-sign-up-for-another-subscription-service</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wNfPn2efh3Z2xYdWEW73zX</guid>
      <description>A new YouTube experiment shows that its free-to-use playback-speed tool could be locked into the YouTube Premium plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp introduces an advanced security mode to protect against hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/whatsapp-introduces-an-advanced-security-mode-to-protect-against-hackers-174144598.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5143d3f4-1bde-4508-8633-31f5c71dfb6e</guid>
      <description>Meta's WhatsApp just introduced something called Strict Account Settings, a tool "that further protects your account from highly sophisticated cyber attacks." This is a one-click button in the settings that automatically initiates a series of defenses.
So what does it do? It blocks media and attachments from unknown senders, disables link previews and silences calls from unknown senders. This results in a more restrictive experience, but hopefully a safer one.
The company says this isn't necessarily for regular users, as conversations are already protected by end-to-end encryption. Instead, th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: This free VPN extension was hijacking CyberGhost's free servers &#8211; here's what it means for your privacy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/exclusive-this-free-vpn-extension-was-hijacking-cyberghosts-free-servers-heres-what-it-means-for-your-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RJLszg42BcpEEmAUBaAiBd</guid>
      <description>TechRadar experts discovered that the 'BiuBiu VPN' Chrome extension was misusing CyberGhost&#8217;s resources. Here's all we know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Walking Pad Deals: Save $150 and More (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/walking-pad-deals-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977a8d38ad4d08d0dc3c325</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re working from home or just trying to hit your step goals, these walking pad deals make it easy to move every day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe finally adds a Clarity and Dehaze layer to Photoshop &#8211; and I can't believe it took this long</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/adobe-finally-adds-a-clarity-and-dehaze-layer-to-photoshop-and-i-cant-believe-it-took-this-long</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">v6NfHvP9y9ZNuPhomzomq6</guid>
      <description>"Control, realism, and precision" - the latest Photoshop updates from Adobe target fast-paced creative professional workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un drone 4K &#224; moins de 200 &#8364; ? C&#8217;est possible pendant les soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957085_un-drone-4k-a-moins-de-200-e-cest-possible-pendant-les-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957085_un-drone-4k-a-moins-de-200-e-cest-possible-pendant-les-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Le drone Potensic ATOM SE est un drone grand public l&#233;ger, &#233;quip&#233; d'un capteur 4K, fourni avec une t&#233;l&#233;commande et surtout propos&#233; &#224; un prix tr&#232;s attractif. Pendant les soldes d'hiver, AliExpress l'affiche &#224; 181,69 euros avec ses accessoires, alors que le bundle &#233;tait auparavant vendu &#224; environ 300 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you live in the UK, you probably won&#8217;t be able to visit Pornhub anymore</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/if-you-live-in-the-uk-you-probably-wont-be-able-to-visit-pornhub-anymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086598</guid>
      <description>Pornhub parent company Aylo will restrict access from U.K. users, rather than comply with age verification mandates, which the company said it believes have not succeeded in promoting online safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Swears It Didn&#8217;t Ban Sharing the Name &#8216;Epstein,&#8217; as Gavin Newsom Announces Investigation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tiktok-swears-it-didnt-ban-sharing-the-name-epstein-as-gavin-newsom-announces-investigation-2000714521</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714521</guid>
      <description>The scrutiny follows a rocky first week under new U.S. ownership./</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why it pays to believe in luck</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477575/why-it-pays-to-believe-in-luck</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477575/why-it-pays-to-believe-in-luck</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s not just skill and hard work that lead to success.
The oil tycoon J. Paul Getty was rumoured to have said that his three rules for how to become rich were: Rise early. Work hard. Strike oil. It&#8217;s one of those eminently quotable remarks because it captures something we all know to be true, that luck and chance have as much to do with success as anything else....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says it&#8217;s still working to recover its U.S. infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/tiktok-says-its-still-working-to-recover-its-u-s-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086628</guid>
      <description>TikTok says some of the glitches continue but it's making "significant progress" in recovering its U.S. infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo is adding generative AI to its search engine</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/yahoo-is-adding-generative-ai-to-its-search-engine-172706249.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db692d13-1bbb-488e-a6c6-ce1e27414497</guid>
      <description>Yahoo has announced a new AI-powered "answer engine", dubbed Yahoo Scout. The new tool is available now in beta and is powered by Anthropic's Claude.
The company says Scout "synthesizes" info from the web, as well as Yahoo's own data and content when constructing responses to user's natural-language search queries. Yahoo says the interface will include interactive digital media, structured lists and tables and visible source links aimed at making answers easier to verify. (Disclosure: Yahoo is the parent company of Engadget.)
Alongside Scout, Yahoo is announcing an "intelligence platform" acro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp is rolling out a new stricter security setting to protect users from cyber attacts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/whatsapp-is-rolling-out-a-new-stricter-security-setting-to-protect-users-from-cyber-attacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086615</guid>
      <description>Days after Meta was sued over alleged false privacy claims surrounding its chat app WhatsApp, the company has rolled out a new setting to protect users against cyber attacks. The feature, called Strict&#160;Account&#160;Settings, adds restrictions like automatically blocking media and attachments from unknown senders, and silencing calls from unknown numbers. Under this setting, link previews [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oppo Reno 15 : quatre nouveaux smartphones et toujours plus de 6000 mAh</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/oppo/2956623_oppo-reno-15-quatre-nouveaux-smartphones-et-toujours-plus-de-6000-mah</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/oppo/2956623_oppo-reno-15-quatre-nouveaux-smartphones-et-toujours-plus-de-6000-mah</guid>
      <description>
Les quatre nouveaux Oppo Reno 15, Reno 15 Pro, Reno 15 F et Reno 15 FS sont officialis&#233;s en France avec, en argument choc, des batteries au dessus des 6000 mAh.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worrying Microsoft Office security flaw patched - update now or risk hackers accessing your files</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/worrying-microsoft-office-security-flaw-patched-update-now-or-risk-hackers-accessing-your-files</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Jof4ywzbk2Pg3RfLhCjbf</guid>
      <description>Microsoft forced to issue an emergency patch to fix an Office zero-day being actively exploited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung confirme le prix du Galaxy Z TriFold, et &#231;a pique</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-son-prix-et-sa-date-de-sortie-fuitent-et-ca-pique.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322645</guid>
      <description>Le puzzle se compl&#232;te enfin pour le Galaxy Z TriFold. Apr&#232;s notre prise en main de ce monstre de technologie, de nouvelles indiscr&#233;tions viennent d&#233;voiler l'addition et le calendrier de lancement. Pr&#233;parez-vous, la facture s'annonce particuli&#232;rement sal&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmes addictifs des r&#233;seaux sociaux | TikTok conclut un accord avant l&#8217;ouverture du proc&#232;s</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-27/algorithmes-addictifs-des-reseaux-sociaux/tiktok-conclut-un-accord-avant-l-ouverture-du-proces.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:13:07 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d9d445691353168996ee97536f9f253</guid>
      <description>Une semaine apr&#232;s Snapchat, TikTok a &#224; son tour pr&#233;f&#233;r&#233; conclure un accord quelques heures avant l&#8217;ouverture du proc&#232;s qui devait les voir compara&#238;tre aux c&#244;t&#233;s de Meta et YouTube, accus&#233;s par des milliers de plaignants d&#8217;avoir sciemment con&#231;u leurs applications pour favoriser la d&#233;pendance des jeunes utilisateurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consommation, recharge, s&#233;curit&#233; : pourquoi la nouvelle Dacia Spring &#233;lectrique devrait &#234;tre plus &#224; l&#8217;aise sur autoroute</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2956989_consommation-recharge-securite-pourquoi-la-nouvelle-dacia-spring-electrique-devrait-etre-plus-a-laise-sur-autoroute</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2956989_consommation-recharge-securite-pourquoi-la-nouvelle-dacia-spring-electrique-devrait-etre-plus-a-laise-sur-autoroute</guid>
      <description>
La Dacia Spring vient de recevoir des moteurs plus puissants. Cela devrait lui faire du bien sur autoroute : outre de meilleures performances, la consommation en baisse &#224; haute vitesse et la recharge plus rapide devraient faire progresser la polyvalence de la voiture &#233;lectrique la moins ch&#232;re du march&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN kills legacy apps &#8211; you have time until March 31 to update yours</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-kills-legacy-apps-you-have-time-until-march-31-to-update-yours</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9YqLaiLK3MBd8buhzovGbK</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN says older app versions will stop connecting after March 31, 2026, as part of a major security update. Check your version, update now, and stay protected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok US is mostly back up and running</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868679/tiktok-down-outage-us-usds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T12:05:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868679</guid>
      <description>As we moved into the third day of the TikTokalypse, the app appears to have finally stabilized in the US, as we verified that it's possible to consistently publish new videos and even have other people watch them. That hasn't been a simple task since the service started having problems early Sunday morning, but on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp renforce la s&#233;curit&#233; des comptes les plus expos&#233;s aux attaques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/whatsapp-renforce-la-securite-des-comptes-les-plus-exposes-aux-attaques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322818</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp propose depuis toujours le chiffrement de bout en bout par d&#233;faut des discussions, ce qui offre un bon niveau de confidentialit&#233; aux &#233;changes. Mais certains utilisateurs peuvent en vouloir davantage, c'est pourquoi la messagerie de Meta propose une nouvelle option de s&#233;curit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel Redmi Note 15 choisir&#160;? Le guide ultime pour s&#8217;y retrouver</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/quel-redmi-note-15-choisir-le-guide-ultime-pour-sy-retrouver.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320592</guid>
      <description>&#192; chaque g&#233;n&#233;ration, les Redmi Note reviennent occuper le terrain du smartphone abordable, au point de devenir un passage quasi oblig&#233; pour les petits budgets. Avec les Redmi Note 15, Xiaomi reconduit la recette, mais la prolif&#233;ration de versions (4G, 5G, Pro et Pro+) brouille s&#233;rieusement les pistes pour le grand public. Ce dossier d&#233;cortique les cinq mod&#232;les, du ticket d&#8217;entr&#233;e &#224; 200 euros jusqu&#8217;au Pro+ &#224; 500 euros, afin de vous aider &#224; comprendre ce que vous gagnez, ou perdez, &#224; chaque palier de prix et &#224; choisir en connaissance de cause....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For some reason, Bethesda has teamed up with Pringles to launch a Fallout 76 Mystery Flavour</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/for-some-reason-bethesda-has-teamed-up-with-pringles-to-launch-a-fallout-76-mystery-flavour</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pjPaeTWHfWjjcY6buhynqf</guid>
      <description>Pringles has launched a new Fallout 76 Mystery Flavour, and to celebrate, fans can submit their guess to win a special prize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: Everything we think the company will unveil</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-everything-we-think-the-company-will-unveil-130000218.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hands-on coverage of Samsung's new smartphones soon after they're announced. While we wait for an official invite, here's everything we expect Samsung will introduce at the first Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026.Galaxy S26, S26+ and S26 UltraSamsung ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following its major restructuring announcement, Ubisoft begins 'a collective, voluntary mutual termination agreement' at its Paris HQ, with 200 jobs on the line</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-industry/following-its-major-restructuring-announcement-ubisoft-begins-a-collective-voluntary-mutual-termination-agreement-at-its-paris-hq-with-200-jobs-on-the-line</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gcKrcgVjUnniC8KcDPhW6T</guid>
      <description>After announcing major restructuring plans at Ubisoft and the cancellation of several games, the company has now begun a voluntary redundancy process at its Paris, France headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s trillion-dollar investments in America from foreign trading partners face skepticism</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481693/trump-economy-investment-foreign-research-study</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T17:00:57</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481693/trump-economy-investment-foreign-research-study</guid>
      <description>Trump used the threat of punitive tariffs to pry concessions out of those trading partners, including the investment pledges. 
President Donald Trump has strong-armed many of America&#8217;s biggest trading partners into pledging trillions of dollars of investment in the United States. But a study out Tuesday raises doubts about whether the money will actually materialize and questions how it would be spent if it did....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Raimi Movies, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-raimi-movies-ranked-2000713699</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713699</guid>
      <description>His new one, 'Send Help,' is out this week, but where does it rank against 'Evil Dead,' 'Spider-Man,' and others?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : il reste un peu plus d&#8217;une semaine pour faire de bonnes affaires, les meilleures offres en DIRECT</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949895_soldes-dhiver-2026-il-reste-un-peu-plus-dune-semaine-pour-faire-de-bonnes-affaires-les-meilleures-offres-en-direct</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949895_soldes-dhiver-2026-il-reste-un-peu-plus-dune-semaine-pour-faire-de-bonnes-affaires-les-meilleures-offres-en-direct</guid>
      <description>
C'est d&#233;j&#224; bient&#244;t la fin des soldes d'hiver. En effet, dans un peu plus d'une semaine, les e-commer&#231;ants tels qu'Amazon, Fnac, Darty, Boulanger ou encore Cdiscount vont arr&#234;ter de partager des offres en ce sens. C'est bient&#244;t la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque, l&#224; o&#249; il y a les meilleures offres &#224; saisir. Tenez-vous pr&#234;t(e)s !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google DeepMind Staffers Ask Leaders to Keep Them &#8216;Physically Safe&#8217; From ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-deepmind-staffers-ice-office-questions-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69783fc373242c9937907204</guid>
      <description>A federal agent allegedly tried to enter Google&#8217;s Cambridge campus in the fall, WIRED has learned. Now, staffers want policies that protect them from immigration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Search now lets you ask AI Overviews follow-up questions</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868497/google-ai-search-follow-up-questions-gemini-3</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868497</guid>
      <description>Google is making Search less about links and more about AI. The company is upgrading its AI-powered search features, adding Gemini 3 to AI Overviews and letting users ask follow-up questions "seamlessly" to make sure Search can answer "whatever's on your mind," a move that feels closer to using an AI chatbot than a search [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The promise and peril of a new online shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/868558/highguard-online-shooters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868558</guid>
      <description>The routine is familiar by now. A new online shooter with bright, colorful graphics launches and rockets up the charts despite the fact that you maybe haven't even heard of it. Or maybe it just has a really forgettable name. But everyone seems to be talking about it, and it's free, so you figure you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google now lets users jump from AI Overviews into AI Mode conversations</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/google-now-lets-users-jump-from-ai-overviews-into-ai-mode-conversations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086581</guid>
      <description>The tech giant also announced that it's making Gemini 3 the new default model for AI Overviews globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android phones are getting more anti-theft features</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/android-phones-are-getting-more-anti-theft-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086593</guid>
      <description>Google says Android devices will get new security features, like stronger authentication safeguards and enhanced recovery tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Search gets smarter AI Overviews with Gemini 3 &#8212; and adds follow&#8209;up chats to your search results</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/gemini/google-search-gets-smarter-ai-overviews-with-gemini-3-and-adds-follow-up-chats-to-your-search-results</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bTsTc3SskNt6ftyH7eRjd8</guid>
      <description>Google Search upgrades AI Overviews with Gemini 3 and a connection to AI Mode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 is now Google's default model for AI Overviews</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/gemini-3-is-now-googles-default-model-for-ai-overviews-170000302.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf9ab5ff-6d05-4bdb-aa4d-dd7c4bafa410</guid>
      <description>Google has begun rolling out two upgrades for Search. Starting today, Gemini 3 is the default model powering AI Overviews. When the company debuted its new family of AI systems last November, it first deployed Gemini 3 in AI Overviews through a router that was programmed to direct the most difficult questions to the new system. Now Google is making Gemini 3 the standard for all users globally. In practice, Gemini 3 should prove better at generating more credible and relevant summaries.&#160;As for that second upgrade, now you can jump into AI Mode conversation directly from an AI Overview. Google f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette galaxie contredit tout ce qu&#8217;on pensait savoir sur l&#8217;Univers primitif</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/univers-cette-galaxie-contredit-tout-ce-quon-pensait-savoir-univers-primitif-w2t8-130489/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/univers-cette-galaxie-contredit-tout-ce-quon-pensait-savoir-univers-primitif-w2t8-130489/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Les galaxies satellites de notre Voie lact&#233;e ont appris beaucoup de choses aux astronomes sur l&#8217;&#233;volution de notre Univers. C&#8217;est du moins ce dont ils &#233;taient convaincus. Mais la d&#233;couverte d&#8217;une toute petite galaxie dans le voisinage d&#8217;Androm&#232;de remet pas mal de choses en question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow these 8 tips to feel secure about your money in retirement</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481688/follow-8-tips-feel-secure-about-your-money-retirement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T16:59:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481688/follow-8-tips-feel-secure-about-your-money-retirement</guid>
      <description>Replace anxiety and nagging worries with financial security.
The greatest financial danger in retirement isn&#8217;t always the stock market. It&#8217;s the constant, nagging fear of running out of money. This anxiety causes many people to underspend and worry, even when their finances are sound.Here are eight ways to replace that worry with lasting security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian states weigh Australia-style ban on social media for children</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/indian-states-weigh-australia-style-ban-on-social-media-for-children/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086579</guid>
      <description>Any move to restrict children's access to social media in India would carry significant implications for global technology companies, for which the South Asian nation is a critical growth market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Pediatricians Give Middle Finger to RFK Jr., Issue Their Own Vaccine Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/us-pediatricians-give-middle-finger-to-rfk-jr-issue-their-own-vaccine-recommendations-2000714459</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714459</guid>
      <description>The American Academy of Pediatrics and 12 other medical groups are recommending the same childhood shots once endorsed by the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel smartphone Oppo choisir en 2026&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/smartphones/709865_guide-smartphones-oppo</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/smartphones/709865_guide-smartphones-oppo</guid>
      <description>
Oppo fait son retour en France et plus largement en Europe. La marque chinoise est revenue sur le march&#233; avec un nouveau t&#233;l&#233;phone haut de gamme.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon se montre bien g&#233;n&#233;reux pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes avec une myriade d&#8217;offres</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-multiplie-les-offres-a-lapproche-de-la-derniere-demarque-les-17-meilleurs-deals-a-saisir</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-multiplie-les-offres-a-lapproche-de-la-derniere-demarque-les-17-meilleurs-deals-a-saisir</guid>
      <description>
La derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver d&#233;marre d&#232;s demain, et Amazon en profite pour proposer des offres toujours plus int&#233;ressantes avant la fin de l&#8217;&#233;v&#233;nement. Smartphones pliants, vid&#233;oprojecteurs &#224; prix cass&#233; et bien d&#8217;autres produits tech sont &#224; saisir d&#232;s maintenant&#8239;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This iPhone offer from AT&amp;T might just be one of the best deals I've seen at the carrier in months - and it's easy to miss</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/this-iphone-offer-from-at-and-t-might-just-be-one-of-the-best-deals-ive-seen-at-the-carrier-in-months-and-its-easy-to-miss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">J3iJ2Vv8Kax7Ed5HNHM5TD</guid>
      <description>This deal on the iPhone Air beats the iPhone 17, 17 Pro, and others</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel 10 users are reporting broken Wi-Fi and Bluetooth with the latest update &#8211; and there&#8217;s no fix in sight</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/google-pixel-phones/google-pixel-10-users-are-reporting-broken-wi-fi-and-bluetooth-with-the-latest-update-and-theres-no-fix-in-sight</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hwbsS25syQTp3uZkyXoTrX</guid>
      <description>The latest Pixel patch fixes bugs but also seems to introduce some, rendering certain Pixel 10 series phones almost unusable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I stock up on these viral Amazon pillows every January &#8212; they have 200,000+ five-star reviews and are just $41.98 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/i-stock-up-on-these-viral-amazon-pillows-every-january-they-have-200-000-five-star-reviews-and-are-just-usd41-98-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LQwYBGcsJxoYUPYUvy5YfR</guid>
      <description>If you're like me and stock up on new pillows every January, then I can't recommend the viral Beckham Hotel Collection pillows, which are on sale for $41.98 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
