<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:23:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deux nouveaux milieux de gamme sold&#233;s &#224; moins de 250 &#8364; : faut&#8209;il craquer pour le Xiaomi Redmi Note 15 5G ou le Nothing Phone (3a) Lite ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944429_deux-nouveaux-milieux-de-gamme-soldes-a-moins-de-250-e-faut%e2%80%91il-craquer-pour-le-xiaomi-redmi-note-15-5g-ou-le-nothing-phone-3a-lite</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944429_deux-nouveaux-milieux-de-gamme-soldes-a-moins-de-250-e-faut%e2%80%91il-craquer-pour-le-xiaomi-redmi-note-15-5g-ou-le-nothing-phone-3a-lite</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver sont souvent le moment id&#233;al pour s&#8217;offrir un nouveau smartphone sans faire exploser son budget. Il y a deux mod&#232;les r&#233;cents sous la barre des 300 euros qui attirent particuli&#232;rement l&#8217;attention : le Xiaomi Redmi Note 15 5G et le Nothing Phone (3a) Lite. On les oppose pour vous aider &#224; choisir celui qui offre le meilleur rapport qualit&#233;-prix.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cute frog game that remixes Nintendo&amp;#8217;s best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/860917/big-hops-review-pc-nintendo-switch-ps5</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860917</guid>
      <description>While playing Big Hops, a new 3D platformer starring an adorable frog, I kept feeling like I was breaking the game - and, like with The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom, breaking it is kind of the point. In Big Hops, you play as a frog named Hop. Early on, Hop is taken [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota wants to win a war of attrition</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/863632/minnesota-walz-trump-sousveillance-ice</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863632</guid>
      <description>As masked and armed men in combat armor swarmed throughout the Twin Cities, Gov. Tim Walz took to primetime television to ask Minnesotans to film ICE. The videos, he said, would "create a database of the atrocities against Minnesotans - not just to establish a record for posterity, but to bank evidence for future prosecution." [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of chips: how gate-all-around design is powering the AI era and the next node</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-future-of-chips-how-gate-all-around-design-is-powering-the-ai-era-and-the-next-node</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6NoZS44vZA3LT9oU2dTTEk</guid>
      <description>Materials innovation drives next-gen AI chips, enabling performance, efficiency and scalability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California AG sends cease and desist to xAI over Grok's explicit deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/california-ag-sends-cease-and-desist-to-xai-over-groks-explicit-deepfakes-140000574.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e11287aa-db96-48c2-aa5d-e3590a0bfe86</guid>
      <description>California Attorney General Rob Bonta has sent a cease and desist letter to xAI, days after his office launched an official investigation into the company over reports that Grok was generating nonconsensual  If you&#8217;ll recall, xAI and Grok have been under fire for taking images of real individuals and putting them in revealing clothing like bikinis upon random users&#8217; requests. Bonta&#8217;s office demands that xAI immediately cease and desist from creating &#8220;digitized sexually explicit material&#8221; when the depicted individual didn&#8217;t consent to it or if the individual is a minor. It also demanded that xA...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to pair AirPods with any device</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/how-to-pair-airpods-with-any-device-140000234.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dd726c0-ef43-4ed4-8d23-6962bf83a1ae</guid>
      <description>AirPods work most smoothly with Apple hardware, but they also connect reliably to Android phones, Windows laptops and other Bluetooth devices. The pairing process depends on the platform in use although the basics remain the same. Once the AirPods are placed in pairing mode, most devices detect them quickly and handle the remaining steps in the background. The guide below explains how to pair AirPods with Apple products, how the process differs on newer iPhones that support H2 features and how to connect them to non-Apple devices.How to pair AirPods with Apple devicesApple builds AirPods to pa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New year, new upgrades &#8211; here are 5 improvements I want Spotify to make in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/spotify/new-year-new-upgrades-here-are-5-improvements-i-want-spotify-to-make-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">spdbSADMy5xAcg3YGReLA7</guid>
      <description>2025 was great, but 2026 could be even better. These are the upgrades I need to see from Spotify this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Greenland is strategically valuable for LEO': CEO of European laser communications startup expands on why lasers complement radio networks - and highlights the critical importance of the North Pole for satellite passes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/greenland-is-strategically-valuable-for-leo-ceo-of-european-laser-communications-startup-expands-on-why-lasers-complement-radio-networks-and-highlights-the-critical-importance-of-the-north-pole-for-satellite-passes</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vhRx8SbkGZJLyVvKcBaac</guid>
      <description>Greenland&#8217;s location near the North Pole makes it a critical site for laser based satellite communications, expert says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un moteur ultra puissant dans un VTC &#233;lectrique ultra &#233;quip&#233; : on a test&#233; le Scott Axis 20 Wave, et c&#8217;est du lourd</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2944057_un-moteur-ultra-puissant-dans-un-vtc-electrique-ultra-equipe-on-a-teste-le-scott-axis-20-wave-et-cest-du-lourd</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2944057_un-moteur-ultra-puissant-dans-un-vtc-electrique-ultra-equipe-on-a-teste-le-scott-axis-20-wave-et-cest-du-lourd</guid>
      <description>
L'essai du Scott Axis 20 Wave montre que la fronti&#232;re entre le VTTAE et le VTC &#233;lectrique est parfois poreuse, car ce mod&#232;le est autant performant hors bitume qu'en ville, jouit d'une bonne polyvalence, est bien &#233;quip&#233; pour le quotidien, sans &#234;tre trop on&#233;reux. Voici notre test complet.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eufy Robot Vacuum Omni E28 Review: A Good Vacuum That Tries to Do Too Much</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/eufy-robot-vacuum-omni-e28-review-a-good-vacuum-that-tries-to-do-too-much-2000699135</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699135</guid>
      <description>Solid vacuuming and a handy deep clean module almost make the Omni E28 a solid choice, if not for a noisy dock and mediocre mopping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and blogging (and prerelease laptop testing) in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/862985/asus-zenbook-a16-snapdragon-x2-ces-early-testing-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862985</guid>
      <description>At CES, I did what you're not supposed to do: I brought a pre-production laptop to use as my primary workhorse during a hectic event. The unproven rifle in question is the new Arm-based Asus Zenbook A16. It's a 16-inch laptop that weighs less than a 13-inch MacBook Air and comes with a high-end Snapdragon [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our favorite cozy game is back</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/863614/animal-crossing-3-rip-netflix-cowork-installer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863614</guid>
      <description>Hi, friends! Welcome to Installer No. 112, your guide to the best and Verge-iest stuff in the world. (If you're new here, welcome, I hope your home is warmer than mine right now, and also you can read all the old editions at the Installer homepage.) This week, I've been reading about WhatsApp and Gavin [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want delicious, quality espresso with the convenience of pods? After two weeks of testing, I can say the Lavazza A Modo Mio Smeg is the coffee maker for you</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/lavazza-a-modo-mio-smeg-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">X7dQc3PQsCyvq7eqNLdzoS</guid>
      <description>This chic espresso machine isn't the cheapest capsule coffee maker around, but it's definitely one of the best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to cancel CyberGhost and get a refund</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-cancel-cyberghost-and-get-a-refund-130000311.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb43eed0-f954-43d3-964f-bfeb8e845bd8</guid>
      <description>I came out of my CyberGhost review with a positive opinion, feeling it had earned its spot in my best VPN roundup. However, even an expert review is subjective, and there's a chance CyberGhost will not work for you. If that&#8217;s the case, here's how to cancel your subscription.How to stop your CyberGhost subscription renewingCancelling your CyberGhost subscription won't end it right away, unless you delete your account or get the refund (I'll explain how to do both of those later). Instead, the way to cancel CyberGhost is to stop your subscription from renewing at the end of each billing period. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le t&#233;lescope James-Webb perce le brouillard de poussi&#232;re d&#8217;une galaxie parmi les plus actives proches de nous</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/galaxie-telescope-james-webb-perce-brouillard-poussiere-galaxie-parmi-plus-actives-proches-nous-130165/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:57:49 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/galaxie-telescope-james-webb-perce-brouillard-poussiere-galaxie-parmi-plus-actives-proches-nous-130165/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le t&#233;lescope spatial James-Webb a observ&#233; une galaxie situ&#233;e &#224; 13 millions d'ann&#233;es-lumi&#232;re de nous avec, en son centre, un trou noir supermassif source de rayonnement infrarouge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batteries de voitures &#233;lectriques : pourquoi on r&#233;gresse alors que la technologie progresse</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2945475_batteries-de-voitures-electriques-pourquoi-on-regresse-alors-que-la-technologie-progresse</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2945475_batteries-de-voitures-electriques-pourquoi-on-regresse-alors-que-la-technologie-progresse</guid>
      <description>
En 2023, la dur&#233;e de vie des batteries de voitures &#233;lectriques s'am&#233;liorait. Mais les derniers chiffres de 2025 viennent de tomber, et c'est la douche froide : nous sommes revenus au niveau de 2020. Pourquoi cette r&#233;gression soudaine ? C'est simple : nous rechargeons mal nos voitures.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best External Hard Drive (2026): SSD to Store Data, Video &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-portable-external-storage-drives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60dc74924abd3c033f4a0180</guid>
      <description>Need an ultrafast drive for video editing or a rugged option to back up your photos in the field? We&#8217;ve got a solution for every situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Samsung Galaxy S26 leak shows no sign of the Pro or Edge models &#8211; but these are the phones we think we will get</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/fresh-samsung-galaxy-s26-leak-shows-no-sign-of-the-pro-or-edge-models-but-these-are-the-phones-we-think-we-will-get</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6xDVWjNhabLkysTGR9KfNA</guid>
      <description>It looks as though Samsung is going to stick with its traditional approach when it comes to its 2026 flagship phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papers Please but with zombies, a farming-based shoot-'em-up and other new indie games worth checking out</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/papers-please-but-with-zombies-a-farming-based-shoot-em-up-and-other-new-indie-games-worth-checking-out-123000437.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65a90182-7193-42ba-8fdd-e43829c445b8</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our latest roundup of what's going on in the indie game space. Several neat-looking games arrived this week, we got release dates for several others that I'm really looking forward to and a brand-new Steam festival was announced.&#160;The Love, Romance, and Heartbreak Debutante Ball is said to be the first Valentine's Day-themed Steam festival. It'll run from February 13 to 20 and feature more than 100 games, including discounts and demos. A showcase will take place on February 13 at 1PM ET on the Sunny Demeanor Games YouTube channel too.Organizers say the festival includes a wide variet...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
