<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:31:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Digg Relaunches From the Grave With Some &#8216;AI Enhancements&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/digg-relaunches-from-the-grave-with-some-ai-enhancements-2000710736</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710736</guid>
      <description>For all the people who've abandoned or been kicked off Reddit, your Bluesky moment has arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon Is Slipping Customers 20 Bucks to Pay for Yesterday&#8217;s Outage</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/verizon-is-slipping-customers-20-bucks-to-pay-for-yesterdays-outage-2000710778</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710778</guid>
      <description>The carrier is offering a $20 credit to customers affected by a widespread and hours-long service outage on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the most interesting automotive tech I saw at CES &#8212; and the ones you should be watching in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/this-is-the-most-interesting-automotive-tech-i-saw-at-ces-and-the-ones-you-should-be-watching-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XoNLrP5EjmpTorwAobkiuG</guid>
      <description>From Qualcomm to Waymo, car companies and their partners are doing autos differently in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les astronomes pensent enfin savoir ce que sont les &#171; points rouges &#187; rep&#233;r&#233;s par le t&#233;lescope James-Webb</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/cosmologie-astronomes-pensent-enfin-savoir-ce-sont-points-rouges-reperes-telescope-james-webb-130212/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:59:31 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/cosmologie-astronomes-pensent-enfin-savoir-ce-sont-points-rouges-reperes-telescope-james-webb-130212/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Des &#171; petits points rouges &#187; dans les images renvoy&#233;es par le t&#233;lescope spatial James-Webb. Plusieurs mois que les astronomes s&#8217;y cassent les dents. Mais de nouvelles donn&#233;es pourraient enfin lever le voile. Ou laisser &#233;clore le papillon cosmique&#8201;?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s New World: Aeternum MMO will shut down next year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862892/amazon-new-world-aeternum-mmo-servers-shut-down-delisted</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T14:52:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862892</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced that the servers for New World: Aeternum, one of the company's MMOs, will be shut down on January 31st, 2027. The game will also be delisted and no longer available for purchase starting today, January 15th. Last year, Amazon announced that it would be pivoting away from MMOs to put more of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flaw in 17 Google Fast Pair audio devices could let hackers eavesdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/flaw-in-17-google-fast-pair-audio-devices-could-let-hackers-eavesdrop-194613456.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8404957d-0b0f-4df4-be02-abfa15084dd2</guid>
      <description>Now would be a good time to update all your Bluetooth audio devices. On Thursday, Wired reported on a security flaw in 17 headphone and speaker models that could allow hackers to access your devices, including their microphones. The vulnerability stems from a faulty implementation of Google's one-tap (Fast Pair) protocol.Security researchers at Belgium's KU Leuven University Computer Security and Industrial Cryptography group, who discovered the security hole, named the flaw WhisperPair. They say a hacker within Bluetooth range would only require the accessory's (easily attainable) device mode...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Code just got updated with one of the most-requested user features</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/claude-code-just-got-updated-with-one-of-the-most-requested-user-features</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7J6Mc1KRAJv7cWPQwJSCRq</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's open source standard, the Model Context Protocol (MCP), released in late 2024, allows users to connect AI models and the agents atop them to external tools in a structured, reliable format. It is the engine behind Anthropic's hit AI agentic programming harness, Claude Code, allowing it to access numerous functions like web browsing and file creation immediately when asked.But there was one problem: Claude Code typically had to "read" the instruction manual for every single tool available, regardless of whether it was needed for the immediate task, using up the available context tha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s Grok &#8216;Undressing&#8217; Problem Isn&#8217;t Fixed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musks-grok-undressing-problem-isnt-fixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6968fedb43f4ea26029fe444</guid>
      <description>X has placed more restrictions on Grok&#8217;s ability to generate explicit AI images, but tests show that the updates have created a patchwork of limitations that fail to fully address the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI video startup, Higgsfield, founded by ex-Snap exec, lands $1.3B valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/ai-video-startup-higgsfield-founded-by-ex-snap-exec-lands-1-3b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083094</guid>
      <description>Higgsfield says it's on a $200 million annual revenue run rate. So it opened its previous Series A round back up and sold another $80 million in shares.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $50 on the OnePlus Watch 3, Which Has Revolutionary Battery Tech</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/oneplus-watch-3-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6969252258f4df04883f0e19</guid>
      <description>Save some cash on this Wear OS smartwatch with a revolutionary battery that can go for five days on a charge (16 days on low-power mode).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A &#8216;chilling effect&#8217;: Press freedom advocates denounce the raid on a Washington Post journalist&#8217;s home</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475709/raid-washington-post-journalist-press-advocates</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T19:18:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475709/raid-washington-post-journalist-press-advocates</guid>
      <description>The action &#8216;signals a growing assault on independent reporting and undermines the First Amendment.&#8217;
If the byproduct of a raid on a Washington Post journalist&#8217;s home is to deter probing reporting of government action, the Trump administration could hardly have chosen a more compelling target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save a massive $400 on the powerful and four-star-rated Dell 16 Plus laptop at Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows-laptops/save-a-massive-usd400-on-the-powerful-and-four-star-rated-dell-16-plus-laptop-at-best-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SqfjyXfkCCMLwh22Jei3rh</guid>
      <description>The Dell 16 plummets back to the record-low price we saw it drop to last year in the Best Buy Winter Sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Is Seriously Playing With Fire</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spotify-is-seriously-playing-with-fire-2000710643</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710643</guid>
      <description>AI slop and price hikes may not be a winning combo when Apple Music is breathing down your neck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS has stopped producing the NVIDIA RTX 5070 Ti and 5060 Ti 16GB, saying they've reached 'end of life'</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/asus-has-stopped-producing-the-nvidia-rtx-5070-ti-and-5060-ti-16gb-saying-theyve-reached-end-of-life-162012253.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcc3c5c6-3d7d-4c24-b666-590fd12d156f</guid>
      <description>YouTube channel Hardware Unboxed is reporting that NVIDIA has &#8220;effectively&#8221; discontinued the RTX 5070 Ti and 5060 Ti 16GB due to the ongoing memory crunch. In its most recent video, the channel states ASUS &#8220;explicitly&#8221; told it the RTX 5070 Ti is &#8220;currently facing a supply shortage.&#8221; As a result, the company has &#8220;placed the model into end of life status,&#8221; and no longer plans to produce it. Hardware Unboxed also spoke to retailers in Australia, who told the channel the 5070 Ti is &#8220;no longer available to purchase from partners and distributors,&#8221; adding they expect that to be the case throughout a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram is nostalgic for 2016 again (yes, really)</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/2016-instagram-tiktok-trend-nostalgia-photo-dumps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05BsIugagoeSK0SW0GRHyWV</guid>
      <description>Everyone seems to miss 2016. And that's why you're seeing old photo dumps all over your Instagram feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is making a Fallout Shelter competition reality TV show</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/amazon-is-making-a-fallout-shelter-competition-reality-tv-show-190151855.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45f465a4-7377-4b4d-a99e-c9ce37c6070c</guid>
      <description>The second season of Amazon's excellent Fallout show is currently airing, but the company is already looking to expand its programming around the popular franchise. Prime Video has greenlit a unscripted reality show titled Fallout Shelter. It will be a ten-episode run with Studio Lambert, the team behind reality projects including Squid Game: The Challenge and The Traitors, as its primary producer.&#160;Bethesda Game Studios&#8217; head honcho Todd Howard is attached as an executive producer. Amazon's description of Fallout Shelter is: "Across a series of escalating challenges, strategic dilemmas and mor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The Bride!&#8217; Creator Maggie Gyllenhaal on Why Jessie Buckley Is the Perfect Monster Heroine</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-bride-creator-maggie-gyllenhaal-on-why-jessie-buckley-is-the-perfect-monster-heroine-2000709958</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709958</guid>
      <description>The writer-director also explains the offbeat 1930s setting of her 'Bride of Frankenstein' riff, which hits theaters in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple lost the AI race &#8212; now the real challenge starts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/861957/google-apple-ai-deal-iphone-gemini</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861957</guid>
      <description>For an AI loser, Apple did an awful lot of winning last year. The mess that was the Apple Intelligence rollout was embarrassing, to be sure, but through it all, the company kept doing what it does best: selling iPhones. With this week's news that it'll use Gemini models to power the long-awaited smarter Siri, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why ICE Can Kill With Impunity</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/why-ice-can-kill-with-impunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695ff523e09fb707598b0b80</guid>
      <description>Over the past decade, US immigration agents have shot and killed more than two dozen people. Not a single agent appears to have faced criminal charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran&#8217;s internet shutdown is now one of its longest ever, as protests continue</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/irans-internet-shutdown-is-now-one-of-its-longest-ever-as-protests-continue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083123</guid>
      <description>Iran&#8217;s government-imposed internet shutdown enters its second week as authorities continue their violent crackdown on protesters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
