<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:30:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>As &#8216;Scream 7&#8217; Arrives, Its Studios Fight to Own Ghostface&#8217;s&#8230; Uh, Face</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/as-scream-7-arrives-its-studios-fight-to-own-ghostfaces-uh-face-2000719059</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719059</guid>
      <description>Rights issues have hovered around the killer's iconic mask for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Opening Ceremony at the 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympics rebroadcast tonight</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-opening-ceremony-at-the-2026-milan-cortina-winter-olympics-rebroadcast-tonight-143529231.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c67003b7-b33a-46d4-8e16-afd2150a7a2a</guid>
      <description>


  The Opening Ceremony for the 2026 Winter Games will re-air tonight on NBC. (Gabriel BOUYS / AFP via Getty Images)
 

  GABRIEL BOUYS via Getty Images
 

The 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympics Opening Ceremony has concluded. The festivities featured performances from Mariah Carey and Andrea Bocelli, 3,000 athletes walking in the Parade of Nations, and not one but two Olympic cauldrons being lit. (One at Milan's Arco della Pace, since Milan is serving as the main hub for this year's Games, and the other in the Alpine city of Cortina d&#8217;Ampezzo, where events like skiing are taking place.) If ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the OpenClaw moment means for enterprises: 5 big takeaways</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/what-the-openclaw-moment-means-for-enterprises-5-big-takeaways</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jLoH9UDhBIbAL3IEW4zjN</guid>
      <description>The "OpenClaw moment" represents the first time autonomous AI agents have successfully "escaped the lab" and moved into the hands of the general workforce. Originally developed by Austrian engineer Peter Steinberger as a hobby project called "Clawdbot" in November 2025, the framework went through a rapid branding evolution to "Moltbot" before settling on "OpenClaw" in late January 2026. Unlike previous chatbots, OpenClaw is designed with "hands"&#8212;the ability to execute shell commands, manage local files, and navigate messaging platforms like WhatsApp and Slack with persistent, root-level permis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We found 20 Verge-approved gifts on sale ahead of Valentine&#8217;s Day</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/873589/valentines-day-gifts-aura-aspen-amazfit-active-2-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T17:45:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873589</guid>
      <description>Valentine&#8217;s Day is coming up fast, and if you haven&#8217;t started shopping yet, there are a lot of great gifts on sale that should still arrive in time if you order soon. Several Verge-approved gadgets are seeing some of their best discounts since the holidays, with options we think will appeal to a wide range [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Svedka to Anthropic, brands make bold plays with AI in Super Bowl ads</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/super-bowl-60-ai-ads-svedka-anthropic-brands-commercials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090483</guid>
      <description>From the first AI-generated Big Game ad courtesy of Svedka to Anthropic's beef with OpenAI, here are the biggest ads from Super Bowl LX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Country Skiing at Winter Olympics 2026 Free Streams: How to watch online from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/cross-country-skiing-at-winter-olympics-2026-free-milano-cortina</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZV6wg6g66NSNSZ2mqstuRC</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Winter Olympics cross-country skiing 2026 live streams for FREE, as the world's best skiers try to stop Norway from dominating the podium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo Catches World Model Fever, and the Only Prescription Is More World Models</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/waymo-catches-world-model-fever-and-the-only-prescription-is-more-world-models-2000719093</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719093</guid>
      <description>What happens if a Waymo runs into an elephant? The world model knows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Agent&#8217;s &#8216;Dragging&#8217; Case May Help Expose Evidence in Renee Good Shooting</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/jonathan-ross-renee-good-roberto-carlos-munoz-guatemala/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698623868d12f90caa65184b</guid>
      <description>The government has withheld details of the investigation of Renee Good&#8217;s killing&#8212;but an unrelated case involving the ICE agent who shot her could force new revelations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto.com Founder Buys AI.com in &#8216;Largest Domain Purchase in History&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/crypto-com-founder-buys-ai-com-in-largest-domain-purchase-in-history-2000719136</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719136</guid>
      <description>Is this what a frothy bubble looks like?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It just got easier for Claude to check in on your WordPress site</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/it-just-got-easier-for-claude-to-check-in-on-your-wordpress-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090484</guid>
      <description>WordPress users can now leverage Claude to analyze web traffic or find information about other internal site metrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Voice Assistants Are Officially a Whiff (for Now)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-voice-assistants-are-officially-a-whiff-for-now-2000719058</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719058</guid>
      <description>Even with the full rollout of Amazon's Alexa+ and Google's Gemini for Home, it feels like we're still shouting into the void.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Marriage Toxin&#8217; Is Bringing Romance to Shonen in a Big Way</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marriage-toxin-is-bringing-romance-to-shonen-in-a-big-way-2000718435</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718435</guid>
      <description>An adult cast romance about a poison assassin seeking love loosely riffing on 'Naruto' is about as peak&#8209;shonen a premise as you can get.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch 2026 Winter Olympics highlights &#8212; it's *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/golf/how-to-watch-2026-winter-olympics-highlights-on-bbc-iplayer-its-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">y2zY4oBM4Jov89Wp8pa4PF</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on how to watch the 2026 Winter Olympics for free on BBC iPlayer no matter where you are in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple will reportedly allow third-party AI assistants in CarPlay</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/apple-will-reportedly-allow-third-party-ai-assistants-in-carplay-213432646.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3fea9ce-ab83-4550-aa5e-3f18f37ce19e</guid>
      <description>Apple plans to allow third-party voice-controlled AI apps in CarPlay, Bloomberg reports. Siri is the default voice assistant for things like controlling music and looking up directions, but future AI apps in CarPlay could handle the complicated, open-ended requests Siri can't answer.The expanded support would let developers like OpenAI or Google offer versions of their ChatGPT and Gemini apps for CarPlay. Similar functionality is possible just by connecting a smartphone to a car over Bluetooth and using an AI app's voice mode, but CarPlay support would presumably make the process a little more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple might let you use ChatGPT from CarPlay</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/875199/apple-carplay-third-party-chatbots-rumor</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T16:32:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875199</guid>
      <description>CarPlay users could soon be able to use their chatbot of choice instead of Siri. As Bloomberg reports, Apple is working to add support for CarPlay voice control apps from OpenAI, Anthropic, Google, and others. Previously, users who wanted to access third-party chatbots in the car would need to go through their iPhone, but soon [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the Trump Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/875190/trump-phone-t1-first-look-design-interview-eric-thomas-don-hendrickson</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T16:32:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875190</guid>
      <description>Where's the Trump phone? We're going to keep talking about it every week. We've reached out, as usual, to ask about the Trump phone's whereabouts. This time, surprisingly, we received a response - and an interview. The Trump phone is real - maybe, sort of, soon? - and I've seen it. Not in the flesh, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
