<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:30:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch the Grammys 2026 for FREE</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/sneaky-way-to-watch-the-2026-grammys-music-awards-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">M9ZiWBiVR9fErcodENjnTX</guid>
      <description>We uncovered a sneaky way to watch the 2026 Grammys for FREE &#8211; from anywhere in the world, without coughing up for a Premium streaming subscription. Here's the trick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Amazon Fire HD 8 Plus tablet drops back to its Black Friday price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tablets/the-amazon-fire-hd-8-plus-tablet-drops-back-to-its-black-friday-price</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 23:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">E6Wtvo8bqoHxxBywvdqcWZ</guid>
      <description>A great price for a basic and cheap tablet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This mini PC offers something pretty special that's sure to turn heads - Aoostar G-Flip sports a flip-up screen, and is now more affordable than ever, even with a hardware upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-mini-pc-offers-something-pretty-special-thats-sure-to-turn-heads-aoostar-g-flip-sports-a-flip-up-screen-and-is-now-more-affordable-than-ever-even-with-a-hardware-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96z3ZGwpiXi3k8CYVi2h7e</guid>
      <description>Aoostar G-Flip refresh offers flip-up touchscreen, upgraded CPU, massive RAM, high-speed storage, and modern connectivity in a compact mini PC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI layoffs or &#8216;AI-washing&#8217;?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/01/ai-layoffs-or-ai-washing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 22:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088565</guid>
      <description>How many of the companies with recent layoffs are just using AI as an excuse?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apex Legends won't be playable on Nintendo Switch after its next season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/apex-legends-wont-be-playable-on-nintendo-switch-after-its-next-season-214153353.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5afe54b-65d1-4c3f-a6b0-6b09dc5de3b2</guid>
      <description>Apex Legends developer Respawn said it's ending Nintendo Switch support for the game this summer, with the release of Season 30. After that point, it'll work with the Switch 2 and all other currently supported platforms, but not the original Switch. "Season 29 will be the final update for Apex Legends on Nintendo Switch," the team wrote in a post on X.Hey legends, we want to share an important update about Apex Legends on the Nintendo Switch. Season 29 will be the final update for Apex Legends on Nintendo Switch. Future seasons of Apex Legends will continue to be available on Nintendo Switch 2...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch Zuffa Boxing 2 for FREE</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/theres-a-sneaky-way-to-watch-zuffa-boxing-2-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8nLvuT9TmCUHu3JqiYTgFK</guid>
      <description>We uncovered a sneaky way to watch Zuffa Boxing 2 for free &#8212; without splashing all your cash on a Paramount+ subscription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock report claims Android apps have leaked over 730TB of user data and Google secrets - here are some of the worst offenders around</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/shock-report-claims-android-apps-have-leaked-over-730tb-of-user-data-and-google-secrets-here-are-some-of-the-worst-offenders-around</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Jjp6wQWdJ4QyvsaKW2vxYS</guid>
      <description>Study of Android AI apps uncovers widespread hardcoded secrets exposing cloud infrastructure payment systems and nearly 730TB of user data</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
