<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:39:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pour No&#235;l, Amazon d&#233;stocke le tr&#232;s bon OnePlus Nord CE5 &#224; un prix in&#233;dit</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2736705_pour-noel-amazon-destocke-le-tres-bon-oneplus-nord-ce5-a-un-prix-inedit</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2736705_pour-noel-amazon-destocke-le-tres-bon-oneplus-nord-ce5-a-un-prix-inedit</guid>
      <description>
Avec une fiche technique &#233;quilibr&#233;e et peu de compromis, le OnePlus Nord CE5 est un smartphone &#224; consid&#233;rer. Il a belles choses &#224; offrir pour satisfaire la plupart des utilisateurs, le tout pour moins de 250 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts for dads that have everything (but deserve more)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780847/best-dad-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:38:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780847</guid>
      <description>What do you get the man who says he has everything? It's a tough question - and one you have a limited amount of time to answer, given the holidays are nearly upon us. You could try dropping subtle hints or asking friends and family for suggestions, but they might save their best ideas for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI just launched an app store inside ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-just-launched-an-app-store-inside-chatgpt-133049586.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89caa5fe-19d2-470b-8701-8f4bd44880af</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has introduced an app directory that's now available right inside ChatGPT, the company announced. "Apps extend ChatGPT conversations by bringing in new context and letting users take action like order groceries, turn an outline into a slide deck or search for an apartment," the company wrote in a blog post. OpenAI also noted in a help document that "connector" apps like Google Drive are now simply called "apps."
The new apps section (on iOS, Android and web) is divided into Feature, Lifestyle and Productivity categories, letting you connect to commonly used apps and sites like Booking.c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 was the beginning of the end of the TV brightness war</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/841054/tv-brightness-hdr-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841054</guid>
      <description>Much like the audio industry's compression-driven loudness war, which reached its distortion-fueled apex (and not the good kind) with Metallica's Death Magnetic in 2008, the television industry has been having its own battle the past couple of years: the brightness war. Sparked by the introduction of HDR and its higher brightness mastering levels, brands began [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best white elephant gifts worth fighting over for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-10-best-white-elephant-gifts-worth-fighting-over-for-2025-150516281.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">167b1092-71dd-42b0-b152-e8240159f089</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of competing ideas as to what a white elephant gift exchange really is. The origins of the term &#8220;white elephant&#8221; point to one definition: According to legend, the King of Siam would give a white elephant to courtiers who had upset them. It was a far more devious punishment than simply having them executed. The recipient had no choice but to simply thank the king for such an opulent gift, knowing that they likely could not afford the upkeep for such an animal. It would inevitably lead them to financial ruin.While that story is almost certainly untrue, it can inform one approach ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AirPods Pro 3 are back on sale for a record low of $199</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-airpods-pro-3-are-back-on-sale-for-a-record-low-of-199-222806371.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42f7f263-d7c8-4a21-ad07-9121207a6244</guid>
      <description>No need to fret if you missed out on some of the best Black Friday deals this year &#8212; some of them have returned already. Case in point: Apple's AirPods Pro 3, which came out in September this year, are back down to $199. That's an all-time-low price and better than the price it was during Black Friday and Cyber Monday. With the new AirPods Pro, Apple made some big improvements, including better battery life and sound quality, and introduced useful new features, such as Live Translation.


The AirPods Pro 3 are the best AirPods available today, with Apple's H2 chip, and earned a score of 90 out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media is merging with a nuclear fusion company</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847159/trump-media-tae-technologies-merger-nuclear-fusion</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:06:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847159</guid>
      <description>Trump Media, the company that runs social network Truth Social, is pivoting to nuclear fusion. It has announced a merger with California-based fusion power company TAE Technologies, and plans to start construction on a fusion power plant in 2026. Trump Media &amp; Technology Group will become the holding company of the new organization, though shareholders [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco says Chinese hackers are exploiting its customers with a new zero-day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/cisco-says-chinese-hackers-are-exploiting-its-customers-with-a-new-zero-day</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cAcZy3FBribm42eBGMyCAL</guid>
      <description>A patch has not yet been released, so Cisco advises rebuilding any affected instances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Ezviz HB8 Lite : une cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; intelligente, efficace et accessible</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ezviz/2906591_test-ezviz-hb8-lite-une-camera-de-securite-intelligente-efficace-et-accessible</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ezviz/2906591_test-ezviz-hb8-lite-une-camera-de-securite-intelligente-efficace-et-accessible</guid>
      <description>
Avec sa Ezviz HB8 Lite, le sp&#233;cialiste de la cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; connect&#233;e se lance un challenge : proposer un produit offrant une belle qualit&#233; d'image, une IA efficiente pour reconna&#238;tre les humains et une vision rotative &#224; 340 &#176; ! De beaux arguments, que le prix de 129 euros ne fait que renforcer. Sur le papier en tout cas.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultrahuman brings snoring detection and respiratory health tracking to the Ring Air</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/ultrahuman-brings-snoring-detection-and-respiratory-health-tracking-to-the-ring-air-130054901.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">531672c2-6c78-4772-a060-a239c188d3f0</guid>
      <description>The Ultrahuman Ring Air now has the capacity to track snoring and general respiratory health. This is thanks to proprietary technology called Respiratory Health PowerPlug, which is basically a suite of audio analysis tools along with some "advanced biomarker tracking" and AI tomfoolery.
All of this results in "one of the most comprehensive consumer tools ever built for understanding nighttime respiratory stability." It details snoring sessions, of course, but also delivers a holistic and "actionable sleep picture." The company says this "reveals patterns, trends and changes in respiratory heal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s the great AGI rebrand</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/845890/ai-companies-rebrand-agi-artificial-general-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845890</guid>
      <description>The cringe comes for us all, and for all our hot new turns of phrase. "Rizz" lost its luster when grandparents started asking about its meaning. Teachers who dressed up as "6-7" on Halloween drove a nail into the coffin of Gen Alpha's rallying cry. And tech CEOs who once trumpeted the quest for "artificial [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FTC is reportedly investigating Instacart over its AI pricing tool</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/the-ftc-is-reportedly-investigating-instacart-over-its-ai-pricing-tool-130000472.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe9cac17-7766-45de-ab3b-cf20e4ad74af</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission has sent Instacart a civil investigative demand, seeking information about its AI-powered pricing tool, according to Reuters. This comes after a recently published pricing experiment study showed that the online grocery delivery app gave different users different prices for the same items from the same store location at the exact same time. Some of the testers saw prices up to 23 percent higher than what the other testers saw, though the average difference for the same list of items was around 7 percent. Those higher prices could cost customers over $1,000 more in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s no such thing as a Republican font</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461588/theres-no-such-thing-as-a-republican-font</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461588/theres-no-such-thing-as-a-republican-font</guid>
      <description>A new study shows that fonts aren&#8217;t inherently partisan&#8212;but humans are.
Last week, two fonts became the unlikely stars of a political messaging firestorm, after the Trump administration replaced Calibri as its official diplomatic font in favor of Times New Roman, claiming that an initial shift to Calibri in 2023 was part of former President Biden&#8217;s &#8220;DEIA&#8221; agenda. The implication was clear: Calibri was framed as a liberal, Democratic font; while Times New Roman took its place as the Trump administration&#8217;s more conservative choice. Now, a new study is revealing the major flaw in this logic: font...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Star Trek Holodeck just got closer &#8211; Apple&#8217;s new AI tool generates 3D scenes from your photos in under a second for VR memories</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/the-star-trek-holodeck-just-got-closer-apples-new-ai-tool-generates-3d-scenes-from-your-photos-in-under-a-second-for-vr-memories</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TiNGDGpgCdudr39S5r95qX</guid>
      <description>Apple has unveiled an AI tool that can convert images from 2D to 3D in under one second.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok aurait acc&#232;s &#224; vos faits et gestes sur cette appli de rencontre, selon cette association</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/tiktok-aurait-acces-a-vos-faits-et-gestes-sur-cette-appli-de-rencontre-selon-cette-association.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316056</guid>
      <description>Le r&#233;seau social chinois suivrait ses utilisateurs sur des applications tierces : la plateforme aurait acc&#232;s &#224; des donn&#233;es collect&#233;es par Grindr, l'application de rencontres gay, selon l'association de d&#233;fense de la vie priv&#233;e NOYB. Ce en violation du RGPD, la loi europ&#233;enne qui prot&#232;ge nos donn&#233;es personnelles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiptole launches 4-ounce bowl of meat for the Ozempic age</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462289/chiptole-launches-4-ounce-bowl-of-meat-for-the-ozempic-age</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T12:53:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462289/chiptole-launches-4-ounce-bowl-of-meat-for-the-ozempic-age</guid>
      <description>The move signals that we&#8217;re about to see a lot more GLP-1-centric menus.
Chipotle is officially in its Ozempic era.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN rolls out major Qt update to boost speed and unify desktop apps</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-rolls-out-major-qt-update-to-boost-speed-and-unify-desktop-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Qtym9iZ3VCeDTkccuRkvKS</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is overhauling its desktop apps with a new Qt-based framework. The update is now live on Linux and macOS &#8211; and Windows is next. Here's all you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoneyBook CRM review 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/software-services/honeybook-crm-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9KbjRXSNgLWkjmuASHA69L</guid>
      <description>HoneyBook stands out as a versatile CRM platform designed specifically for creative entrepreneurs and small businesses. It excels in simplifying client management, automating workflows, and integrating essential business tools. While primarily focused on creative industries, its intuitive interface and continual improvements make it a valuable asset for most small businesses....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose QC Ultra Earbuds (2e Gen) : ces &#233;couteurs &#224; l&#8217;ANC in&#233;gal&#233;e sont &#224; prix cass&#233; pour No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2914653_bose-qc-ultra-earbuds-2e-gen-les-ecouteurs-a-lanc-inegalee-sont-a-prix-casse-pour-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2914653_bose-qc-ultra-earbuds-2e-gen-les-ecouteurs-a-lanc-inegalee-sont-a-prix-casse-pour-noel</guid>
      <description>
La seconde it&#233;ration des QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds de Bose,  n&#8217;est pas une simple mise &#224; jour cosm&#233;tique : c&#8217;est une piq&#251;re de rappel sur ce que la marque sait faire de mieux. De quoi glisser ces &#233;couteurs dans la hotte du P&#232;re No&#235;l &#224; 229 euros au lieu de 299 euros chez Boulanger, avec retrait en magasin sous 1 heure ou livraison d&#232;s le 23 d&#233;cembre.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosses are getting tired of AI at work, and preferring to hire humans for "specialist" roles once again</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/bosses-are-getting-tired-of-ai-at-work-and-preferring-to-hire-humans-for-specialist-roles-once-again</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ozA5Y6krXjLXe2TrMLN9JF</guid>
      <description>AI perception is still torn, but the fact is that companies are shifting their hiring strategies rather than fully displacing human workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Currys has slashed the prices on all its PS5 consoles just in time for Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/ps5/currys-has-slashed-the-prices-on-all-its-ps5-consoles-just-in-time-for-christmas</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zGTuMbD3UrJNZDhYXrZbge</guid>
      <description>Currys has discounted the price of PS5 Slim and PS5 Pro consoles drastically right before Christmas. Our article highlights the best deals at the retailer right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of work isn&#8217;t man versus machine. It&#8217;s man plus machine</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458261/the-future-of-work-isnt-man-versus-machine-its-man-plus-machine-ai-future-of-work</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T12:10:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458261/the-future-of-work-isnt-man-versus-machine-its-man-plus-machine-ai-future-of-work</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s how leaders can get there.
There&#8217;s no shortage of apocalyptic headlines about the future of work in the era of artificial intelligence. For workers, the technology has inflicted anxiety and uncertainty, provoking questions of when, how many, and which kinds of workers will be replaced. Companies have been propelled into a FOMO fury to integrate AI expediently or miss out on efficiency, cost savings, and competitive advantage. The disruption is inevitable, but from where I sit at the nexus of employee mental health and technology, we&#8217;re asking the wrong questions....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agile CRM review 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/software-services/agile-crm-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xBmo7qemys3aCSJT8mwE39</guid>
      <description>Agile CRM is a feature-rich all-in-one CRM solution that caters to the needs of small and medium-sized businesses. With its affordable pricing plans and a wide range of tools for sales, marketing, and customer service, it provides good value for money. But the lack of consistent support, combined with a dated interface, hampers usability. There are competitors who do all of this with better execution, but not necessarily at a cheaper price point....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C&#8217;est une premi&#232;re dans l&#8217;histoire : une femme en fauteuil roulant va aller dans l&#8217;espace cet apr&#232;s-midi</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronaute-cest-premiere-histoire-femme-fauteuil-roulant-va-aller-espace-cet-apres-midi-129338/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:03:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronaute-cest-premiere-histoire-femme-fauteuil-roulant-va-aller-espace-cet-apres-midi-129338/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Pour la premi&#232;re fois de l'histoire, une femme en fauteuil roulant va &#234;tre envoy&#233;e dans l'espace ce jeudi 18 d&#233;cembre. Michaela Benthaus doit partir &#224; bord d'une fus&#233;e&#160;pour une mission suborbitale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Amazon Luna gaming bundle deals could save your wallet this Christmas at better than half price discounts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/these-amazon-luna-gaming-bundle-deals-could-save-your-wallet-this-christmas-at-better-than-half-price-discounts</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zwPLT9jgJUWWgCcbN6E2Rk</guid>
      <description>Christmas shopping sorted &#8212; these Amazon Luna gaming bundles are better than half price right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony settles with Tencent over 'slavish' Horizon clone</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/sony-settles-with-tencent-over-slavish-horizon-clone-120042886.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c772014a-453a-4787-b0a5-36516764b300</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year Sony sued Tencent for copyright infringement over its Light of Motiram game, calling it a "slavish clone" of Horizon Zero Dawn. Then, earlier this month, Tencent agreed to stop promoting and publicly testing the game. Now, the two companies have reached a "confidential settlement" and the case has been dismissed, according to court documents seen by The Verge. Light of Motiram has also disappeared from Steam and Epic's game stores.&#160;
"SIE and Tencent are pleased to have reached a confidential resolution and will have no further public comment on this matter," Tencent's spokesp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Day Was Disney&#8217;s Biggest Streaming Day of the Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-day-was-disneys-biggest-streaming-day-of-the-year-2000701092</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701092</guid>
      <description>'The Mandalorian' also joined the billion-hours-streamed club, but what does it all mean?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Protein Powders, According to 2 Years of Testing (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-protein-powders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67df14a66e8fc14316580a6a</guid>
      <description>We found the best protein powders that won&#8217;t make your shake taste like drywall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Filmmaker Made a Sam Altman Deepfake&#8212;and Got Unexpectedly Attached</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/a-filmmaker-made-a-sam-altman-deepfake-and-got-unexpectedly-attached/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69405cc99989398f17e1e94b</guid>
      <description>The director of Deepfaking Sam Altman created a &#8220;Sam Bot&#8221; when he couldn&#8217;t get an interview with the OpenAI CEO. Watch an exclusive trailer for the documentary, which comes out in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emily in Paris season 5 dedication explained: who is Diego Borella?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/emily-in-paris-season-5-dedication-explained-who-is-diego-borella</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8KcCjrDQEDpGbbZnHbN4QK</guid>
      <description>If you're watching Emily in Paris season 5, you'll have noticed a dedication to Diego Borella at the end of episode 10. But who is he?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From SaaS to AI: the technological and cultural shifts leaders must confront</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/from-saas-to-ai-the-technological-and-cultural-shifts-leaders-must-confront</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">t7T4RmRZKxTERxLCCXcCMa</guid>
      <description>AI adoption requires more than technology &#8212; it demands cultural leadership that addresses fear and builds confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple opens iOS to third-party app stores in Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847149/apple-third-party-app-stores-payment-processing-ios-japan</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T06:55:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847149</guid>
      <description>Apple has announced the changes it's making to the iOS App Store in Japan in order to comply with recent legislation in the country. It will allow third-party app stores and payment processing options, though is introducing new commission fees for those transactions. Developers in Japan will now be able to distribute apps on alternative [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.3 is now out in beta &#8211; here are 3 new features to expect on your iPhone soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/ios/ios-26-3-is-now-out-in-beta-here-are-3-new-features-to-expect-on-your-iphone-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QqAyQuWnuzAtFJ5hvVUug9</guid>
      <description>The first iOS 26.3 beta includes new weather wallpapers, an easier way to switch to Android, and the framework for another new feature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Rams vs. Seahawks in the NFL online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/rams-seahawks-nfl-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02RMcRX3eePVdLz8yfFLbJe</guid>
      <description>How to watch NFL for free. Live stream the NFL for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone Air 2&#160;: Apple corrigerait deux gros d&#233;fauts du premier mod&#232;le</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/iphone-air-2-apple-corrigerait-deux-gros-defauts-premier-modele.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316044</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;iPhone Air n&#8217;a clairement pas trouv&#233; son public, mais Apple ne semble pas pr&#234;t &#224; tirer un trait sur le format ultra-fin. Un iPhone Air 2 serait d&#233;j&#224; &#224; l&#8217;&#233;tude, avec des changements importants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get this speedy Crucial X9 2TB Portable SSD for &#163;105.99 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/storage-backup/get-this-speedy-crucial-x9-2tb-portable-ssd-for-gbp105-99-at-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GJkm7Y3cmWDWGwMuSuDCpV</guid>
      <description>The Crucial X9 2TB Portable SSD is discounted down to &#163;105.99 at Amazon but it's a limited-time deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Wi-Fi 7 absent sur les futurs iPhone 17e et MacBook pas chers d&#8217;Apple : la puce N1 sera toujours un luxe en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2914725_le-wi-fi-7-absent-sur-les-futurs-iphone-17e-et-macbook-pas-chers-dapple-la-puce-n1-sera-toujours-un-luxe-en-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2914725_le-wi-fi-7-absent-sur-les-futurs-iphone-17e-et-macbook-pas-chers-dapple-la-puce-n1-sera-toujours-un-luxe-en-2026</guid>
      <description>
L'adoption du Wi-Fi 7 dans le catalogue d'Apple semble se faire au ralenti. Comme le sugg&#232;rent les leaks sur les futurs produits Apple, la puce N1 ne sera pas d&#233;ploy&#233;e sur tous les nouveaux produits de la marque &#224; la pomme et sera m&#234;me r&#233;serv&#233;e &#224; ses fers de lance.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
