<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:03:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mac mini shortages are starting to happen &#8212; and the OpenClaw AI boom is a key reason</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/macs/mac-mini-shortages-are-starting-to-happen-and-the-openclaw-ai-boom-is-a-key-reason</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TbmEwBikTZTjSYoejbKCHZ</guid>
      <description>Apple's Mac mini and the Mac Studio now have very long lead times for delivery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climactic launches hybrid fund to get startups through the &#8216;valley of death&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/17/climactic-launches-hybrid-fund-to-get-startups-through-the-valley-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093543</guid>
      <description>The new project, called Material Scale, will initially focus on climate tech startups in the apparel industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Time to Admit Working in VR Has Been One Big Failure</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/its-time-to-admit-working-in-vr-has-been-one-big-failure-2000722789</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722789</guid>
      <description>Working in VR is really not working out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealth-mode: 30 all-black home office finds for a distraction-free workspace</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/stealth-mode-30-all-black-home-office-finds-for-a-distraction-free-workspace</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ghpUJvvfTLoyRic44q2VQD</guid>
      <description>Create a fully focused monochromatic workspace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battlefield 6 producer says Season 2 is 'the foundation' for future seasons and believes it will bring back players who may have left after Season 1's extension &#8212; 'I think this is going to be the strongest season'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/battlefield-6-producer-says-season-2-is-the-foundation-for-seasons-ahead-and-believes-it-will-bring-back-players-who-may-have-left-after-season-1s-extension-i-think-this-is-going-to-be-the-strongest-season</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RfPE9QCFSY6oED4ophi9NE</guid>
      <description>Battlefield Studios producer Phil Girette and associate producer Kit Eklof believe Battlefield 6 Season 2 is the "strongest" season yet that will bring back the "die hard" fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress&#8217; new AI assistant will let users edit their sites with prompts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/880223/wordpress-launches-ai-assistant</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-17T13:33:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880223</guid>
      <description>Starting on Tuesday, WordPress users can edit their websites using the new AI assistant built into the platform's site editor and media library, TechCrunch reports. The AI has a sidebar in the WordPress site editor where users can ask it to edit and translate text, generate and edit images using Google's Nano Banana, and make [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Water Be the Future of Space Propulsion? This Startup Thinks So</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/space-startup-plans-to-turn-water-into-orbital-propellant-2000722824</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722824</guid>
      <description>General Galactic is aiming to fly a satellite using a water-powered propulsion system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI Mini 3 : le pack Fly More Combo de cet excellent drone n&#8217;a jamais eu un prix aussi bas que maintenant sur Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2980493_dji-mini-3-le-pack-fly-more-combo-de-cet-excellent-drone-na-jamais-eu-un-prix-aussi-bas-que-maintenant-sur-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2980493_dji-mini-3-le-pack-fly-more-combo-de-cet-excellent-drone-na-jamais-eu-un-prix-aussi-bas-que-maintenant-sur-amazon</guid>
      <description>
Avec le DJI Mini 3 Fly More Combo, vous allez obtenir un drone l&#233;ger qui filme en 4K accompagn&#233; de trois batteries, mais le plus int&#233;ressant, c'est cette grosse promotion chez Amazon qui le fait tomber &#224; 506,60 euros au lieu de 649 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some top password managers can be hacked and hijacked to change your passwords - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/some-top-password-managers-can-be-hacked-and-hijacked-to-change-your-passwords-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">N7xcfmdnovx78o2ePdPtTo</guid>
      <description>Researchers uncovered vulnerabilities in cloud-based password managers spanning recovery, encryption, sharing, and backwards compatibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Cast and Creator on Episode 5&#8217;s Shocking Demise</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-episode-5-baelor-death-explained-2000722876</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722876</guid>
      <description>'In the Name of the Mother' marks a turning point not just for the HBO show, but in Westeros history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best Presidents Day deals you can still grab</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/875949/best-presidents-day-sales-deals-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-17T13:10:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875949</guid>
      <description>Deals have been pretty scarce since the holidays, but now that February is in full swing, we&#8217;ve seen strong discounts return across a range of categories. Both Valentine&#8217;s Day and Presidents Day brought a deluge of discounts, and although both have passed, a number of notable deals remain. In fact, you can still save on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix is adapting the board game Ticket to Ride</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/netflix-is-adapting-the-board-game-ticket-to-ride-180505164.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0dfa681b-a566-48e3-a1c0-ded576978c54</guid>
      <description>Netflix has been in the game adaptation business for a while now, but until recently most of its attention had been on adapting video games. That&#8217;s still very much happening, but the streaming giant is also now buying up rights for board game IP too, with the latest being Asmodee&#8217;s Ticket to Ride.
Netflix will look to greenlight a number of projects spanning TV, film and "additional formats," it wrote in a press release. The first of these will be a feature film written by Ben Mekler and Chris Amick. Ticket to Ride creator Alan R. Moon will serve as an executive producer on the project, which ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save up to 81 percent on ExpressVPN two-year plans right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/save-up-to-81-percent-on-expressvpn-two-year-plans-right-now-180602273.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $88 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.14 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic releases Sonnet 4.6</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/17/anthropic-releases-sonnet-4-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093500</guid>
      <description>Anthropic has released a new version of its mid-size Sonnet model, keeping pace with the company's four-month update cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We march now towards our annihilation': House of Dragon season 3 update sparks Game of Thrones fan excitement over possible launch date and trailer reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/we-march-now-towards-our-annihilation-house-of-dragon-season-3-update-sparks-game-of-thrones-fan-excitement-over-possible-launch-date-and-trailer-reveals</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rQuxRYT9dUksx7Dzex4PyJ</guid>
      <description>HBO appears to be teasing that a big announcement about House of the Dragon season 3 is on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's Sonnet 4.6 matches flagship AI performance at one-fifth the cost, accelerating enterprise adoption</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/anthropics-sonnet-4-6-matches-flagship-ai-performance-at-one-fifth-the-cost</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Q5pyitLDPFOoYIW1Fg30L</guid>
      <description>Anthropic on Tuesday released Claude Sonnet 4.6, a model that amounts to a seismic repricing event for the AI industry. It delivers near-flagship intelligence at mid-tier cost, and it lands squarely in the middle of an unprecedented corporate rush to deploy AI agents and automated coding tools.The model is a full upgrade across coding, computer use, long-context reasoning, agent planning, knowledge work, and design. It features a 1M token context window in beta. It is now the default model in claude.ai and Claude Cowork, and pricing holds steady at $3/$15 per million tokens &#8212; the same as its p...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's acquisition of OpenClaw signals the beginning of the end of the ChatGPT era</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/openais-acquisition-of-openclaw-signals-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">lD36UJNTXLKIIvjPV5vOY</guid>
      <description>The chatbot era may have just received its obituary. Peter Steinberger, the creator of OpenClaw &#8212; the open-source AI agent that took the developer world by storm over the past month, raising concerns among enterprise security teams &#8212; announced over the weekend that he is joining OpenAI to "work on bringing agents to everyone." The OpenClaw project itself will transition to an independent foundation, though OpenAI is already sponsoring it and may have influence over its direction.The move represents OpenAI's most aggressive bet yet on the idea that the future of AI isn't about what models can s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Zootopia 2 online and from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/zootopia-2</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KBi8qYwHeyYE3oFSNMcq5R</guid>
      <description>Here's how you can watch Zootopia 2 online and from anywhere in the world. It's currently available to buy/rent and will soon land on Disney+ worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress adds an AI assistant</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/wordpress-adds-an-ai-assistant-174719676.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d2177d9-b540-4762-aa87-44bb6025e55c</guid>
      <description>Web designers of the world: The Automattic-owned WordPress.com is further embracing AI on its platform. On Tuesday, it expanded its one-off AI site builder into a persistent AI assistant for editing and media creation.In the site editor, the AI assistant can help with site-wide structure and design choices. For example, you can ask the chatbot to "give me more font options that feel clean and professional or &#8220;change my site colors to be brighter and bolder." It also includes image generation and writing assistance, such as "rewrite this to sound more confident." (Who needs learning when you ha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette brosse &#224; dents &#233;lectrique Xiaomi qui optimise le nettoyage de vos petite quenottes est en promotion</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2980207_cette-brosse-a-dents-electrique-xiaomi-qui-optimise-le-nettoyage-de-vos-petite-quenottes-est-en-promotion</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2980207_cette-brosse-a-dents-electrique-xiaomi-qui-optimise-le-nettoyage-de-vos-petite-quenottes-est-en-promotion</guid>
      <description>
Avec ses vibrations soniques rapides combin&#233;es &#224; des mouvements oscillants, la Xiaomi Oscillation Electric Toothbrush Pro, dot&#233;e d'un &#233;cran bien pratique, est arm&#233;e pour nettoyer vos dents en profondeur. Une brosse &#224; dents &#233;lectrique pleine de promesses que vous trouverez &#224; 44,99 euros au lieu de 49,99 euros sur le site officiel de Xiaomi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Colbert Says CBS Bowed to FTC Pressure, Dropped Interview With Democrat</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stephen-colbert-says-cbs-bowed-to-ftc-pressure-dropped-interview-with-democrat-2000722812</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722812</guid>
      <description>Here's the interview that CBS and the FTC don't want you to see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When my friend's oven broke she turned to an air fryer deal like this one from Ninja</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/air-fryers/when-my-friends-oven-broke-she-turned-to-an-air-fryer-deal-like-this-one-from-ninja</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JAXbEXLeDeRJzvbmC9NCZf</guid>
      <description>The Ninja Foodi Max drops to its lowest price since Black Friday at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant X-Rays Deliver the Sharpest View Yet of Fusion Plasma Gone Haywire</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/giant-x-rays-deliver-the-sharpest-view-yet-of-fusion-plasma-gone-haywire-2000722814</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722814</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Our understanding of instabilities&#8212;when they grow, how they grow&#8212;is important to making fusion work.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral AI buys Koyeb in first acquisition to back its cloud ambitions</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/17/mistral-ai-buys-koyeb-in-first-acquisition-to-back-its-cloud-ambitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3093487</guid>
      <description>Mistral AI has agreed to buy Koyeb, a Paris-based startup that simplifies AI app deployment at scale and manages the infrastructure behind it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Liga wins court order, requiring NordVPN and Proton VPN to block illegal football streams in Spain &#8212; but VPN firms say they have not been notified</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/la-liga-wins-court-order-requiring-nordvpn-and-proton-vpn-to-block-illegal-football-streams-in-spain-but-vpn-firms-say-they-have-not-been-notified</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Jv85vYLd455Ytitj6mUUaX</guid>
      <description>La Liga's war on piracy has escalated significantly, with a Spanish court ruling that NordVPN and Proton VPN need to block IP addresses transmitting illegal football streams. Here's all we know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battlefield 6 is getting gas reminiscent of Battlefield 1, but the game's producer says its for strategic depth rather than to damage players &#8212; 'It plays with visibility. It plays a little bit with perception as well'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/battlefield-6-is-getting-gas-reminiscent-of-battlefield-1-but-the-games-producer-says-its-for-strategic-depth-rather-than-to-damage-players-it-plays-with-visibility-it-plays-a-little-bit-with-perception-as-well</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jU7NqWLtWimP4xoLw9MvCT</guid>
      <description>Battlefield 6 Season 2 has officially begun, and it's brought back of the divisive toxic gas from Battlefield 1. However this gas will act much differently and offer new tactical ways to play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed Philips' new flagship OLED TV and it's the brightest I've measured &#8212; while being way cheaper than LG and Samsung's rivals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/philips-oled910-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fG7bmWkzX8vmrsXWH8FpKM</guid>
      <description>The Philips OLED910 promises flagship performance but for cheaper than its rivals &#8211; can it deliver?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle promises 'decisive new approach' to MySQL - so will this mean some big changes coming soon?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/oracle-promises-decisive-new-approach-to-mysql-so-will-this-mean-some-big-changes-coming-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9U6SuVsPCxbcaqFN7wkgF</guid>
      <description>Oracle acknowledges community concerns over MySQL, and has promised to be more open and collaborative going forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $13,500 that changed the fate of humanity: how the term Artificial Intelligence was first coined 71 years ago &#8212; but sadly without the legendary visionary soul who imagined it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-usd13-500-that-changed-the-fate-of-humanity-how-the-term-artificial-intelligence-was-first-coined-71-years-ago-but-sadly-without-the-legendary-visionary-soul-who-imagined-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YR4BFVjpU5Z3fCRrH2UuUb</guid>
      <description>From Alan Turing&#8217;s early thought experiments to the Dartmouth project that coined the term, the origins of artificial intelligence is a fascinating story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of stock: Valve Steam Deck is the latest casualty of global memory shortage</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/valve-steam-deck-latest-casualty-of-global-memory-shortage</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01WjQgS9Oj5sTe5vpI2mEdc</guid>
      <description>The popular handheld gaming console may not be so easy to find in the coming year, Valve warned shoppers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Considers Designating Anthropic AI as a &#8216;Supply Chain Risk&#8217;: Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pentagon-considers-designating-anthropic-ai-as-a-supply-chain-risk-report-2000722805</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722805</guid>
      <description>The move would require anyone doing business with the U.S. military to cut ties with the AI company.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
