<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 18:32:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Kinect for kids is outselling Xbox to become the hot console this holiday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844380/nex-playground-outselling-the-xbox</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-13T13:17:20-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844380</guid>
      <description>It's a small sample size, likely driven by Black Friday discounts and temporary virality, but the Nex Playground has gone from little-known console curiosity to best-seller. It's now on track to quadruple its sales from last year. According to research firm Circana, the Playground was the second best-selling console in the US for the week [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.2 is here with another Liquid Glass tweak, new Podcasts features and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/ios-262-is-here-with-another-liquid-glass-tweak-new-podcasts-features-and-more-181020133.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c499b10-66a7-4aa3-9c99-23fc15c4a7be</guid>
      <description>Apple has released iOS 26.2, bringing a number of new convenience features and security updates. The update includes auto-generated chapters for episodes in the Podcasts app, the option to make AirDrop more secure using verification codes, alarms for Reminders and more. It also introduces new controls for how Liquid Glass appears on the Lock Screen, adding a slider to adjust the transparency level. The drop also includes updates for iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, visionOS and tvOS.
What's new in iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2
It's not exactly a major update feature-wise, but iOS and iPadOS 26.2 bring a bun...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRKD's Nitro Deck 2 works for both the Nintendo Switch and Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/crkds-nitro-deck-2-works-for-both-the-nintendo-switch-and-switch-2-173920127.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48db9481-69dd-4a41-8f37-b01ca12ca343</guid>
      <description>Even though Nintendo made some serious upgrades with the Joy-Con 2, you still might end up ditching them for CRKD's Nitro Deck 2. After winning over Nintendo Switch owners with its first Nitro Deck, CRKD followed it up with an improved design that works for both the original Switch and the Switch 2.
To refine the original design, CRKD added several upgrades to the Nitro Deck 2 based on community feedback. The new-and-improved accessory features the company's CaptiStick Technology, which prevents stick drift and isn't affected by magnetic interference like other Hall effect joysticks. CRKD also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Cyberpunk 2077&#8217; Proved a Game Can Change Itself, But Not Its History</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cyberpunk-2077-proved-a-game-can-change-itself-but-not-its-history-2000689506</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000689506</guid>
      <description>It ain't a thing of beauty, but 'Cyberpunk 2077' eventually became a good game that knows how it got there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slab is the first MIDI controller built exclusively for Serato Studio</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/839732/serato-slab-midi-controller-studio</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-13T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839732</guid>
      <description>Native Instruments and Ableton have had incredible success with their custom MIDI controllers that integrate with their DAWs (digital audio workstations), Maschine and Live, respectively. Native Instruments' Maschine (yes, it's the name of the hardware and the software) and Ableton's Push are pretty much the gold standard for integration between music-making software and hardware. Serato [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bosch Tassimo Finesse Friendly is a super affordable coffee maker, but beware &#8211; there's a catch that means it could cost you in the long run</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/bosch-tassimo-finesse-friendly-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6NbbYbJgJ97fJe9U2aWBg8</guid>
      <description>Looking for a cheap and cheerful coffee maker? The Finesse Friendly could be the one for you, but mind how much you're spending on pods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Shark StainForce : voici un d&#233;tacheur compact et sans-fil &#224; l&#8217;efficacit&#233; redoutable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2894315_test-du-shark-stainforce-voici-un-detacheur-compact-et-sans-fil-a-lefficacite-redoutable</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/2894315_test-du-shark-stainforce-voici-un-detacheur-compact-et-sans-fil-a-lefficacite-redoutable</guid>
      <description>
Avec le StainForce, Shark propose un d&#233;tacheur bien plus compact que les mod&#232;les traditionnels, convenant particuli&#232;rement pour les usages occasionnels et les petits espaces. Nous l'avons test&#233; sur des taches difficiles, verdict dans ce test complet.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette option m&#233;connue de Windows 11 va vous changer la vie quand un programme plante</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2908361_cette-option-meconnue-de-windows-11-va-vous-changer-la-vie-quand-un-programme-plante</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2908361_cette-option-meconnue-de-windows-11-va-vous-changer-la-vie-quand-un-programme-plante</guid>
      <description>
On vous dit comment activer un raccourci tr&#232;s pratique pour forcer la fermeture des applications qui plantent sur Windows 11.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le meilleur appareil photo compact de l&#8217;ann&#233;e &#8211; Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2903509_voici-le-meilleur-appareil-photo-compact-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2903509_voici-le-meilleur-appareil-photo-compact-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
Le meilleur bo&#238;tier photo compact de l'ann&#233;e sur Frandroid est le Ricoh GR IV. D&#233;couvrez pourquoi ce produit a re&#231;u le Frandroid Awards avec Delos de sa cat&#233;gorie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google reportedly takes down AI videos of Disney characters following cease and desist</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/google-takes-down-ai-videos-of-disney-characters-cease-and-desist</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03uc6M4iUIFJdJIXCm06yF4</guid>
      <description>Google is complying with Disney's cease-and-desist letter over AI videos using its characters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
