<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:34:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp will now charge AI chatbots to operate in Italy</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/whatsapp-will-now-charge-ai-chatbots-to-operate-in-italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087325</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp plans to charge developers of AI chatbots per message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook calls for deescalation but avoids criticizing Trump after Minneapolis death</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482738/tim-cook-calls-for-deescalation-but-avoids-criticizing-trump-after-minneapolis-death</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T19:11:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482738/tim-cook-calls-for-deescalation-but-avoids-criticizing-trump-after-minneapolis-death</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s internal letter called for &#8220;deescalation,&#8221; but avoided criticizing the president, sparking anger among employees in the wake of the Minneapolis shooting.
Trump is facing a rare bipartisan backlash after a group of federal agents shot and killed protester Alex Pretti in Minneapolis on Saturday, but tech industry leaders &#8211; once some of Trump&#8217;s fiercest critics &#8211; are sitting this one out....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Garner&#8217;s Once Upon a Farm resumes IPO plans</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/jennifer-garners-once-upon-a-farm-resumes-ipo-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087307</guid>
      <description>The organic kids' snack food company may debut as soon as next week. It has issued a price range for shares, an SEC filing shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still using WinRAR? You should probably look out for these potentially dangerous security flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/still-using-winrar-you-should-probably-look-out-for-these-potentially-dangerous-security-flaws</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kQ9JKvZKvRQdTaGjbGsXxh</guid>
      <description>A high severity flaw in WinRAR allows crooks to execute malware remotely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surface Laptop Is $400 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/surface-laptop-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a49f579d46123bdbb40aa</guid>
      <description>Take home a sweet discount on Microsoft's first-party laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give Your Problems (and Passwords) to Moltbot, Then Watch It Go</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/clawdbot-moltbot-viral-ai-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6978fc5575b4432f40d9f9da</guid>
      <description>A viral new virtual assistant formerly known as Clawdbot is complex and brings security risks&#8212;but some early adopters say it feels like the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI data labeler Handshake buys  Cleanlab, an acquisition target of multiple others</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/ai-data-labeler-handshake-buys-cleanlab-an-acquisition-target-of-multiple-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087279</guid>
      <description>The deal is structured as an acquihire of nine key Cleanlab's researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a Nespresso machine? I'm a qualified barista and these are the 3 I recommend for authentic-tasting espresso</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/small-appliances/looking-for-a-nespresso-machine-im-a-qualified-barista-and-these-are-the-3-i-recommend-for-authentic-tasting-espresso</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9aixqfRw8aL639EvPGhnuZ</guid>
      <description>Want the convenience of instant coffee with the rich flavor of fresh beans? You need a Nespresso machine, and these are the best ones around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another apparel brand is closing all retail stores. It was once a tech bro favorite</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482655/allbirds-closing-stores-locations-list-tech-bro-favorite-retail-e-commerce</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482655/allbirds-closing-stores-locations-list-tech-bro-favorite-retail-e-commerce</guid>
      <description>A growing number of retailers are reducing their physical footprint in favor of e-commerce, and the latest was once a Silicon Valley staple.
Allbirds shoe brand announced on Wednesday that it will close all of its U.S. stores by the end of February (with the exception of two outlets) and go online, turning to e-commerce instead. It will, however, continue to operate two London-based brick-and-mortar locations....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxpayers may face issues this 2026 tax season after IRS layoffs and new laws, a watchdog warns</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482745/irs-tax-season-taxpayer-advocate-report</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T18:39:34</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482745/irs-tax-season-taxpayer-advocate-report</guid>
      <description>The IRS started 2025 with about 102,000 employees and finished with about 74,000.
The national taxpayer advocate is cautioning that&#160;the 2026 tax filing season&#160;is likely to present challenges for taxpayers who encounter problems with filing their taxes given the exodus of IRS workers since the start of the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native Instruments enters into insolvency proceedings, leaving its future uncertain</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/native-instruments-enters-into-insolvency-proceedings-leaving-its-future-uncertain-183206826.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e88ab674-b98f-4a2e-a8a5-67c23b02df61</guid>
      <description>Music hardware and software manufacturer Native Instruments has entered into preliminary insolvency proceedings, according to a report by Create Digital Music. This is the company behind iconic software like Massive, Traktor and Kontakt and hardware like Maschine+. Native Instruments also owns the brands iZotope, Brainworx and Plugin Alliance.
We don't have many specifics as to what this entails and what the future of the company will look like. We do know that an administrator has been appointed to handle restructuring and, potentially, to sell off existing assets. Native Instruments employs ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify says it paid out $11 billion in royalties in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869523/spotify-11-billion-in-royalties</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T13:22:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869523</guid>
      <description>Today, Spotify announced that it had paid out more than $11 billion to the music industry in 2025. It's an impressive-sounding number that's a full $1 billion more than it paid last year. And, according to Spotify, that accounts for roughly 30 percent of the entire recording industry's revenue. And, according to Spotify, that accounts [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed: SoundCloud data breach hit 29.8 million accounts - how to find out if you're affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/confirmed-soundcloud-data-breach-hit-29-8-million-accounts-how-to-find-out-if-youre-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SaXv27ps4f6vvHi3xDMmJU</guid>
      <description>HaveIBeenPwned confirms extent of the SoundCloud incident, allowing users to see if they're affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process Zero II will let you do a little processing, if you want</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/869354/halide-mark-iii-process-zero-update</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T13:01:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869354</guid>
      <description>Popular iPhone camera app Halide is debuting a major update today: Halide Mark III. It's been years in the making, and it'll be available as a "Public Preview," letting users get their hands on new features while design is finalized. This update includes the next iteration of the app's much-discussed Process Zero mode, adding HDR [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s New Chrome &#8216;Auto Browse&#8217; Agent Attempts to Roam the Web Without You</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-chrome-auto-browse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977bd968b3ddccd846ec307</guid>
      <description>Google&#8217;s latest addition to its Chrome browser puts generative AI behind the wheel and you in the passenger seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome takes on AI browsers with tighter Gemini integration, agentic features for autonomous tasks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/chrome-takes-on-ai-browsers-with-tighter-gemini-integration-agentic-features-for-autonomous-tasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086514</guid>
      <description>Google Chrome is adding Gemini in the sidebar and is rolling out an agentic feature for AI Pro and Ultra users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested these quirky wireless earbuds that even let you play games on the charging case &#8212; and they cost less than &#163;40</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/groov-e-neo-buds-true-wireless-earbuds-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vjdpXpamNs7LBeHhfYMzs8</guid>
      <description>I tested the sub-&#163;40 wireless earbuds attempting to challenge JBL, but are they really up to the task?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome gets its biggest upgrade in years &#8212; the new Gemini side panel puts AI agents, multitasking, and Nano Banana inside the browser</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chrome-gets-its-biggest-upgrade-in-years-the-new-gemini-side-panel-puts-ai-agents-multitasking-and-nano-banana-inside-the-browser</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V3LbgQHa77ehckmGZvk67</guid>
      <description>Google&#8217;s biggest Chrome update in years bakes Gemini AI agents, multitasking, and image editing directly into the browser, turning everyday web browsing into a hands-off experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Wonder Man directly set up a major storyline in Spider-Man: Brand New Day? The Marvel TV show's head writer has his say</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/does-wonder-man-directly-set-up-a-major-storyline-in-spider-man-brand-new-day-the-marvel-tv-shows-head-writer-has-his-say</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EKCZTyTKBJnsRrjQYpCpDn</guid>
      <description>Wonder Man's showrunner stopped short of confirming if the new Disney+ show will impact Spider-Man 4's story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google brings its Nano Banana image generator to Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-brings-its-nano-banana-image-generator-to-chrome-180000104.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b00cd63e-ecd1-4cbb-ac5b-1602200e7eea</guid>
      <description>Following its recent AI makeover of Gmail, Google is bringing more Gemini-powered tools to Chrome. Starting today, a host of new features are rolling out for the browser, with more to come over the next few months.&#160;The first of the new features is a sidebar. Available to all Gemini in Chrome users, the interface allows you to chat with Gemini and keep a conversation going across multiple tabs. Google suggests the sidebar is useful for multitaskers.&#160;"Our testers have been using it for all sorts of things: comparing options across too-many-tabs, summarizing product reviews across different sites...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does your baby qualify for a $1,000 Trump Account? Here&#8217;s what to know</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482736/trump-accounts-babies-investment-explained</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482736/trump-accounts-babies-investment-explained</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s a new savings tool where money is invested in the stock market on behalf of a child. 
As a continuation of President&#160;Donald Trump&#8216;s pitch to Americans on affordability and the economy under his administration, the U.S. Treasury and White House are celebrating the upcoming launch of a program they view as a key milestone: &#8220;Trump Accounts.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Napoli vs. Chelsea online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/napoli-chelsea-champions-league-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01uCMAy1XfJBSbwUzfx9ZlY</guid>
      <description>How to watch Champions League for free. Live stream Napoli vs. Chelsea in the Champions League for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free your photos from your camera roll with this Kodak Dock Plus deal</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-kodak-dock-plus-photo-printer-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06rwxWuySjOnkwfWtzgKEKD</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 28, the Kodak Dock Plus 4PASS Instant Photo Printer Bundle is on sale for $110.49 at Amazon. That's a 26% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tout savoir sur Kimi K2.5, le nouveau concurrent open source et &#171;&#160;gratuit&#160;&#187; qui se frotte &#224; Claude 4.5 et GPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2958953_tout-savoir-sur-kimi-k2-5-le-nouveau-concurrent-open-source-et-gratuit-qui-se-frotte-a-claude-4-5-et-gpt-5-2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2958953_tout-savoir-sur-kimi-k2-5-le-nouveau-concurrent-open-source-et-gratuit-qui-se-frotte-a-claude-4-5-et-gpt-5-2</guid>
      <description>
On nous promet souvent la r&#233;volution. Mais quand un mod&#232;le open source vient titiller Claude 4.5 Opus sur son propre terrain tout en g&#233;rant de la vid&#233;o native, on touche quelque chose d'int&#233;ressant. Voici Kimi K2.5 qui peut tourner en local.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple tells Patreon to move creators to in-app purchase for subscriptions by November</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/apple-tells-patreon-to-move-creators-to-in-app-purchase-for-subscriptions-by-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087258</guid>
      <description>Patreon isn&#8217;t happy about Apple&#8217;s new subscription billing mandate, arguing Apple&#8217;s shifting rules create uncertainty for creators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tag/ai-pro</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Y9GHv8UUn2fEdUZXVvDBqj</guid>
      <description>All TechRadar Pro stories tagged AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;You&#8217;ll rarely experience spy-movie stealth or the constant frustration of corporate geofences.&#8217; How 24 hours connected to a VPN changed my perspective on personal data security</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/youll-rarely-experience-spy-movie-stealth-or-the-constant-frustration-of-corporate-geofences-how-24-hours-connected-to-a-vpn-changed-my-perspective-on-personal-data-security</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aQFdZg5xXXMxxq2VMMBRr</guid>
      <description>I put the reality of using VPNs to the test, and the results weren't what I expected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orastone hand warmers are 50% off and Mashable-tested</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-orastone-hand-warmer-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01Uuh2EelAVaFsMEhvji8rE</guid>
      <description>The Orastone rechargable hand warmers are on sale at Amazon for $14.99, down from the normal price of $29.99. That's a 50% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s noise-canceling AirPods 4 are down to one of their best prices to date</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/869428/apple-airpods-4-active-noise-cancellation-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T12:36:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869428</guid>
      <description>The AirPods Pro 3 may be on sale for $199 ($50 off), but that&#8217;s still a lot of money. If you want noise cancellation for less, fortunately you can buy the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation for $119 ($60 off) at Amazon and Walmart. That&#8217;s the cheapest they&#8217;ve been since the holidays, and only [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Its freezing out &#8212; heres everything you need to stay warm for less</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-cold-weather-essentials-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00zovuMcA1uQDaAyP8FOYvj</guid>
      <description>Shop Amazon deals on winter safety essentials. Save on Lasko space heaters, rechargeable hand warmers, and heated blankets.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
