<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:03:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sony and Honda&#8217;s Afeela EV will start customer deliveries in late 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855883/sony-honda-afeela-customer-delivery-suv-concept-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T20:54:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855883</guid>
      <description>Sony and Honda's joint venture, Sony Honda Mobility (SHM), said it will start customer deliveries of the $90,000 Afeela 1 electric vehicle in in the US in late 2026. The company also showed off an SUV concept that it said would inform a production model in the US for as early as 2028. The new [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus ROG Invites Gamers to the Open-Ear Audio Party</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/asus-rog-invites-gamers-to-the-open-ear-audio-party-2000705824</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705824</guid>
      <description>Why should non-gaming folks have all the fun?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rokid introduces display-free AI smartglasses at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/rokid-introduces-display-free-ai-smartglasses-at-ces-2026-010017906.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">056a9b2c-72a5-4468-9714-767098ebe8b8</guid>
      <description>Smartglasses company Rokid has introduced new display-free AI glasses at CES 2026. Dubbed "Style", the glasses are intended for all-day use and are compatible with users' corrective prescriptions.
Style supports multiple AI engines, including ChatGPT and DeepSeek, instead of being locked to any LLM. The glasses can also work with Google Maps and Microsoft AI translation.
Style is powered by a dual-chip setup, with an NXP RT600 handling low-power, always-on tasks and a Qualcomm AR1 taking on heavier AI and imaging workloads. Rokid claims this architecture helps it reach up to 12 hours of batter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel d&#233;fi AMD : une vague de consoles portables Panther Lake arrive</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929875_intel-defi-amd-une-vague-de-consoles-portables-panther-lake-arrive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929875_intel-defi-amd-une-vague-de-consoles-portables-panther-lake-arrive</guid>
      <description>
Au CES 2026 de Las Vegas, Intel a annonc&#233; le d&#233;veloppement d'une plateforme d&#233;di&#233;e au jeu vid&#233;o sur console PC.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This tabletop sleep device and sunrise alarm clock aims to help you put your phone away before bed</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/this-tabletop-sleep-device-and-sunrise-alarm-clock-aims-to-help-you-put-your-phone-away-before-bed-004751464.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95a8f19-9e7b-4662-8bf7-4679e03ced4a</guid>
      <description>"Relaxing" isn't a word anyone is likely to associate with CES. If anything, it is the antithesis of CES, an exhausting and wildly overstimulating marathon event that takes place in the already exhausting and wildly overstimulating Las Vegas. But a demo of Ambient's bedside device, Dreamie, ahead of its appearance at CES-adjacent Pepcom had me properly lulled and ready to go right back to bed. Dreamie is a smart sunrise alarm clock and nighttime wind-down device that has a built-in podcast player, a catalog of green, pink and brown noise sound masks, guided breathing programs, contactless moti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI Wants to Prove It Can Do Business Laptops, Too</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/msi-wants-to-prove-it-can-do-business-laptops-too-2000705195</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705195</guid>
      <description>The new Prestige series seem pretty enticing for creatives, if RAM prices hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin now offers nutrition tracking</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855884/garmin-connect-nutrition-tracking</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T19:39:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855884</guid>
      <description>Garmin announced that it's adding nutrition tracking to the Garmin Connect app as a perk for users with a Garmin Connect Plus subscription. The feature lets users "track their calories and macros (proteins, fats and carbs) and receive Active Intelligence insights to help them achieve their nutrition goals," according to Garmin. To log foods, you [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel&#8217;s New Chips Promise Power and Battery Life in Equal Measure</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/intels-new-chips-promise-power-and-battery-life-in-equal-measure-2000705890</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705890</guid>
      <description>Here are all the details on the Intel Core Ultra Series 3 that you&#8217;ll find in practically every laptop this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell revives its XPS laptops after a boneheaded rebranding</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/dell-revives-its-xps-laptops-after-a-boneheaded-rebranding-001028029.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fcc565f-aee8-413a-b8f8-0cc5f443bc32</guid>
      <description>Last year, Dell killed off all of its PC brands, including the iconic XPS lineup, and replaced them with a simplified naming scheme. It was a move meant to make it easier for people to discern between the company's many brands, but in reality, it just just made the company's lineup even more confusing. We called it an unforced error at the time, but after seeing how much Dell's PC market share fell over 2025, it's fair to say that rebranding was an absolute marketing disaster. So, with its tail between its legs, Dell has returned to CES some welcome news for its fans: XPS lives! And the compan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $699 5K, Thunderbolt-5 monitor is the perfect partner for your Apple Mac Mini and even comes with a hidden SSD slot</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-usd699-5k-thunderbolt-5-monitor-is-the-perfect-partner-for-your-apple-mac-mini-and-even-comes-with-a-hidden-ssd-slot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R7mZhLM2uihgLcSMV3qxn9</guid>
      <description>The StudioDock Pro combines a 5K display, hub, and storage expansion into a Mac mini-focused monitor offered through crowdfunding.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
