<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:27:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>California is investigating Grok over AI-generated CSAM and nonconsensual deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/california-is-investigating-grok-over-ai-generated-csam-and-nonconsensual-deepfakes-202029635.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afc82bf8-c680-4d61-bc55-e26654ca4424</guid>
      <description>California authorities have launched an investigation into xAI following weeks of reports that the chatbot was generating sexualized images of children. "xAI appears to be facilitating the large-scale production of deepfake nonconsensual intimate images that are being used to harass women and girls across the internet, including via the social media platform X," California Attorney General Rob Bonta's office said in a statement.&#160;The statement cited a report that "more than half of the 20,000 images generated by xAI between Christmas and New Years depicted people in minimal clothing," including...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When PC Memory Prices Are Too Much to Handle?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/what-happens-when-pc-memory-prices-are-too-much-to-handle-2000710305</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710305</guid>
      <description>The world's largest PC maker tells us why the next PC you buy may be more premium or less powerful than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies confess their agentic AI goals aren't really working out - and a lack of trust could be why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/companies-confess-their-agentic-ai-goals-arent-really-working-out-and-a-lack-of-trust-could-be-why</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bohwdMrggYUpmCNDJ5eWaH</guid>
      <description>Many companies are still operating AI agents in silos &#8211; a lack of trust could be preventing them from setting it free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network appears to be having technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Verizon customers on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even the network provider&#8217;s own status page is struggling to load during the outage.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally, at least for some users. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started growing around 12PM ET and numbered in th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientists Decipher Procrastination: A Brain Mechanism Explains Why People Leave Certain Tasks for Later</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/neuroscience-procrastination-brain-mechanism-task-avoidance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967dd15685933202e631c14</guid>
      <description>New research has discovered that a neural circuit may explain procrastination. Scientists were able to disrupt this connection using a drug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save up to 78 percent on ExpressVPN two-year plans right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/save-up-to-78-percent-on-expressvpn-two-year-plans-right-now-180602838.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $101 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.59 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App downloads declined again in 2025, but consumer spending soared to nearly $156B</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/app-downloads-declined-again-in-2025-but-consumer-spending-soared-to-nearly-156b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082733</guid>
      <description>Global app downloads were down, but consumer spending was up to nearly $156B in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX Hit by Another Workplace Injury Lawsuit, This Time Over Falling Debris in an Elevator Shaft</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spacex-hit-by-another-workplace-injury-lawsuit-this-time-over-falling-debris-in-an-elevator-shaft-2000710249</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710249</guid>
      <description>The rocket company&#8217;s safety record continues to fall short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Big on One of Our Favorite Desk Lamps from Lume Cube</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/lume-edge-light-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967d577585d9a70fc535832</guid>
      <description>Lume Cube has a variety of marked down lighting products to help revamp your home office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Marty Supreme&#8217; Almost Ended With an Actual Vampire</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marty-supreme-almost-ended-with-an-actual-vampire-2000710371</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710371</guid>
      <description>The award-winning Timoth&#233;e Chalamet movie mentions vampires&#8212;but at one point, the script went even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMW says electric M3 will be a &#8216;new level&#8217; of performance</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861955/bmw-m3-electric-ev-quad-motor-neue-klasse</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T14:30:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861955</guid>
      <description>BMW teased its forthcoming all-electric M-series performance sedan today, promising that the quad-motor M3 sports car would feature specs that are truly next level when it arrives in 2027. The M3 will have four electric motors and simulated gear shifting, a feature that is quickly becoming a must-have for electrified sports cars. BMW says the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve tested 30 smart locks, and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23393163/best-smart-door-lock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T14:27:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23393163/best-smart-door-lock</guid>
      <description>A smart lock is an easy solution to some common problems. Locked yourself out? Need to let a friend in to water the plants? Your latchkey kid lost their key? Hands are full, and it&#8217;s raining cats and dogs? A smart lock solves all of these problems and more. One of the best smart home [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;It will refuse to produce anything illegal&#8217;: Elon Musk rails against Grok backlash, but UK Prime Minister says &#8216;we&#8217;re not going to back down&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/it-will-refuse-to-produce-anything-illegal-elon-musk-rails-against-grok-backlash-but-uk-prime-minister-says-were-not-going-to-back-down</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jdhtdmLB4rHuVWhgQfmAe7</guid>
      <description>X CEO Elon Musk disputes image generation charges leveled at Grok AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 8 best earbuds of 2026, tested by audio experts</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/roundup/best-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06IWFHfJ7yAAffPn0vTjQpE</guid>
      <description>Mashable's audio experts tested the best earbuds at every price point &#8212; here are the ones they recommend picking up during the holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI models are starting to crack high-level math problems</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/ai-models-are-starting-to-crack-high-level-math-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082724</guid>
      <description>Since the release of GPT 5.2, AI tools have become inescapable in high-level mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon breaks silence on massive outage. Heres what they said.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-outage-service-down-statement</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05FQVRD8Wv5jVZoKCSg1jpd</guid>
      <description>In a statement, Verizon acknowledged that its customers were impacted by a major disruption on Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla just switched to a Netflix-style subscription model for Full Self-Driving &#8211; here's why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/dash-cams/tesla-just-switched-to-a-netflix-style-subscription-model-for-full-self-driving-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">trvah5Jocpry5dsdtgD3aZ</guid>
      <description>Musk moves self-driving technology to subscription model only as of February 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackstone, General Atlantic-backed Liftoff Mobile files for IPO</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/blackstone-general-atlantic-backed-liftoff-mobile-files-for-ipo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082643</guid>
      <description>The company offers a platform that helps mobile app developers market their wares and has an army of bankers working on its IPO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI&#8217;s Hacking Skills Are Approaching an &#8216;Inflection Point&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-models-hacking-inflection-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965470bbf96e65096dda90d</guid>
      <description>AI models are getting so good at finding vulnerabilities that some experts say the tech industry might need to rethink how software is built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digg launches its new Reddit rival to the public</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/digg-launches-its-new-reddit-rival-to-the-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082570</guid>
      <description>Digg, a reboot of an earlier social news site, is now relaunching as a Reddit competitor focused on communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea will team up with Roblox on a pop-up to reach Gen Alpha shoppers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474816/ikea-roblox-pop-up</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474816/ikea-roblox-pop-up</guid>
      <description>Virtual Stockholm sofas. No assembly required.
Ikea&#8217;s new store is in the metaverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last chance to get a Kindle for up to 31% off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-kindle-last-chance-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04bwDannfE0rRQRFr9myT2j</guid>
      <description>The Kindle, Kindle Scribe, and Kindle Colorsoft are still on sale for the next day. This is your last chance to get a deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose&#8217;s first-gen QC Ultra headphones have returned to their best price to date</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/861286/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-headphones-steam-detective-fest-sale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:56:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861286</guid>
      <description>This year&#8217;s CES introduced a bevy of unique headphones, including Fender&#8217;s first set and a pair that roll up to become a Bluetooth speaker when you want to share your music with friends. However, despite the interesting advancements, we doubt any of them will dethrone our favorite pair for travel: the Bose QuietComfort Ultra Headphones. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s first original podcasts star Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861971/netflix-original-podcasts-pete-davidson-michael-irvin</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:56:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861971</guid>
      <description>Netflix is launching its first pair of original video podcasts, hosted by Saturday Night Live alum Pete Davidson and NFL commentator and former star Michael Irvin. While The Pete Davidson Show makes its debut on January 30th, you can find Irvin's The White House on the streaming service on January 19th. The two shows will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon Outage Knocks Out US Mobile Service, Including Some 911 Calls</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/verizon-outage-knocks-out-us-mobile-service-including-some-911-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967dbfa585d9a70fc535833</guid>
      <description>A major Verizon outage appeared to impact customers across the United States starting around noon ET on Wednesday. Calls to Verizon customers from other carriers may also be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robloxs new age verification is reportedly fooled by shockingly simple tactics</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/roblox-age-verfication-system-fooled</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01xZmFrFkdR7kDKuUbuNhvw</guid>
      <description>The AI-powered age verification system rolled out by Roblox appears to be identifying kids as adults and adults as kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab the March of the Machine Draft Box for near market value</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-magic-the-gathering-march-of-the-machine-draft-booster-box-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05IJ3UsTNIyj5JOYvJG0Wid</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 14, you can get the Magic: The Gathering March of the Machine Draft Booster Box for $136.83, down from $149.99, at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon&#8217;s wireless network is down for many people nationwide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861956/verizon-is-down-outage-cell-wireless-service-sos-mode</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T13:44:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861956</guid>
      <description>The first big outage of 2026 is here, as Verizon customers across the US, including several of our phones, complain that service has been spotty or nonexistent starting at around noon ET, with phones switching to SOS Mode and being unable to connect. This cell service outage follows a "software issue" that cut off service [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. suspends immigrant visa processing from 75 countries</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474978/us-suspends-immigrant-visa-processing-75-countries</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T18:41:30</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474978/us-suspends-immigrant-visa-processing-75-countries</guid>
      <description>The statement did not identify which countries would be affected by the pause.
The State Department says it will suspend the processing of immigrant visas for citizens of 75 countries whose nationals are deemed likely to require public assistance while living in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Gemini&#8217;s &#8216;Personal Intelligence&#8217; Pulls from Your Search and YouTube History</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-geminis-personal-intelligence-pulls-from-your-search-and-youtube-history-2000710312</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710312</guid>
      <description>Personalization that is maybe a bit too personal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon, AT&amp;T, T-Mobile outages, disruptions: Which services are down right now.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-t-mobile-att-outages-what-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01F1gwYZcHQJE83rLCR7xAZ</guid>
      <description>Verizon, T-Mobile, and AT&amp;T customers all reported service problems starting midday on Wednesday, Jan. 4. Verizon has acknowledged network problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Nigeria vs. Morocco online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nigeria-morocco-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05Y5zf6YzUtErL0WWBURTBz</guid>
      <description>How to watch Africa Cup of Nations for free. Live stream Nigeria vs. Morocco in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Trends Explore page gets new Gemini capabilities</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/googles-trends-explore-page-gets-new-gemini-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082705</guid>
      <description>The Trends Explore page for users to analyze search interest just got a major upgrade. It now uses Gemini to identify and compare relevant trends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPEngine buys major WordPress agency in drive to add more enterprise customers faster</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/wpengine-buys-major-wordpress-agency-in-drive-to-add-more-enterprise-customers-faster</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7DsBDEExqPC7Mrf4TyB2un</guid>
      <description>WP Engine acquires Big Bite, ending its agency role and integrating engineers internally to expand WordPress products for publishers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 30 Most Anticipated Films of 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/most-anticipated-movies-2026-ranked-2000708402</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708402</guid>
      <description>Here are the sci-fi, fantasy, horror, animated, and superhero movies we're most excited about coming out this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's new Cowork tool offers Claude coding help to non-experts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/anthropics-new-cowork-tool-offers-claude-coding-help-to-non-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vmYiuq5re8ogYbWViMo2ph</guid>
      <description>Cowork will make plans and execute tasks just like a colleague, so all you have to do is tell it what you want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A critical climate trend just reversed&#8212;driven by crypto and data centers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474856/climate-change-trend-just-reversed-ai-data-centers-crypto-mining-coal-pushed-us-greenhouse-gas-emissions-up</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474856/climate-change-trend-just-reversed-ai-data-centers-crypto-mining-coal-pushed-us-greenhouse-gas-emissions-up</guid>
      <description>After two years in decline, the United States&#8217; greenhouse gas emissions grew more than its economy in 2025.
After two years of declines, United States greenhouse gas emissions increased in 2025&#8212;a change driven by increased electricity use, due in part to data centers and cryptocurrency mining, as well as cold winter temperatures that meant homes required more heating....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
