<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:38:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tineco revient avec du lourd en 2026 : voici les deux nouveaux aspirateurs lavants</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tineco/2926335_tineco-revient-avec-du-lourd-en-2026-voici-les-deux-nouveaux-aspirateurs-lavants</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tineco/2926335_tineco-revient-avec-du-lourd-en-2026-voici-les-deux-nouveaux-aspirateurs-lavants</guid>
      <description>
Tineco, marque leader des balais laveurs, vient de pr&#233;senter deux nouveaux mod&#232;les au CES 2026. Tandis que l'un est un monstre de puissance haut de gamme, l'autre mise sur l'aspect pratique, gr&#226;ce &#224; son design pliable qui lui permet de passer facilement sous les meubles et de se ranger dans les espaces exigus.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Music Studio 5 and 7 hands-on: Unique speaker designs debut at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/samsung-music-studio-5-and-7-hands-on-unique-speaker-designs-debut-at-ces-2026-052009007.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0425fd88-5b85-4383-a128-cea5b7f17be9</guid>
      <description>In addition to its annual soundbar updates, Samsung debuted two new home speakers at CES 2026. The Music Studio 5 and 7 are Bluetooth and Wi-Fi units designed to blend in with your home decor thanks to their minimalist look. They certainly don&#8217;t look like your typical speakers, and Samsung has packed them with features that it says will ensure optimal sound quality from each one.&#160;The Music Studio 5 has a four-inch woofer and two tweeters, and a sound profile that&#8217;s optimized by AI Dynamic Bass Control. The design is an interesting interplay between a circle and a square, but the speaker delive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The LG C6 OLED TV comes in two versions, and one's way better than the other &#8212; here's what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-lg-c6-oled-tv-comes-in-two-versions-and-ones-way-better-than-the-other-heres-what-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXrhxCKsiJpRDd27bYz2Ga</guid>
      <description>The C6 and the C6H have two very important differences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's new flagship OLED TV has a secret simultaneous upgrade and downgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/samsungs-new-flagship-oled-tv-has-a-secret-simultaneous-upgrade-and-downgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KUVGAEYEUQuFY6QRAjADfH</guid>
      <description>The Samsung S95H OLED TV has a step back for some, but an improvement for others</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birdbuddy&#8217;s new smart feeders aim to make spotting birds easier, even for beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/850488/birdbuddy-2-mini-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850488</guid>
      <description>Birdbuddy is introducing two new smart bird feeders: the flagship Birdbuddy 2 and the more compact, cheaper Birdbuddy 2 Mini aimed at first-time users and smaller outdoor spaces. Both models are designed to be faster and easier to use than previous generations, with upgraded cameras that can shoot in portrait or landscape and wake instantly [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung HW-QS90H soundbar hands-on: Impressive bass performance without a subwoofer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/samsung-hw-qs90h-soundbar-hands-on-impressive-bass-performance-without-a-subwoofer-045727939.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">111b80f0-36b2-4869-bf3f-da4eb2ff2e10</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re used to Samsung updating its Q990 soundbar at CES every year, and 2026 is no different. However, the company also debuted the HW-QS90H: a new all-in-one option that Samsung says won&#8217;t require a standalone subwoofer due to its Quad Bass Woofer system. The QS90H offers 7.1.2-channel audio with 13 total drivers. Before the show properly kicks off, we got to listen to the new soundbar for a quick judge of its merits.&#160;The first thing I noticed about the QS90H is its impressive bass performance. Most of the time when a company claims its soundbar doesn&#8217;t need a subwoofer, that proves to be unt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG announces new OLED TVs at CES &#8212; brighter G6, the C6 splits in two, ultra-thin Wallpaper OLED, and the world's first 4K 120Hz cloud gaming TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lg-announces-the-lg-oled-evo-g6-tv-at-ces-2026-20-percent-brighter-lower-reflections-and-the-worlds-first-with-4k-120hz-cloud-gaming</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2tS69ZEwfQai5muxA7cPtY</guid>
      <description>LG's flagship OLED will be 20% brighter in 2026, and the C6 gets the next-gen Tandem RGB panel, but only in some sizes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry Tamagotchi Fans, It&#8217;s AI Time</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sorry-tamagotchi-fans-its-ai-time-2000705349</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705349</guid>
      <description>It was only a matter of time before someone took a Tamagotchi-like toy and crammed AI into it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just want to keep unfolding the Samsung Z Trifold</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854352/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T23:02:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854352</guid>
      <description>Holding the Z Trifold confirmed my suspicions: it's a tablet with a phone attached. And after spending an hour folding and unfolding it, I'm pretty much ready to trade in the single-hinge foldable I've been carrying for the past couple of weeks. I used the Google Pixel 10 Pro Fold over the holidays as my [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is This the Thinnest Tablet Ever?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/is-this-the-thinnest-tablet-ever-2000705357</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705357</guid>
      <description>Maybe?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
