<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:33:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Section 230 turns 30 as it faces its biggest tests yet</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/875300/section-230-turns-30-social-media-addiction-cases-sunset</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875300</guid>
      <description>Thirty years ago today, Section 230 of the Communications Decency Act, a bill credited with creating the groundwork for the modern internet, became law and set off a chain of events that would make it a lightning rod for the techlash. The statute has survived everything from the dot-com bubble to a Supreme Court challenge [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 7 on Hulu and Disney+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hulu/tell-me-lies-season-3-episode-7-release-date-time-disney-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6C7cmGZUrsXkpPvzxb5ZwU</guid>
      <description>Wrigley and Bree finally kissed last week, but what does that mean for Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 7, and when is it on Hulu and Disney+?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une exolune autour d'une naine brune, comme dans Avatar, a peut-&#234;tre &#233;t&#233; d&#233;tect&#233;e !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-exolune-autour-naine-brune-comme-avatar-peut-etre-ete-detectee-130808/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:47:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-exolune-autour-naine-brune-comme-avatar-peut-etre-ete-detectee-130808/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Des exolunes pourraient exister et abriter des formes de vie. Les astronomes les chassent et quelques-unes sont peut-&#234;tre tomb&#233;es dans leurs filets, par exemple tout derni&#232;rement gr&#226;ce &#224; l'instrument Gravity &#233;quipant les grands t&#233;lescopes de l'Eso au Chili.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s how I optimize my iPhone&#8217;s battery life to make it last longer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/heres-how-i-optimize-my-iphones-battery-life-to-make-it-last-longer</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oNnzk9srmmpFyjw25nBKXj</guid>
      <description>Between various modes, automations, and settings, there are lots of tools I use to make my iPhone's battery go further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify just got a neat upgrade to give you the stories behind the songs &#8211; but it looks like YouTube Music is removing a key feature from free accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/spotify/spotify-just-got-a-neat-upgrade-to-give-you-the-stories-behind-the-songs-but-it-looks-like-youtube-music-is-removing-a-key-feature-from-free-accounts</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nQUaiQbB8WcKnkfjaHNQ8B</guid>
      <description>There's good news if you're a Spotify Premium subscriber, but less good news if you're on the free YouTube Music tier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to stream the 2026 Super Bowl for free this weekend: Patriots vs. Seahawks time, where to watch and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-stream-the-2026-super-bowl-for-free-this-weekend-patriots-vs-seahawks-time-where-to-watch-and-more-124512717.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b2b14-4380-47f2-9cb8-bd2dfe744915</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Super Bowl between the New England Patriots and the Seattle Seahawks will air on NBC this Sunday, Feb. 8. The Big Game will also stream live on Peacock. If you no longer subscribe to cable, don't have access to NBC over the air and aren't currently signed up for Peacock, there are still ways to watch Super Bowl LX &#8212; and Bad Bunny's history-making Super Bowl Halftime Show &#8212; for free. Here's how to tune in.&#160;
How to watch Super Bowl LX free:




Date: Sunday, Feb. 8
Time: 6:30 p.m. ET
Location: Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.
TV channel: NBC, Telemundo
Streaming: Peacock, DirecTV, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl on NBC: Patriots vs. Seahawks kickoff time, where to stream, TV channel and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-on-nbc-patriots-vs-seahawks-kickoff-time-where-to-stream-tv-channel-and-more-175759659.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is just one day away. This Sunday, the Big Game will be played at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA. The 2026 NFL Championship Game kicks off at 6:30PM ET. Pre-game coverage starts at 12PM ET. Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the Super Bowl will be broadcast on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. Here's everything you need to know to tune in to Super Bowl LX on Feb. 8, including the game channel, where to stream, and all about the Halftime Show.
How to watch Super Bowl LX



...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Wireless Earbuds (2026): Apple, Sony, Bose, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-wirefree-earbuds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d3f2e4877f7410008d5316c</guid>
      <description>Ready to cut the cord? These are our favorite buds that will never, ever get tangled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpO2 : pourquoi votre montre connect&#233;e s&#8217;&#233;claire en rouge la nuit (et quand s&#8217;inqui&#233;ter) ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2966707_spo2-pourquoi-votre-montre-connectee-seclaire-en-rouge-la-nuit-et-quand-sinquieter</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2966707_spo2-pourquoi-votre-montre-connectee-seclaire-en-rouge-la-nuit-et-quand-sinquieter</guid>
      <description>
Longtemps r&#233;serv&#233;e au milieu m&#233;dical, la mesure de l'oxyg&#232;ne sanguin (SpO2) s'est g&#233;n&#233;ralis&#233;e sur nos montres, bagues et bracelets connect&#233;s. D&#233;couvrez comment votre montre analyse votre sang et pourquoi ces donn&#233;es sont cruciales pour d&#233;tecter l'apn&#233;e du sommeil ou optimiser vos performances sportives.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital car keys are getting more sophisticated</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/873197/digital-key-car-ccc-plugfest-rivian</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873197</guid>
      <description>Last month, over a dozen automobile and smartphone manufacturers gathered in Palo Alto, California, for the 16th annual "Plugfest," hosted by the Car Connectivity Consortium (CCC) to test out the latest in digital key technology. Digital keys, which allow vehicle owners to lock, unlock, and start their cars using smartphones or other digital devices, are [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s Warner Bros. merger puts rival streamers in survival mode</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/874781/netflix-warner-bros-merger-other-streamers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874781</guid>
      <description>This is The Stepback, a weekly newsletter breaking down one essential story from the tech world. For more news about the streaming wars, follow Emma Roth. The Stepback arrives in our subscribers' inboxes at 8AM ET. Opt in for The Stepback here. How it started From 2019 to around 2021, we were in the midst [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liverpool vs Man City Live Streams: How to watch Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/liverpool-vs-man-city-watch-premier-league-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">k8e59JCDGnd6hfBCF6stzD</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Liverpool vs Man City live streams online and from anywhere, with Pep Guardiola's side looking to secure their first win at Anfield in the Premier League since 2003.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
