<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:24:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Disney to Pay $10 Million After Feds Say It Broke Kids&#8217; Privacy Rules on YouTube</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-to-pay-10-million-after-feds-say-it-broke-kids-privacy-rules-on-youtube-2000704462</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704462</guid>
      <description>The DOJ accused Disney of mislabeling videos aimed at children, resulting in targeted ads and unlawful data collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does 2026 have in store for AI? We asked ChatGPT, Gemini, and Claude &#8212; here's what they said</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/what-does-2026-have-in-store-for-ai-we-asked-chatgpt-gemini-and-claude-heres-what-they-said</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gscVtZMB4SX8JvwV7vViEE</guid>
      <description>Here's what ChatGPT, Gemini, and Claude predict about AI in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The OneXSugar Wallet is an upcoming retro handheld with a 4:3 foldable screen</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-onexsugar-wallet-is-an-upcoming-retro-handheld-with-a-43-foldable-screen-215528433.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac10bd63-48b3-4735-b93e-1db00401354f</guid>
      <description>OneXPlayer is quickly establishing itself as a company that isn't afraid to get weird as hell. (Take, for example, its transforming dual-screen gaming portable.) Its latest venture is another retro gaming handheld that, at first glance, looks like a standard dual-screen model. But the Android-powered OneXSugar Wallet uses a single foldable screen instead.The device was teased via a 54-second video on the Chinese video-sharing platform Bilibili. Retro Handhelds reports that the Wallet uses an 8.01-inch OLED with a 2,480 x 1,860 resolution. (That's a 4:3 aspect ratio when unfolded.) The video al...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After &#8216;Pluribus&#8217;, Revisit Rhea Seehorn&#8217;s Next Best Genre Role: &#8216;Magic: The Gathering&#8217; Tutorial Sorceress</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/after-pluribus-revisit-rhea-seehorns-next-best-genre-role-magic-the-gathering-tutorial-sorceress-2000704456</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704456</guid>
      <description>Carol Sturka's career as a romantasy author suddenly makes a lot more sense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDC warns of major PC market downturn due to memory crunch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/idc-warns-of-major-pc-market-downturn-due-to-memory-crunch-214510197.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b98375-aae9-443d-863d-37a7ad0aa41d</guid>
      <description>The demand building out AI infrastructure has placed on PC component makers has already led to the death of one consumer-facing RAM brand, but a new report from the International Data Corporation (IDC) suggests it could have an even worse impact on the PC industry at large. In its worst-case-scenario model, the IDC predicts PC shipments could shrink by up to 8.9 percent in 2026 because of the high cost of memory."Instead of expanding conventional DRAM and NAND used in smartphones, PCs and other consumer electronics, major memory makers have shifted production toward memory used in AI data cent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone AI, like Siri and Gemini, has a credibility crisis &#8211; a true agentic interface is the logical next step</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/smartphone-ai-like-siri-and-gemini-has-a-credibility-crisis-a-true-agentic-interface-is-the-logical-next-step</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kEQHBqL4WhDZUUBLpDmGz7</guid>
      <description>Today's AI features are rife with problems, but agentic AI is inevitable, so let's get rid of the worst AI problems now while we train the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Cuts and Borked Code Delay Important Energy Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doge-cuts-and-borked-code-delay-important-energy-report-2000704413</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704413</guid>
      <description>The ghost of Elon continues to haunt the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: Why Disney Destiny&#8217;s ship horn is built like an instrument, not a speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/exclusive-why-disney-destinys-ship-horn-is-built-like-an-instrument-not-a-speaker</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaXpJDRxiVu6rsvDbfQZRQ</guid>
      <description>The inside story on the 18-horn sound system on Disney Destiny, Disney Cruise Line&#8217;s latest Wish-class ship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deadly, Drug-Resistant Fungus Threatens People Around the World, Scientists Warn</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-deadly-super-fungus-is-on-the-rise-scientists-warn-2000704305</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 20:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704305</guid>
      <description>The global burden of Candida auris has been increasing since its discovery in 2009, a new review finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Clooney Would Like You to Remember &#8216;Batman Has Nipples, Dude&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/george-clooney-batman-and-robin-nipples-2000704408</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 20:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704408</guid>
      <description>The star of 1997's 'Batman &amp; Robin' looks back on his superhero moment&#8212;and that infamous costume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docking stations are merging with external GPU bases &#8212; Minisforum's DEG2 even has a free SSD slot and TB5 compatibility, but I just wish it had more ports</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/docking-stations-are-merging-with-external-gpu-bases-minisforum-deg2-even-has-a-free-ssd-slot-and-tb5-compatibility-but-i-just-wish-it-had-more-ports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FF7EpdtEskESZAxGqAoT37</guid>
      <description>Minisforum DEG2 blends external GPU support with limited docking features, focusing on PCIe bandwidth, internal SSD expansion, and user-supplied components.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules White House must continue to fund CFPB</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467882/cfpb-judge-rules-white-house-must-continue-funding</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-30T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467882/cfpb-judge-rules-white-house-must-continue-funding</guid>
      <description>The CFPB has largely been inoperable since President Trump&#8217;s return to office.
The White House cannot lapse in its funding of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, a federal district court judge ruled on Tuesday, only days before funds at the bureau would have likely run out and the consumer finance agency would have no money to pay its employees....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
