<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 02:02:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I'm prepared to die for these limited edition Hatsune Miku Sony earbuds and I don't care who knows it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/im-prepared-to-die-for-these-limited-edition-hatsune-miku-sony-earbuds-and-i-dont-care-who-knows-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qbu65UBc2v7qVoA9RdDD6W</guid>
      <description>Sony has unveiled a new limited edition Hatsune Miku variant of its LinkBuds Fit earbuds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta sets up 'top-level' Compute initiative to make sure its AI data centers get all the power they need - Zuckerberg promises 'tens of gigawatts this decade, and hundreds of gigawatts or more over time'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/meta-sets-up-top-level-compute-initiative-to-make-sure-its-ai-data-centers-get-all-the-power-they-need-zuckerberg-promises-tens-of-gigawatts-this-decade-and-hundreds-of-gigawatts-or-more-over-time</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LN8hamS8MQYxgWWpLcpjV8</guid>
      <description>Meta Compute will oversee AI infrastructure expansion, unify leadership, and plan for tens to hundreds of gigawatts over the next decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Why your phone says SOS, what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-outage-phone-sos-what-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b3BjNJgL2nDXUlVE7I4JU</guid>
      <description>There appears to be a major Verizon outage. Here's what to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're definitely beta testing this technology": is Alexa+ really bad, or are our expectations for free services too high?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/were-definitely-beta-testing-this-technology-is-alexa-really-bad-or-are-our-expectations-for-free-services-too-high</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">phADXC6XhGdRyPywAot3Wa</guid>
      <description>Alexa+ just rolled out for Prime customers for free, but not everyone is thrilled by the change. Others argue you really should be, here's why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 signs that ChatGPT is hallucinating</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/5-signs-that-chatgpt-is-hallucinating</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SxsDCvXfpusJAjvYWgHnp7</guid>
      <description>How to recognize when AI chatbots hallucinate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best e-reader to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23769068/best-ebook-readers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T19:54:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23769068/best-ebook-readers</guid>
      <description>Any ebook reader will let you cram a Beauty and the Beast-sized library&#8217;s worth of books in your pocket, but so will your phone. An ebook reader offers a more book-like reading experience, with fewer distractions and less eye strain, and many include extra features, like adjustable frontlighting. Some really are pocketable. Others are waterproof [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X claims it has stopped Grok from undressing people, but of course it hasn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862372/x-grok-ai-policy-update-deepfake-bikini-poses</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T19:46:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862372</guid>
      <description>Following the proliferation of the nonconsensual sexual deepfakes on X, the platform has detailed changes to the Grok account's ability to edit images of real people. They match the changes reported on Tuesday by The Telegraph, as Grok's responses to prompts like "put her in a bikini" became censored. But in tests of the feature [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Thinking Machines Lab Cofounders Are Leaving to Rejoin OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/thinking-machines-lab-cofounders-leave-for-openai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69682efe6376ac7cbf488f44</guid>
      <description>The news is a blow for Thinking Machines Lab. Two narratives are already emerging about what happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FTC&#8217;s data-sharing order against GM is finally settled</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/the-ftcs-data-sharing-order-against-gm-is-finally-settled/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082822</guid>
      <description>The order, first proposed a year ago, bans GM from collecting and then selling geolocation data to third parties, like data brokers and insurance companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network is experiencing technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Verizon customers on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even the network provider&#8217;s own status page struggled to load, likely due to the number of customers trying to access it.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally, at least for some users. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started growing a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India&#8217;s Emversity doubles valuation as it scales workers AI can&#8217;t replace</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/indias-emversity-doubles-valuation-as-it-scales-workers-ai-cant-replace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082634</guid>
      <description>Emversity has raised $30 million in a new round as it scales job-ready training in India.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
