<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:32:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darty fait une belle offre sur ce SSD T7 de Samsung avec de 2 To et inclut m&#234;me un cadeau</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2976345_darty-fait-une-belle-offre-sur-ce-ssd-t7-de-samsung-avec-de-2-to-et-inclut-meme-un-cadeau</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2976345_darty-fait-une-belle-offre-sur-ce-ssd-t7-de-samsung-avec-de-2-to-et-inclut-meme-un-cadeau</guid>
      <description>
Alors que les prix du stockage repartent &#224; la hausse en 2026, ce pack sign&#233; Samsung tombe &#224; pic pour ceux qui veulent faire des &#233;conomies sans sacrifier la qualit&#233;. Il r&#233;unit le SSD portable T7 avec 2 To de capacit&#233; et une carte microSD Evo Plus de 64 Go, le tout &#224; seulement&#160;219&#8201;euros au lieu de 249&#8201;euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day sales 2026: The best tech deals to shop this weekend from Apple, Sony, Anker and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/presidents-day-sales-2026-the-best-tech-deals-to-shop-this-weekend-from-apple-sony-anker-and-others-163000988.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba4f502-86ba-4c79-a2ff-b27b6e52c38b</guid>
      <description>You can find a lot of good deals for Presidents&#8217; Day, but to say it&#8217;s a tech-deal boon would be an overstatement. The best Presidents&#8217; Day deals are usually on mattresses, appliances and furniture, but you can find some decent tech sales thrown in as well. This year, Presidents&#8217; Day comes right after Valentine&#8217;s Day and Super Bowl 2026, which means there are even more chances to save as sales and discounts overlap. If you&#8217;re looking for a new streaming device, a fresh iPad or an upgraded vacuum so you can enter the spring-cleaning season properly, we have you covered. These are the best Presid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 8 on Hulu and Disney+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hulu/tell-me-lies-season-3-episode-8-release-date-time-disney-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZdUAX3uwvvZB3Uv7eRKwue</guid>
      <description>The end is in sight but it's not going to be pretty. When does Tell Me Lies season 3 episode 8 air on Hulu and Disney+?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 21 best Presidents' Day TV deals of 2026 &#8212; my top recommendations if you're buying a new display</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-21-best-presidents-day-tv-deals-of-2026-my-top-recommendations-if-youre-buying-a-new-display</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PcjVRU5VSWUsiDMx4WWUSb</guid>
      <description>I'm rounding up today's 21 best Presidents' Day TV sales of 2026 that I personally recommend buying if you're looking to buy a new display.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How George Washington&#8217;s mistakes in Pennsylvania&#8217;s wilderness provided valuable leadership lessons</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490268/how-george-washingtons-mistakes-pennsylvanias-wilderness-provided-valuable-leadership-lessons</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T14:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490268/how-george-washingtons-mistakes-pennsylvanias-wilderness-provided-valuable-leadership-lessons</guid>
      <description>This Presidents&#8217; Day, there are lessons to be learned from the father of our country&#8217;s worst moments. 
This Presidents&#8217; Day, I&#8217;ve been thinking about George Washington&#8212;not at his finest hour, but possibly at his worst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the 512GB Samsung P9 microSD Express card for 33 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-the-512gb-samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-for-33-percent-off-right-now-143849920.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7c1c9b1-8762-4b3b-bd34-558e13eba66f</guid>
      <description>MicroSD Express cards are still a little hard to find, considering they're pretty new and only really started becoming popular last year once the Switch 2 came out. These upgraded versions of microSD cards are the only ones compatible with the Switch 2 for expanding its storage, os if you're already starting to feel the crunch on your console, it's worth picking one up. Samsung's P9 microSD Express card is on sale right now &#8212; you can grab the 512GB version of $80, which is 33 percent off and one of the best prices we've seen.
The P9 boasts transfer speeds of up to 800MB/s, making moving games ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The design of Samsung's competitor to the iPhone Fold may have just leaked in One UI 9</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-design-of-samsungs-competitor-to-the-iphone-fold-may-have-just-leaked-in-one-ui-9</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iJMYd6bTNmpNtXuRSc7mG9</guid>
      <description>Samsung is apparently developing a 'wide fold' model that more closely matches what Apple has in the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's 45W Nano charger with smart display is $10 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/ankers-45w-nano-charger-with-smart-display-is-10-off-160707508.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker rolled out a bunch of new chargers and other gear at CES 2026, including a cute one that's already on sale. The new Nano charger with smart display, which is an upgrade to the existing Nano charger in Anker's lineup, is on sale for $30 right now. That's $10 off the regular price.
The 45W charger includes a smart display that shows real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to ensure a longer battery lifespan. 
To that e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this the beginning of the end for humanity? Slightly terrifying 3D printing breakthrough means we can now print robotic 'muscle'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/slightly-terrifying-3d-printing-breakthrough-means-we-can-now-print-robotic-muscle-so-is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-humanity</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zcMTLiyU2hcx65Di8hjRSW</guid>
      <description>Harvard engineers develop a 3D printing method for producing robotic muscles with programmed movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moulinex Cookeo Infinity : j&#8217;ai test&#233; le multicuiseur connect&#233; le plus complet du moment</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robots-cuiseurs/2877937_moulinex-cookeo-infinity-jai-teste-le-multicuiseur-connecte-le-plus-complet-du-moment</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robots-cuiseurs/2877937_moulinex-cookeo-infinity-jai-teste-le-multicuiseur-connecte-le-plus-complet-du-moment</guid>
      <description>
Avec pas moins de 17 modes de cuisson au menu, le nouveau multicuiseur connect&#233; de Moulinex, le Cookeo Infinity, se propose de r&#233;unir le meilleur des univers en fusionnant les technologies de cuisson sous pression, vapeur et maintenant AirFryer ! Nous l'avons donc test&#233; de fa&#231;on intensive durant une semaine et continuons m&#234;me apr&#232;s. Voici le verdict apr&#232;s 3 mois.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Epstein&#8217;s emails full of equals signs?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/879016/epstein-files-emails-text-errors-encoding</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879016</guid>
      <description>Many of the emails released by the Department of Justice from its investigation into Jeffrey Epstein are full of garbled symbols like: Or: The scrambled text is so ubiquitous that it's spurred conspiracy theories that it could be some kind of code. But as believable as it might be that a cabal of elite sex [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can&#8217;t make good video game worlds yet, and it might never be able to</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/879524/ai-video-game-worlds-project-genie</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-15T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879524</guid>
      <description>This is The Stepback, a weekly newsletter breaking down one essential story from the tech world. For more news about video game industry's pushback against generative AI, follow Jay Peters. The Stepback arrives in our subscribers' inboxes at 8AM ET. Opt in for The Stepback here. How it started Long before the generative AI explosion, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick of charging your Apple Watch every day? The Coros Pace 4 offers up to 19 days of battery, and costs less than an SE 3</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/coros-pace-4-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">G3KqCrCxFJ7dvKRK4j6XX8</guid>
      <description>The Coros Pace 4 is a joy to wear during all types of activity, but there's a GPS margin of error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Presidents' Day sales: Get the Apple Watch Series 11 for $299, plus more deals to shop this weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apple-presidents-day-sales-get-the-apple-watch-series-11-for-299-plus-more-deals-to-shop-this-weekend-151616206.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78902e66-331a-45a8-8c59-e293650f49bb</guid>
      <description>Whether you're one of the few people still keeping up with New Year's resolutions or just want an upgraded smartwatch, now is a good time to get an Apple Watch. Currently, the Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for $299 for Presidents' Day, down from $399. The 25 percent discount brings the 2025 model back down to its record-low price. A number of other Apple devices are on sale for the holiday as well.
We named the Apple Watch Series 11 as our choice for best smartwatch overall. It scored a 90 in our review thanks to its 24 hours-plus of battery life and a thin, light design that's easy to wear...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
