<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:27:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>2026 could well be the year of the $500 32GB DDR5 memory module &#8212; experts predict DDR will go up by 60% in Q1 2026 alone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/2026-could-well-be-the-year-of-the-usd500-32gb-ddr5-memory-module-experts-predict-ddr-will-go-up-by-60-percent-in-q1-2026-alone</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AMaNVjgtEKxAptVrnbQyJk</guid>
      <description>2026 could see 32GB DDR5 memory costing $500 as analysts warn of steep DRAM price rises driven by server demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Coin Zcash Drops 20% as Core Dev Team Departs Electric Coin Company</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/privacy-coin-zcash-drops-20-as-core-dev-team-departs-electric-coin-company-2000707755</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707755</guid>
      <description>The fears of centralizing forces in crypto are creating a lot of skittishness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics unveils production-ready version of Atlas robot at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/boston-dynamics-unveils-production-ready-version-of-atlas-robot-at-ces-2026-234047882.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">207c5a82-d64f-4628-b6d7-ef00999cd1c5</guid>
      <description>After years of testing its humanoid robot (and forcing it to dance), Boston Dynamics' Atlas is entering production. The robotics company said at CES 2026 that the final product version of the robot is being built now, and the first companies that will receive deployments are Hyundai, Boston Dynamics' majority shareholder, and Google DeepMind, the firm's newly minted AI partner.This final enterprise version of Atlas "can perform a wide array of industrial tasks," according to Boston Dynamics, and is specifically designed with consistency and reliability in mind. Atlas can work autonomously, via...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Emmys Create a New &#8216;Legacy Award&#8217; to Honor Old Favorites</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/emmys-legacy-award-franchises-2000707772</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707772</guid>
      <description>The nostalgia-fueled prize is designed to honor shows that have made 'a profound and lasting impact' on culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer put a waifu in a bottle at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/razer-put-a-waifu-in-a-bottle-at-ces-2026-205315908.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b82353d-fa02-44f4-a29f-03c921796cd4</guid>
      <description>Last year Razer showed off Project Ava as a digital assistant that lived inside your computer to help adjust settings or provide gaming tips. But now at CES 2026, the company&#8217;s AI companion platform has gotten a major glow-up while moving into some new digs.&#160;Now, in lieu of being constrained entirely to your PC&#8217;s screen, Razer has given Project Ava a real home in the form of a small tube that can display a 5.5-inch animated hologram of the AI&#8217;s avatar. You&#8217;ll still need to connect it to your computer via USB-C to provide Ava with the power and data it needs. However, all of your companion&#8217;s ot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal data on over 700,000 exposed by Illinois government agency</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/personal-data-on-over-700-000-exposed-by-illinois-government-agency</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5v58FY9nBdnyZqTihJfidL</guid>
      <description>A human mistake resulted in a major data leak in late September 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truly phoneless AI glasses to the first specs with HDR10 &#8212; here are the best smart glasses from CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/truly-phoneless-ai-glasses-to-the-first-specs-with-hdr10-here-are-the-best-smart-glasses-from-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">W7AMzeHYh3QscoEnsmg77f</guid>
      <description>We got 20-26 vision at CES this year thanks to the five best smart glasses announced at the show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to Demolish Iconic Towers Used to Test Saturn V, Space Shuttle</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-to-demolish-iconic-towers-used-to-test-saturn-v-space-shuttle-2000707670</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707670</guid>
      <description>One of the test stands was last used as a drop tower for microgravity testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will let you exclude Shorts from search results</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/youtube/youtube-will-let-you-exclude-shorts-from-search-results-204500097.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ad1c89f-f184-4edc-8abe-d92077cb182d</guid>
      <description>YouTube introduced some new filters to its advanced search tools today. Possibly the most exciting change is that Shorts are now listed as a content type, so the three-minute-or-less videos can be excluded as results in your searches. This is a welcome update for any of us who have been on the hunt for a long-form explainer only to wade through dozens of ten-second clips before finding anything close to our goal. Especially with the addition of even more AI slop last year thanks to the Google Veo 3 engine, an option to exclude Shorts may look even more appealing.The other updates include a pai...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands-on with Fender Audio's headphones and speakers at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/hands-on-with-fender-audios-headphones-and-speakers-at-ces-2026-203104561.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17e8d8d5-ed2c-4cd6-b88b-119c4d9244e4</guid>
      <description>Fender Audio may have announced its new headphones and speakers right before CES, but Las Vegas afforded us the first opportunity to see the brand&#8217;s new lineup in person. Fender Audio is a Fender-owned brand from Riffsound that&#8217;s designing and making new devices after licensing the name. It&#8217;s been a while since the guitar and amplifier company made any general-use speakers of its own, and this new arrangement is similar to what Zound was doing with Marshall for a spell. Logistics out of the way, let&#8217;s get down to what the Mix and Ellie are like in the flesh. First, the Mix headphones offer a m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 CES gadgets you can buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/19-ces-gadgets-you-can-buy-right-now-164325541.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">486c0883-fd9d-4677-b8fe-ca2db36c7354</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is nearly over and it&#8217;s been a fruitful one with a lot of new, weird and impressive tech. But you don&#8217;t have to wait until later this year to get your hands on some of the things announced this week in Las Vegas. A surprising number of gadgets are up for pre-order, if not outright available to buy already, from chargers and docks to projectors, keyboards and smart home gear. CES remains a place for companies to showcase concepts and big ideas, but these are the gadgets that have real prices and real order buttons as of today. Check out all of the CES 2026 gadgets you can buy right now...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra n&#8217;est pas encore l&#224;, mais les coques de protection sont d&#233;j&#224; pr&#234;tes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2936111_le-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-nest-pas-encore-la-mais-les-coques-de-protection-sont-deja-pretes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2936111_le-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-nest-pas-encore-la-mais-les-coques-de-protection-sont-deja-pretes</guid>
      <description>
Le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra n'est pas encore officialis&#233;, mais on a d&#233;j&#224; vu des coques de protection pr&#234;tes pour le smartphone, au CES 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Grok and X Still Available in App Stores?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/x-grok-app-store-nudify-csam-apple-google-content-moderation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695e909fd435a2f4643b6d47</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s chatbot has been used to generate thousands of sexualized images of adults and apparent minors. Apple and Google have removed other &#8220;nudify&#8221; apps&#8212;but continue to host X and Grok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest new TV announcements at CES 2026 from Samsung, LG and TCL</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/the-biggest-new-tv-announcements-at-ces-2026-from-samsung-lg-and-tcl-190929614.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecf435a5-d2a0-4321-9064-dcce9611c48e</guid>
      <description>TVs are a staple of CES, and so far, manufacturers have not disappointed with their announcements at CES 2026. Companies including Samsung, LG and others came to the event ready to show off updates to existing display tech and some genuinely new technologies. OLED and Mini LED remain central to most lineups, while Micro RGB has emerged as one of the most talked-about developments at the show so far, especially at the higher end of the TV market.Below are the TV announcements that stood out most from the pre-show events and early press conferences, with more expected as CES continues. Also, be ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The weirdest tech we've seen at CES 2026 so far</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-weirdest-tech-weve-seen-at-ces-2026-so-far-134056504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a400df8-3389-4aee-8595-d1a0f59b424f</guid>
      <description>The usual suspects always show up at CES &#8212; new TVs, laptops, chips, robots and the like. But CES is also a place where companies feel free to ask some very strange questions about how technology could further infiltrate our lives. For example, should your toilet analyze your poop? Should your nails change color on command?  From experimental laptops to health tech that probably didn&#8217;t need a camera, these are the weirdest gadgets we spotted at CES 2026. Also, be sure to check out our list of the best CES tech we saw this year at the show.Throne toilet computerThe Throne device perched on the s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workplaces are integrating nature to bring balance and calm. Here&#8217;s how</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471472/workplaces-nature-balance-calm</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T20:22:08</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471472/workplaces-nature-balance-calm</guid>
      <description>Some employees reported they felt like they&#160;handled stress&#160;better as a result of spending more time outside.
The crisp crinkle of fallen leaves beneath your feet. The swish and trickle of water moving through a stream. A breath of crisp, fresh air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The coolest laptops we saw at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858897/ces-2026-best-laptops-asus-dell-acer-msi-hp-lenovo-concepts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T15:20:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858897</guid>
      <description>CES is always jam-packed with new laptop announcements, acting as a barometer for the year's upcoming releases. The proofs of concept at the show display what could potentially come further in the future. 2026 will soon bring us new chip options from Intel, AMD, and Qualcomm. While I'm excited to see how the latest horse [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Is Already Rewriting the ICE Shooting in Minneapolis</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/maga-trump-rewriting-ice-shooting-minneapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695fbfb833fe679ee74ae7ec</guid>
      <description>The federal government&#8217;s narrative of the Minneapolis shooting conflicts wildly with video footage of the incident shared online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerson Smart brings offline voice control to lamps and fans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/emerson-smart-brings-offline-voice-control-to-lamps-and-fans-201500078.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">545e2238-777a-4daa-a5bf-b36d441b2d33</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you like the idea of controlling your home appliances with your voice, but aren&#8217;t super keen on a data center processing recordings of you. Fair enough. The trade-off for most smart home conveniences is relinquishing at least some of your privacy. Today at CES, I saw a line of voice-controlled home appliances from Emerson Smart that adjust power and setting via voice commands. But commands are recognized on the devices themselves, not carried through Wi-Fi and processed elsewhere. 
The huge array of smart plugs, fans, heaters and even air fryers require no app for setup and don&#8217;t need ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Will Stand Alone Outside the World&#8217;s Climate Treaty</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-us-will-stand-alone-outside-the-worlds-climate-treaty-2000707741</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707741</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday, President Trump announced he was withdrawing the U.S. from the principal treaty for international cooperation on climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget's best of CES 2026: All the new tech that caught our eye in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/engadgets-best-of-ces-2026-all-the-new-tech-that-caught-our-eye-in-las-vegas-200057123.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">289bf078-4351-4457-b4ba-74ba94fb78b6</guid>
      <description>This year, over 4,000 exhibitors descended on Las Vegas, Nevada to showcase their wares at CES, and the Engadget team was out in full force. The week started with press conferences from the biggest companies at the show, which were often a flurry of AI buzzwords, vague promises and very little in the way of hard news.&#160;More than one company even decided to forgo announcing things during their conferences to make way for more AI chatter, only to publish press releases later quietly admitting that, yes, actually, they did make some consumer technology. It's appropriate, I guess, that as we're beg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Jujustu Kaisen&#8217; Opening Is an Art History Fever Dream</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jujutsu-kaisen-jjk-culling-game-season-3-classic-art-reference-opening-theme-2000707576</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707576</guid>
      <description>Sukuna pinkies up, everyone. We're looking at all the art references sprinkled in season 3's opening sequence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A lifeline in real time</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462740/a-lifeline-in-real-time</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462740/a-lifeline-in-real-time</guid>
      <description>Micro-philanthropy can help a women-led Sumatra coffee cooperative recover from natural disaster.
In the heart of Aceh province in northwestern Sumatra, the Ketiara Cooperative, led by the remarkable Ibu Rahmah, is facing a crisis unfolding as we speak. This community of women-led farmers was devastated by the rare Cyclone Senyar over the Thanksgiving weekend, which caused catastrophic mudslides. Farms have been decimated, homes destroyed, and two vital bridges have been washed away, isolating entire villages and cutting off access to essentials like food, clean water, and electricity. Hundred...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US withdraws from dozens of international bodies, including climate-focused organizations</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-us-withdraws-from-dozens-of-international-bodies-including-climate-focused-organizations-195259578.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf3a3fcf-2159-49d1-9f59-4e6e17b36cba</guid>
      <description>In a new executive order, President Donald Trump has declared that the United States will withdraw from 66 international organizations and bodies, including several focused on tackling climate change. Trump made his disregard for climate change clear when he withdrew the US from the Paris climate agreement for a second time in early 2025, but these new withdrawals further confirm the second Trump administration is against global collaboration in general.Among the organizations targeted, the US will no longer participate in the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change, the Intergovernmental Pa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone 4 is the classic camera phone that retro lovers can't get enough of &#8212; but don't skip these essential security tips</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/the-iphone-4-is-the-classic-camera-phone-that-retro-lovers-cant-get-enough-of-but-dont-skip-these-essential-security-tips</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2yvsFVo2mwS7k64nREZE5</guid>
      <description>Demand for the iPhone 4 is up almost 1,000%, but using such an old handset comes with a few cyber security caveats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoLTE, 3G, itin&#233;rance Orange, satellite, 5G sur l&#8217;Apple Watch, 5G SA : le directeur c&#339;ur de r&#233;seau de Free r&#233;pond &#224; toutes nos questions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2935865_volte-3g-itinerance-orange-satellite-5g-sur-lapple-watch-5g-sa-le-directeur-reseau-de-free-repond-a-toutes-nos-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2935865_volte-3g-itinerance-orange-satellite-5g-sur-lapple-watch-5g-sa-le-directeur-reseau-de-free-repond-a-toutes-nos-questions</guid>
      <description>
C'est une mise au point n&#233;cessaire. Alors que certains abonn&#233;s &#233;voquent des probl&#232;mes d'appels chez Free Mobile, nous avons interrog&#233; Pascal Mayeux, directeur du c&#339;ur de r&#233;seau. On en a profit&#233; pour poser plein d'autres questions.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing NBC on Fubo? Here's how to watch Sunday Night Football, figure skating, and more this week</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/missing-nbc-on-fubo-heres-how-to-watch-sunday-night-football-figure-skating-and-more-this-week-014052346.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7c5b935-7bd3-4149-94ef-aa50624bc67b</guid>
      <description>


  Amber Glenn is competing in the 2026 United States Figure Skating Championships this week.(Jamie Squire/Getty Images)
 

  Jamie Squire via Getty Images
 

It's been almost two months since Fubo has stopped carrying NBCUniversal-owned channels, and there's still no sign of them coming back to the streaming service. Customers have had to find alternate methods of watching Sunday Night Football, all the latest episodes of the Real Housewives franchise, and so much more because of Fubo and NBCUniversal's contract dispute, so channels like NBC, USA Network, Telemundo, and Bravo have been unav...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vantrue unveils world&#8217;s first dash cam with thermal imaging for Predator-style night vision on the move</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/vantrue-unveils-worlds-first-dash-cam-with-thermal-imaging-for-predator-style-night-vision-on-the-move</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2LMbKJk2f85yPQPkDdDLMf</guid>
      <description>Vantrue's Pilot 2 claims to be the world's first system with integrated thermal imaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Forced Copilot Into Your Life. Now It Can Accidentally Drain Your Bank Account</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsoft-forced-copilot-into-your-life-now-it-can-accidentally-drain-your-bank-account-2000707721</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707721</guid>
      <description>The agent has your wallet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three months of Audible is only $3 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/three-months-of-audible-is-only-3-right-now-193859847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>Have a hankering for some audiobooks? Audible is holding one heck of a sale right now, giving users three months of access for $3. That's a dollar per month. This is something of a winter tradition for the Amazon-owned platform and the promotion ends on January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated titles. Think of it like N...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional staff emails hacked as part of Salt Typhoon campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/congressional-staff-emails-hacked-as-part-of-salt-typhoon-campaign</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">F45DkKB4eTYDtGYUczU2im</guid>
      <description>Emails used by staff members of &#8220;powerful committees in the US House of Representatives were allegedly breached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who needs AI deepfakes when the Trump government can dispute video evidence that we can plainly see?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471355/who-needs-ai-deepfakes-when-the-trump-government-can-dispute-video-evidence-that-we-can-plainly-see</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T19:35:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471355/who-needs-ai-deepfakes-when-the-trump-government-can-dispute-video-evidence-that-we-can-plainly-see</guid>
      <description>A fatal ICE shooting in Minneapolis and a new January 6 web page show that humans are fully capable of distorting reality without any help from bots.
In the age of rampant AI slop, seeing isn&#8217;t always believing. There&#8217;s more than one way, though, to make people doubt their own eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans think mysterious countdown on Amazons website teases a Fallout 3 remaster</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/fallout-countdown-amazon-3-new-vegas</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05e7YFZqF1qXyZIhZE8mWHM</guid>
      <description>Amazon is teasing something on its 'Fallout' website, and we'll all find out what it is in early February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Bird Feeders With Cameras, Tested and Reviewed (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-smart-bird-feeders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6671f1ec865e53584d1a830b</guid>
      <description>These bird feeders come with cameras and connected apps to let you see and learn about the birds in your neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herm&#232;s&#8217; hand-illustrated website is the ultimate luxury</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471305/hermes-hand-illustrated-website-is-the-ultimate-luxury</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471305/hermes-hand-illustrated-website-is-the-ultimate-luxury</guid>
      <description>The luxury fashion house pulled a power move in an era dominated by AI imagery: It hired a living, breathing artist. 
If you visit the Herm&#232;s website in search of a scarf or a handbag, you&#8217;ll be greeted by a collection of whimsical sea creatures swimming across the screen. To navigate to the watch section, you&#8217;ll click on an image of a watch flanked by an eel. To locate shoes, you&#8217;ll click on a loafer with a pelican sitting inside it as if it were riding a boat....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTMfund&#160;has rewritten the distribution&#160;playbook for the AI era</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/gtmfund-has-rewritten-the-distribution-playbook-for-the-ai-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081272</guid>
      <description>Building software products has never been easier, so why are so many well-funded startups&#160;failing to take&#160;off no matter how good their product is? In this season finale episode of Build Mode, our guest has an answer: Startups have focused too much on product development and not enough on distribution excellence. Paul Irving is partner and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
