<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 18:41:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>'What we really wanted was Mike': How Mike Markkula was Apple's first true master marketer before Steve Jobs and wrote the business plan that made Apple a Fortune 500 company</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-we-really-wanted-was-mike-how-mike-markkula-was-apples-first-true-master-marketer-before-steve-jobs-and-wrote-the-business-plan-that-made-apple-a-fortune-500-company</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iieYfsvFSbiJkeppw32CeG</guid>
      <description>How Mike Markkula transformed Apple from garage experiment into the business that reshaped personal computing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A judge ruled Tesla still has to pay $243 million for a fatal crash involving Autopilot</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/a-judge-ruled-tesla-still-has-to-pay-243-million-for-a-fatal-crash-involving-autopilot-174548093.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb7e45e7-dc0a-4eba-b7bf-f574b107b4f6</guid>
      <description>Tesla is still on the hook for $243 million after a US judge rejected the EV maker's bid to overturn a jury verdict from last year. On Friday, US District Judge Beth Bloom upheld the jury's decision to hold Tesla partially responsible for a deadly crash that happened in 2019 and involved the self-driving Autopilot feature.
The judge added that there was enough evidence to support the jury's verdict, which was delivered in August 2025 and ordered Tesla to pay millions in compensatory and punitive damages to the two victims in the case. Judge Bloom added that Tesla didn't present any new argumen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#8217;s new gaming CEO vows not to flood the ecosystem with &#8216;endless AI slop&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/21/microsofts-new-gaming-ceo-vows-not-to-flood-the-ecosystem-with-endless-ai-slop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095331</guid>
      <description>Is Microsoft's gaming division doubling down on AI?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp could get a Reddit-style spoiler-hiding feature &#8211; so you won't have to hide from group chats if you&#8217;re behind on the big shows</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/whatsapp-could-get-a-reddit-style-spoiler-hiding-feature-so-you-wont-have-to-hide-from-group-chats-if-youre-behind-on-the-big-shows</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">txjsCBWFvEebXx4U8ya8oU</guid>
      <description>Spoiler tags look like they're on their way to WhatsApp, to keep you from finding out plot twists before you're ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Original 151 Pok&#233;mon and Their History Are Up for Auction</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-original-151-pokemon-and-their-history-are-up-for-auction-2000725006</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725006</guid>
      <description>Games, anime merch, and most importantly cards are all up for sale in a celebration auction of the Pok&#233;mon franchise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android 17 : le dossier ultime pour tout savoir sur la future mise &#224; jour de vos smartphones et tablettes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/mises-a-jour-android/2978341_android-17-le-dossier-ultime-pour-tout-savoir-sur-la-future-mise-a-jour-de-vos-smartphones-et-tablettes</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/mises-a-jour-android/2978341_android-17-le-dossier-ultime-pour-tout-savoir-sur-la-future-mise-a-jour-de-vos-smartphones-et-tablettes</guid>
      <description>
Les chantiers d'Android 17 ont &#233;t&#233; officiellement lanc&#233;s par Google. Voici les nouveaut&#233;s, les dates importantes et les smartphones compatibles avec la mise &#224; jour encore en b&#234;ta.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man City vs Newcastle Live Streams: How to watch Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/man-city-vs-newcastle-premier-league-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fAJrvS3z2bVcMaSDytTTP</guid>
      <description>We'll show you how to watch Man City vs Newcastle live streams from anywhere in the world as home side looks to close the gap at the top of the Premier League.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Leigh Wood vs Josh Warrington 2: live stream boxing rematch online</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/boxing/leigh-wood-vs-josh-warrington-2</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CJhmK56g7vUvBKFUL4gzsh</guid>
      <description>See how to watch Leigh Wood vs Josh Warrington 2 live streams online, as the Leeds Warrior looks to avenge surprise defeat to Leigh-thal in this massive rematch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13-hour AWS outage reportedly caused by Amazon's own AI tools</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/13-hour-aws-outage-reportedly-caused-by-amazons-own-ai-tools-170930190.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a17f916d-18e0-47e3-939e-e9e6a677cbb7</guid>
      <description>A recent Amazon Web Services (AWS) outage that lasted 13 hours was reportedly caused by one of its own AI tools, according to reporting by Financial Times. This happened in December after engineers deployed the Kiro AI coding tool to make certain changes, say four people familiar with the matter.
Kiro is an agentic tool, meaning it can take autonomous actions on behalf of users. In this case, the bot reportedly determined that it needed to "delete and recreate the environment." This is what allegedly led to the lengthy outage that primarily impacted China.
Amazon says it was merely a "coincide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia says Elon Musk&#8217;s America PAC violated election law</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/882838/georgia-elon-musk-america-pac-voter-fraud</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-21T11:55:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882838</guid>
      <description>For all his bluster about voter fraud, Elon Musk has been one of the most flagrant flaunters of US election law. Now his America PAC has been slapped with a reprimand by the Georgia State Election Board for sending out pre-filled absentee ballot applications. State law prohibits anyone, other than an authorized relative, from sending [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
