<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:26:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Hurst cast as Kratos for live-action God of War show</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/ryan-hurst-cast-as-kratos-for-live-action-god-of-war-show-211655396.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c4ada36-d4aa-42b3-a369-27c1e0f7d547</guid>
      <description>Amazon's upcoming God of War live-action TV adaptation has cast Ryan Hurst as its Kratos. Sony announced the casting today on X with a brief post and an image of both Hurst and Kratos in full scowl mode. Hurst is already sporting a very Kratos-style beard, so he's already got the right vibe going for him. He has past credits on familiar shows such as Sons of Anarchy and The Walking Dead. The upcoming Amazon series also isn't his first rodeo acting in this universe; Hurst voiced Thor in the video game God of War Ragnarok. But the most important question with this casting news is whether Hurst w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>In a chaotic world, one thing you can count on is your own common-sense steps toward better cybersecurity. January is a great time to grab a subscription for yourself or a loved one, as a few holiday sales are (inexplicably) still happening. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart online trackers.
We strongly recommend using a VPN, but you might get stuck with a substandard app if you jump on the very first deal you see. You might also mistakenly end up paying more than you want...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Launches Investigation Into Grok&#8217;s Nonconsensual Sexual Images</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/california-investigation-grok-xai-nudes-attorney-general-2000710374</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710374</guid>
      <description>The AG said that "the avalanche of reports detailing the non-consensual, sexually explicit material that xAI has produced" is shocking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network appears to be having technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Verizon customers on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even the network provider&#8217;s own status page struggled to load, likely due to the number of customers trying to access it.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally, at least for some users. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started grow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming Just Greenlit America&#8217;s Largest Data Center Project, and Locals Are Bracing for Impact</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wyoming-just-greenlit-americas-largest-data-center-project-and-locals-are-bracing-for-impact-2000710447</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710447</guid>
      <description>The commissioners of Laramie County, Wyoming, unanimously voted to build a data center campus that will be designed to scale to 10 gigawatts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Just Absolutely Gutted the Best Part of Quest VR Headsets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meta-just-absolutely-gutted-the-best-part-of-quest-vr-headsets-2000710320</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710320</guid>
      <description>It is, once again, a very bad moment for VR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Z.ai's open source GLM-Image beats Google's Nano Banana Pro at complex text rendering, but not aesthetics</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/z-ais-open-source-glm-image-beats-googles-nano-banana-pro-at-complex-text</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nmLS5k44rJC3ykgyQRjMW</guid>
      <description>The two big stories of AI in 2026 so far have been the incredible rise in usage and praise for Anthropic's Claude Code and a similar huge boost in user adoption for Google's Gemini 3 AI model family released late last year &#8212; the latter of which includes Nano Banana Pro (also known as Gemini 3 Pro Image), a powerful, fast, and flexible image generation model that renders complex, text-heavy infographics quickly and accurately, making it an excellent fit for enterprise use (think: collateral, trainings, onboarding, stationary, etc).But of course, both of those are proprietary offerings. And yet,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s first original video podcasts feature Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/netflixs-first-original-video-podcasts-feature-pete-davidson-and-michael-irvin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082820</guid>
      <description>As Netflix tries to take down YouTube&#8217;s dominance in the podcast space, it's getting new originals with Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon didn&#8217;t have to go far to find its live-action Kratos</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/862089/god-of-war-kratos-casting-amazone-prime-video</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T15:47:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862089</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced the first cast member of its God of War live-action adaptation on Prime Video. Ryan Hurst, known for his work as Opie in Sons of Anarchy and Beta in The Walking Dead, will play the titular God of War, Kratos. Though the casting might come as a bit of a disappointment to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Being Marketed Like This?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-is-avengers-doomsday-being-marketed-like-this-2000706181</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706181</guid>
      <description>Marvel's been doling out 'Avengers: Doomsday' info in two different ways, and they both tell us what the film's ambitions are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even AI skeptic Linus Torvalds is getting involved in 'vibe coding' - so could this herald a new dawn for Linux? Probably not...</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/even-ai-skeptic-linus-torvalds-is-getting-involved-in-vibe-coding-so-could-this-herald-a-new-dawn-for-linux-probably-not</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hm6mf83BHE7sAJ2Ufoqi7h</guid>
      <description>Torvalds says he briefly used AI for a hobby project, reinforcing pragmatic limits, skepticism toward hype, and caution around critical software development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX offers free Starlink access to Iranian demonstrators amid Internet blackout</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474999/starlink-spacex-iran-free-internet</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:34:10</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474999/starlink-spacex-iran-free-internet</guid>
      <description>Starlink is banned in Iran by telecommunication regulations.
Iranian demonstrators&#8217; ability to get details of&#160;bloody nationwide protests&#160;out to the world has been given a strong boost, with SpaceX&#8217;s Starlink satellite internet service dropping its fees to allow more people to circumvent the Tehran government&#8217;s strongest attempt ever to prevent information from spilling outside its borders, activists said Wednesday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization VII comes to Apple Arcade in February</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/civilization-vii-comes-to-apple-arcade-in-february-203000754.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c585f358-08d1-4793-ad2a-3ea102210515</guid>
      <description>The App Store is a home for many kinds of apps (including, inexplicably, one that lets users undress strangers without their consent). But hey, it also has games! And soon the store's Apple Arcade service will include one more: the not-so-highly rated Civilization VII.Apple announced on Wednesday that Sid Meier's Civilization VII will arrive almost exactly a year after launch. The game is already available for Apple devices, but its arrival on Apple Arcade will be a first.Civilization VII arrives on Apple Arcade on February 5.Firaxis Games / Apple&#8220;Free (for Apple Arcade subscribers)&#8221; may be th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilt 2.0&#8217;s low-interest premium card takes on Chase Sapphire Reserve&#8212;with mortgage and rent rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474985/bilt-credit-card-2-0-new-premium-rewards-for-mortgage-rent-low-interest-rate-loyalty-points-perks-chase-sapphire-reserve</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474985/bilt-credit-card-2-0-new-premium-rewards-for-mortgage-rent-low-interest-rate-loyalty-points-perks-chase-sapphire-reserve</guid>
      <description>Bilt is shaking up the credit card rewards race with a new offering&#8212;but the points system is complicated. Here&#8217;s what to know.
As Americans struggle with an affordability crisis&#8212;high inflation and an even higher cost of living, especially when it comes to housing&#8212;Bilt is launching three new, low interest credit cards with rates capped at 10% on new purchases for the first year&#8212;including a premium card offering with a $495 annual fee....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California is investigating Grok over AI-generated CSAM and nonconsensual deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/california-is-investigating-grok-over-ai-generated-csam-and-nonconsensual-deepfakes-202029635.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afc82bf8-c680-4d61-bc55-e26654ca4424</guid>
      <description>California authorities have launched an investigation into xAI following weeks of reports that the chatbot was generating sexualized images of children. "xAI appears to be facilitating the large-scale production of deepfake nonconsensual intimate images that are being used to harass women and girls across the internet, including via the social media platform X," California Attorney General Rob Bonta's office said in a statement.&#160;The statement cited a report that "more than half of the 20,000 images generated by xAI between Christmas and New Years depicted people in minimal clothing," including...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When PC Memory Prices Are Too Much to Handle?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/what-happens-when-pc-memory-prices-are-too-much-to-handle-2000710305</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710305</guid>
      <description>The world's largest PC maker tells us why the next PC you buy may be more premium or less powerful than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla puts full self-driving behind a monthly paywall</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474691/tesla-puts-full-self-driving-behind-a-monthly-paywall</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474691/tesla-puts-full-self-driving-behind-a-monthly-paywall</guid>
      <description>Drivers will now need to subscribe monthly to access Tesla&#8217;s most advanced driver-assistance features.
If you&#8217;re sick of paying for subscription services, Tesla has some bad news for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies confess their agentic AI goals aren't really working out - and a lack of trust could be why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/companies-confess-their-agentic-ai-goals-arent-really-working-out-and-a-lack-of-trust-could-be-why</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bohwdMrggYUpmCNDJ5eWaH</guid>
      <description>Many companies are still operating AI agents in silos &#8211; a lack of trust could be preventing them from setting it free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientists Decipher Procrastination: A Brain Mechanism Explains Why People Leave Certain Tasks for Later</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/neuroscience-procrastination-brain-mechanism-task-avoidance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967dd15685933202e631c14</guid>
      <description>New research has discovered that a neural circuit may explain procrastination. Scientists were able to disrupt this connection using a drug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save up to 78 percent on ExpressVPN two-year plans right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/save-up-to-78-percent-on-expressvpn-two-year-plans-right-now-180602838.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $101 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.59 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App downloads declined again in 2025, but consumer spending soared to nearly $156B</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/app-downloads-declined-again-in-2025-but-consumer-spending-soared-to-nearly-156b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082733</guid>
      <description>Global app downloads were down, but consumer spending was up to nearly $156B in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX Hit by Another Workplace Injury Lawsuit, This Time Over Falling Debris in an Elevator Shaft</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spacex-hit-by-another-workplace-injury-lawsuit-this-time-over-falling-debris-in-an-elevator-shaft-2000710249</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710249</guid>
      <description>The rocket company&#8217;s safety record continues to fall short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Apple&#8217;s new Creator Studio actually for?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474571/who-is-apple-creator-studio-subscription-for</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474571/who-is-apple-creator-studio-subscription-for</guid>
      <description>Too complex for the Canva crowd, and too lightweight for Adobe users, Apple&#8217;s Creator Studio subscription straddles an challenging middle ground.
Apple was the last champion of the &#8220;pay once, own forever&#8221; crowd, a safe harbor for some of the creatives fleeing Adobe&#8217;s monthly ransom. Now it has introduced Creator Studio, its own subscription-based offering that bundles together tools including Final Cut Pro, Logic Pro, Pixelmator Pro, Motion, Compressor, and MainStage (as well as newly AI-infused productivity apps like Pages and Numbers)....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why &#8220;becoming Chinese&#8221; is taking over social media</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474875/why-becoming-chinese-is-taking-over-social-media</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474875/why-becoming-chinese-is-taking-over-social-media</guid>
      <description>If your TikTok For You Page has recently shifted to videos of people boiling apples and shuffling around in house slippers, here&#8217;s why.
&#8220;I see a bunch of Americans drinking hot water with lemon and honey, eating congee, drinking hot pot, drinking more soup, eating Chinese vegetables,&#8221; one Chinese creator, Emma Peng, recently shared in a TikTok, currently with over 3 million views. &#8220;I just want to say that my culture can be your culture. You&#8217;re doing really good hydrating yourself. I&#8217;m proud of you.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilt&#8217;s new credit cards to feature 10% interest rate, answering lawmakers&#8217; pleas</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474989/bilt-credit-cards-10-percent-interest-rate-cap</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T19:57:02</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474989/bilt-credit-cards-10-percent-interest-rate-cap</guid>
      <description>Bilt CEO Ankur Jain said the company was deciding to cap its interest rates on credit cards for one year to meet the &#8216;bipartisan call for a solution&#8217; on affordability.
Silicon Valley fintech giant Bilt announced an overhaul of its credit cards on Wednesday, which notably will include an introductory rate on all card users&#8217; interest rates at 10% for one year....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Big on One of Our Favorite Desk Lamps from Lume Cube</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/lume-edge-light-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967d577585d9a70fc535832</guid>
      <description>Lume Cube has a variety of marked-down lighting products to help revamp your home office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop exporting stress and build a workplace people enjoy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475101/stop-exporting-stress-and-build-a-workplace-people-enjoy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T19:41:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475101/stop-exporting-stress-and-build-a-workplace-people-enjoy</guid>
      <description>The biggest performance unlock wasn&#8217;t a new tool or process, but learning to regulate my emotional state. You can stop that leak in your leadership, too.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Marty Supreme&#8217; Almost Ended With an Actual Vampire</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marty-supreme-almost-ended-with-an-actual-vampire-2000710371</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710371</guid>
      <description>The award-winning Timoth&#233;e Chalamet movie mentions vampires&#8212;but at one point, the script went even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMW says electric M3 will be a &#8216;new level&#8217; of performance</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861955/bmw-m3-electric-ev-quad-motor-neue-klasse</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T14:30:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861955</guid>
      <description>BMW teased its forthcoming all-electric M-series performance sedan today, promising that the quad-motor M3 sports car would feature specs that are truly next level when it arrives in 2027. The M3 will have four electric motors and simulated gear shifting, a feature that is quickly becoming a must-have for electrified sports cars. BMW says the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve tested 30 smart locks, and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23393163/best-smart-door-lock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T14:27:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23393163/best-smart-door-lock</guid>
      <description>A smart lock is an easy solution to some common problems. Locked yourself out? Need to let a friend in to water the plants? Your latchkey kid lost their key? Hands are full, and it&#8217;s raining cats and dogs? A smart lock solves all of these problems and more. One of the best smart home [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
