<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:39:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Channel your inner Leon S Kennedy with this slick limited edition Resident Evil Requiem watch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/channel-your-inner-leon-s-kennedy-with-this-slick-limited-edition-resident-evil-requiem-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saXNZLieLyiL3VzMz7fAMn</guid>
      <description>$2,000+ might be a lot for a limited edition watch, but this Resi timepiece is pure quality with some great detail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD CPU users beware - this security flaw could spill all your secrets</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/amd-cpu-users-beware-this-security-flaw-could-spill-all-your-secrets</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3aDSsafWNj2e5LJQNyAKHT</guid>
      <description>AMD gave the bug a low severity score and released a fix, so update now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Sarandos says Netflix will commit to 45-day theatrical releases</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/863511/ted-sarandos-netflix-theatrical-movie-release-windows</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:24:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863511</guid>
      <description>Though Netflix's plan to buy Warner Bros. Discovery has prompted concerns about how the deal might hurt the movie theater business, the streamer's co-CEO says that there is nothing to worry about. In a new interview with The New York Times, Netflix co-CEO Ted Sarandos said that, should the WBD acquisition go through, the streamer [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Creator on Working With George R.R. Martin</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-creator-on-working-with-george-r-r-martin-2000710370</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710370</guid>
      <description>Ira Parker says that collaborating with the 'Game of Thrones' author on their new HBO series has been a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads Are Coming to ChatGPT. Here&#8217;s How They&#8217;ll Work</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-testing-ads-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6969b129d6ddbc660392573b</guid>
      <description>OpenAI says ads will not influence ChatGPT&#8217;s responses, and that it won&#8217;t sell user data to advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads are coming soon to ChatGPT, starting with shopping links</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863428/openai-chatgpt-shopping-ads-test</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863428</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT will soon start showing you sponsored products or services if they're related to your conversation. In an announcement on Friday, OpenAI says it will start testing ads in the coming weeks for logged-in users in the US who use the app for free or have a ChatGPT Go subscription. The "clearly labeled" ads will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases a cheaper ChatGPT subscription</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863466/openai-chatgpt-go-global-release</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863466</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is expanding a low-cost subscription tier called ChatGPT Go to the US and the rest of the world. Go was released in India in August and later became available in another 170 countries prior to Friday's global release. "In markets where Go has been available, we've seen strong adoption and regular everyday use for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PlayStation Portal was my gaming savior over an extended holiday break &#8212; but this one flaw still grinds my thumbsticks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/ps5/the-playstation-portal-was-my-gaming-savior-over-an-extended-holiday-break-but-this-one-flaw-still-grinds-my-thumbsticks</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qHa3WUX8uArasXALNUjzAi</guid>
      <description>I have always enjoyed the PlayStation Portal and sung its praises as often as I can, but its slow-charging battery is a real drawback and became apparent when relying on the device over the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye cheap OLED TVs &#8212; you had a good run, but RGB mini-LED and &#8216;wallpaper&#8217; OLEDs will soon make you irrelevant</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/goodbye-cheap-oled-tvs-you-had-a-good-run-but-rgb-mini-led-and-wallpaper-oleds-will-soon-make-you-irrelevant</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fueC9ULzRtBgJtbw9ESUgE</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, it was clear that OLED TV makers are shifting focus to higher-end, design-forward models. Meanwhile, RGB mini-LED is coming to smaller screen sizes to challenge OLED's dominance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many words per minute can you read? Find out now</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476036/how-many-words-per-minute-can-you-read-find-out-now</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476036/how-many-words-per-minute-can-you-read-find-out-now</guid>
      <description>Your brain slips into a different mode when taking on this viral speed-reading challenge on X.
Put down Wordle. New brain-exercise-for-the-day just dropped.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Reddit, TikTok, and AI are changing the game for substance&#160;use researchers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474911/reddit-tiktok-ai-changing-the-game-substance-use-researchers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:59:58</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474911/reddit-tiktok-ai-changing-the-game-substance-use-researchers</guid>
      <description>Advances in artificial intelligence are helping make sense of these conversations at a scale that wasn&#8217;t possible before.
When you think of tools for studying substance use and addiction, a social media site like Reddit, TikTok, or YouTube probably isn&#8217;t the first thing that comes to mind. Yet the stories shared on social media platforms are offering unprecedented insights into the world of substance use....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z travelers want destinations that haven&#8217;t been spoiled by Instagram. These cities are topping the list</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475874/gen-z-travelers-want-destinations-that-havent-been-spoiled-by-instagram-these-cities-are-topping-the-list</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:55:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475874/gen-z-travelers-want-destinations-that-havent-been-spoiled-by-instagram-these-cities-are-topping-the-list</guid>
      <description>Vacation goals are changing for younger generations as travel-related content has flooded social media and worsened an overtourism crisis. 
Big city or small town? Tourist trap or undiscovered sights? Following an itinerary or spontaneous exploring?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mova Rover Master : j&#8217;ai vu le robot de piscine du futur qui a un bras articul&#233; pour servir l&#8217;ap&#233;ro</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mova/2946081_mova-rover-master-jai-vu-le-robot-de-piscine-du-futur-qui-a-un-bras-articule-pour-servir-lapero</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mova/2946081_mova-rover-master-jai-vu-le-robot-de-piscine-du-futur-qui-a-un-bras-articule-pour-servir-lapero</guid>
      <description>
Mova ne s'arr&#234;te plus. Apr&#232;s son robot aspirateur volant, la spin-off de Dreame profite du CES 2026 pour d&#233;voiler un prototype de robot de piscine pour le moins audacieux. &#201;quip&#233; d'un bras bionique articul&#233;, il ramasse jouets &#233;gar&#233;s et peut m&#234;me transporter vos boissons dans la piscine.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh No, Meta Just Killed Off Working in VR</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oh-no-meta-just-killed-off-working-in-vr-2000711072</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711072</guid>
      <description>The VR dream is dead, but AR glasses may still force us to work two inches from our screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada cuts tariffs on Chinese EVs as part of new deal</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/canada-cuts-tariffs-on-chinese-evs-as-part-of-new-deal-174241990.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95e68105-d4e2-4897-ac41-f9408ab08251</guid>
      <description>Canada has agreed to drastically reduce its tariffs on imported Chinese EVs from 100 percent to 6.1 percent as part of a new deal between the two countries. In return, China will be reducing tariffs on Canadian canola seeds from 84 percent to about 15 percent.
The move is a break from the United States, which maintains a 100 percent tariff on EVs from China, effectively banning them in the country. Mexico currently tariffs the vehicles at 50 percent after increasing its rate last year.
Under the agreement, which Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney called "preliminary," Canada will allow up to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want more people to use public transit? Make it safer</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469963/want-more-people-to-use-public-transit-make-it-safer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:36:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469963/want-more-people-to-use-public-transit-make-it-safer</guid>
      <description>When people don&#8217;t feel secure, they opt out.
If a City is going to operate a multimodal transportation system, then it helps to understand the motivations of people who continue to choose personal cars for their short trips.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Ask SEC to Explain Lack of Enforcement on Trump-Linked Crypto Entities</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/democrats-ask-sec-to-explain-lack-of-enforcement-on-trump-linked-crypto-entities-2000711123</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711123</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Given the industry&#8217;s history of investor-harm... this turn raises troubling questions about the SEC&#8217;s priorities and effectiveness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Huawei Pura 80 Ultra : ses incroyables aptitudes en photo compensent-elles ses nombreuses faiblesses ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/huawei/2859125_test-huawei-pura-80-ultra-ses-incroyables-aptitudes-en-photo-compensent-elles-ses-nombreuses-faiblesses</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/huawei/2859125_test-huawei-pura-80-ultra-ses-incroyables-aptitudes-en-photo-compensent-elles-ses-nombreuses-faiblesses</guid>
      <description>
Avec son capteur de 1 pouce et ses deux t&#233;l&#233;objectifs, ce nouveau Pura Ultra peut-il faire oublier le fait que Huawei ne puisse pas avoir acc&#232;s &#224; une puce Qualcomm, &#224; la 5G et aux applications et services Google ? Pas s&#251;r, compte tenu de son prix tr&#232;s &#233;lev&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X has been down for most of the morning</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/x-has-been-down-for-most-of-the-morning-171843527.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">814237b9-63ca-4ae5-9c95-a454783a5e0b</guid>
      <description>X is still struggling with an outage that has intermittently taken the service offline and made it slow to load for much of the morning. According to X&#8217;s developer platform page,  there is an ongoing incident related to streaming endpoints that&#8217;s caused increased errors. The incident started at 7:39AM PT, according to the page.That roughly coincides with a spike in reports at Down Detector. The issues seems to be somewhat intermittent. At some points, X&#8217;s website has loaded partially and only shown older posts. At other times, the app and website have failed to load at all. As of 9:30AM PT, X&#8217;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After today&#8217;s big memory upgrade, ChatGPT can now remember conversations from a year ago, and link you directly to them</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/after-todays-big-memory-upgrade-chatgpt-can-now-remember-conversations-from-a-year-ago-and-link-you-directly-to-them</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5WAGZJ45crKWBdyiUT9Xxg</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT&#8217;s new memory upgrade lets Plus and Pro users instantly revisit conversations from a year ago &#8212; complete with direct links to the original chats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quand Google cesse d&#8217;envoyer des lecteurs aux sites web</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/quand-google-cesse-denvoyer-des-lecteurs-aux-sites-web.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320788</guid>
      <description>Google a beau s&#8217;en d&#233;fendre, le constat est sans appel : le moteur de recherche renvoie de moins en moins de trafic vers les sites web. En cause, notamment, ses r&#233;sum&#233;s g&#233;n&#233;r&#233;s par intelligence artificielle, qui fournissent des r&#233;ponses sans n&#233;cessiter le moindre clic. En coulisses, les &#233;diteurs prennent acte de cette &#233;rosion et tentent, tant bien que mal, de pr&#233;parer un avenir o&#249; Google ne sera plus un passage oblig&#233;....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest Legend of Zelda Lego set pays tribute to Ocarina of Time's final battle</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/the-latest-legend-of-zelda-lego-set-pays-tribute-to-ocarina-of-times-final-battle-172212137.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">481fc99a-94b1-4315-887f-9d174d1c4593</guid>
      <description>We already knew something Ocarina of Time-related was coming from Nintendo and Lego in 2026, and now we know exactly what that set will look like. Weighing in at a surprisingly modest 1,003 pieces, the typically word salad-y Lego The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time - The Final Battle is the second Lego Zelda set, following the 2,500-piece Great Deku Tree set in 2024.
While the latter lets you choose between building either a Breath of the Wild or OoT-themed replica of the wise old guardian of the forest, the upcoming set is aimed squarely at fans of the series&#8217; debut 3D outing. As you can pro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesses are struggling to achieve AI success - this report reveals why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/businesses-are-struggling-to-achieve-ai-success-this-report-reveals-why</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kNkR95jb2XydwtneoxzNxA</guid>
      <description>Many businesses are reporting setbacks and even failures &#8211; cloud and simplification are just two of the solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a hacking campaign targeted high-profile Gmail and WhatsApp users across the Middle East</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/how-a-hacking-campaign-targeted-high-profile-gmail-and-whatsapp-users-across-the-middle-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083348</guid>
      <description>The phishing campaign targeted users on WhatsApp, including an Iranian-British activist, and stole the credentials of a Lebanese cabinet minister and at least one journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinemark will fill almost anything with popcorn this weekend&#8212;but there&#8217;s a catch</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476342/cinemark-will-fill-almost-anything-with-popcorn-this-weekend-but-theres-a-catch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476342/cinemark-will-fill-almost-anything-with-popcorn-this-weekend-but-theres-a-catch</guid>
      <description>For $5, customers can fill nearly any container with popcorn&#8212;up to a generous size limit.
If you&#8217;re planning to hit up a movie over the long weekend, you&#8217;re in luck. Going to the theater will be a bit cheaper for two days, as long as you believe popcorn is a must-have movie accessory.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X is still having issues following an hour-long outage on Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863425/x-twitter-outage-january-16th-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T12:09:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863425</guid>
      <description>On Friday morning, X and Grok went offline for users around the world on both the websites and apps. Outage reports began spiking on DownDetector around 10:00AM ET, while Cisco's ThousandEyes outage map noted over 600 X servers around the world that were having problems. Attempts to load the site with either the Twitter.com or [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok sued by former workers over alleged union-busting</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/tiktok-sued-by-former-workers-over-alleged-union-busting-170446921.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16c8dbff-af18-4b78-abc2-8c21cd1bf9c0</guid>
      <description>You know things are messed up when a Big Tech company fights accusations of union-busting by insisting it was only AI layoffs. That's where things stand after a group of fired TikTok moderators in the UK filed a legal claim with an employment tribunal. The Guardian reported on Friday that around 400 TikTok content moderators who were unionizing were laid off before Christmas.The workers were sacked a week before a vote was scheduled to establish a collective bargaining unit. The moderators said they wanted better protection against the personal toll of processing traumatic content at a high sp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung : quand les promotions des soldes cassent les prix des Galaxy S, Galaxy Book, Galaxy Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2939747_samsung-quand-les-promotions-des-soldes-cassent-les-prix-des-galaxy-s-galaxy-book-galaxy-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2939747_samsung-quand-les-promotions-des-soldes-cassent-les-prix-des-galaxy-s-galaxy-book-galaxy-watch</guid>
      <description>
La deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque des soldes apporte son lot de nouvelles offres Samsung&#8239;! Et &#224; l&#8217;approche du week-end, c&#8217;est le moment id&#233;al pour saisir les meilleurs deals du g&#233;ant sud-cor&#233;en. Entre TV QLED &#233;l&#233;gants, smartphones &#224; clapet et &#233;crans Ultra Wide OLED, il y en a pour tous les go&#251;ts &#8212; avec, en vedette, un vid&#233;oprojecteur affichant plus de 60&#8239;% de remise&#8239;!
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#8217;s Talk About the Ending of &#8217;28 Years Later: The Bone Temple&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/28-years-later-bone-temple-ending-explained-2000709797</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709797</guid>
      <description>Ralph Fiennes and Jack O'Connell star in the second of three '28 Years Later' sequels, now in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willpower will fail you. Systems are the real secret to winning at work and life</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475190/willpower-will-fail-you-systems-real-secret-winning-at-work-life</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:00:19</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475190/willpower-will-fail-you-systems-real-secret-winning-at-work-life</guid>
      <description>They take away unnecessary mental decisions and make good habits stick.
I told myself I won&#8217;t check emails until I check off my &#8220;one thing&#8221; to do for the day. I couldn&#8217;t do it. I always reach for the phone in the morning. Willpower wasn&#8217;t enough. The brain is wired to take the path of least resistance. Fighting it every day with willpower won&#8217;t work. These days I use systems. I work with rituals. I get my most important tasks (MIT) done between 9 a.m. and 12 p.m....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : voici les meilleure offres pour ce week-end de 2e d&#233;marque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-offres-week-end-2e-demarque</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-offres-week-end-2e-demarque</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver suivent leur chemin et nous arrivons au d&#233;j&#224; au deuxi&#232;me week-end ! Au programme : toujours plus d'offres Tech &#224; prix cass&#233;s, que ce soient les smartphones, les tablettes, les t&#233;l&#233;viseurs 4K, et surtout les ordinateurs portables, gaming ou de bureautique. M&#234;me le gaming s'invite avec la PS5 en promo. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs ordinateurs portables grand format de 16, 17 et 18 pouces en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-ordinateurs/1044735_meilleurs-pc-portables-17-pouces-comparatif</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-ordinateurs/1044735_meilleurs-pc-portables-17-pouces-comparatif</guid>
      <description>
Les ordinateurs portables de 16 et 18 pouces offrent une exp&#233;rience visuelle immersive et un espace de travail optimis&#233;.  Vous cherchez un mod&#232;le de grand laptop adapt&#233; ? D&#233;couvrez notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs PC portables grand format pour faire le bon choix. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Pixel Watch pourrait sauver votre journ&#233;e gr&#226;ce &#224; cette nouvelle alerte</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2945499_pixel-watch-cette-nouvelle-fonctionnalite-dalerte-pourrait-bien-sauver-votre-journee</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2945499_pixel-watch-cette-nouvelle-fonctionnalite-dalerte-pourrait-bien-sauver-votre-journee</guid>
      <description>
Google travaillerait &#224; une nouvelle fonction d'alerte sur ses montres Pixel Watch. Elle permettrait de pr&#233;venir l'utilisateur lorsqu'il s'&#233;loigne trop de son smartphone et risque de l'oublier. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man&#8217;s Switch to Keto Diet Triggers Bizarre, Rare Rash</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mans-switch-to-keto-diet-triggers-bizarre-rare-rash-2000711067</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711067</guid>
      <description>Only around 300 cases of so-called "keto rash" have been documented worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger multiplie les r&#233;ductions durant les soldes : les 16 deals &#224; saisir ce weeke-end</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-multiplie-les-reductions-durant-les-soldes-les-14-deals-a-saisir-ce-weeke-end</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-multiplie-les-reductions-durant-les-soldes-les-14-deals-a-saisir-ce-weeke-end</guid>
      <description>
&#192; l&#8217;occasion du week-end de la deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque des soldes, Boulanger propose de belles offres pour se faire plaisir. L&#8217;enseigne affiche d&#8217;importantes r&#233;ductions sur les smartphones haut de gamme, comme l&#8217;ancien flagship de Google ou le r&#233;cent milieu de gamme de Xiaomi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du REKT Shogun 68 : ce clavier est vendu comme un Wooting pas cher</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/peripheriques-pc/clavier/2945715_test-du-rekt-shogun-68-ce-clavier-est-vendu-comme-un-wooting-pas-cher</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/peripheriques-pc/clavier/2945715_test-du-rekt-shogun-68-ce-clavier-est-vendu-comme-un-wooting-pas-cher</guid>
      <description>
Pourquoi payer 190 &#8364; quand on peut avoir le Rapid Trigger pour 99 &#8364; ? 8000 Hz, activation &#224; 0,01 mm, switchs magn&#233;tiques Amber Pro... on a test&#233; le REKT Hiro 60.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscience just showed how 1 type of activity stops your brain from aging</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476338/neuroscience-just-showed-1-type-activity-stops-your-brain-aging</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T16:47:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476338/neuroscience-just-showed-1-type-activity-stops-your-brain-aging</guid>
      <description>You might think it&#8217;s just a hobby. It&#8217;s also a powerful tool for brain health.
How can you&#160;keep your brain agile&#160;and young throughout your life, even as you get older? By spending time on creative pursuits as often as you can. That&#8217;s the fascinating finding of a&#160;study&#160;by researchers from Universidad Adolfo Ib&#225;&#241;ez in Chile and Trinity College in Ireland, among others....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audible deal: Three months of access is only $3 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/audible-deal-three-months-of-access-is-only-3-right-now-193859977.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>One way to read more in the new year is to incorporate audiobooks as part of your reading habit. Audible is having a sale right now that makes that easier and cheaper to do: you can get three months of access for only $1 per month, or a total of $3. The promotion runs through January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated tit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada is going to start importing Chinese EVs &#8212; will the US follow?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/863393/canada-china-ev-import-trade-deal-us-trump-tariffs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T11:43:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863393</guid>
      <description>Is the North American blockade on Chinese EVs softening? Today, Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney announced a deal with China to slash tariffs on electric vehicles in exchange for lowering duties on canola products. Canada will initially allow up to 49,000 Chinese EVs at a 6.1 percent tariff, Carney said, though the exact timeline was [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600,000 Trump Mobile phones sold? There&amp;#8217;s no proof.</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/863381/trump-mobile-viral-preorder-figures-600000</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T11:41:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863381</guid>
      <description>Where's the Trump phone? We're going to keep talking about it every week. We've reached out, as usual, to ask about the Trump phone's whereabouts. As usual, we're still waiting for a response. In the meantime, some impressive alleged sales figures have gone viral - but they might be too good to be true. This [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you &#8216;grounded&#8217; or in a rut in your career? &#8216;Stable&#8217; or stuck?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470828/are-you-grounded-or-in-a-rut-in-your-career-stable-or-stuck</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T16:40:55</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470828/are-you-grounded-or-in-a-rut-in-your-career-stable-or-stuck</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s how to tell the difference&#8212;and what to do about it.
For a long time, I told myself I was choosing stability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fnac Darty lance une grande braderie pour le week-end de la 2e d&#233;marque des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-darty-lance-une-grande-braderie-pour-le-week-end-de-la-2e-demarque-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-darty-lance-une-grande-braderie-pour-le-week-end-de-la-2e-demarque-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Le week-end approche, et Fnac et Darty passent &#224; la vitesse sup&#233;rieure pour la deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque des soldes&#8239;! Les deux enseignes cassent encore les prix sur des produits d&#233;j&#224; en promo&#8239;: laptop &#224; double &#233;cran &#224; prix mini, Apple Watch en baisse, trottinette Xiaomi encore plus abordable&#8230; C&#8217;est le bon moment pour craquer avant la fin des stocks&#8239;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Getting Filthy Rich season 4 online &#8211; free stream, release date</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/watch-getting-filthy-rich-season-4-online</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9o9kJ27LPPKiiZZE239Jv4</guid>
      <description>Olivia Attwood: Getting Filthy Rich returns to our screens for its third series. Read here for how to watch Olivia Attwood: Getting Filthy Rich season 4 online and free from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
