<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:29:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel&#8217;s Grand &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Plans Have Started Hitting the Web</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avengers-doomsday-trailer-leak-reveal-chris-evans-2000699881</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699881</guid>
      <description>A leaked teaser trailer seemingly reveals that another major Avenger is making their return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korean AI startup Motif reveals 4 big lessons for training enterprise LLMs</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/korean-ai-startup-motif-reveals-4-big-lessons-for-training-enterprise-llms</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2YOQ8cBbgujbHn8uvhmJKu</guid>
      <description>We've heard (and written, here at VentureBeat) lots about the generative AI race between the U.S. and China, as those have been the countries with the groups most active in fielding new models (with a shoutout to Cohere in Canada and Mistral in France). But now a Korean startup is making waves: last week, the firm known as Motif Technologies released Motif-2-12.7B-Reasoning, another small parameter open-weight model that boasts impressive benchmark scores, quickly becoming the most performant model from that country according to independent benchmarking lab Artificial Analysis (beating even re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's surprising stealth superfast SSD surfaces silently &#8212; PM9E1 turns out to be a mini-9100 Pro measuring just 22 x 42mm with PCIe Gen5 capabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/samsungs-surprising-stealth-superfast-ssd-surfaces-silently-pm9e1-turns-out-to-be-a-mini-9100-pro-measuring-just-22-x-42mm-with-pcie-gen5-capabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uqMmKaSCWLsLZbfVhd3tqD</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s PM9E1 combines PCIe Gen5 speeds with an ultra-compact form factor, highlighting technical progress while exposing practical limits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie's Marathon will arrive on PS5 and PC in March</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/bungies-marathon-will-arrive-on-ps5-and-pc-in-march-200838462.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e26e2f94-5e0c-47a6-9b5b-4d01b9612966</guid>
      <description>
Bungie&#8217;s Marathon has a new release window. The survival extraction shooter was originally set to hit PlayStation 5 and PC in September, but by June, Sony had delayed it indefinitely. Now, with a plagiarism issue largely in the rearview mirror, Bungie has confirmed that Marathon will arrive in March and and plans to sell it for $40.
Alongside the release date and price announcement, Bungie released a 23-minute video that takes a deep dive into the game and shows off the current state of Marathon. New features include proximity chat and a solo mode, while Bungie says it has upgraded the enviro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors are Using the Same Tool as &#8216;The Big Short&#8217; Guys to Hedge Against an AI Bubble</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/investors-are-using-the-same-tool-as-the-big-short-guys-to-hedge-against-an-ai-bubble-2000699860</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699860</guid>
      <description>That's a good sign, right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christianity May Have Brought Face Tattoos to Medieval Nubia</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/christianity-may-have-brought-face-tattoos-to-medieval-nubia-2000699441</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699441</guid>
      <description>Researchers traced tattoos across hundreds of human remains from northeastern Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Freston&#8217;s new memoir shows how a &#8216;bebop lifestyle&#8217; can lead to success</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460800/tom-freston-memoir-unplugged</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:59:18</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460800/tom-freston-memoir-unplugged</guid>
      <description>He hopes readers, especially younger ones, appreciate the musical notes of his life and apply it to their own.
Tom Freston could easily fill a book with stories from the formative days of MTV and his celebrity encounters &#8212; Bono would merit a few chapters on his own. Ultimately, though, Freston feels that his life has a more valuable lesson to offer....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merriam-Webster names &#8216;slop&#8217; the word of the year</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/merriam-webster-names-slop-the-word-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075979</guid>
      <description>AI-generated content has dominated the internet over the past year, and America's dictionary took note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;It: Welcome to Derry&#8217; Star Taylour Paige Wasn&#8217;t Happy With Her Character&#8217;s Big Choice</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/it-welcome-to-derry-star-taylour-paige-wasnt-happy-with-her-characters-big-choice-2000699800</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699800</guid>
      <description>The Stephen King adaptation wrapped up its first season on HBO last night with plenty of mayhem and a few plot contortions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Connecticut became a hot spot for Hallmark holiday movie fans</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460788/connecticut-hallmark-holiday-movies-fans-tours</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:33:08</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460788/connecticut-hallmark-holiday-movies-fans-tours</guid>
      <description>Connecticut&#8217;s Christmas Movie Trail is part of a multipronged rebranding effort.
&#8220;Christmas at Pemberley Manor&#8221; and &#8220;Romance at Reindeer Lodge&#8221; may never make it to Oscar night, but legions of fans still love these sweet-yet-predictable holiday movies&#8212;and this season, many are making pilgrimages to where their favorite scenes were filmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI&#8217;s $16 trillion problem: It still isn&#8217;t working on the factory floor</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91446538/ai-manufacturing-factories</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91446538/ai-manufacturing-factories</guid>
      <description>Why artificial intelligence isn&#8217;t fulfilling its potential in manufacturing and how that could change soon.
In theory, AI should have transformed manufacturing by now. From predictive maintenance and fatigue detection to real-time quality control, the promise has always been smarter, faster, and safer operations. But in practice, the factory floor is still a place where AI ambitions often run into real-world limitations....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New survey reveals this surprising fact about companies that successfully use AI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460733/ai-jobs-layoffs-productivity-new-survey-reveals-this-surprising-fact-about-companies-that-successfully-use-artificial-intelligence</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460733/ai-jobs-layoffs-productivity-new-survey-reveals-this-surprising-fact-about-companies-that-successfully-use-artificial-intelligence</guid>
      <description>A lot has been written about AI replacing jobs of human workers, but an EY survey found such layoffs may not be that common.
A lot has been written about how AI is coming for your job, but EY&#8217;s latest&#160;AI survey found some surprising results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive data breach sees credit card details of over 5.6 million victims leaked - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/massive-data-breach-sees-credit-card-details-of-over-5-6-million-victims-leaked-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">APHXKQuV9Tqizg6PS8J9sV</guid>
      <description>Affected 700Credit customers are being offered free credit monitoring and reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s &#8216;dark web report&#8217; feature will no longer be available starting in February</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/googles-dark-web-report-feature-will-no-longer-be-available-starting-in-february/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076072</guid>
      <description>Google has revealed that its &#8220;dark web report&#8221; feature will be discontinued starting February 16, 2026. Launched initially about a year and a half ago, this tool aimed to help users monitor their personal information on the dark web For some users, the dark web report seemed like a valuable tool, scanning various data breach [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is recruiting Big Tech workers for the government</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844804/trump-tech-force-usds-apple-google-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T14:18:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844804</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump will recruit workers from Amazon, Apple, Google, Meta, Microsoft, and other tech giants to form the US Tech Force, a new program that aims to "modernize the federal government," according to an announcement on Monday. Under the new program, Trump plans to hire around 1,000 technology specialists to work across federal agencies [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise, surprise: People don&#8217;t want AI slop on &#8216;SNL&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460547/surprise-surprise-people-dont-want-ai-slop-on-snl</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:14:12</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460547/surprise-surprise-people-dont-want-ai-slop-on-snl</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Booooooo,&#8217; one viewer said.
Across the internet, eagle-eyed sleuths are crying &#8220;AI slop&#8221; after Saturday Night Live aired segments with what looks like AI-generated imagery. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU prepares ground for wider data retention &#8211; and VPN providers are among the targets</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/the-eu-prepares-ground-for-wider-data-retention-and-vpn-providers-are-among-the-targets</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vcYNnAcMnPBwGxa7RCi6UQ</guid>
      <description>With the Chat Control bill entering its final stage, the EU Council has been busy thinking about what a new data retention framework could look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift-giving advice for the office: Etiquette experts on what to get your coworkers, employees, or boss</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452638/gift-giving-advice-for-the-office-etiquette-experts-on-what-to-get-your-coworkers-employees-or-boss</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452638/gift-giving-advice-for-the-office-etiquette-experts-on-what-to-get-your-coworkers-employees-or-boss</guid>
      <description>Company-wide white elephant have you stumped? Or wondering what to get your workplace bestie for the holidays? This guide has you covered.
The holidays are the perfect time to show people that you appreciate their time, their effort, and the value they bring. But when it comes to giving gifts at work, most people are confused about what to do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain orders Airbnb to pull thousands of unlicensed property ads</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460597/spain-airbnb-unlicensed-property-ads</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460597/spain-airbnb-unlicensed-property-ads</guid>
      <description>Officials say listings violated consumer laws and contributed to rising housing costs in tourist-heavy cities.
Airbnb may finally pay the price of long-simmering tensions about overtourism in Spain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: &#8216;Housing market faces some really significant challenges&#8217; that a 25 basis-point rate cut won&#8217;t resolve</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460718/housing-market-faces-significant-challenges-that-25-bps-rate-cut-wont-resolve-federal-reserve-chair-jerome-powell</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460718/housing-market-faces-significant-challenges-that-25-bps-rate-cut-wont-resolve-federal-reserve-chair-jerome-powell</guid>
      <description>Fed Chair Jerome Powell acknowledged that recent rate cuts alone won&#8217;t restore affordability in the housing market.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Fitbits for your fitness and health</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22982833/best-fitbit-watch-fitness-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:59:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22982833/best-fitbit-watch-fitness-tracker</guid>
      <description>In 2025, you might wonder if Fitbit is still relevant. Despite being acquired by Google, Fitbit remains one of the most recognizable names in the industry. Fitbit trackers aren&#8217;t meant for the most hardcore of athletes, but they&#8217;re still excellent devices for tracking overall activity as well as monitoring certain health and wellness metrics, like [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook prend une d&#233;cision incompr&#233;hensible : fin de Messenger sur Windows et Mac</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2911001_facebook-prend-une-decision-incomprehensible-fin-de-messenger-sur-windows-et-mac</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2911001_facebook-prend-une-decision-incomprehensible-fin-de-messenger-sur-windows-et-mac</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu ce pop-up en ouvrant Messenger sur votre Mac ce matin ? Ce n'est pas un bug. Meta tue officiellement ses applications de bureau pour Windows et macOS. Alors que WhatsApp gagne en fonctionnalit&#233;s natives, Messenger fait un bond de dix ans en arri&#232;re. La logique m'&#233;chappe.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Best Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and Horror TV Shows of 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-12-best-sci-fi-fantasy-and-horror-tv-shows-of-2025-2000698626</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698626</guid>
      <description>In a year full of standout shows, io9 picks the very best genre stories to hit the small screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Things season 5 volume 2's trailer teases a character's death and I'm already terrified</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/stranger-things-season-5-volume-2s-trailer-teases-a-characters-death-and-im-already-terrified</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xn7otaiTyYZdCgwRoTL9Sa</guid>
      <description>The Stranger Things season 5 volume 2 trailer is here and you won't be able to take your eyes off it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie&amp;#8217;s delayed shooter Marathon launches in March</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844780/bungie-marathon-march-launch-delay</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:42:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844780</guid>
      <description>Bungie's Marathon, its upcoming extraction shooter that it delayed from a planned September release, will now launch in March 2026. The studio is "targeting" a price of $39.99, and "purchasing Marathon will give you full access to the game, including a roadmap of free gameplay updates as the year progresses," according to a blog post. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift guide: TechCrunch&#8217;s favorite things</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/gift-guide-techcrunchs-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075952</guid>
      <description>As tech journalists we have a lot of opinions. So if we really like something, it's probably good!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon sells MOBA March of Giants to Ubisoft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/amazon-sells-moba-march-of-giants-to-ubisoft-183948291.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3db79d71-d375-4ff8-8b02-f502e57de22c</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft is moving deeper into MOBAs after buying March of Giants  from Amazon and acquiring the team that made the game. As part of the agreement, Amazon will help promote March of Giants on Twitch. The deal is expected to close on December 16There&#8217;s no release date as yet for March of Giants. Amazon announced the free-to-play game back in August and there was a closed alpha playtest the following month. The next playtest will take place in 2026.  The next major update for March of Giants will include &#8220;new giants, expanded competitive modes and foundational systems designed to support long-ter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We filled the internet with garbage, and now Slop is the word of the year &#8212; nice going, AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/we-filled-the-internet-with-garbage-and-now-slop-is-the-word-of-the-year-nice-going-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7uCp4rDG2KVMuLJD4wGZ7h</guid>
      <description>Merriam-Webster has named "Slop" as its word of the year. Here's why this is all about AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messaging app Freedom Chat exposes user phone numbers and more - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/messaging-app-freedom-chat-exposes-user-phone-numbers-and-more-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yx6hTuQg7pxzQyTNrmiHsN</guid>
      <description>A patch was released to fix the bugs and users were forced to update their PIN codes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lidar-maker Luminar files for bankruptcy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844755/luminar-lidar-chapter-11-bankruptcy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:32:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844755</guid>
      <description>Luminar, the lidar manufacturer that rode a wave of self-driving car hype to land deals with major automakers like Volvo and Mercedes-Benz, filed for bankruptcy Monday. The company has been mired in a legal fight with its founder and former CEO, Austin Russell, who was ousted earlier this year following an ethics inquiry. As part [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok is rebranding ice hockey rinks as &#8216;boy aquariums&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460524/tiktok-ice-hockey-boys-aquarium</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460524/tiktok-ice-hockey-boys-aquarium</guid>
      <description>While it&#8217;s a tongue-in-cheek joke, the trend risks playing into harmful stereotypes of female sports fans. 
&#8220;There are boy aquariums all over the United States,&#8221; a TikTok creator explains in a recent post.&#160;&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How &#8216;slop&#8217; became the defining word of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460529/how-slop-became-the-defining-word-of-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460529/how-slop-became-the-defining-word-of-2025</guid>
      <description>AI spam, fake videos, and junk content turned a centuries-old word into the perfect label for today&#8217;s internet.
It&#8217;s official: 2025 was the year of slop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Ecovacs Deebot mini : le mini robot aspirateur qui a tout d&#8217;un grand</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/test/2860197_test-du-ecovacs-deebot-mini-le-mini-robot-aspirateur-qui-a-tout-dun-grand</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/test/2860197_test-du-ecovacs-deebot-mini-le-mini-robot-aspirateur-qui-a-tout-dun-grand</guid>
      <description>
L&#8217;Ecovacs Deebot Mini est l&#8217;un des rares mini-robots aspirateurs du march&#233;. Pens&#233; pour les petits int&#233;rieurs, il se veut aussi efficace que s&#233;duisant gr&#226;ce &#224; son format compact. Alors que la concurrence reste assez minimaliste, Ecovacs propose un v&#233;ritable robot aspirateur-laveur, aussi complet que les mod&#232;les classiques, avec une base capable d&#8217;autovidange et de nettoyer la vadrouille. Sur le papier, c&#8217;est tr&#232;s s&#233;duisant. Mais cela se v&#233;rifie-t-il au quotidien ?
...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
