<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 23:34:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl LX ads: all AI everything</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/874504/super-bowl-lx-ads-big-game</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T18:10:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=874504</guid>
      <description>Super Bowl LX is nearly here, with the Seattle Seahawks taking on the New England Patriots. While Bad Bunny will be the star of the halftime show, AI could be the star of the commercial breaks, much like crypto was a few years ago. Last year&#8217;s Super Bowl featured a Google Gemini ad that fumbled [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York lawmakers introduce bill that aims to halt data center development for three years</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/new-york-lawmakers-introduce-bill-that-aims-to-halt-data-center-development-for-three-years-224005266.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c2d37d0-44ef-4d31-9f79-34822b342bc5</guid>
      <description>On Friday, New York State Senators Liz Krueger and Kristen Gonzales introduced a bill that would stop the issuance of permits for new data centers for at least three years and ninety days to give time for impact assessments and to update regulations. The bill would require the Department of Environmental Conservation and Public Service Commissions to issue impact statements and reports during the pause, along with any new orders or regulations that they deem necessary to minimize data centers' impacts on the environment and consumers in New York.The bill would require these departments to stud...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if we treated the Nvidia GB10 as an employee: AI could remove reporting roles entirely from businesses with thousands of job losses, here's how this reviewer did it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-if-we-treated-the-nvidia-gb10-as-an-employee-ai-could-remove-reporting-roles-entirely-from-businesses-with-thousands-of-job-losses-heres-how-this-reviewer-did-it</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bDEAZRSaN7oPQYRTNySck8</guid>
      <description>A review replaced manual reporting with Nvidia GB10 AI systems, reducing staff needs while maintaining data accuracy and operational efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;m addicted to Nintendo Switch Online, but I wish I&#8217;d known about these hidden gems sooner</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/im-addicted-to-nintendo-switch-online-but-i-wish-id-known-about-these-hidden-gems-sooner</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Eafe4rTfqWJ5ftvXCBcCXo</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve got a Nintendo Switch Online subscription, these classic games are absolute must-play &#8211; but you may not be all too familiar with them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Office Professional 2021 for Windows is $34.97</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-7-microsoft-office-professional-2021-for-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">004b56pKzEBlyMRVaPBNko5</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Office Professional 2021 for Windows is on sale for $34.97 through Feb. 22, offering a lifetime license with Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
