<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:24:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cet ultrabook Lenovo avec &#233;cran OLED 3K et Ryzen AI 9 perd 25 %  de son prix pour No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2920459_cet-ultrabook-lenovo-avec-ecran-oled-3k-et-ryzen-ai-9-perd-25-de-son-prix-pour-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2920459_cet-ultrabook-lenovo-avec-ecran-oled-3k-et-ryzen-ai-9-perd-25-de-son-prix-pour-noel</guid>
      <description>
Dalle OLED 3K, puce Ryzen AI 9, RAM g&#233;n&#233;reuse, bonne autonomie... Le PC portable Copilot+ Lenovo Yoga Pro 7 ne manque clairement pas de points forts. Si vous souhaitez changer votre &#233;quipement de travail et miser sur cette bonne machine, sachez que la Fnac et Darty la proposent actuellement &#224; 1 279,99 euros au lieu de 1 699,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Revisits Its Most Controversial Change From the Games</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-season-2-episode-2-shady-sands-maximus-2000703139</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703139</guid>
      <description>The second episode of its sophomore season sees 'Fallout' entrench its big new arc in a look back to its recent past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I re-created Google&amp;#8217;s cute Gemini ad with my own kid&amp;#8217;s stuffie, and I wish I hadn&amp;#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/849998/gemini-ai-stuffed-animal-commercial</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-25T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849998</guid>
      <description>When your kid starts showing a preference for one of their stuffed animals, you're supposed to buy a backup in case it goes missing. I've heard this advice again and again, but never got around to buying a second plush deer once "Buddy" became my son's obvious favorite. Neither, apparently, did the parents in Google's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried using a dock for my Asus ROG Ally for the first time &#8212; and it could draw me back to living room gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/i-tried-using-a-dock-for-my-asus-rog-ally-for-the-first-time-and-it-could-draw-me-back-to-living-room-gaming</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6suG68hwLjBG6YoLKFDmS</guid>
      <description>I'd long since given up on 'couch gaming', but docking my Asus ROG Ally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to explain the importance of a VPN to your parents this Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/how-to-explain-the-importance-of-a-vpn-to-your-parents-this-christmas</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GfdaPCHEe2ivWH2NxxqsR8</guid>
      <description>What else would you chat about over Christmas dinner?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's the most efficient type of electric heater you can buy? Here are the best options to avoid sky-high bills</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/whats-the-most-efficient-type-of-electric-heater-you-can-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hpqaoCPYXFuu3Xww5Lor5P</guid>
      <description>From fan heaters to oil-filled radiators, we explain which portable heater will warm your home best, without sending your power bill through the roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood cozied up to AI in 2025 and had nothing good to show for it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/848119/hollywood-film-tv-ai-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-25T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848119</guid>
      <description>AI isn't new to Hollywood - but this was the year when it really made its presence felt. For years now, the entertainment industry has used different kinds of generative AI products for a variety of post-production processes ranging from de-aging actors to removing green screen backgrounds. In many instances, the technology has been a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 was a good year for cameras, but it was even better for lenses &#8211; these are my 5 innovative new favorites</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-lenses/2025-was-a-good-year-for-cameras-but-it-was-even-better-for-lenses-these-are-my-5-innovative-new-favorites</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z3ek93hhm3iMAyekTfDpeU</guid>
      <description>Lens design innovation exceeded that of cameras in 2025, and these Sony, Canon, Nikon, OM System and Viltrox optics in particular all impressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to transfer your games to the Nintendo Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/how-to-transfer-your-games-to-the-nintendo-switch-2-130000702.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">810be60f-92c1-4187-80b2-7e8306461826</guid>
      <description>Upgrading to the Switch 2 is a big step forward, thanks to the larger screen, new features and improved performance. But shifting to a new console naturally raises the question of what happens to all your games and save data on the one you already have. Thankfully, Nintendo has built a clear System Transfer process that lets you move your account, digital purchases, save files and other key data from your original Switch to the Switch 2. If you prepare ahead of time, you can be back to playing your favorite titles on new hardware in minutes.We&#8217;ll walk you through everything you need to know, i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Christmas Day NFL games: How to watch today, full streaming schedule and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/2025-christmas-day-nfl-games-how-to-watch-today-full-streaming-schedule-and-more-233022063.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dba1595-094e-49de-b9e8-4dba27caeb24</guid>
      <description>Christmas Day famously belongs to football. This Dec. 25, there are three NFL games to watch: the Dallas Cowboys vs. Washington Commanders, the Detroit Lions vs. the Minnesota Vikings and the Denver Broncos vs. Kansas City Chiefs. Here's what you need to know about Thursday's football slate, and the rest of the Week 17 schedule.&#160;
How to watch the NFL Christmas Day games:&#160;




Date: Thursday, Dec. 25, 2025
Start times: 1 PM ET, 4:30 PM ET, 8:15 PM ET
TV channels: N/A
Streaming: Netflix, Prime Video&#160;
2025 Christmas Day NFL game slate:&#160;
Thursday, Dec. 25, 2025

Cowboys vs. Commanders: 1 p.m. (Net...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton VPN r&#233;duit de 75 % le prix de son abonnement de 2 ans, id&#233;al pour s&#233;curiser 10 appareils</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2919723_proton-vpn-reduit-de-75-le-prix-de-son-abonnement-de-2-ans-ideal-pour-securiser-10-appareils</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2919723_proton-vpn-reduit-de-75-le-prix-de-son-abonnement-de-2-ans-ideal-pour-securiser-10-appareils</guid>
      <description>
Proton VPN est aujourd'hui l'un des r&#233;seaux virtuels priv&#233;s les plus pl&#233;biscit&#233;s. L'abonnement est plut&#244;t on&#233;reux en temps normal, mais actuellement, l'offre de 24 mois peut vous revenir &#224; 2,49 euros par mois au lieu de 9,99 euros par mois.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up a Smartphone for Elderly Loved Ones</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-set-up-smartphone-for-parents-grandparents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">612f7f0e20bf2c9c1ab27236</guid>
      <description>Here's how to make iPhone and Android devices a little easier to use.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
