<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:30:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ces deux smartphones d&#8217;&#233;lite passent sous les 650 &#8364; : entre le Galaxy S25 et le Pixel 10, lequel choisir ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2983553_ces-deux-smartphones-delite-passent-sous-les-650-e-entre-le-galaxy-s25-et-le-pixel-10-lequel-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2983553_ces-deux-smartphones-delite-passent-sous-les-650-e-entre-le-galaxy-s25-et-le-pixel-10-lequel-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Deux smartphones not&#233;s 8/10 et en promo sous les 650 euros : le Samsung Galaxy S25 et le Google Pixel 10 sont aujourd&#8217;hui, en 2026, des valeurs s&#251;res. Ces deux r&#233;f&#233;rences Android s&#8217;imposent comme d&#8217;excellents choix en promo, mais lequel choisir ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aerial_Knight&#8217;s DropShot captures the thrill of skydiving and makes it stylish</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/875259/dropshot-aerial-knight-review-pc-playstation-xbox</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-21T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875259</guid>
      <description>I've always wanted to go skydiving. Aerial_Knight's DropShot, from indie developer Aerial_Knight, lets me live out that dream - at least in a safe, virtual kind of way. It also lets me shoot bullets from finger guns, wield laser skulls, and wear cool sunglasses while I'm falling through the air. So maybe it's better than [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;My love letter to an underappreciated work of art&#8217;: this is the one GameCube title that I want to see on Nintendo Switch Online</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/my-love-letter-to-an-underappreciated-work-of-art-this-is-the-one-gamecube-title-that-i-want-to-see-on-nintendo-switch-online</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">X4xXubCduaH4JWYbMYmvc8</guid>
      <description>This obscure GameCube title is easily one of my favorites, and if it doesn&#8217;t get added to Nintendo Switch Online, it will be a giant disappointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mandalorian and Grogu: release date, trailer, cast, plot, and everything else we know about the new Star Wars movie</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/the-mandalorian-and-grogu-hub</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dVXijinwyvvHWgFKQkhUe</guid>
      <description>The Mandalorian and Grogu will arrive this May &#8212; here's what we know so far about the next Star Wars movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping the human touch in tech: what over-automation gets wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/keeping-the-human-touch-in-tech-what-over-automation-gets-wrong</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pqmLgLESBrU7mEQD62P6BK</guid>
      <description>As AI scales across IT services, removing human judgement risks brittle systems, rising costs, and eroding customer trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 is tipped to get 2 smart camera upgrades &#8211; but the OnePlus 16 may show it up with an elite new telephoto sensor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/the-samsung-galaxy-s26-is-tipped-to-get-2-smart-camera-upgrades-but-the-oneplus-16-may-show-it-up-with-an-elite-new-telephoto-sensor</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KoWdNMYfchaGuKJmdePBSg</guid>
      <description>We have some fresh rumors around two of the most powerful smartphones expected to launch this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch India vs. South Africa in the 2026 T20 World Cup online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/india-south-africa-t20-world-cup-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">008DoAamMbJIWIGUOr4ENDv</guid>
      <description>How to watch T20 World Cup for free. Live stream India vs. South Africa in the 2026 T20 World Cup for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch New Zealand vs. Pakistan in the 2026 T20 World Cup online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/new-zealand-pakistan-t20-world-cup-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">055hoT3U9CPSXPLRNlJ7pJX</guid>
      <description>How to watch T20 World Cup for free. Live stream New Zealand vs. Pakistan in the 2026 T20 World Cup for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Canada vs. USA in mens ice hockey final online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/canada-usa-mens-ice-hockey-final-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05swBEnY0e8iAU4YLpesOSQ</guid>
      <description>How to watch ice hockey for free. Live stream Canada vs. USA in men's ice hockey final for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google's 'America-India Connect' is filling in the last gaps for a truly global subsea cable network</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/googles-america-india-connect-is-filling-in-the-last-gaps-for-a-truly-global-subsea-cable-network</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xHTozeuEnzkUaSnkyeXPcQ</guid>
      <description>Google&#8217;s America-India Connect strengthens subsea networks across continents and enables high-capacity AI infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; ce casque v&#233;lo qui permet d&#8217;&#233;couter de la musique et de passer des appels : promesse tenue, mais des d&#233;fauts qui font t&#226;che</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tenways/2977097_on-a-teste-ce-casque-velo-qui-permet-decouter-de-la-musique-et-de-passer-des-appels-promesse-tenue-mais-des-defauts-qui-font-tache</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tenways/2977097_on-a-teste-ce-casque-velo-qui-permet-decouter-de-la-musique-et-de-passer-des-appels-promesse-tenue-mais-des-defauts-qui-font-tache</guid>
      <description>
Int&#233;grant des haut-parleurs pour la musique et les appels, ainsi qu&#8217;un &#233;clairage avec clignotant, le casque v&#233;lo Tenways EH20 est complet pour son prix de 159 euros. Mais il doit encore progresser pour vraiment convaincre. Voici notre test complet. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis is in a crisis of its own making</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/881987/stellantis-crisis-ev-loss-sales-regulations</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-21T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881987</guid>
      <description>Demand for EVs has gone glacial, and one automaker after another is running aground: General Motors threw $7.6 billion overboard. Ford washed $19.5 billion off its books. Leave it to Stellantis to face the most titanic charge yet, a $26.5 billion bill for its own misplaced bet on EVs. The Jeep, Dodge, and Chrysler parent [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed Philips' affordable Fidelio stereo speakers that look 'too good to be true' on the spec sheet &#8212; and they nearly pull it off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/philips-fidelio-fa3-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xmVbxummeTerkJuJaQhTv6</guid>
      <description>An active wireless speaker system with specification beyond the asking price, and an actually useful app &#8212; what&#8217;s the catch?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Wales vs Scotland: Free Streams, TV Channels &amp; Preview for Six Nations 2026 clash</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/rugby/wales-vs-scotland-six-nations-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q5GHGXsUsf9UDTpMNUn6UQ</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Wales vs Scotland live streams online &#8211; including for FREE &#8211; in the 2026 Six Nations Round 3 clash at the Principality Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to know if an AirTag is tracking you</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/how-to-know-if-an-airtag-is-tracking-you-130000764.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ed2b124-dd5c-4928-9913-2e06174d4f2d</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s AirTag is designed to help people keep track of personal belongings like keys, bags and luggage. But because AirTags and other Bluetooth trackers are small and discreet, concerns about unwanted tracking are understandable. Apple has spent years building safeguards into the AirTag and the Find My network to reduce the risk of misuse and to alert people if a tracker they don&#8217;t own appears to be moving with them.If you&#8217;re worried about whether an AirTag or similar tracker might be following you, here&#8217;s how Apple&#8217;s unwanted tracking alerts work, what notifications to look for and what you ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget review recap: Sony WF-1000XM6, ASUS Zenbook Duo and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/engadget-review-recap-sony-wf-1000xm6-asus-zenbook-duo-and-more-130000298.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa1adb0c-47fe-452b-bf30-eeea543ed81e</guid>
      <description>Gather &#8216;round, it&#8217;s time to catch up on the latest batch of Engadget reviews. Whether you missed our in-depth testing of Sony&#8217;s latest flagship earbuds or a truly unique ASUS laptop, I&#8217;ve compiled our recent reviews so you can get up to speed quickly. Read on for the list that also includes a love letter to a tiny camera and another VPN option that worth considering. 
Sony WF-1000XM6


Sony&#8217;s 1000X earbuds have always been the top pick in our best wireless earbuds guide. With the M6 though, the company doesn&#8217;t do enough to clearly separate itself from the competition like it has in the past. &#8220;...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
