<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:24:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Disney wants to drag you into the slop</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/842992/disney-openai-sora-ai-slop-partnership</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T18:03:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842992</guid>
      <description>Disney and OpenAI's new $1 billion partnership feels emblematic of the terrible times we're living through. In exchange for access to the generative AI firm's APIs and tools like ChatGPT, the studio plans to let users of OpenAI's Sora AI video generator create clips featuring hundreds of Disney-owned characters. Sora AI users will be able [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best earbuds we&#8217;ve tested for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s hard to buy a bad pair of wireless earbuds these days, and with constant discounts and deals wherever you look, now is as good a time as any to splurge on the pair you&#8217;ve been eyeing. The market has come a long way since the early era of true wireless earbuds, when we had [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which brand has the best pet hair tool? I tested a whole bunch &#8211; here are the results</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/which-brand-has-the-best-pet-hair-tool-i-tested-a-whole-bunch-here-are-the-results</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dPdnyXCh8ogmgwkQWP9A7N</guid>
      <description>If you need a tool to de-fuzz your sofa, these are the brands to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT 5.2 is here and all about being a better thinker &#8211; here are the 3 things you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/openai/chatgpt-5-2-is-here-and-all-about-being-a-better-thinker-here-are-the-3-things-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XgFDPFFYtQXESsZTaWKrKT</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT 5.2 is here and offers the smartest, most dependable version of the AI chatbot yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google brings Gemini&#8217;s Chrome integration to iPhone and iPad</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842987/google-gemini-chrome-ios</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:51:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842987</guid>
      <description>Built-in Gemini AI features in Chrome are now becoming more widely available on the iOS version of Google's browser, as reported by 9to5Google and Engadget. They're popping up several months after the features' rollout on the desktop version started in September. Once the new Gemini features are active on your iPhone or iPad, Chrome users [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook&#8217;s lobbying hangs over a key kids online safety vote</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/842993/kids-online-safety-markup-energy-commerce-tim-cook-apple</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:50:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842993</guid>
      <description>At a congressional meeting to vote on the future of kids online safety, the most spirited debate of the day was about a bill that wasn't even on the agenda and Apple CEO Tim Cook. 18 bills that aim to regulate the internet to protect children are now headed for a vote before the full [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Prime Video pulls AI-powered recaps after Fallout flub</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842978/amazon-prime-video-ai-fallout-recap</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:46:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842978</guid>
      <description>Amazon Prime Video has pulled its AI-powered video recap of Fallout after viewers noticed that it got key parts of the story wrong. The streaming service began testing Video Recaps last month, and now they're missing from the shows included in the test, including Fallout, The Rig, Tom Clancy's Jack Ryan, Upload, and Bosch. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Doctor Who&#8217; and the Disintegration of 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doctor-who-2025-retrospective-disney-bbc-2000698641</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698641</guid>
      <description>2025 should've been a banner year for 'Doctor Who,' but instead it almost became one of its darkest hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple loses contempt appeal in Epic case</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842991/apple-epic-appeal-loses-contempt</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:44:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842991</guid>
      <description>Apple has lost its appeal of a massive district court ruling in its ongoing antitrust dispute with Epic Games. That April ruling from Judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers said that Apple "willingly" failed to comply with a 2021 order allowing mobile app developers to link to payment options outside of Apple's, and she barred Apple from [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is clapping back at Google&#8217;s Gemini 3 with a new GPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459305/openai-gpt-google-gemini-3</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T22:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459305/openai-gpt-google-gemini-3</guid>
      <description>The new model displays expert-level skill in work tasks, and exceeds Gemini in several benchmarks.
OpenAI on Thursday released its answer to Google&#8217;s impressive Gemini 3 Pro model&#8211;GPT-5.2&#8212;and by the looks of some head-to-head benchmark test scores, it looks like a winner. The new model took the highest score on a number of benchmark tests covering coding, math, science, tool use, and vision. (Benchmarks should, of course, be combined with real-world use to tell the whole story. But still . . .)...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Magnate Do Kwon Sentenced to 15 Years in Prison</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/do-kwon-terraform-sentenced-prison-crypto-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69331cbb515c709022917daa</guid>
      <description>The founder of Terraform Labs was sentenced today for lying about &#8220;experimental&#8221; coins that blew a $40 billion hole in the crypto economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warnings Mount in Congress Over Expanded US Wiretap Powers</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/warnings-mount-in-congress-over-expanded-us-wiretap-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693adec55885de020c5e2195</guid>
      <description>Experts tell US lawmakers that a crucial spy program&#8217;s safeguards are failing, allowing intel agencies deeper, unconstrained access to Americans&#8217; data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flip's affordable NBN plan pricing doesn't mean you'll be left high and dry if you ever need help</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/wi-fi-broadband/flips-affordable-nbn-plan-pricing-doesnt-mean-youll-be-left-high-and-dry-if-you-ever-need-help</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9tdrtowVjoPfpRwXxAAisD</guid>
      <description>Finding an affordable and reliable NBN service is one thing, but can you be sure you'll get satisfactory support further down the line? This Aussie-owned telco stakes its reputation on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.&#8217;s Health Department Is Pondering a National Men&#8217;s Health Initiative</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/rfk-jrs-health-department-is-pondering-a-national-mens-health-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939e0b327661e7f07f6ab3d</guid>
      <description>At an FDA discussion of testosterone replacement therapy, a top official called for special health centers to address a &#8220;men&#8217;s health crisis.&#8221; Others called to ease men&#8217;s access to hormones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1X&#160;struck a deal to send its &#8216;home&#8217; humanoids to&#160;factories and warehouses</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/1x-struck-a-deal-to-send-its-home-humanoids-to-factories-and-warehouses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075424</guid>
      <description>Despite launching as a humanoid robot designed to help consumers around the house, 1X's Neo robots are heading to industrial use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best phone to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</guid>
      <description>Haven&#8217;t you heard? Phones are boring now. And that&#8217;s just fine! Most people buying a new phone just want something familiar that works better than the device they&#8217;re replacing. If that&#8217;s your MO, then you&#8217;re sure to find something reliable in my recommendations below. But even if you&#8217;re looking for something a little more extra, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's AI-generated recap tool didn't watch Fallout very closely</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazons-ai-generated-recap-tool-didnt-watch-fallout-very-closely-215712958.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">317af2d4-87d3-43fd-b4f4-321618fa824b</guid>
      <description>Amazon's plan to offer AI-generated recaps of Prime Video shows isn't off to a great start. The company's recap of the first season of Fallout features multiple errors, GamesRadar+ writes, including basic facts about the plot of the show.You can watch the recap yourself in the "Extras" section of Amazon's Fallout season two listing in Prime Video. Besides being somewhat dry, the AI-generated recap incorrectly identifies the time period of the show's Los Angeles-set flashbacks as being the 1950s, when they're actually 2077 (the Fallout franchise is set in an alternate history that diverged from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSA imagines AI chatbots as creepy humans who harm kids</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/ai-chatbot-psa</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06HF4Kl75YoBhFJ5RMy3qog</guid>
      <description>President Trump says he won't let states pass AI laws. This ad says they're necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After striking OpenAI deal, Disney demands Google cease and desist from AI infringement</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/disney-cease-and-desist-google-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07xCS2JXPM0k4Wja4YIfeUL</guid>
      <description>Disney has sent a legal threat to Google, telling the company to stop using its characters in its AI models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is the sex in Heated Rivalry so hot?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/why-is-heated-rivalry-show-hbo-max-so-hot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01GY8cuOIucUJAbu4LC44xM</guid>
      <description>Queer sex never looked better than it does in HBO Max's hit 'Heated Rivalry.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How everyday investors are redefining the American dream</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459184/how-everyday-investors-are-redefining-the-american-dream</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:42:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459184/how-everyday-investors-are-redefining-the-american-dream</guid>
      <description>The new wealth builders are relying on software to help easily manage real estate. 
A quiet shift is reshaping the trajectory of wealth in America, but it isn&#8217;t happening in the boardrooms of Wall Street or the halls of Silicon Valley. It&#8217;s unfolding in neighborhoods, driveways, and home offices across the country, powered by teachers, software engineers, nurses, military families, and small-business owners who never expected to become real estate investors at all....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Mogul/Secretary of (*checks notes) the Interior Says AI Will Cure Cancer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/software-mogul-secretary-of-checks-notes-the-interior-says-ai-will-cure-cancer-2000698612</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698612</guid>
      <description>"This is the miracle of AI. We can actually manufacture intelligence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech transformation isn&#8217;t about how many tools you buy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459120/tech-transformation-isnt-about-how-many-tools-you-buy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:35:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459120/tech-transformation-isnt-about-how-many-tools-you-buy</guid>
      <description>A successful implementation requires focus on people more than tools.
Every company is racing to modernize. There&#8217;s a sense that if you aren&#8217;t adopting new technology fast enough, you&#8217;re already behind. From AI and automation to digital platforms, the list keeps growing. Leaders make big investments, employees sit through onboarding sessions, and for a few weeks, excitement fills the air. Then the momentum fades....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atmospheric River That Drenched the Northwest Is Now Supercharging 2 Winter Storms</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/atmospheric-river-that-drenched-the-northwest-is-now-supercharging-2-winter-storms-2000698742</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698742</guid>
      <description>The moisture from this storm system will help two fast-moving winter storms spread snow across the eastern U.S., with another atmospheric river on its way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York&amp;#8217;s new law forces advertisers to say when they&amp;#8217;re using AI avatars</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842848/new-york-law-ai-advertisements-sag-aftra-labor</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T16:30:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842848</guid>
      <description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul signed a bill Thursday that will require advertisers to identify if an ad includes AI-generated people. Hochul's announcement said the bill, S.8420-A/A.8887-B, was the first of its kind in the US, describing it as a "common sense" law that would bring increased transparency and protect consumers. A separate bill also [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney's deal with OpenAI is about controlling the future of copyright</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/disneys-deal-with-openai-is-about-controlling-the-future-of-copyright-213009504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7536cc3-9fa1-46e3-9d78-c284f35a6c3c</guid>
      <description>This morning Disney and OpenAI announced a three-year licensing agreement: Starting in 2026, ChatGPT and Sora can generate images and videos incorporating Disney IP, including more than 200 characters from the company's stable of Star Wars, Pixar and Marvel brands. To say these companies make for strange bedfellows is an understatement.&#160;&#160;The agreement brings together two parties with very different public stances on copyright. Before OpenAI released Sora, the company reportedly notified studios and talent agencies they would need to opt out of having their work appear in the new app. The compa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 88-core AMD CPU surfaces on eBay, and here's why I think it's the start of something big</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/mysterious-88-core-amd-cpu-surfaces-on-ebay-and-heres-why-i-think-its-the-start-of-something-big</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wRDcfa7tDkgxy4G8YEddCR</guid>
      <description>Recently surfaced AMD processors with unusual core counts hint at rapid hyperscale refresh cycles and possible large-scale recovery of usable DDR4 memory.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
