<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:42:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia&#8217;s Futuristic Megacity Runs Into Dilemma: Why Build Housing When You Can Build a Data Center?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/saudi-arabias-futuristic-megacity-runs-into-dilemma-why-build-housing-when-you-can-build-a-data-center-2000714028</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714028</guid>
      <description>The Line is shrinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette manette polyvalente au look r&#233;tro style Super Nintendo est affich&#233;e &#224; prix cass&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2955561_cette-manette-polyvalente-au-look-retro-style-super-nintendo-est-affichee-a-prix-casse</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2955561_cette-manette-polyvalente-au-look-retro-style-super-nintendo-est-affichee-a-prix-casse</guid>
      <description>
La 8BitDo SN30 Pro est une manette sans&#8209;fil compacte &#224; l&#8217;esth&#233;tique r&#233;tro inspir&#233;e de la Super Nintendo, qui tombe &#224; 29 euros alors qu&#8217;on la trouve plut&#244;t aux alentours de 40 euros habituellement, ce qui en fait une vraie bonne affaire pour les joueurs console, PC ou mobile.&#160;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even the big dick subreddit is mad about ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/867967/ice-shooting-minneapolis-reddit-communities-activism</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T13:31:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=867967</guid>
      <description>"Fuck ICE first, second, third, and fourth. Then worry about fucking me," a Reddit post reads. "Immigrants of any status are my friends, neighbors, and colleagues." Across the internet - and in the streets - the sentiment is unavoidable, especially after a federal immigration agent shot and killed Alex Pretti, a 37-year-old nurse, in Minneapolis [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listening to Music With Beat-Based Stimulation Could Help Reduce Anxiety, Researchers Find</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/listening-to-music-with-beat-based-stimulation-could-help-reduce-anxiety-researchers-find-2000713964</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713964</guid>
      <description>Just 24 minutes of music paired with auditory simulation seemed to significantly reduce people's anxiety symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enfin un smartphone qui apporte quelque chose de nouveau</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2955795_enfin-un-smartphone-qui-apporte-quelque-chose-de-nouveau</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2955795_enfin-un-smartphone-qui-apporte-quelque-chose-de-nouveau</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que le march&#233; du smartphone ennuyeux ? Cela s'entend, m&#234;me si le TriFold est surprenant. Maos attendez de voir ce que pr&#233;pare OrangePi. La marque, c&#233;l&#232;bre pour ses alternatives au Raspberry Pi, vient de lever le voile sur un concept de t&#233;l&#233;phone qui ignore superbement toutes les r&#232;gles actuelles du design industriel pour se concentrer sur une seule chose : la libert&#233; totale de bidouiller.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus may have just released the most powerful business laptop ever: ExpertBook B3 G2 has an AMD Ryzen AI 9 HX 470 and weighs only 1.41Kg</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/asus-may-have-just-released-the-most-powerful-business-laptop-ever-expertbook-b3-g2-has-an-amd-ryzen-ai-9-hx-470-and-weighs-only-1-41kg</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KTqtnPj36jbmDm7iYUqzzb</guid>
      <description>Asus ExpertBook B3 G2 business laptop sports Ryzen AI 9 HX 470 and a 1.41kg starting weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Wireless Mic Kit Is $70 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/dji-mic-3-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977a04e65684b6a8b3deeee</guid>
      <description>Save on a full DJI Mic 3 bundle, or pick and choose to build your own portable recording setup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok alternative Skylight soars to 380K+ users after TikTok U.S. deal finalized</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/tiktok-alternative-skylight-soars-to-380k-users-after-tiktok-u-s-deal-finalized/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086026</guid>
      <description>Skylight, a TikTok alternative built on open protocols, has had a busy weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Showrunner Explains That Eye-Popping Nude Scene</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-nude-scene-episode-2-2000714043</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714043</guid>
      <description>Ser Arlan of Pennytree made an oversized impression in the opening moments of this week's episode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to generate AI images using ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/how-to-generate-ai-images-using-chatgpt-120000560.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cae2b0e-a866-4c00-8dcd-1f7113fe54b1</guid>
      <description>Since March 2025, ChatGPT has been capable of generating images. Following a period where it briefly wasn't available to free users, you now don't even pay for one of OpenAI's subscriptions to use this feature. And while making images inside of ChatGPT is easy, there are some nuances worth explaining. For example, did you know you can ask ChatGPT to edit photos you've taken? It's more powerful than you might think. Here&#8217;s everything you need to know about generating AI images with ChatGPT.&#160;&#160;How to create images with ChatGPT using text prompts&#160;To begin making an image in ChatGPT, you can start ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattle TV has turned a Hitchcock classic into a vertical video &#8216;microdrama&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/867844/tattle-tv-the-lodger-hitchcock</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T13:00:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=867844</guid>
      <description>Most vertical video microdrama apps have been focused on putting out newly produced series meant to be watched on your phone. But Tattle TV thinks that people might also be interested in checking out bite-size pieces of cinematic history. Though Tattle TV - a UK-based streaming platform created by filmmakers Philip McGoldrick and Marina Elderton [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP unites Claude chat with apps like Slack, Figma, and Canva</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/867673/claude-mcp-app-interactive-slack-figma-canva</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=867673</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's Claude got a bit livelier today thanks to a new extension to MCP, the open-source protocol that allows AI agents to easily access tools and data across the internet. Users will now be able to interact with apps directly inside the Claude chatbot, letting you draft and format Slack messages to colleagues and create [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic launches interactive Claude apps, including Slack and other workplace tools</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/anthropic-launches-interactive-claude-apps-including-slack-and-other-workplace-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085959</guid>
      <description>Claude users will now be able to call up interactive apps inside the chatbot interface, with Cowork integration coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obvious Ventures lands fund five with a 360-degree view of planetary, human, economic health</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/obvious-ventures-lands-fund-five-with-a-360-degree-view-of-planetary-human-economic-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086074</guid>
      <description>The 12-year-old firm raised $360,360,360 for its fifth fund. And there's a reason for that number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude now offers deeper integrations with apps like Canva and Slack</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/claude-now-offers-deeper-integrations-with-apps-like-canva-and-slack-180000604.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1ed1d18-91f6-43ce-93d3-30c269fbad43</guid>
      <description>Anthropic has been building out support for third-party apps inside of Claude. As of today, the chatbot can now connect to platforms like Slack and Canva, fetching up files from inside those apps or performing tasks within them on a user's behalf.For instance, when connected to Box, Claude can now search for files, preview documents inline and answer questions about the content in front of you. Meanwhile, with a connection to Asana, it can now turn chats into projects, tasks and timelines your co-workers can then find and interact with on the project management app.&#160;Box and Asana are just two ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic embeds Slack, Figma and Asana inside Claude, turning AI chat into a workplace command center</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/anthropic-embeds-slack-figma-and-asana-inside-claude-turning-ai-chat-into-a</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03oDN0cI7Gft3o1oUn9As</guid>
      <description>Anthropic announced Monday that users can now open and interact with popular business applications directly inside Claude, the company's AI assistant&#8212;a significant expansion that transforms the chatbot from a conversational tool into an integrated workspace where employees can build project timelines, draft Slack messages, create presentations, and visualize data without switching browser tabs.The rollout, which goes live today, includes integrations with Amplitude, Asana, Box, Canva, Clay, Figma, Hex, Monday.com, and Slack. Salesforce integration is coming soon. The feature marks a new chapte...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test de l&#8217;Asus Zenbook Duo (2026) : le Core Ultra X9 388H au firmament</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2953795_test-de-lasus-zenbook-duo-2026-le-core-ultra-x9-388h-au-firmament</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2953795_test-de-lasus-zenbook-duo-2026-le-core-ultra-x9-388h-au-firmament</guid>
      <description>
L'Intel Core Ultra X9 388H se pr&#233;sente officiellement sous la forme de l'Asus Zenbook Duo, nouveau portable deux &#233;crans du constructeur ta&#239;wanais.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin reportedly plans to use AI to write federal regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/trump-admin-reportedly-plans-to-use-ai-to-write-federal-regulations-175155111.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c56888-99bb-4834-b50c-eeedd5a6ab3f</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration is planning on using Google Gemini to draft important federal regulations, as reported by ProPublica. This is starting with the Department of Transportation, according to interviews with agency staffers. Regulations created by the DOT help keep us safe when traveling.
The plan was initially presented to DOT staffers last month, with agency attorney Daniel Cohen writing to colleagues about AI's "potential to revolutionize the way we draft rulemakings." Gregory Zerzan, the agency's general counsel, has indicated that President Donald Trump is "very excited by this initia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok attributes recent glitches to a power outage at a U.S. data center</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/tiktok-attributes-recent-glitches-to-a-power-outage-at-a-u-s-data-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086046</guid>
      <description>The timing of these outages lines up with the long-awaited creation of a separate U.S. TikTok entity last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTokers are heading to UpScrolled following US takeover</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/867958/tiktok-upscrolled-app-us-takeover</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T12:47:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=867958</guid>
      <description>TikTok's takeover in the US has prompted users to join an alternative social platform called UpScrolled. The app, which is available on Android and iOS, currently holds the 12th spot in Apple's App Store, and it's struggling to keep up with an influx of new traffic. "You showed up so fast our servers tapped out," [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN deal: Two-year plans are up to 78 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-deal-two-year-plans-are-up-to-78-percent-off-180602243.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $101 for two years, plus four additional free months. That works out to $3.59 per month during the promotional period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel&#8217;s Panther Lake Chips Aren&#8217;t Just Good&#8212;They Beat Apple's M5</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/intel-panther-lake-core-ultra-series-3-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fd2185963d82ddd46cfa9</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;ve tested a laptop powered by Panther Lake&#8212;pitting them head-to-head against laptops with Apple Silicon&#8212;and Intel has finally scored a much-needed win with the Core Ultra Series 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; C&#8217;est du d&#233;lire &#187; : les benchmarks et tests d&#8217;Intel Panther Lake sont unanimes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/intel/2955691_cest-du-delire-les-benchmarks-et-tests-dintel-panther-lake-sont-unanimes</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/intel/2955691_cest-du-delire-les-benchmarks-et-tests-dintel-panther-lake-sont-unanimes</guid>
      <description>
On nous l'a vendue comme la puce de la r&#233;demption, celle qui devait laver l'affront Lunar Lake en ramenant la production &#224; la maison. Panther Lake est enfin l&#224;, et les premiers tests sont unanimes : Intel a enfin arr&#234;t&#233; de nous mener en bateau.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ball x Pit's first update brings an endless mode and much more to the chaos</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ball-x-pits-first-update-brings-an-endless-mode-and-much-more-to-the-chaos-174306548.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaec43fe-3b9d-4261-aad2-f3bac9fe4cbb</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s time to jump back into the pit. Ball x Pit is one of the very best games of 2025 and there&#8217;s now even more to play around with in the brick-busting roguelite. The first major free update for the game (one of three that&#8217;s on the cards this year) just arrived on all platforms. It added a bunch more stuff to the mix, including two new characters, eight extra special balls with powerful abilities and an endless mode.Developer Kenny Sun wrote on the PlayStation Blog that because fans demanded it so much, endless mode jumped right to the top of the to-do list. After you beat a level&#8217;s boss, you...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s Grok Is Under EU Investigation Over Sexual Deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musks-grok-is-under-eu-investigation-over-sexual-deepfakes-2000713956</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713956</guid>
      <description>Regulatory scrutiny of nonconsensual sexual image generation is rising. But will it be enough to address the problem?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Microsoft VSCode AI extensions might have hit over 1.5 million users</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/malicious-microsoft-vscode-ai-extensions-might-have-hit-over-1-5-million-users</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oyN82Dqki8UmwAKK4cUKXW</guid>
      <description>Two VSCode extensions are harvesting sensitive data and sending it to China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember the vaguely nightmarish free 4K TV that serves you ads on a second screen? It's off to a rough start &#8212; but apparently, actually does make money</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/remember-the-vaguely-nightmarish-free-4k-tv-that-serves-you-ads-on-a-second-screen-its-off-to-a-rough-start-but-apparently-actually-does-make-money</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b7Y5FG2UstL6byTp7LLQZ</guid>
      <description>Telly isn't doing the big numbers it promised, but thousands of US owners are still enjoying free 4K TVs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duolingo launches Bad Bunny 101 ahead of Super Bowl LX halftime show</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/duolingo-bad-bunny-101-super-bowl-learn-spanish</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043wxsrXXYpckWDg7vS1e8x</guid>
      <description>Duolingo launches "Bad Bunny 101" ahead of the Super Bowl LX halftime show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says a power outage is causing issues with the app in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/tiktok-says-a-power-outage-is-causing-issues-with-the-app-in-the-us-173426617.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c92f4e5-a484-40cc-b29f-ef5732fb73d6</guid>
      <description>If your TikTok feed has felt a little off lately, it's not just you. TikTok says it's working to fix its service in the US following a power outage at one of its data centers that's caused widespread issues in the app. TikTok users have reported problems logging in and uploading videos, as well as with the app's "for you" algorithm."Since yesterday we&#8217;ve been working to restore our services following a power outage at a U.S. data center impacting TikTok and other apps we operate," the company wrote in a statement Monday. "We're working with our data center partner to stabilize our service. We'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you finally read a Kindle book on your Kobo? Amazon launches DRM-free ebooks.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/kindle-launches-drm-free-ebooks</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04pQC2bGvI2SsNwo49QJzoZ</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 20, 2026, Kindle now allows for DRM-free e-books. Here's what this could mean for your library, and if you'll finally be able to read Kindle e-books on a Kobo or other e-reader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 of the best free movies to stream on Tubi, Pluto TV and more this week (January 26)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/5-of-the-best-free-movies-to-stream-on-tubi-pluto-tv-and-more-this-week-january-26</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HdKhtacYHiVp38u2LdYcre</guid>
      <description>Prey is one of the five great movies I recommend streaming for free this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VC firm 2150 raises &#8364;210M fund to solve cities&#8217; climate challenges</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/vc-firm-2150-raises-e210m-fund-to-solve-cities-climate-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086062</guid>
      <description>Europe-based venture fund 2150 raised the money to invest in climate tech startups that help solve cities' carbon footprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La NASA veut utiliser ce logiciel de benchmarking PC gratuit pour ses simulateurs</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/la-nasa-veut-utiliser-ce-logiciel-de-benchmarking-pc-gratuit-pour-ses-simulateurs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322546</guid>
      <description>L'agence spatiale am&#233;ricaine a lanc&#233; une proc&#233;dure officielle pour valider l'usage de CapFrameX. Ce logiciel de benchmarking bien connu des joueurs PC pourrait servir &#224; auditer les performances vid&#233;o des simulateurs de vol de l'agence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avant la hausse des prix annonc&#233;e, ce SSD WD_Black 1 To compatible PC et PS5 qui tourne jusqu&#8217;&#224; 7250 Mo/s est sold&#233; &#224; -39 %</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2955485_avant-la-hausse-des-prix-annoncee-ce-ssd-wd_black-1-to-compatible-pc-et-ps5-qui-tourne-jusqua-7250-mo-s-est-solde-a-39</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2955485_avant-la-hausse-des-prix-annoncee-ce-ssd-wd_black-1-to-compatible-pc-et-ps5-qui-tourne-jusqua-7250-mo-s-est-solde-a-39</guid>
      <description>
Si vous avez besoin de place dans votre machine, que ce soit un PC ou une console Sony, PC Componentes propose le WD_Black SN7100 1 To pour 121,38 euros au lieu de 199,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Olympics: How to watch, schedule of events, and everything else you need to know about the 2026 Milano Cortina games</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/winter-olympics-how-to-watch-schedule-of-events-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-the-2026-milano-cortina-games-172409424.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eca0487b-e039-4319-89d0-8969baa49f32</guid>
      <description>


  The Milano Cortina 2026 Winter Olympics are coming up. (Mattia Ozbot/Getty Images)
 

  Mattia Ozbot via Getty Images
 

The 2026 Winter Olympics are taking place in Italy this year, with all the action taking place in Milan and the Alpine city of Cortina. This year marks the fourth time Italy has hosted the Winter Games; most recently, Turin hosted in 2006. Of the 16 sports that will be featured at the Winter Olympics, there will be 15 returning favorites, including figure skating, Alpine skiing, curling, ice hockey, speedskating, snowboarding, freestyle skiing and ski jumping, and one e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi satirist hacked with Pegasus spyware wins damages in court battle</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/26/saudi-satirist-hacked-with-pegasus-spyware-wins-damages-in-court-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086035</guid>
      <description>The London High Court awarded the London-based satirist and human rights activist Ghanem Al-Masarir more than &#163;3 million, after finding the Saudi government hacked his phone and was likely behind a physical attack targeting him in London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Roborock Q7 M5+ is down to $249.99 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-26-roborock-q7-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">049Grremx0afnt2jQoXYzhA</guid>
      <description>Save 24% on the Roborock Q7 M5+ at Amazon. Now $249.99, this robot vacuum features 10,000Pa suction and a self-emptying dock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm a shopping expert &#8212; here are 12 deals that are actually worth buying at Best Buy's 48-hour flash sale</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/im-a-shopping-expert-here-are-12-deals-that-are-actually-worth-buying-at-best-buys-48-hour-flash-sale</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tZ2CmgZLXdHLqf3bZqgSZD</guid>
      <description>Best Buy has launched a 48-hour sale, and as a shopping expert, I've rounded up the 12 best deals worth buying, including TVs, laptops, iPads, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo gaming laptops are up to $900 off right now - these are the RTX 5070, 5060, and 5050 models I'd buy personally</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/lenovo-gaming-laptops-are-up-to-usd900-off-right-now-these-are-the-rtx-5070-5060-and-5050-models-id-buy-personally</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bSCjVx46kydisAnwvbZJTX</guid>
      <description>The official Lenovo Store has a handy coupon code you can use right now to get some serious savings on the brand's line-up of gaming laptops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Have Mapped the Universe&#8217;s Dark Matter Like Never Before</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/researchers-have-mapped-the-universes-dark-matter-like-never-before-2000713985</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713985</guid>
      <description>This new map is not only the most detailed view of the universe&#8217;s invisible scaffolding to date, it also allows astronomers to look deeper into cosmic history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Un &#233;norme &#233;cart&#160;&#187; : quand Audi et Porsche d&#233;chantent face au logiciel Rivian</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/volkswagen/2955677_un-enorme-ecart-quand-audi-et-porsche-dechantent-face-au-logiciel-rivian</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/volkswagen/2955677_un-enorme-ecart-quand-audi-et-porsche-dechantent-face-au-logiciel-rivian</guid>
      <description>
Vous vous souvenez du soulagement de VW en signant avec Rivian ? Des fuites internes r&#233;v&#232;lent aujourd'hui un logiciel incomplet, incapable de g&#233;rer correctement une climatisation ou des assistances de conduite avanc&#233;es. Pour Audi et Porsche,  le r&#234;ve am&#233;ricain a un go&#251;t de code b&#226;cl&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The Handmaid&#8217;s Tale&#8217; Sequel &#8216;The Testaments&#8217; Is Coming Very Soon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-testaments-release-date-handmaid-tale-hulu-2000714022</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714022</guid>
      <description>Chase Infiniti and Ann Dowd star in Hulu's next adaptation set in Margaret Atwood's dystopian but eerily timely world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clawdbot users are snapping up the Mac Mini &#8212; and it&#8217;s under $500 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-26-apple-mac-mini-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07Fgy8pfAd5yMMp7j2jm8SK</guid>
      <description>The M4 Mac Mini is on sale at Amazon for $499, down from the normal price of $599. That's a 17% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Marvel movies and TV shows do I need to watch before Wonder Man?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/what-marvel-movies-and-tv-shows-do-i-need-to-watch-before-wonder-man</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5YLVAqF3Ro4vfBLaQhh2FE</guid>
      <description>TechRadar reveals the MCU productions you might want to stream before Wonder Man arrives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browser-based attacks hit 95% of enterprises &#8212; and traditional security tools never saw them coming</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/security/browser-security-gap-ciso-enterprise-breaches</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26qfLvnrQfZj7q7fk6BsFf</guid>
      <description>Your web gateway can't see it. Your cloud access broker can't see it. Your endpoint protection can't see it. And yet 95% of organizations experienced browser-based attacks last year, according to Omdia research conducted across more than 1,000 IT and security leaders.Still, three campaigns in 12 months are making the threat more concrete. ShadyPanda infected 4.3 million users through extensions that had been legitimate for seven years. Cyberhaven's security extension was weaponized against 400,000 corporate customers on Christmas Eve. Trust Wallet lost $8.5 million from 2,520 wallets in 48 hou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send Help review: GLOP! Youre not ready for Rachel McAdams latest... but I love it</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/send-help-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ndjQxKTY192ZIQ5RYGx3L</guid>
      <description>Sam Raimi is hitting "Evil Dead" levels of glop with his new movie, "Send Help," and we're here for it.&#160;Rachel McAdams and Dylan O'Brien co-stars. Review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce trou noir primitif est si rapide qu&#8217;il d&#233;fie les lois connues de la physique</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/trou-noir-ce-trou-noir-primitif-si-rapide-quil-defie-lois-connues-physique-w2t8-130481/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/trou-noir-ce-trou-noir-primitif-si-rapide-quil-defie-lois-connues-physique-w2t8-130481/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Des astronomes ont observ&#233; un trou noir supermassif pour le moins surprenant. Seulement 1,5&#160;milliard d&#8217;ann&#233;es apr&#232;s le Big Bang, il se nourrit &#224; un rythme extr&#234;me. Au-del&#224; m&#234;me de la limite th&#233;orique &#233;tablie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI chatbots like ChatGPT are using info from Elon Musks Grokipedia, report reveals</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ai-chatbots-chatgpt-sourcing-elon-musk-grokipedia</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">008XICbWZoS2Gz7E9zNpYqw</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT and other AI chatbots are starting to use Elon Musk's Grokipedia as a source. That's concerning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comment diff&#233;rencier l&#8217;AirTag 1 et l&#8217;AirTag 2 lors de votre achat</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2955637_comment-differencier-lairtag-1-et-lairtag-2-lors-de-votre-achat</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/2955637_comment-differencier-lairtag-1-et-lairtag-2-lors-de-votre-achat</guid>
      <description>
Vous voulez le nouvel AirTag 2, mais vous avez peur de repartir avec un vieux mod&#232;le de 2021 ? C'est normal : ils se ressemblent comme deux gouttes d'eau. Voici quelques conseils.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le retour d&#8217;Unlock Talk avec un gros montage PC et double Matinale : voici notre programme Twitch de la semaine</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2632585_le-retour-dunlock-talk-avec-un-gros-montage-pc-et-double-matinale-voici-notre-programme-twitch-de-la-semaine</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2632585_le-retour-dunlock-talk-avec-un-gros-montage-pc-et-double-matinale-voici-notre-programme-twitch-de-la-semaine</guid>
      <description>
Notre programme Twitch de la semaine du lundi 26 janvier 2026, c&#8217;est juste ici : nous vous donnons rendez-vous, mercredi, jeudi et vendredi sur notre cha&#238;ne Frandroidlive, autant pour siroter votre caf&#233; devant notre Matinale Tech' que pour profiter de la 41e d'Unlock Talk. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal chats show how social media companies discussed teen engagement</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/867845/meta-youtube-snap-tiktok-social-media-trials-documents</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-26T11:46:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=867845</guid>
      <description>Recently released documents show the big business opportunity that social media companies saw in recruiting teens to their platforms and how they discussed risks that heavy digital engagement could pose. The documents were released last week as part of a major set of trials brought by school districts, state attorneys general, and others against Meta, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More AI malware has been found - and this time, crypto developers are under attack</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/more-ai-malware-has-been-found-this-time-targeting-crypto-developers</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xgMiQW2sCrFgiLYbGe9gU7</guid>
      <description>KONNI is using AI-generated backdoors to target crypto bros - and security pros should pay attention.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
