<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:53:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's iPhone Air MagSafe battery pack is cheaper than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-iphone-air-magsafe-battery-pack-is-cheaper-than-ever-144516417.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b81fb587-99ff-4a0a-8491-b9b9460d3e9a</guid>
      <description>We found the iPhone Air to have a pretty decent battery life for such a thin-and-light phone, somewhere in the region of 27 hours if you&#8217;re continuously streaming video. But it's still a phone, arguably your most used device on a daily basis, so you may need to top it up during the day if you're using it constantly. That&#8217;s where Apple&#8217;s iPhone Air MagSafe battery pack comes in, and it&#8217;s currently on sale for $79.


This accessory only works with the iPhone Air, but much like the phone it attaches to, it&#8217;s extremely slim at 7.5mmm, so crucially doesn&#8217;t add so much bulk when attached that it def...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI, Reliance partner to add AI search to JioHotstar</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/openai-reliance-partner-to-add-ai-search-to-jiohotstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094286</guid>
      <description>The rollout includes two-way integration that surfaces streaming links directly inside ChatGPT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-founders behind Reface and Prisma join hands to improve on-device model inference with Mirai</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/co-founders-behind-reface-and-prisma-join-hands-to-improve-on-device-model-inference-with-mirai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094275</guid>
      <description>Mirai raised a $10 million seed to improve how AI models run on devices like smartphones and laptops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super deal sur ce TV Neo QLED Mini LED de 55&#8243; not&#233; 8/10 quasiment &#224; moiti&#233; prix pour une immersion totale</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982999_super-deal-sur-ce-tv-neo-qled-mini-led-de-55-note-8-10-quasiment-a-moitie-prix-pour-une-immersion-totale</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982999_super-deal-sur-ce-tv-neo-qled-mini-led-de-55-note-8-10-quasiment-a-moitie-prix-pour-une-immersion-totale</guid>
      <description>
Le Samsung TQ55QN80F est un t&#233;l&#233;viseur milieu de gamme qui utilise la technologie Mini LED coupl&#233;e &#224; des Quantum Dots pour des couleurs vives et une image contrast&#233;e. Sorti &#224; 1 290 euros, il est brad&#233; &#224; 655 euros sur Ubaldi.com.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polestar d&#233;voile son plan de voitures &#233;lectriques jusqu&#8217;en 2028 avec quelques surprises</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/polestar/2982711_polestar-devoile-son-plan-de-voitures-electriques-jusquen-2028-avec-quelques-surprises</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/polestar/2982711_polestar-devoile-son-plan-de-voitures-electriques-jusquen-2028-avec-quelques-surprises</guid>
      <description>
Accul&#233; par des pertes financi&#232;res importantes, Polestar, sous le giron du constructeur chinois Geely, va sortir l'artillerie lourde. Sous l'impulsion de son nouveau patron, Michael Lohscheller, la marque sino-su&#233;doise d&#233;voile une feuille de route pour le moins ambitieuse avec 4 nouvelles voitures d'ici 2028, avec pour objectif de doubler sa part de march&#233; &#233;lectrique.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor, fitness, bracelet&#8230; Garmin trace le chemin d&#8217;une ann&#233;e 2026 riche en nouveaut&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/garmin/2982821_outdoor-fitness-bracelet-garmin-trace-le-chemin-dune-annee-2026-riche-en-nouveautes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/garmin/2982821_outdoor-fitness-bracelet-garmin-trace-le-chemin-dune-annee-2026-riche-en-nouveautes</guid>
      <description>
Lors d'un appel aux investisseurs, le patron de Garmin a donn&#233; quelques pistes sur les mod&#232;les de montres attendues cette ann&#233;e, mais pas seulement. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo just shadowdropped Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition - Nintendo Switch 2 Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nintendo-just-shadowdropped-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition-nintendo-switch-2-edition</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LCtej5KrX5BMF5BsyoGYah</guid>
      <description>Nintendo just made the surprise announcement that a Switch 2 version of Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition is available to buy right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apr&#232;s le hack des imp&#244;ts, les donn&#233;es de 53 millions de Fran&#231;ais expos&#233;es par une faille de s&#233;curit&#233; critique chez IDMerit</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/securite-applications/2983091_apres-le-hack-des-impots-les-donnees-de-53-millions-de-francais-exposees-par-une-faille-de-securite-critique</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/securite-applications/2983091_apres-le-hack-des-impots-les-donnees-de-53-millions-de-francais-exposees-par-une-faille-de-securite-critique</guid>
      <description>
L'h&#233;catombe continue pour nos donn&#233;es personnelles. Cette fois, c'est un interm&#233;diaire crucial, IDMerit, qui a laiss&#233; ouverte une base de donn&#233;es d'un milliard de comptes clients. Il est tr&#232;s utilis&#233; dans le secteur bancaire.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration is building a website to help Europeans evade content bans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/the-trump-administration-is-building-a-website-to-help-europeans-evade-content-bans</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96JqCiUeMucgAaFtcZNg89</guid>
      <description>The US government is escalating its feud with the EU over free speech by building a dedicated portal that lets users access banned content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest 45W Anker Nano charger with smart display is $10 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-latest-45w-anker-nano-charger-with-smart-display-is-10-off-right-now-160707685.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker rolled out a bunch of new chargers and other gear at CES 2026, including a cute one that's already on sale. The new Nano charger with smart display, which is an upgrade to the existing Nano charger in Anker's lineup, is on sale for $30 right now for Prime members. That's $10 off the regular price.
The 45W charger includes a smart display that shows real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to ensure a longer battery li...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft admits an Office bug exposed confidential user emails to Copilot</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/microsoft-admits-an-office-bug-exposed-confidential-user-emails-to-copilot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">u6pxBqFju7kSYkqHTgZrZa</guid>
      <description>M365 Copilot Chat was summarizing your emails, whether you granted it access or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Sonic&#8217; Movies Have Found Their Amy Rose</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sonic-the-hedgehog-4-amy-rose-voice-actor-kristen-bell-2000723696</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723696</guid>
      <description>Plus, could the new 'Mario' movie include a wild Nintendo crossover?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abxylute&#8217;s new Switch 2 controller prototype has one big problem</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/880971/abxylute-n6-switch-2-hands-on-controller</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880971</guid>
      <description>Gaming accessory company Abxylute has launched a Kickstarter campaign for its upcoming N6 and GameCube-style N9C Switch 2 dock-style controllers. If the ergonomics of Nintendo's Joy-Cons don't jibe with you, these aim to be solid alternatives, particularly for people with medium-to-large-size hands. Both of Abxylute's new controllers have bigger, more comfortable grips than Joy-Cons offer, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This former Big Tech engineers are using AI to navigate Trump&#8217;s trade chaos</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/this-former-big-tech-engineers-are-using-ai-to-navigate-trumps-trade-chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094121</guid>
      <description>Amari AI is making custom AI-powered software that helps customs brokers modernize and minimize constantly shifting trade policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For open-source programs, AI coding tools are a mixed blessing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/for-open-source-programs-ai-coding-tools-are-a-mixed-blessing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094127</guid>
      <description>AI coding tools have enabled a flood of bad code that threatens to overwhelm many projects. Building new features is easier but maintaining them is just as hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future Games Show has announced the hosts for its Spring 2026 showcase, along with the first few games that will be featured next month</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-industry/the-future-games-show-has-announced-the-hosts-for-its-spring-2026-showcase-along-with-the-first-few-games-that-will-be-featured-next-month</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RDECzuVt2Qe5eJsyxTBYE</guid>
      <description>The Future Games Show Spring 2026 showcase has found its hosts in Baldur&#8217;s Gate 3's Devora Wilde and LEGO Batman: Legacy of the Dark Knight's Shai Matheson ahead of the presentation next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft's ROG Xbox Ally X just saw price hikes in Australia and Japan  &#8212; I'm willing to bet that other regions are next</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/xbox/microsofts-rog-xbox-ally-x-just-saw-price-hikes-in-australia-and-japan-im-willing-to-bet-that-other-regions-are-next</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3HkeBtXaek7pmLEtxKj3Nm</guid>
      <description>Microsoft's ROG Xbox Ally X handheld may be the latest victim hit by the ongoing RAM crisis, after price increases in Japan and Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapidata emerges to shorten AI model development cycles from months to days with near real-time RLHF</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/rapidata-emerges-to-shorten-ai-model-development-cycles-from-months-to-days</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1uB8gY2U58meO9VuBxb3gR</guid>
      <description>Despite growing chatter about a future when much human work is automated by AI, one of the ironies of this current tech boom is how stubbornly reliant on human beings it remains, specifically the process of training AI models using reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF). At its simplest, RLHF is a tutoring system: after an AI is trained on curated data, it still makes mistakes or sounds robotic. Human contractors are then hired en masse by AI labs to rate and rank a new model's outputs while it trains, and the model learns from their ratings, adjusting its behavior to offer higher-r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le mini frigo de la Xbox Series X revient &#224; moiti&#233; prix pour avoir toujours une canette fra&#238;che lors de vos parties</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2012608_le-mini-frigo-de-la-xbox-series-x-revient-a-moitie-prix-pour-avoir-toujours-une-canette-fraiche-lors-de-vos-parties</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2012608_le-mini-frigo-de-la-xbox-series-x-revient-a-moitie-prix-pour-avoir-toujours-une-canette-fraiche-lors-de-vos-parties</guid>
      <description>
L'une des plus grandes r&#233;ussites de Microsoft, c'est probablement d'avoir transform&#233; les railleries des internautes sur sa Xbox Series X en monnaie sonnante et tr&#233;buchante, et &#231;a, c'est du g&#233;nie. N&#233; d'une simple blague, le mini frigo Xbox Series X est devenu un v&#233;ritable succ&#232;s commercial et aujourd'hui, sa version de 4,5 litres est disponible &#224; 54,99 euros au lieu de 99,99 euros chez Micromania. 
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's recent blocking of Telegram is reportedly disrupting its military operations in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/russias-recent-blocking-of-telegram-is-reportedly-disrupting-its-military-operations-in-ukraine-135250159.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac0c86d1-6d60-4d1e-be35-374dc721c9ca</guid>
      <description>A decision to ban Telegram on home soil may have backfired on the Kremlin. Last week, Russia went on a blocking spree, banning a number of Western apps in an effort to push domestic users towards Max, an unencrypted state-owned app. One of the restricted apps was WhatsApp (which was also blocked) rival Telegram, a move that drew rare internal criticism from soldiers and pro-war bloggers, with the army being heavily reliant on the cloud-based messaging service for communications.
As reported by Bloomberg, pro-Russian military channels are now complaining that the sudden Telegram blackout &#8212; coup...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#8217;s MAGA v Broligarch in the battle over prediction markets</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/881139/broligarch-prediction-markets</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T08:50:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/881139/bezos-could-have-saved-the-washington-posts-local-news-and-sports-reporters</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers about the love-hate (but mostly hate) relationship between Silicon Valley and Washington. I hope everyone got to celebrate George Washington's birthday in their preferred manner: skiing, staycationing, subscribing to The Verge if you haven't already, etc. Prediction: this is going to be a mess Political [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google adds a camera to Snapseed on iOS</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881260/google-snapseed-ios-camera-manual-controls-film-filters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T08:49:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881260</guid>
      <description>Google has updated the iPhone version of its photo editing app Snapseed with its own camera, including a suite of manual controls and retro film emulation effects. It's the second major update to the app in less than 12 months, after it had previously been left to languish by Google for years. The Snapseed camera [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Altman and Amodei share a moment of awkwardness at India&#8217;s big AI summit</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/altman-and-amodei-share-a-moment-of-awkwardness-at-indias-big-ai-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094313</guid>
      <description>When Prime Minister Narendra Modi prompted speakers at the event to join hands and raise them in a show of unity, all executives on stage obliged, except OpenAI's Sam Altman and Anthropic's Dario Amodei, who held their hands conspicuously apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher dev says the remake will need to rework the Wild Hunt because CD Projekt Red didn't know they were elves at the time &#8212; 'This part will probably need to be changed a bit in the remake'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-witcher-dev-says-the-remake-will-need-to-rework-the-wild-hunt-because-cd-projekt-red-didnt-know-they-were-elves-at-the-time-this-part-will-probably-need-to-be-changed-a-bit-in-the-remake</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">r8HnX8zXuYFa63KMPTmx6n</guid>
      <description>The Witcher's lead story designer, Artur Ganszyniec, has revealed new behind-the-scenes details about the development of the 2007 game ahead of the game's remake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get a four-pack of first-gen AirTags for only $64</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-a-four-pack-of-first-gen-airtags-for-only-64-163619159.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e745850-e368-4111-83ab-157ddbe84ac4</guid>
      <description>Good deals on Apple products aren&#8217;t as frequent as we&#8217;d like them to be, but if there&#8217;s one of the company&#8217;s products that does seem to enjoy pretty regular price cuts, it&#8217;s the AirTag. Right now you can pick up a four-pack of Apple&#8217;s diminutive first-generation Bluetooth trackers for $64, which translates to 35 percent off and a near record low price.
Bear in mind that this deal brings the price per AirTag down to about $16 if you were to buy them individually, and when not on sale they usually cost $29. 


If you use Apple devices and consider yourself to be a serial thing-misplacer, AirTags...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Envie d&#8217;un Air Fryer pas cher ? Celui de Ninja &#224; -33 % est l&#8217;un des meilleurs &#224; ce prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982827_envie-dun-air-fryer-pas-cher-celui-de-ninja-a-33-est-lun-des-meilleurs-a-ce-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982827_envie-dun-air-fryer-pas-cher-celui-de-ninja-a-33-est-lun-des-meilleurs-a-ce-prix</guid>
      <description>
Si vous cherchez &#224; cuisiner plus sainement sans renoncer au croustillant de vos plats pr&#233;f&#233;r&#233;s, optez pour un Air Fryer : Ninja est une marque r&#233;put&#233;e dans ce domaine et son mod&#232;le AF110EU est justement en promotion. Il passe de 99 euros &#224; 66 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; un code promo.&#160;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quand Copilot fouille l&#224; o&#249; il ne devrait pas</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/quand-copilot-fouille-la-ou-il-ne-devrait-pas.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1326889</guid>
      <description>Difficile d'accorder une confiance totale &#224; l'IA g&#233;n&#233;rative quand celle-ci va fouiner dans des dossiers qui lui sont sp&#233;cifiquement interdits. Microsoft, pourtant attendu au tournant sur la s&#233;curit&#233; de ses outils, a laiss&#233; Copilot r&#233;sumer des courriels auxquels il n&#8217;aurait jamais d&#251; acc&#233;der. Le probl&#232;me a depuis &#233;t&#233; corrig&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Music&#8217;s 5 new upgrades are just what the platform needs to one-up Spotify &#8212; but its new UI has users begging for simplicity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/apple-music/apple-musics-5-new-upgrades-are-just-what-the-platform-needs-to-one-up-spotify-but-its-new-ui-has-users-begging-for-simplicity</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VQc35dVfK9foU7pmDKjHXL</guid>
      <description>Apple Music's new features could breathe new life into the platform, but its UI redesign has divided subscribers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le rouleau compresseur automobile chinois ralentit : ce qui explique la crise de ce d&#233;but 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2982895_le-rouleau-compresseur-automobile-chinois-ralentit-ce-qui-explique-la-crise-de-ce-debut-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2982895_le-rouleau-compresseur-automobile-chinois-ralentit-ce-qui-explique-la-crise-de-ce-debut-2026</guid>
      <description>
Vu d&#8217;Europe ou des &#201;tats-Unis, le rouleau compresseur automobile chinois semble inarr&#234;table, port&#233; par une avance technologique ind&#233;niable et des prix agressifs. Pourtant, derri&#232;re cette fa&#231;ade de conqu&#234;te internationale, les constructeurs locaux font face &#224; une r&#233;alit&#233; bien plus complexe en ce d&#233;but d'ann&#233;e 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs smartphones pliables en 2026 ? Samsung Galaxy Z, Honor Magic V, Motorola Razr&#8230; le comparatif</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1617799_meilleur-smartphone-pliant-quel-telephone-pliable-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1617799_meilleur-smartphone-pliant-quel-telephone-pliable-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Les smartphones pliants ont une belle place sur le march&#233;. Tr&#232;s compacts une fois referm&#233;s, ils d&#233;ploient de grands &#233;crans pour une exp&#233;rience visuelle plus agr&#233;able. D&#233;couvrez ici notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs mod&#232;les pliables, test&#233;s et approuv&#233;s par nos soins.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab this Elevation Lab 10-year extended battery case for AirTag for only $16</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/grab-this-elevation-lab-10-year-extended-battery-case-for-airtag-for-only-16-151215800.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61f14f8b-e71c-4724-a1bf-0d7992632921</guid>
      <description>If you're an iPhone user who likes to keep tabs on where your stuff is, you can't go far wrong with an AirTag. The second-gen model that Apple just released outpaces the original in every way (aside from the galling lack of a keyring hole, that is). While it's easy enough to replace the battery in both versions of the AirTag, you might not want to have to worry about the device's battery life for a very long time. Enter Elevation Lab's extended battery case for the AirTag, which is currently on sale at Amazon for $16.
The case usually sells for $23, so that's a 30 percent discount. It's not th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Et si des champs magn&#233;tiques &#233;taient la solution de l'&#233;nigme de l'expansion de l'espace ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-si-champs-magnetiques-etaient-solution-enigme-expansion-espace-131332/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:08:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-si-champs-magnetiques-etaient-solution-enigme-expansion-espace-131332/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Einstein &#233;tait initialement pass&#233; &#224; c&#244;t&#233; de la pr&#233;diction de l'expansion de l'espace faite par sa th&#233;orie de la relativit&#233; g&#233;n&#233;rale. Nous n'avons pas encore perc&#233; tous&#160;les secrets de cette expansion et m&#234;me sa mesure pr&#233;cise rend perplexes les cosmologistes qui se demandent bien ce qui se cache...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thought AMD's FSR had caught up with Nvidia's DLSS? This extensive survey of PC gamers very much suggests otherwise</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/thought-amds-fsr-had-caught-up-with-nvidias-dlss-this-extensive-survey-of-pc-gamers-very-much-suggests-otherwise</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eQZZTijvUsn3izKZ38HKCV</guid>
      <description>DLSS owns FSR in battle of the upscaling techs &#8212; and native 4K can't hold a rendered candle to Nvidia's GPU-booster either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Unlimited Phone Plan: T-Mobile, AT&amp;T, Verizon Compared (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-unlimited-phone-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ab3f852624d1d6458b7880e</guid>
      <description>We sifted through the fine print to figure out how to score the best deal on all the major carriers in 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Predator: Badlands&#8217; Is a Huge Hulu Hit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/predator-badlands-is-a-huge-hulu-hit-2000723826</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723826</guid>
      <description>Director Dan Trachtenberg notched the streamer&#8217;s biggest movie debut since another Trachtenberg-directed &#8216;Predator&#8217; entry: 2022&#8217;s &#8216;Prey.&#8217;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Computer Monitors (2026): Budget, OLED, 4K, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-computer-monitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62ec197954d910713ee4f16f</guid>
      <description>The Gear team spends countless hours in front of displays while writing for you. So we reviewed those too (including a portable screen).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RAM shortage is coming for everything you care about</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/880812/ramageddon-ram-shortage-memory-crisis-price-2026-phones-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880812</guid>
      <description>Maybe you've heard: Memory is expensive now. The price of RAM has tripled, quadrupled, even sextupled depending on the type of chip, all because AI companies are gobbling it up. But maybe you've thought: I don't buy memory sticks! I don't build my own PCs! It won't affect me, right? I'm here to tell you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freeform raises $67M Series B to scale up laser AI manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/freeform-raises-67m-series-b-to-scale-up-laser-ai-manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094239</guid>
      <description>&#8220;I think we're the only quote-unquote manufacturing company out there that has H200 clusters in a data center on site."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hunting Party isn&#8217;t Netflix&#8217;s only new thriller worth watching this weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/the-hunting-party-isnt-netflixs-only-new-thriller-worth-watching-this-weekend</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i3aPW6jfnXyXnfocRmhufL</guid>
      <description>Looking for some high-octane viewing? Stream three of the best new Netflix thriller series, including NBC's hit crime drama The Hunting Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s threat intel chief explains why AI is now both the weapon and the target</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494157/googles-threat-intel-chief-explains-why-ai-is-now-both-the-weapon-and-the-target</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494157/googles-threat-intel-chief-explains-why-ai-is-now-both-the-weapon-and-the-target</guid>
      <description>As rivals and nation-states try to extract proprietary models, John Hultquist says cybersecurity is entering an autonomous era.
Generative AI has rapidly become core infrastructure, embedded across enterprise software, cloud platforms, and internal workflows. But that shift is also forcing a structural rethink of cybersecurity. The same systems driving productivity and growth are emerging as points of vulnerability....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple CarPlay gets a big AI upgrade in iOS 26.4 that lets you talk to ChatGPT, Gemini and Claude &#8212; but there&#8217;s a catch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/car-infotainment/apple-carplay-gets-a-big-ai-upgrade-in-ios-26-4-that-lets-you-talk-to-chatgpt-gemini-and-claude-but-theres-a-catch</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8PtTUwcShYoBDiYBUMXAWZ</guid>
      <description>Apple has opened up CarPlay to conversational AI bots other than Siri, as previously rumored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not going to criticize other games, but all of our voices are done by humans' &#8212; Crimson Desert dev suggests the upcoming game won't feature characters voiced by AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/im-not-going-to-criticize-other-games-but-all-of-our-voices-are-done-by-humans-crimson-desert-dev-suggests-the-upcoming-game-wont-feature-characters-voiced-by-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QVyiu3iG9A7LpdPRGADxnc</guid>
      <description>Pearl Abyss has assured fans that Crimson Desert will be fully voiced by human beings, with marketing director Will Powers confirming that "all the main NPCs and those in side quests have actors' voices".</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
