<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:09:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Box TV&#160;: quel est le meilleur bo&#238;tier TV Android et Apple en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/387028_quelle-box-sous-android-tv-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/387028_quelle-box-sous-android-tv-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Pour regarder Netflix sur sa TV ou pour jouer, les box TV sont d&#233;sormais des produits tr&#232;s efficaces qui viennent compl&#233;ter les fonctions de votre t&#233;l&#233;viseur. Voici notre s&#233;lection de box TV compatibles Android, mais aussi Amazon et Apple.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;It&#8217;s cheaper for you and more profitable for us&#8221;: In 1998, Larry Ellison predicted the world we live in today, where you pay over and over for software you don&#8217;t own</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/its-cheaper-for-you-and-more-profitable-for-us-in-1998-larry-ellison-predicted-the-world-we-live-in-today-where-you-pay-over-and-over-for-software-you-dont-own</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KMfYkWS8CmjmSaewomZBem</guid>
      <description>Larry Ellison&#8217;s 1998 vision of leasing software predicted today&#8217;s cloud subscriptions and the end of traditional software ownership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Et si Donald Trump nous coupait l&#8217;acc&#232;s aux GAFAM ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/politique/2950557_trump-na-aucune-limite-il-peut-tout-couper-la-france-et-leurope-seraient-a-genoux-sans-ces-services-americains</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/politique/2950557_trump-na-aucune-limite-il-peut-tout-couper-la-france-et-leurope-seraient-a-genoux-sans-ces-services-americains</guid>
      <description>
Si &#224; l'&#233;chelle individuelle, il est possible de se passer de nombreux services num&#233;riques am&#233;ricains, certains sont si int&#233;gr&#233;s &#224; nos vies qu'ils sont indispensables. Si l'Europe &#233;tait coup&#233;e des services am&#233;ricains, elle serait vite &#224; genoux sur le plan technologique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Paso airspace closure was reportedly triggered by the CBP&#8217;s use of an anti-drone laser</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/878108/el-paso-airspace-closure-cbp-anti-drone-laser</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T12:02:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878108</guid>
      <description>The hours-long closure of El Paso airspace stemmed from the use of an anti-drone laser deployed by Customs and Border Protection, according to reports from The New York Times and the Associated Press. Sources tell The Times that CBP officials didn't give the Federal Aviation Administration "enough time to assess the risks to commercial aircraft," [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AST SpaceMobile Unfolds the Largest Commercial Communications Array Antenna in Low Earth Orbit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ast-spacemobile-unfolds-the-largest-commercial-communications-array-antenna-in-low-earth-orbit-2000721010</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721010</guid>
      <description>The first of the company's next-generation satellites stretches across 2,400 square feet (223 square meters).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ready to Become Obsessed With the New Horror Film &#8216;Obsession&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/obsession-trailer-curry-barker-blumhouse-2000720656</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720656</guid>
      <description>Curry Barker wrote and directed the twisted, intense new film, out May 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every little thing she does is magic</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/877290/3d-animation-stop-motion-cinema-4d-woman-creator-witch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877290</guid>
      <description>In a style that feels nostalgic and nascent, Bree O'Donnell is crafting her singular vision of a 3D witch named Mary. Through the tiny window of short clips on Instagram and TikTok, Mary's world seems enchanting and vast. Bree's work exudes melancholic emotion and ethereal femininity, painting the surfaces of Mary's world in the vibrating [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is coming to the Apple Vision Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/878097/youtube-apple-vision-pro-visionos-app</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878097</guid>
      <description>The Apple Vision Pro is finally getting an official visionOS YouTube app on Thursday. With the visionOS YouTube app, you'll be able to watch all videos available on YouTube, including standard videos, Shorts, 3D, 360, and VR180 videos, Apple spokesperson Corey Nord tells The Verge. The Vision Pro launched more than two years ago, but [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is coming to Apple Vision Pro &#8212; and it might be the best reason to finally buy one, seriously</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/youtube-is-coming-to-apple-vision-pro-and-it-might-be-the-best-reason-to-finally-buy-one-seriously</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">g8YN2ecH6HhaLTi9Bm6fy8</guid>
      <description>YouTube has finally launched a native app for Apple Vision Pro, eliminating the Safari workaround and bringing the world&#8217;s largest video platform fully into visionOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Vision Pro finally gets a YouTube app today</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/apple-vision-pro-finally-gets-a-youtube-app-today-170000886.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8535746-270a-4860-b9a7-60cabdb1c91c</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s Vision Pro is a curious product &#8212; it initially wowed me two years ago, but it was hard to ignore that the visionOS platform felt incomplete without dedicated apps for YouTube and Netflix. Well, it seems that Google has finally decided to take the Vision Pro seriously, as it&#8217;s launching a YouTube app on the platform today. Previously, you could only view YouTube videos via Safari, or through third-party apps like Tubular Pro.According to an Apple representative, the YouTube Vision Pro app features every video on on the service, including shorts, 360, 3D and VR 180 content. I haven&#8217;t tri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highguard studio lays off 'most' of its team just weeks after the game went live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/highguard-studio-lays-off-most-of-its-team-just-weeks-after-the-game-went-live-165919815.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db26f930-5609-4e75-ac37-f36137f82e4a</guid>
      <description>Wildlight Entertainment, the studio behind Highguard, has laid off many staffers. Level designer Alex Graner wrote in a LinkedIn post that the layoffs impacted "most of the team." The company says it's keeping a "core group of developers to continue innovating on and supporting the game." That sounds like a skeleton crew.
Today we made an incredibly difficult decision to part ways with a number of our team members while keeping a core group of developers to continue innovating on and supporting the game.We're proud of the team, talent, and the product we've created together. We're also gratefu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More U.S. investors sue South Korean government over handling of Coupang data breach</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/more-u-s-investors-sue-south-korean-government-over-handling-of-coupang-data-breach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092220</guid>
      <description>Coupang&#8217;s massive data breach has sparked U.S. investor lawsuits against the South Korean government over alleged discrimination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snuggle up for the big freeze: these heated blankets, warming cushions, and fan heaters from Argos will keep you snug from just &#163;25</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/snuggle-up-for-the-big-freeze-these-heated-blankets-warming-cushions-and-fan-heaters-from-argos-will-keep-you-snug-from-just-gbp25</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UZ2V2FCrsQQdv6bMcD5uHB</guid>
      <description>Cold weather is on the way this weekend, so make sure you're prepared with the right tech to keep you toasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec cette r&#233;duction de 25 %, ces &#233;couteurs sans fil de Bose poss&#232;dent l&#8217;un des meilleurs rapports qualit&#233;-prix du moment</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2975221_avec-cette-reduction-de-25-ces-ecouteurs-sans-fil-de-bose-possedent-lun-des-meilleurs-rapports-qualite-prix-du-moment</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2975221_avec-cette-reduction-de-25-ces-ecouteurs-sans-fil-de-bose-possedent-lun-des-meilleurs-rapports-qualite-prix-du-moment</guid>
      <description>
Pour s'isoler du monde ext&#233;rieur sans se ruiner, vous pourrez compter sur les Bose QuietComfort Earbuds et il est difficile de trouver des &#233;couteurs sans fil qui cochent autant de cases pour moins de 150 euros comme c'est le cas dans ces offres.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp is completely blocked in Russia, as authorities route users to this messaging site</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491731/whatsapp-completely-blocked-russia-authorities-route-users-messaging-site</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:48:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491731/whatsapp-completely-blocked-russia-authorities-route-users-messaging-site</guid>
      <description>A WhatsApp spokesperson said the block is intended to &#8220;drive users to a state-owned surveillance app.&#8221;
Russia has attempted to fully block WhatsApp in the country, the company said, the latest move in an ongoing government effort to tighten control over the internet.A WhatsApp spokesperson said late Wednesday that the Russian authorities&#8217; action was intended to &#8220;drive users to a state-owned surveillance app,&#8221; a reference to Russia&#8217;s own state-supported MAX messaging app that&#8217;s seen by critics as a surveillance tool.&#8220;Trying to isolate over 100 million people from private and secure communicatio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm sick of RAM-hogging Google Chrome slowing my laptop to a crawl, so the Asus Vivobook 16's record-low price at Best Buy is seriously tempting</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/im-sick-of-ram-hogging-google-chrome-slowing-my-laptop-to-a-crawl-so-the-asus-vivobook-16s-record-low-price-at-best-buy-is-seriously-tempting</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LhzB8Krrr33RM7Qm2co9gZ</guid>
      <description>I'm terrible for having multiple apps and websites open at once while I work, so it's about time I get a new laptop - and the Asus Vivobook 16 could be perfect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This underrated monitor accessory has made a world of difference to my eyes when gaming and working on my PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/this-underrated-monitor-accessory-has-made-a-world-of-difference-to-my-eyes-when-gaming-and-working-on-my-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DeVS466nGnT8aBhadRj79h</guid>
      <description>This monitor accessory has reduced my eyestrain immensely, and is one of the most underrated things you can add to a gaming setup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel VPN by Google gets a Quick Settings upgrade to boost usability</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/pixel-vpn-by-google-gets-a-quick-settings-upgrade-to-boost-usability</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oozoDNPhep3cooFj8YEDSF</guid>
      <description>Pixel VPN by Google is rolling out a usability-focused update that adds live connection status to its Quick Settings tile, making it easier to check whether your VPN is connected, paused, or having issues at a glance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Super League 2026: free streams, preview for rugby league season</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/super-league-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">h8bakajwLNeNcLzAbiKEY9</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Super League 2026 live streams for FREE, with Jake Connor's Leeds and Bevan French's Wigan gunning for Mikey Lewis's Hull KR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI expert predicted AI would end humanity in 2027&#8212;now he&#8217;s changing his timeline</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491098/ai-expert-predicted-ai-would-end-humanity-2027-now-hes-changing-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491098/ai-expert-predicted-ai-would-end-humanity-2027-now-hes-changing-timeline</guid>
      <description>The former OpenAI employee has rescheduled the end of the world.
Daniel&#160;Kokotajlo&#160;predicted the end of the world would happen in April 2027.&#160;In&#160;&#8220;AI 2027&#8221; &#8212; a document outlining the impending impacts of&#160;AI, published in April 2025 &#8212; the former OpenAI employee and several peers announced that by April 2027, unchecked AI development would lead to superintelligence and consequently destroy&#160;humanity....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec l&#8217;iPhone Fold, Apple pourrait enterrer les smartphones pliants &#224; clapet</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/avec-liphone-fold-apple-pourrait-enterrer-les-smartphones-a-clapet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325754</guid>
      <description>Malgr&#233; des prix toujours tr&#232;s &#233;lev&#233;s, les smartphones pliants au format &#171;&#160;livre &#187; ont toutes les chances de devenir le format dominant cette ann&#233;e. Et avec le lancement attendu de l'&#171;&#160;iPhone Fold &#187; cet automne, ce design devrait d&#233;finitivement s'imposer au d&#233;triment des mod&#232;les &#224; clapet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,200 Ubisoft workers went on strike in response to company restructuring and mandatory return-to-work policy</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/1200-ubisoft-workers-went-on-strike-in-response-to-company-restructuring-and-mandatory-return-to-work-policy-163714986.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f828b810-94cc-45cf-a358-ab1af2fe1aa2</guid>
      <description>At the end of last month, Ubisoft workers in the publisher&#8217;s native France threatened to strike in the wake of sweeping layoffs and cost-cutting measures. This week, they made good on those threats. According to GamesIndustry.biz, union members confirmed that at least 1,200 staff participated in the three-day strike, which was due to run from February 10 to February 12.
While the strike action primarily took place in France, GamesIndustry.biz was told that Ubisoft&#8217;s Milan office also took part. The union Solidaires Informatique, which represents French workers from a number of companies in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Gorilla Tag is weathering the VR winter</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/877473/gorilla-tag-vr-winter-quest</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T11:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877473</guid>
      <description>This is Lowpass by Janko Roettgers, a newsletter on the ever-evolving intersection of tech and entertainment, syndicated just for The Verge subscribers once a week. The VR industry has been on edge since Meta's massive job cuts earlier this year: One exec called the layoff announcements "one of VR's darkest weeks." There's talk of a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome ships WebMCP in early preview, turning every website into a structured tool for AI agents</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/google-chrome-ships-webmcp-in-early-preview-turning-every-website-into-a</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cQJGeecbys9C1cUUOrOpJ</guid>
      <description>When an AI agent visits a website, it&#8217;s essentially a tourist who doesn&#8217;t speak the local language. Whether built on LangChain, Claude Code, or the increasingly popular OpenClaw framework, the agent is reduced to guessing which buttons to press: scraping raw HTML, firing off screenshots to multimodal models, and burning through thousands of tokens just to figure out where a search bar is.That era may be ending. Earlier this week, the Google Chrome team launched WebMCP &#8212; Web Model Context Protocol &#8212; as an early preview in Chrome 146 Canary. WebMCP, which was developed jointly by engineers at Go...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is rewriting 70 years of lending rules</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491780/how-ai-is-rewriting-70-years-of-lending-rules</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:26:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491780/how-ai-is-rewriting-70-years-of-lending-rules</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence provides the clearest path toward a fair and accurate credit ecosystem. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular Microsoft Outlook add-in has been hijacked to try and steal user accounts - here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-popular-microsoft-outlook-add-in-has-been-hijacked-to-try-and-steal-user-accounts-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeVZoHf2pjPSvkRQ7mD69f</guid>
      <description>A Microsoft Outlook add-in was abandoned and taken over by hackers, who used it to collect email accounts and banking data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day is actually a great time to buy a TV &#8212; here are 13 deals that I recommend from Samsung, Sony, and LG</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/presidents-day-is-actually-a-great-time-to-buy-a-tv-here-are-15-deals-that-i-recommend-from-samsung-sony-and-lg</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fzbMiyFf2LeKr3nNyaapHM</guid>
      <description>Presidents' Day is the perfect time to buy a new TV, and as TechRadar's deals editor, I've rounded up 11 TVs that I recommend from Samsung, LG, and TCL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The surprising case for AI judges</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/877299/ai-arbitrator-bridget-mccormack-aaa-arbitration-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T11:22:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877299</guid>
      <description>Today, we&#8217;re going to talk about the role AI might play in deciding legal disputes. Not just drafting memos and doing research &#8212; actually deciding who&#8217;s right and who&#8217;s wrong, and who should pay. My guest today is Bridget McCormack, the former chief justice for the Michigan Supreme Court and now president and CEO of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch PlayStation's hour-long State of Play and what to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/how-to-watch-playstations-hour-long-state-of-play-and-what-to-expect-162128585.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88840c35-375f-4401-8480-4fd502e3ed66</guid>
      <description>PlayStation&#8217;s first State of Play of the year is shaping up to be quite newsworthy. While Sony hasn&#8217;t revealed too much about what it will show off (with one notable exception), the stream is slated to last for over an hour, so there should be at least some interesting stuff. The showcase will get underway at 5PM ET on February 12. You can click the play button on the YouTube video above to watch the State of Play in English when the time is right.The PlayStation YouTube channel is hosting alternative versions of the stream. One has English subtitles and the other is in Japanese. Otherwise, yo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher 4 might have just gained a BioWare veteran as CD Projekt Red hires new AI director &#8212; 'Amazing things to come!'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-witcher-4-might-have-just-gained-a-bioware-veteran-as-cd-projekt-red-hires-new-ai-director-amazing-things-to-come</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GGpUkJWLBf9QkdZj54BemC</guid>
      <description>CD Projekt Red has hired a new AI director, Dorian Kieken, a former BioWare developer with credits on the Mass Effect series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Spotify vient de saccager leur api &#187; : le service de streaming provoque de nouveau l&#8217;ire de ses utilisateurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/services/streaming-musical/2975707_spotify-vient-de-saccager-leur-api-le-service-de-streaming-provoque-de-nouveau-lire-de-ses-utilisateurs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/services/streaming-musical/2975707_spotify-vient-de-saccager-leur-api-le-service-de-streaming-provoque-de-nouveau-lire-de-ses-utilisateurs</guid>
      <description>
C'est un nouveau bad buzz pour Spotify. Le service de streaming musical coupe dans l'acc&#232;s aux d&#233;veloppeurs externes. C'est tout un &#233;cosyst&#232;me qui pourrait s'&#233;teindre.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get two years of Proton VPN for 70 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-two-years-of-proton-vpn-for-70-percent-off-right-now-123000652.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dac4d6ed-e475-4c0c-80c0-7c390227395c</guid>
      <description>Proton VPN is offering a steep discount on its Proton VPN Plus subscription, with the two-year plan currently priced at $2.99 per month. You&#8217;ll pay $72 upfront for 24 months of service, which amounts to 70 percent off the usual monthly rate and brings the long-term cost well below what many premium VPNs typically charge.We&#8217;ve consistently been impressed by Proton VPN&#8217;s focus on privacy, its nonprofit ownership structure and the way it balances security features with strong real-world speeds. It&#8217;s a top pick in our best VPN guide, and this promotion also appears in our running list of the best ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPN use soars in Argentina following anti-piracy blocks &#8211; here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/vpn-use-soars-in-argentina-following-anti-piracy-blocks-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nZFYoWZYKgvmrgfFs4cyp8</guid>
      <description>Proton VPN and Windscribe have both recorded spikes starting from Monday (February 9). This coincides with the decision to block two major pirated streaming sites in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS announces the end of its &#8220;surge operation&#8221; in Minneapolis, but not entirely</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/878017/dhs-ends-minneapolis-operation-metro-surge-tom-homan</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T11:11:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878017</guid>
      <description>The government's siege of the Twin Cities is reportedly coming to an end. "I have proposed, and President Trump has concurred, that this surge operation conclude," border czar Tom Homan announced Thursday. This isn't the first time Department of Homeland Security officials have claimed that Operation Metro Surge, its massive campaign in Minnesota, was slowing [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Come for the Air-Powered Display, Stay for the Accidental ASMR</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/come-for-the-air-powered-display-stay-for-the-accidental-asmr-2000720763</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720763</guid>
      <description>Satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A filmmaker needs a deep personal connection to the material': The Mortuary Assistant director on why he wanted to turn the horror game into a movie</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/a-filmmaker-needs-a-deep-personal-connection-to-the-material-the-mortuary-assistant-director-on-why-he-wanted-to-turn-the-horror-game-into-a-movie</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TVemUMjRuWeseDkrDZHR4H</guid>
      <description>The Mortuary Assistant video game was very special to Jeremiah Kipp, inspiring him to adapt it into a movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Noir looks like a hard-boiled thriller in first trailer</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/877922/spider-noir-trailer-release-date-amazon-mgm-plus</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T11:01:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877922</guid>
      <description>Though it's going to be a while before we see more of Sony's animated Spider-Verse or Marvel's live-action take on Peter Parker, Amazon's Spider-Noir series is right around the corner. Today, Amazon dropped a new trailer for its upcoming Spider-Noir starring Nicolas Cage as a brooding Spider-Man variant. Set in an alternate reality where it's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test des Sony WF-1000XM6 : la claque audiophile</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2970723_test-sony-wf-1000xm6-la-claque-audiophile</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2970723_test-sony-wf-1000xm6-la-claque-audiophile</guid>
      <description>
Les Sony WF-1000XM6 d&#233;barquent avec une feuille de route ambitieuse : bousculer la hi&#233;rarchie &#233;tablie par les AirPods Pro 3, les Bose QuietComfort Ultra 2nd et consorts. Au programme, puce QN3e, transducteurs sp&#233;cialement d&#233;velopp&#233;s, LDAC, 360 Reality Audio et collaboration avec quatre ing&#233;nieurs du son. Mais que vallent-ils exactement ? 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic shelf labels mean grocery stores can now change their prices anytime they want, in seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488571/electronic-shelf-labels-grocery-shopping-kroger-elizabeth-warren</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:00:32</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488571/electronic-shelf-labels-grocery-shopping-kroger-elizabeth-warren</guid>
      <description>The makers of electronic shelf labels defend their polarizing rollout by retailers like Kroger, while consumer advocates, including Sen. Elizabeth Warren, sound the alarm about how the tech will raise prices for Americans.
Perusing the grocery aisle in the Westside Market on 23rd Street in Manhattan, you might not even notice the screens. They look just like paper price labels and, alongside a bar code, use a handwriting-style font we&#8217;ve come to associate with a certain merchant folksiness. They&#8217;re not particularly bright or showy. The only clues that they&#8217;re not ordinary sticky shelf labels a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Trailer for &#8216;Spider-Noir&#8217; Teases a Comic Book Thriller</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spider-noir-tv-show-trailer-release-date-2000720163</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720163</guid>
      <description>Can Spider-Noir crack the case and save New York? We'll find out when the series hits Prime Video this spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony WF-1000XM6: Yes, These Wireless Earbuds Sound That Good</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-wf-1000xm6-yes-these-wireless-earbuds-sound-that-good-2000720319</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720319</guid>
      <description>Sony's WF-1000XM6 are my new favorite earbuds for sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sony WF-1000XM6 earbuds reclaim the noise-canceling crown</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/877503/sony-wf-1000xm6-earbuds-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877503</guid>
      <description>Apple, Bose, and Sony are in a running battle for the best noise-canceling earbuds, and the Sony WF-1000XM6 put Sony back in first place - if you can get a good fit with the included foam tips. With each iteration of the XM series, Sony has aimed for - and delivered - incredible noise-canceling performance [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo&#8217;s next-gen robotaxi is ready for passengers &#8212; and also &#8216;high-volume production&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/877902/waymo-sixth-generation-robotaxi-ojai-hyundai-sensors-cost</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877902</guid>
      <description>After years of testing and validation, Waymo announced today that it's sixth-generation robotaxi technology is finally ready for passenger trips. The updated autonomous driving system will first be rolled out for employees and their friends in San Francisco and Los Angeles, with public customers to follow. Waymo's current fleet of Jaguar I-Pace vehicles runs on [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed Sony's flagship WF-1000XM6 earbuds &#8212; and it's another case of 'great sound, impressive features, middling noise cancellation'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/sony-wf-1000xm6-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">emdCZ7HSx9GkbNtPxYKPMa</guid>
      <description>Sony's WF-1000XM6 are smaller again and the sound is admirable, but while there's an extra mic per bud, I'm not sure it's being perfectly utilised here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony officially unveils the WF-1000XM6 flagship earbuds &#8212; here are the 5 big upgrade areas you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/sony-officially-unveils-the-wf-1000xm6-flagship-earbuds-here-are-the-5-big-upgrade-areas-you-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SZ7gtthLZjYpJssfWZGWc6</guid>
      <description>New design, new sound, new features &#8212; Sony's changed a lot in its new earbuds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony WF-1000XM6 review: Facing tougher competition</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/sony-wf-1000xm6-review-facing-tougher-competition-160000652.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">657b184a-1fdb-4dfe-a4b0-a601ed2bb079</guid>
      <description>Sony&#8217;s 1000X earbuds have been at the top of Engadget&#8217;s best wireless earbuds list since we first published it. With each new generation, the company managed to retain its crown, primarily thanks to a massive collection of features and an effective mix of sound quality and active noise cancellation (ANC) performance. Today, Sony revealed the latest entry in the series, the WF-1000XM6, delivering yet another redesign both inside and out. The company&#8217;s tried and true formula of features and audio performance remains, but it may no longer be enough to elevate the M6 above the competition.&#160;&#160;


Des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI inference costs dropped up to 10x on Nvidia's Blackwell &#8212; but hardware is only half the equation</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/ai-inference-costs-dropped-up-to-10x-on-nvidias-blackwell-but-hardware-is</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">J1OCbwEZ2jIY0mZtDG5P8</guid>
      <description>Lowering the cost of inference is typically a combination of hardware and software. A new analysis released Thursday by Nvidia details how four leading inference providers are reporting 4x to 10x reductions in cost per token.The dramatic cost reductions were achieved using Nvidia's Blackwell platform with open-source models. Production deployment data from Baseten, DeepInfra, Fireworks AI and Together AI shows significant cost improvements across healthcare, gaming, agentic chat, and customer service as enterprises scale AI from pilot projects to millions of users.The 4x to 10x cost reductions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook&#8217;s new profile animation feature is Boomerang for the AI era</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491254/facebook-animate-profile-picture-with-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491254/facebook-animate-profile-picture-with-ai</guid>
      <description>The feature is part of a wider push toward AI content in Meta apps.
Meta announced on February 10 that it&#8217;s introducing a new AI animation feature that lets users turn their still profile photos into AI-generated looping videos. It reads like an uncanny valley version of yesteryear&#8217;s Boomerang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Van Der Beek&#8217;s death rekindles a painful question about U.S. healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491693/james-van-der-beeks-death-rekindles-a-painful-question-about-u-s-healthcare</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491693/james-van-der-beeks-death-rekindles-a-painful-question-about-u-s-healthcare</guid>
      <description>Auctioned memorabilia, medical debt, and a GoFundMe campaign tell a familiar American story.
James Van Der Beek was one of the biggest stars of the late 1990s and early 2000s. His family still couldn&#8217;t afford the cost of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony WF-1000XM6 : une nouvelle r&#233;f&#233;rence des &#233;couteurs sans fil &#224; r&#233;duction de bruit</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2973271_sony-wf-1000xm6-une-nouvelle-reference-des-ecouteurs-sans-fil-a-reduction-de-bruit</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2973271_sony-wf-1000xm6-une-nouvelle-reference-des-ecouteurs-sans-fil-a-reduction-de-bruit</guid>
      <description>
Les Sony WF&#8209;1000XM6 marquent l&#8217;arriv&#233;e d&#8217;une nouvelle g&#233;n&#233;ration d&#8217;&#233;couteurs intra&#8209;auriculaires sans fil haut de gamme, avec une r&#233;duction de bruit annonc&#233;e comme la plus performante du march&#233; et de nombreuses am&#233;liorations face aux WF&#8209;1000XM5.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Galaxy S26 is looming - and Google is already aggressively price-cutting the Pixel 10 series</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-galaxy-s26-is-looming-and-google-is-already-aggressively-price-cutting-the-pixel-10-series</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EDsjSn3SkDZqXjnpbYpAAf</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S26 series is coming, but here's why you may want to consider the still-excellent Google Pixel 10 series (Hint: they're super cheap right now).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange et Sosh offrent des cadeaux &#224; leurs abonn&#233;s les plus fid&#232;les</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/orange-sosh-offrent-cadeaux-abonnes-fideles.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325693</guid>
      <description>Les abonn&#233;s Sosh et Orange voient (enfin, diront certains) leur fid&#233;lit&#233; r&#233;compens&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day sales 2026: The best tech deals to shop this week from Apple, Sony, Samsung and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/presidents-day-sales-2026-the-best-tech-deals-to-shop-this-week-from-apple-sony-samsung-and-others-163000831.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba4f502-86ba-4c79-a2ff-b27b6e52c38b</guid>
      <description>Presidents&#8217; Day is a great time to buy appliances, mattresses and furniture as they are often on sale for the holiday. Tech also gets discounted around this time, but you have to do a bit more digging to find actually good deals. And this year, Presidents&#8217; Day comes right after Valentine&#8217;s Day and Super Bowl 2026, which means there are some overlapping sales to consider. If you don&#8217;t want to sort through the mess of bad deals out there, Engadget has you covered. We&#8217;re curating the best President Day sales on tech we can find right here. We&#8217;ll update this post through the holiday as more deals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Votre montre connect&#233;e pourrait rep&#233;rer des signes avant une rechute d&#233;pressive</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2975521_votre-montre-connectee-pourrait-reperer-des-signes-avant-une-rechute-depressive</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2975521_votre-montre-connectee-pourrait-reperer-des-signes-avant-une-rechute-depressive</guid>
      <description>
D'apr&#232;s une &#233;tude publi&#233;e cette semaine, les montres connect&#233;es seraient efficaces pour analyser les risques de rechute d&#233;pressive en se basant sur le sommeil et l'activit&#233; des utilisateurs. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparatif des imprimantes multifonctions 2026 : quelle est la meilleure selon vos besoins ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/684861_guide-imprimantes-jet-encre-laser</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/684861_guide-imprimantes-jet-encre-laser</guid>
      <description>
Une imprimante multifonction avec scanner est toujours utile &#224; la maison (ou au bureau !). Nous avons s&#233;lectionn&#233; et rassembl&#233; les meilleures imprimantes multifonctions pour tous les budgets.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec cette offre, il est enfin possible de trouver une PlayStation 5 pour moins de 450 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2975445_avec-cette-offre-il-est-enfin-possible-de-trouver-une-playstation-5-pour-moins-de-450-e</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2975445_avec-cette-offre-il-est-enfin-possible-de-trouver-une-playstation-5-pour-moins-de-450-e</guid>
      <description>
L'&#233;dition fat de la PS5 se fait de plus en plus rare tant le mod&#232;le Slim a pris sa place. Cependant, PC Componentes remet la version originale sur le devant de la sc&#232;ne avec cette promotion de 100 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge OneFly data breach sees traveler IDs and payment details leaked</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/huge-onefly-data-breach-sees-traveler-ids-and-payment-details-leaked</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PPhpXtwtagLnxBqGGZE7eX</guid>
      <description>Full payment data, in cleartext, was leaked, affecting at least 6,000 OneFly customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Les poign&#233;es d&#8217;urgence ? C&#8217;est pour nos techniciens&#160;&#187; : l&#8217;&#233;trange choix de Rivian pour les portes de ses voitures &#233;lectriques</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/rivian/2975383_les-poignees-durgence-cest-pour-nos-techniciens-letrange-choix-de-rivian-pour-les-portes-de-ses-voitures-electriques</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/rivian/2975383_les-poignees-durgence-cest-pour-nos-techniciens-letrange-choix-de-rivian-pour-les-portes-de-ses-voitures-electriques</guid>
      <description>
Alors que le SUV &#233;lectrique R2 se d&#233;voile progressivement avant son lancement pr&#233;vu en mars, Rivian fait face &#224; une controverse inattendue. Le syst&#232;me de verrouillage &#233;lectronique des portes, et surtout ses dispositifs d'urgence, divise les clients. Le directeur logiciel de la marque d&#233;fend un choix technique qui interroge sur la priorit&#233; donn&#233;e &#224; la s&#233;curit&#233; des passagers.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the &#8216;baby food method&#8217; can help you accomplish your biggest goals</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480879/how-baby-food-method-can-help-you-accomplish-your-biggest-goals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T15:34:38</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480879/how-baby-food-method-can-help-you-accomplish-your-biggest-goals</guid>
      <description>The secret to tackling big things is to take them on one small bite at a time.
January filled our inboxes with productivity advice. Set stretch goals! Think bigger! Dream audaciously! What was conspicuously absent from all that exhortation was any practical guidance on how to move from grand vision to daily action without becoming paralyzed by the enormity of what we&#8217;ve committed to.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple acquires all rights to &#8216;Severance,&#8217; will produce future seasons in-house</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/apple-acquires-all-rights-to-severance-will-produce-future-seasons-in-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092395</guid>
      <description>The show is expected to run for four seasons, with the possibility of spin-offs, a prequel, and foreign versions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Presidents' Day sales: Get the Apple Watch Series 11 for $299, plus more deals</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apple-presidents-day-sales-get-the-apple-watch-series-11-for-299-plus-more-deals-151616971.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78902e66-331a-45a8-8c59-e293650f49bb</guid>
      <description>If you need a little help with your New Year's resolution to be more active, you can save on the latest Apple Watch right now. The Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for $299 for Presidents' Day, which is $100 off and the lowest price we've seen. A number of other Apple devices are on sale for the holiday as well.
We named the Apple Watch Series 11 as our choice for best smartwatch overall. It scored a 90 in our review thanks to its 24 hours-plus of battery life and a thin, light design that's easy to wear. It also offers new health metrics, including Apple's hypertension alerts system and Sleep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ByteDance&#8217;s next-gen AI model can generate clips based on text, images, audio, and video</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/877931/bytedance-seedance-2-video-generator-ai-launch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T10:26:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877931</guid>
      <description>Big Tech's race to leapfrog the latest AI models continues with the launch of ByteDance's next-gen video generator. In a blog post, ByteDance - the China-based company behind TikTok - says Seedance 2.0 supports prompts that combine text, images, video, and audio. The company claims it "delivers a substantial leap in generation quality," offering improvements [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un vrai-faux drone abattu par un laser&#160;? La confusion est totale apr&#232;s la fermeture de l&#8217;espace a&#233;rien au Texas</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/un-vrai-faux-drone-abattu-par-un-laser-la-confusion-est-totale-apres-la-fermeture-de-lespace-aerien-au-texas.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325715</guid>
      <description>Mauvaise surprise ce mardi soir : les autorit&#233;s am&#233;ricaines de l'aviation ont d&#233;cid&#233; de fermer l'espace a&#233;rien autour d'El Paso, au Texas, pendant dix jours pour des raisons de s&#233;curit&#233;. Une d&#233;cision extraordinaire et qui n'a finalement dur&#233; que dix heures. Mais des questions demeurent sur la raison de cette fermeture exceptionnelle, la version officielle, peu claire, &#233;tant contest&#233;e....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom has a host of new AI tools it thinks can supercharge your productivity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/zoom-has-a-host-of-new-ai-tools-it-thinks-can-supercharge-your-productivity</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4F4gAk77Jqu6tmmjQM3CbS</guid>
      <description>After the launch of Zoom AI Companion 3.0, Zoom is adding even more tools to make its agentic AI platform "proactive," not "reactive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeForce Now d&#233;barque sur Amazon Fire TV et PC Linux avec une s&#233;lection de nouveaux jeux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/cloud-gaming/2975461_geforce-now-debarque-sur-amazon-fire-tv-et-pc-linux-avec-une-selection-de-nouveaux-jeux</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/cloud-gaming/2975461_geforce-now-debarque-sur-amazon-fire-tv-et-pc-linux-avec-une-selection-de-nouveaux-jeux</guid>
      <description>
Nvidia a lanc&#233; une application officielle de son service GeForce Now sur une partie de la gamme de dispositifs fonctionnant sous Fire TV, mais aussi sur les PC sous Linux, permettant d&#233;sormais de jouer &#224; des jeux via le cloud. Cette extension s&#8217;accompagne de nouveaux titres.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11&#160;: Microsoft va ressusciter la barre des t&#226;ches personnalisable</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/windows-11-microsoft-va-ressusciter-la-barre-des-taches-personnalisable.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325712</guid>
      <description>Microsoft doit sauver le navire Windows 11. La firme de Redmond, qui a promis d&#8217;am&#233;liorer la stabilit&#233; de son OS pour 2026. Et pour satisfaire les utilisateurs, l&#8217;entreprise va s&#8217;attaquer &#224; sa tr&#232;s critiqu&#233;e barre des t&#226;ches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major staffing cuts are coming to D.C.&#8217;s Kennedy Center ahead of its 2-year closure</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491715/major-staffing-cuts-coming-d-c-s-kennedy-center-ahead-2-year-closure</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-12T15:13:09</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491715/major-staffing-cuts-coming-d-c-s-kennedy-center-ahead-2-year-closure</guid>
      <description>Tax records from 2025 show about 2,500 people were employed at the venue during the 2023 calendar year. 
As the Trump administration prepares to close the Kennedy Center for a two-year renovation, the head of Washington&#8217;s performing arts center has warned its staff about impending cuts that will leave &#8220;skeletal teams.&#8221;In a Tuesday memo obtained by the Associated Press, Kennedy Center President Richard Grenell told staff that &#8220;departments will obviously function on a much smaller scale with some units totally reduced or on hold until we begin preparations to reopen in 2028,&#8221; promising &#8220;permanen...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
