<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:56:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Gozney Dome (Gen 2) might be the ultimate backyard pizza oven &#8211; but its pro features come with a steep price tag</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/gozney-dome-gen-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nBbLxiNiv6tZpjCNHfJ58S</guid>
      <description>The Gozney Dome (Gen 2) may be a pizza oven first and foremost, but it's ability to be used as a fully-fledged outdoor kitchen makes it invaluable for budding chefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG and Dolby partner to release the first FlexConnect soundbar</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846608/lg-dolby-flexconnect-speakers-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846608</guid>
      <description>Dolby Atmos FlexConnect technology debuted this year with the TCL Z100 speakers, and now we're getting our first FlexConnect soundbar thanks to LG. The new H7 soundbar - which runs on the same Alpha 11 Gen 3 chip as LG's OLEDs and new Micro RGB LED - is a part of the LG Sound Suite, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG&#8217;s 2026 TVs and soundbars get the Dolby Atmos FlexConnect treatment</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lgs-2026-tvs-and-soundbars-get-the-dolby-atmos-flexconnect-treatment</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dzkz9Fy5UwFojNrordFBuh</guid>
      <description>LG's Sound Suite speakers and soundbar will make setting up a Dolby Atmos home theater sound system easier than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried talking to Google Maps with Gemini, and it actually understood what I wanted</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/gemini/i-tried-talking-to-google-maps-with-gemini-and-it-actually-understood-what-i-wanted</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZqsymxvJd7HP8V3rrdtBY</guid>
      <description>With Gemini now integrated into Google Maps, navigation becomes conversational and context-aware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolby and LG introduce a modular home audio system for CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/dolby-and-lg-introduce-a-modular-home-audio-system-for-ces-2026-010000126.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6914371d-6ad7-43ef-b34f-ab037db29c8a</guid>
      <description>LG is teaming up with Dolby for a new collection of speakers that the companies are unveiling ahead of CES 2026. The LG Sound Suite features a modular lineup the H7 soundbar, M7 and M5 wireless surround speakers and the W7 subwoofer. The speakers can be combined in more than two dozen different configurations, from a pair to a full 13.1.7 channel surround sound home theater setup.The main pitch of the LG Sound Suite is its application of Dolby Atmos FlexConnect. This is the audio brand's tech for optimizing sound from wherever wireless speakers are placed. It's meant to deliver optimal sound e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe hit with proposed class-action, accused of misusing authors&#8217; work in AI training</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/adobe-hit-with-proposed-class-action-accused-of-misusing-authors-work-in-ai-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077070</guid>
      <description>The lawsuit is just the latest in a string of copyright-related legal complaints aimed at the AI industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;I think $2.3 billion says you might be wrong on that&#8217;: James Cameron shoots down critics of 3D in Avatar, as fresh lawsuit emerges from animator</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/i-think-usd2-3-billion-says-you-might-be-wrong-on-that-james-cameron-shoots-down-critics-of-3d-in-avatar-as-fresh-lawsuit-emerges-from-animator</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">A7Y26ojRSCmBN8YpcEffHA</guid>
      <description>The lawsuit claims Cameron copied the story for Avatar: The Way of Water from a fellow animator's original sci-fi idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reportedly has a prototype EUV machine built by ex-ASML employees</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/china-reportedly-has-a-prototype-euv-machine-built-by-ex-asml-employees-235833756.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54abef41-f21b-4871-b840-cb54c0eb95d5</guid>
      <description>A report from Reuters claims that scientists in China have created a prototype of a machine that could eventually be used to produce semiconductor chips capable of powering artificial intelligence. Sources told the publication that a team in Shenzhen completed the prototype of an extreme ultraviolet lithography machine earlier this year and it is allegedly now undergoing testing. The EUV machine was reportedly made by former engineers from Dutch semiconductor supplier ASML. Reuters states that China is targeting production of its own EUV chips beginning in 2028, although other experts have pro...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
