<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:33:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking graphics card was broken, until this YouTuber repaired the Nvidia RTX 5070 Ti &#8212; then used it to dominate this 8K GPU benchmark</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/record-breaking-graphics-card-was-broken-until-this-youtuber-repaired-the-nvidia-rtx-5070-ti-then-used-it-to-dominate-this-8k-gpu-benchmark</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NtQSSGRTJrBQ5Vn26px6Qc</guid>
      <description>An RTX 5070 Ti graphics card with a hole in it wasn't just brought back to life &#8211; a YouTuber broke a GPU world record with it, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra leak reveals its big camera overhaul &#8211; here are 5 changes to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-leak-reveals-its-big-camera-overhaul-here-are-5-changes-to-expect</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RLodh8xpVZnqyuJZSuRBR9</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra's cameras could have a new look, better hardware, and improved processing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Is Rolling xAI Into SpaceX&#8212;Creating the World&#8217;s Most Valuable Private Company</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/spacex-acquires-xai-elon-musk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69811ed989a6549d64641b2a</guid>
      <description>By fusing SpaceX and xAI&#8212;which acquired X last year&#8212;Elon Musk tightens his grip over technologies that shape national security, social media, and artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo raises $16B to scale robotaxi fleet internationally</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/02/waymo-raises-16-billion-round-to-scale-robotaxi-fleet-london-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088954</guid>
      <description>The round, led by Dragoneer Investment Group, DST Global, and Sequoia Capital, now values the autonomous vehicle company at $126 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moltbook, the AI social network, exposed human credentials due to vibe-coded security flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/moltbook-the-ai-social-network-exposed-human-credentials-due-to-vibe-coded-security-flaw-230324567.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">037e5db3-0c41-4fbb-8b4b-5990d2273c3e</guid>
      <description>Moltbook bills itself as a social network for AI agents. That's a wacky enough concept in the first place, but the site apparently exposed the credentials for thousands of its human users. The flaw was discovered by cybersecurity firm Wiz, and its team assisted Moltbook with addressing the vulnerability. The issue appears to be the result of the entire Reddit-style forum being vibe-coded; Moltbook's human founder posted a few days ago on X that he "didn't write one line of code" for the platform and instead directed an AI assistant to create the whole setup.&#160;According to the blog post from Wiz...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-4o is going away on February 13 &#8212; here are 5 ways you can survive the upcoming 4o-pocalypse</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/chatgpt-4o-is-going-away-on-february-13-here-are-5-ways-you-can-survive-the-upcoming-4o-pocalypse</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EYRScJZJU6DLcmRUDZnWen</guid>
      <description>As OpenAI prepares to retire ChatGPT-4o, here are 5 practical ways you can adapt, protest, or keep using the model you love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Animate is shutting down next month</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/872731/adobe-animate-app-shutdown-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T17:58:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872731</guid>
      <description>Adobe is pulling the plug on Adobe Animate. In a FAQ posted to Adobe's website, the company says it will stop selling the animation software on March 1st, citing the emergence of new platforms "that better serve the needs of the users." Users have until March 1st, 2027 (or March 1st, 2029 for enterprise customers) [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Ring Wants to Wash Away Your Surveillance Concerns With Lost Puppies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ring-wants-to-wash-away-your-surveillance-concerns-with-lost-puppies-2000716802</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716802</guid>
      <description>Every technology has positives and negatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Pretty Please, I Don&#8217;t Want to Be a Magical Girl&#8217; Has the Juice</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pretty-please-i-dont-want-to-be-a-magical-girl-has-the-juice-2000716465</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716465</guid>
      <description>The animatic webseries is getting some well-deserved love and standing out as an indie darling to watch for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo raises $16 billion to take its robotaxi business &#8216;global&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/872651/waymo-raises-16-billion-investment-value-robotaxi</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T17:30:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872651</guid>
      <description>Waymo announced a $16 billion investment round aimed at bringing its robotaxi business to more US cities, as well as some overseas markets. The funding round was led by Dragoneer Investment Group, a "crossover" firm known for investing in late-stage tech companies before they go public. Waymo's co-CEOs said in a blog post they would [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda has finally given us a new trailer for Fallout 3 and Fallout: New Vegas&#8230; but it isn&#8217;t quite what I had in mind</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/bethesda-has-finally-given-us-a-new-trailer-for-fallout-3-and-fallout-new-vegas-but-it-isnt-quite-what-i-had-in-mind</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">n3p6YRRzHpU76G3QFrj7Ug</guid>
      <description>The Fallout 3 and Fallout: New Vegas rumors continue to swirl as Bethesda drops a new trailer for the games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s SpaceX officially acquires Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI, with plan to build data centers in space</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/02/elon-musk-spacex-acquires-xai-data-centers-space-merger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088937</guid>
      <description>The merger creates the world's most valuable private company, and paves the way for Musk to try and prove out the usefulness of space-based data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle chases $50 billion for AI buildout as doubts mount on Wall Street</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485608/oracle-chases-50-billion-ai-buildout-wall-street-doubts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T22:17:24</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485608/oracle-chases-50-billion-ai-buildout-wall-street-doubts</guid>
      <description>The software giant wants to expand its cloud infrastructure, even as its stock trails and investor concerns deepen.
Oracle shares fell 2% Monday following the company&#8217;s announcement it planned to raise upwards to $50 billion in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk's SpaceX has acquired his AI company, xAI</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/elon-musks-spacex-has-acquired-his-ai-company-xai-221617040.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc76b481-2ec2-4d81-8af5-053fc4db5885</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s SpaceX has acquired Musk&#8217;s xAI, the companies announced. The merger will &#8220;form the most ambitious, vertically-integrated innovation engine on (and off) Earth, with AI, rockets, space-based internet, direct-to-mobile device communications and the world&#8217;s foremost real-time information and free speech platform,&#8221; Musk wrote in an update.The AI company that right now is best known for its CSAM-generating chatbot might seem like a strange fit for a rocket company. But SpaceX is key to Musk&#8217;s latest scheme to build AI data centers in space. In his update, Musk wrote that &#8220;global electric...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One job where AI stepping up isn't such a problem - AI-assisted cybersecurity team discovers mass of OpenSSL vulnerabilities, praised for 'high quality of the reports and their constructive collaboration'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-might-be-one-job-where-ai-stepping-up-isnt-such-a-problem-ai-assisted-cybersecurity-team-discovers-mass-of-openssl-vulnerabilities-praised-for-high-quality-of-the-reports-and-their-constructive-collaboration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2owxxDBYciqPKxievQiYRK</guid>
      <description>AI-assisted analysis revealed 12 long-standing OpenSSL vulnerabilities, exposing the limits of manual review and accelerating coordinated remediation across critical internet infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft fires employee who publicly criticized its RTO plan</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ubisoft-fires-employee-who-publicly-criticized-its-rto-plan-220913747.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11e7f272-fc8b-4167-bc55-096c33c2e509</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft continues to raise eyebrows around how it is treating employees as it attempts a business overhaul. David Michaud-Cromp, a level design team lead at Ubisoft Montreal, said last week that he was suspended for three days without pay after voicing opposition to the company's return to office mandate. Today, Michaud-Cromp posted on LinkedIn that he has been fired. "I was terminated by Ubisoft, effective immediately," he wrote. "This was not my decision."A spokesperson for Ubisoft gave Kotaku the following statement regarding Michaud-Cromp's dismissal: "Sharing feedback or opinions respectf...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best Apple Watch deals available right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21289209/best-apple-watch-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T17:08:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21289209/best-apple-watch-deals</guid>
      <description>In September, Apple launched its latest fleet of smartwatches, including the Apple Watch Series 11, the SE 3, and the Ultra 3. Each wearable offers something a little different (their prices indicate their breadth of features), and we&#8217;re already starting to see big price drops. Additionally, we&#8217;re still recommending some recent predecessors in Apple&#8217;s portfolio, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX rach&#232;te xAI : Elon Musk veut &#171; rendre le soleil conscient &#187; avec des bases lunaires et des serveurs orbitaux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/spacex/2963685_spacex-rachete-xai-elon-musk-fusionne-ses-entreprises-pour-lia-spatiale</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/spacex/2963685_spacex-rachete-xai-elon-musk-fusionne-ses-entreprises-pour-lia-spatiale</guid>
      <description>
L'IA consomme trop d'&#233;lectricit&#233; sur Terre ? Elon Musk a la solution : l'envoyer en orbite. En fusionnant SpaceX et xAI, le milliardaire veut d&#233;ployer des millions de tonnes de serveurs gr&#226;ce au Starship. L'objectif est de b&#226;tir une infrastructure capable de capturer l'&#233;nergie pure du Soleil.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed the Yamaha True X Surround 90A Dolby Atmos soundbar, and its spatial positioning is as good as it gets &#8212; but boy does it come at a price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/i-reviewed-the-yamaha-true-x-surround-90a-dolby-atmos-soundbar-and-its-spatial-positioning-is-as-good-as-it-gets-but-boy-does-it-come-at-a-price</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6MThLtWM6vdkysaDaatPvm</guid>
      <description>The Yamaha True X Surround 90A is an impressive flagship Dolby Atmos soundbar system, but it comes at a big price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans Tesla-style doors because they&#8217;re a public safety hazard</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485331/china-bans-tesla-style-doors-because-theyre-a-public-safety-hazard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485331/china-bans-tesla-style-doors-because-theyre-a-public-safety-hazard</guid>
      <description>Beijing is outlawing the concealed, electronic door handles commonly found in EVs.  
China has become the first nation to outlaw the Tesla-style concealed door handle. Demanded by Elon Musk against the safety concerns of his own engineers, the handle and its electronic opening mechanism have been implicated in multiple fatal incidents where trapped passengers couldn&#8217;t open their doors from the inside, and emergency rescuers could not access from the outside.The Chinese Ministry of Industry and Information Technology issued new safety rules, mandating all cars sold in the country must feature a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is leading the fight against hidden car door handles</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/02/china-is-leading-the-fight-against-hidden-car-door-handles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 21:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088714</guid>
      <description>The Chinese government issued a new rule that goes into effect January 1, 2027.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major California Union Calls for Waymo to Be Kicked Off the Streets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/major-california-union-calls-for-waymo-to-be-kicked-off-the-streets-2000716937</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716937</guid>
      <description>Teamsters California wants to see Waymo&#8217;s operating license suspended over safety concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk merges SpaceX with xAI (and X)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/872619/elon-musk-merges-spacex-with-xai-and-x</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T16:53:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872619</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is merging two of the companies that he leads, SpaceX and xAI (which also owns X), into one. According to an announcement from Musk: SpaceX has acquired xAI to form the most ambitious, vertically-integrated innovation engine on (and off) Earth, with AI, rockets, space-based internet, direct-to-mobile device communications and the world's foremost real-time [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Elon Musk&#8217;s emails with Jeffrey Epstein derail his very important year?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/872450/elon-musk-jeffrey-epstein-emails-spacex-ipo-tesla</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-02T16:49:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=872450</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Department of Justice released a trove of documents related to its case against Jeffrey Epstein, its largest to date. Amid the millions of files were many mentions of Elon Musk. A search of Musk's name in the department's database results in at least 1,500 hits. Since the release, Musk has been - [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumors point to a surprise Nintendo Direct later this week: What we know</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nintendo-direct-partner-february-2026-rumors-speculation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 21:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06bAnkcnBdOW0SCfZByFGew</guid>
      <description>Multiple sources are saying a Nintendo Direct will happen this week, but it might not be the kind you think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Picked the Stupidest Possible Week to Go Back to the Moon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-picked-the-stupidest-possible-week-to-go-back-to-the-moon-2000716954</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 21:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716954</guid>
      <description>Artemis 2 could launch as early as this coming weekend. If it does, the 10-day mission will have to compete with the Olympics and Super Bowl for media attention.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
