<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:10:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the brands bringing ads to ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/877148/openai-chatgpt-advertisers-target-adobe-audible</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T11:08:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877148</guid>
      <description>OpenAI officially launched its advertising pilot in ChatGPT, leaving us with a better idea of the kinds of products we might see stuffed beneath our conversations with the AI chatbot. Several companies have announced plans to show ads inside ChatGPT - placements that will reportedly cost them a pretty penny - ranging from major retailers [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean hackers use AI-generated video to deliver malware for macOS and Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/north-korean-hackers-use-ai-generated-video-to-deliver-malware-for-macos-and-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K7o8hWxFXYQq3us4fU6zo7</guid>
      <description>UNC1069 has gotten super creative lately, using a mix of Business Telegram Compromise, deepfakes, and malware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFR annonce la SFR Box 10, une nouvelle box internet Wi-Fi 7 &#171;&#160;accessible &#224; tous les clients&#160;&#187;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sfr/2974133_sfr-annonce-la-sfr-box-10-une-nouvelle-box-internet-wi-fi-7-accessible-a-tous-les-clients</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sfr/2974133_sfr-annonce-la-sfr-box-10-une-nouvelle-box-internet-wi-fi-7-accessible-a-tous-les-clients</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s Bouygues Telecom en janvier, c'est maintenant &#224; SFR de lancer une nouvelle box internet Wi-Fi 7 abordable. L'op&#233;rateur au carr&#233; rouge annonce le lancement prochain de la SFR Box 10, actuellement en d&#233;veloppement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Showrunner Isn&#8217;t Worried About Becoming &#8216;Game of Thrones&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-game-of-thrones-ending-george-r-r-martin-2000720594</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720594</guid>
      <description>Unlike the latter stages of 'Thrones', or the controversies of 'House of the Dragon', 'Knight' is planning on keeping George R.R. Martin involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reanimal wants to devour you</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/876355/reanimal-review-ps5-xbox-switch-steam</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876355</guid>
      <description>The woods in Reanimal are full of surprises. You will encounter human cadavers that slither like snakes, gigantic talking pigs, and, at one point, a forlorn, supersized whale who seems resigned to an agonizingly slow death. These variously monstrous beings inhabit a realm that, though it looks like our own, seems to defy spatial logic: [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Founders Fund VC Sam Blond launches AI sales startup to upend Salesforce</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/former-founders-fund-vc-sam-blond-launches-ai-sales-startup-to-upend-salesforce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091318</guid>
      <description>The startup, Monaco, has come out of stealth as an AI-native all-in-one CRM plus more system backed by names like the Collison brothers and Garry Tan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upside Robotics is reducing fertilizer use and waste in corn crops</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/upside-robotics-is-reducing-fertilizer-use-and-waste-in-corn-crops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091866</guid>
      <description>Upside Robotics builds autonomous solar-powered robots that can help farmers reduce their fertilizer use by 70%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched Chris Hemsworth's new movie Crime 101 &#8212; and the heist thriller commits too many offences to be the Marvel megastar's best non-MCU film</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/crime-101-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oeghzmMGCrnaafoznW48ee</guid>
      <description>Crime 101 is a somewhat engaging cat-and-mouse story, but commits too many offences to be a genre classic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox&#160;: la v&#233;rification d&#8217;&#226;ge vire au cauchemar pour les joueurs</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/xbox-la-verification-dage-vire-au-cauchemar-pour-les-joueurs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325482</guid>
      <description>M&#234;me quand on s'appelle Microsoft, la v&#233;rification de l'&#226;ge ne va pas de soi. La nuit derni&#232;re, de nombreux joueurs anglais ont eu la mauvaise surprise de voir leur partie brutalement interrompue par une demande de contr&#244;le d&#8217;&#226;ge&#8230; qui, dans bien des cas, ne fonctionnait pas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony's new WF-1000XM6 elite earbuds seem to be imminent &#8212; here are 3 upgrades I hope to see, as a headphones reviewer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/sonys-new-wf-1000xm6-elite-earbuds-seem-to-be-imminent-here-are-3-upgrades-i-hope-to-see-as-a-headphones-reviewer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CZ66TTAn7ot7vzrwMg7vz8</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s been nearly three years since the Sony WF-1000XM5; there are some open goals for Sony to improving on in the new version, which it's teasing heavily for a launch this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Pharmacy to expand same-day delivery to nearly 4,500 US cities</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/amazon-pharmacy-to-expand-same-day-delivery-to-nearly-4500-us-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091906</guid>
      <description>The expansion will cover customers in newly served states such as Idaho and Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surtaxes UE&#160;: voici le premier v&#233;hicule &#233;lectrique made in China officiellement exempt&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/surtaxes-ue-voici-le-premier-vehicule-electrique-made-in-china-officiellement-exempte.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325427</guid>
      <description>Le Cupra Tavascan devient officiellement le premier mod&#232;le produit en Chine &#224; &#233;chapper aux lourdes surtaxes douani&#232;res de l'UE. Une victoire strat&#233;gique pour Volkswagen qui pourrait bien faire jurisprudence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA reopens Texas airspace after declaring a 10-day block on flights to and from El Paso</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490893/faa-reopens-texas-airspace-after-declaring-10-day-block-flights-el-paso</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T15:38:06</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490893/faa-reopens-texas-airspace-after-declaring-10-day-block-flights-el-paso</guid>
      <description>The closure would have grounded all flights to and from El Paso International Airport. 
The Federal Aviation Administration reopened the airspace around El Paso International Airport in Texas on Wednesday morning, just hours after it announced a 10-day closure that would have grounded all flights to and from the airport.The Federal Aviation Administration said in a social media post that it has lifted the temporary closure of the airspace over El Paso, saying there was no threat to commercial aviation and that all flights will resume.Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said in a post on X that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NanoClaw solves one of OpenClaw's biggest security issues &#8212; and it's already powering the creator's biz</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/nanoclaw-solves-one-of-openclaws-biggest-security-issues-and-its-already</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WV7X4jTsjfHjqMqMFebym</guid>
      <description>The rapid viral adoption of Austrian developer Peter Steinberger's open source AI assistant OpenClaw in recent weeks has sent enterprises and indie developers into a tizzy.It's easy to easy why: OpenClaw is freely available now and offers a powerful means of autonomously completing work and performing tasks across a user's entire computer, phone, or even business with natural language prompts that spin up swarms of agents. Since its release in November 2025, it's captured the market with over 50 modules and broad integrations &#8212; but its "permissionless" architecture raised alarms among develope...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi cette rivale de la GoPro et de la DJI Osmo Action devient incontournable avec cette baisse de 20 % ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2973883_pourquoi-cette-rivale-de-la-gopro-et-de-la-dji-osmo-action-devient-incontournable-avec-cette-baisse-de-20</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2973883_pourquoi-cette-rivale-de-la-gopro-et-de-la-dji-osmo-action-devient-incontournable-avec-cette-baisse-de-20</guid>
      <description>
Bonne nouvelle pour les baroudeurs&#8239;: l&#8217;Insta360 Ace Pro 2, une cam&#233;ra d&#8217;action id&#233;ale pour immortaliser vos aventures, voit son prix chuter de 469 &#224; 379&#8239;euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoir un PC gamer neuf tous les ans : HP lance un abonnement pour louer son ordinateur</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hp/2973963_avoir-un-pc-gamer-neuf-tous-les-ans-hp-lance-un-abonnement-pour-louer-son-ordinateur</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hp/2973963_avoir-un-pc-gamer-neuf-tous-les-ans-hp-lance-un-abonnement-pour-louer-son-ordinateur</guid>
      <description>
C'est une petite r&#233;volution silencieuse qui pourrait bien changer notre rapport au mat&#233;riel informatique. HP lance un programme audacieux aux &#201;tats-Unis : des PC portables gaming haut de gamme disponibles via un abonnement mensuel, sans option d'achat final. Fini la propri&#233;t&#233;, place &#224; l'usage pur et dur.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit&#8217;s Gemini-powered AI health coach is rolling out to iOS users &#8211; here&#8217;s how to get it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitbits-gemini-powered-ai-health-coach-is-rolling-out-to-ios-users-heres-how-to-get-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HrbrmPWwns4Hp6hKEbDPZQ</guid>
      <description>Fitbit has expanded its Google Gemini-powered AI health coach to iOS users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick up Apple's Magic Mouse while it's on sale for $68</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/pick-up-apples-magic-mouse-while-its-on-sale-for-68-152708776.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db9ace1c-df7d-4478-9957-f3e8dd33594e</guid>
      <description>Amazon has a rare discount on Apple's USB-C Magic Mouse right now. You can grab the white version for $68, which is 14 percent off its usual price.
The multi-touch mouse was first released in 2009 with a modest refresh released in 2015 and the addition of a USB-C port in 2024. The rechargeable mouse features gesture controls and automatically pairs with your Mac when connected via USB. The Magic Mouse can also be used with an iPad via Bluetooth, or with a Windows PC, though in that case, functionality would be limited. 
Famously, Jony Ive's design of the Magic Mouse sees its charge port on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consent is broken. How do we fix it?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/consent-is-broken-how-do-we-fix-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vKiFj2yxmtrii6fwBjWiTb</guid>
      <description>The consent process is designed for compliance, not for people, but how do we fix it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;I&#8217;m losing one of the most important people in my life&#8221; &#8212; the true emotional cost of retiring ChatGPT-4o</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/im-losing-one-of-the-most-important-people-in-my-life-the-true-emotional-cost-of-retiring-chatgpt-4o</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gQ7F9Kfeu9jXea3YyBhcA8</guid>
      <description>The retirement of ChatGPT-4o has triggered an emotional backlash, revealing how deeply people can bond with AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day sales 2026: The best early tech deals to shop this week from Apple, Sony, Samsung and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/presidents-day-sales-2026-the-best-early-tech-deals-to-shop-this-week-from-apple-sony-samsung-and-others-163000257.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba4f502-86ba-4c79-a2ff-b27b6e52c38b</guid>
      <description>Presidents&#8217; Day is a great time to buy appliances, mattresses and furniture as they are often on sale for the holiday. Tech also gets discounted around this time, but you have to do a bit more digging to find actually good deals. And this year, Presidents&#8217; Day comes right after Valentine&#8217;s Day and Super Bowl 2026, which means there are some overlapping sales to consider. If you don&#8217;t want to sort through the mess of bad deals out there, Engadget has you covered. We&#8217;re curating the best President Day sales on tech we can find right here. We&#8217;ll update this post through the holiday as more deals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraft Heinz announces it&#8217;s pausing plans to split into 2 companies. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491032/kraft-heinz-announces-its-pausing-plans-to-split-into-2-companies-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T15:19:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491032/kraft-heinz-announces-its-pausing-plans-to-split-into-2-companies-heres-why</guid>
      <description>CEO Steve Cahillane says the company&#8217;s issues are &#8216;fixable.&#8217;
Kraft Heinz said Wednesday it&#8217;s pausing its plans to split into two companies.Steve Cahillane, a former Kellogg chief who became CEO of Kraft Heinz on January 1, said he wants to ensure that all of the company&#8217;s resources are focused on profitable growth.&#8220;I have seen that the opportunity is larger than expected and that many of our challenges are fixable and within our control,&#8221; Cahillane said in a statement.The company&#8217;s shares dropped 5.2% in early trading Wednesday as Kraft Heinz reported lower quarterly and annual results.Kraft H...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why 2026 is the year AI finally understands the work behind the work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/why-2026-is-the-year-ai-finally-understands-the-work-behind-the-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SFFNTQFTX2PckVNAyd5Lci</guid>
      <description>How AI can now understand your work's context.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hair Extensions Found to Contain Dozens of Hazardous Chemicals</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hair-extensions-found-to-contain-dozens-of-hazardous-chemicals-2000720464</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720464</guid>
      <description>Researchers found that a majority of tested brands contained potentially hazardous chemicals, including flame retardants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les ventes de ces smartphones explosent en France, merci la crise de la RAM ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fairphone/2973931_les-ventes-de-ces-smartphones-explosent-en-france-merci-la-crise-de-la-ram</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fairphone/2973931_les-ventes-de-ces-smartphones-explosent-en-france-merci-la-crise-de-la-ram</guid>
      <description>
Alors que la crise de la RAM freine les envies d'achats des consommateurs, une marque de smartphones enregistre des chiffres records sur 2025.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobs report: a surprising 130,000 jobs were added in January, but Labor Department makes major revisions to last year&#8217;s numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490907/jobs-report-surprising-130000-jobs-added-january-labor-dept-makes-major-revisions-last-years-numbers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T15:02:03</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490907/jobs-report-surprising-130000-jobs-added-january-labor-dept-makes-major-revisions-last-years-numbers</guid>
      <description>The Labor Department said unemployment fell to 4.3%.
U.S. employers added a surprisingly strong 130,000 jobs last month, but government revisions cut 2024-2025 U.S. payrolls by hundreds of thousands.The unemployment rate fell to 4.3%, the Labor Department said Wednesday.The report included major revisions that reduced the number of jobs created last year to just 181,000, weakest since the pandemic year of 2020, and less than half the previously reported 584,000.The job market has been sluggish for months even though the economy is registering solid growth.But the January numbers came in strong...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diesel&amp;#8217;s wired earbuds look exactly like wired earbuds from Diesel</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/877091/diesel-60458-wired-earbuds-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T10:01:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877091</guid>
      <description>Despite evidence to the contrary, not only are wired earbuds alive and well, they're enjoying a resurgence. Brands like Belkin and even respected headphone maker Master &amp; Dynamic now offer tethered earbuds again. Even the Italian fashion brand Diesel has decided wired headphones are still cool and has launched a pair of earbuds it describes [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Year in &#8216;Magic: The Gathering&#8217; Brought Some Good News for Classic Players</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/magic-the-gathering-sales-2025-lorwyn-eclipsed-records-universes-beyond-2000720572</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720572</guid>
      <description>'Magic' fans who fear the game's future being dominated by crossovers have a glimmer of hope in Hasbro's latest financial earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures serrures connect&#233;es en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guide-dachat-maison-connectee/840576_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-serrures-connectees-en-2021</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guide-dachat-maison-connectee/840576_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-serrures-connectees-en-2021</guid>
      <description>
Une serrure connect&#233;e permet de s&#233;curiser votre porte, vous permettant de l'ouvrir via un code, votre smartphone ou votre smartwatch. Nous avons s&#233;lectionn&#233; pour vous les meilleurs mod&#232;les de serrures et de verrous connect&#233;s du march&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Switch 2&#8217;s GameShare multiplayer turns this horror game into an unexpected comedy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/876621/nintendo-switch-2-gameshare-tokyo-scramble</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876621</guid>
      <description>GameShare, a multiplayer feature that's exclusive to the Switch 2, is a neat concept that so far has mostly been used in pretty standard ways. It lets you use one copy of a game and beam it to multiple Switches, making it a great way to experience local co-op titles like Survival Kids or Split [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a pipeline and close deals with an exhibit table at TechCrunch Disrupt 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/build-a-pipeline-and-close-deals-with-an-exhibit-table-at-techcrunch-disrupt-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091829</guid>
      <description>Get an unmatched ROI by exhibiting your startup in front of 10,000 tech leaders and investors at TechCrunch Disrupt 2026, October 13-15 in San Francisco. Book your table now before it's gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Thursday, February 12 (game #1480)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-12-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">giP2uJucjerbGrYdpoFqNg</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Thursday, February 12 (game #977)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-12-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7nK54BBUyNSpNMF4RJRr5m</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Thursday, February 12 (game #711)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-12-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zrK6ps2MPm7pTiRgR3UzUi</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber Eats&#8217; new Cart Assistant feature is an AI hack for your grocery shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/uber-eats-new-cart-assistant-feature-is-an-ai-hack-for-your-grocery-shopping-145733478.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3141fdbf-2909-459c-8c2c-7efa25f1d494</guid>
      <description>If there&#8217;s any area of your life that you might be willing to introduce more AI into, it&#8217;s likely something as mundane as grocery shopping. That&#8217;s what Uber is betting on with its new AI-powered feature in the Uber Eats app.
Cart Assistant lets you "build grocery baskets faster and with less effort" by using AI to automatically fill your basket with items included on your shopping list. To use it, you search for a supported grocery store on the home screen of the app and tap the new Cart Assistant icon that appears at the top of the screen.
From there, you can either manually type out a shoppi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's new 45W Nano charger with smart display is on sale for $10 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/ankers-new-45w-nano-charger-with-smart-display-is-on-sale-for-10-off-160707585.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker rolled out a bunch of new chargers and other gear at CES 2026, including a cute one that's already on sale. The new Nano charger with smart display, which is an upgrade to the existing Nano charger in Anker's lineup, is on sale for $30 right now when you clip an on-page coupon on Amazon. That's $10 off the regular price.
The 45W charger includes a smart display that shows real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware, this fake site offers up a malicious 7-Zip installer laced with malware</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/beware-this-fake-site-offers-up-a-malicious-7-zip-installer-laced-with-malware</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sV9EbGQe4dU5t2mpgpsn9G</guid>
      <description>Fake 7zip.com site sounds incredible, but don't be fooled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images rares et spectaculaires d&#8217;une com&#232;te qui s&#8217;est disloqu&#233;e sous les yeux des plus grands t&#233;lescopes</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-images-rares-spectaculaires-comete-disloquee-sous-yeux-plus-grands-telescopes-131154/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:51:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-images-rares-spectaculaires-comete-disloquee-sous-yeux-plus-grands-telescopes-131154/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Une com&#232;te s'est bris&#233;e en plusieurs morceaux en passant pr&#232;s du Soleil. Il s'agit de C/2025 K1 dont la fin a &#233;t&#233; immortalis&#233;e par des t&#233;lescopes, ce qui met fin &#224;&#160;quelques mois d'observation pour cette visiteuse &#233;ph&#233;m&#232;re.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don&#8217;t need Ring Search Party to find your lost dog. Privacy advocates and pet lovers say try this instead</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490852/you-dont-need-ring-search-party-to-find-your-lost-dog-privacy-advocates-and-pet-lovers-say-try-this-instead</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T14:51:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490852/you-dont-need-ring-search-party-to-find-your-lost-dog-privacy-advocates-and-pet-lovers-say-try-this-instead</guid>
      <description>After a Super Bowl commercial for Amazon&#8217;s home security brand raised eyebrows, a popular dog community weighed in with alternatives.
There are few things everyone can rally behind as much as finding a lost dog. But what if that mission is actually a workaround for mass surveillance?&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok launches an opt-in Local Feed in the U.S. leveraging users&#8217; precise location</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/tiktok-launches-an-opt-in-local-feed-in-the-u-s-leveraging-users-precise-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091882</guid>
      <description>TikTok's new Local Feed will show you nearby shopping, dining, events, news, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance de masse&#160;: et si les sonnettes Ring traquaient bien plus que des chiens disparus&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/surveillance-de-masse-et-si-les-sonnettes-ring-traquaient-bien-plus-que-des-chiens-disparus.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325455</guid>
      <description>Comment faire accepter la surveillance de masse ? En mettant les toutous &#224; contribution, pardi ! &#199;a n'est &#233;videmment pas le message qu'a voulu faire passer Amazon pour faire la promotion des sonnettes connect&#233;es Ring, mais c'est celui qu'ont entendu de nombreux internautes craignant le pire pour leur vie priv&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Simple but dangerous&#8217; &#8211; Top VPNs targeted by typosquatting as 14% of fake domains found to be malicious</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/simple-but-dangerous-top-vpns-targeted-by-typosquatting-as-14-percent-of-fake-domains-found-to-be-malicious</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KNXSGWNhwTqNTHxJahwj5V</guid>
      <description>Major providers including NordVPN, ExpressVPN, and Proton VPN are among those targeted by lookalike domains. Here's how to stay safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A good way of dealing with overpopulation&#8217;: Epstein files reveal how the rich fuel climate denialism</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490280/epstein-files-how-ultra-wealthy-peddle-climate-denialism</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T14:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490280/epstein-files-how-ultra-wealthy-peddle-climate-denialism</guid>
      <description>Jeffrey Epstein and his vast network of elite figures routinely traded in myths that undermine climate progress. Experts say it&#8217;s not an accident. 
The trove of documents released by the Department of Justice (DOJ) in relation to Jeffrey Epstein have revealed just how close the convicted child sex offender and financier was to all sorts of politicians, academics, business leaders, and other prominent figures....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone Air MagSafe battery is cheaper than ever right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-iphone-air-magsafe-battery-is-cheaper-than-ever-right-now-144516705.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b81fb587-99ff-4a0a-8491-b9b9460d3e9a</guid>
      <description>We found the iPhone Air to have a pretty decent battery life for such a thin-and-light phone, somewhere in the region of 27 hours if you&#8217;re continuously streaming video. But it's still a phone, arguably your most used device on a daily basis, so you may need to top it up during the day if you're using it constantly. That&#8217;s where Apple&#8217;s iPhone Air MagSafe battery pack comes in, and it&#8217;s currently on sale for $79.


This accessory only works with the iPhone Air, but much like the phone it attaches to, it&#8217;s extremely slim at 7.5mmm, so crucially doesn&#8217;t add so much bulk when attached that it def...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 ans apr&#232;s iOS, Gmail pour Android va enfin recevoir cette fonction utile</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2973869_6-ans-apres-ios-gmail-pour-android-va-enfin-recevoir-cette-fonction-utile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2973869_6-ans-apres-ios-gmail-pour-android-va-enfin-recevoir-cette-fonction-utile</guid>
      <description>
Une option pr&#233;sente depuis des ann&#233;es dans Gmail sur PC et iOS va d&#233;barquer dans l'application Android. Pas trop t&#244;t.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate raises $17M to move defense project management into the 21st century</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/integrate-raises-17m-to-move-defense-project-management-into-the-21st-century/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091872</guid>
      <description>The round was led by FPV Ventures co-founder and managing partner Wesley Chan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decathlon brade ce compteur v&#233;lo GPS Garmin r&#233;put&#233; pour son autonomie record et ses fonctions avanc&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2973807_decathlon-brade-ce-compteur-velo-gps-garmin-repute-pour-son-autonomie-record-et-ses-fonctions-avancees</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2973807_decathlon-brade-ce-compteur-velo-gps-garmin-repute-pour-son-autonomie-record-et-ses-fonctions-avancees</guid>
      <description>
Si vous comptez vous mettre s&#233;rieusement au cyclisme, il vous faut du mat&#233;riel de qualit&#233; comme ce compteur v&#233;lo GPS Garmin Edge 1040 ultra-pr&#233;cis disponible &#224; 389,99 euros au lieu de 449,99 euros sur Decathlon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN ditches USD-only billing for fixed local rates in major update</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-ditches-usd-only-billing-for-fixed-local-rates-in-major-update</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pQb2bwRnaQ9RZHmjS35rEd</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is ditching its USD-only billing model in favor of fixed local currency pricing, ending exchange rate fluctuations for users in the UK, Eurozone, and Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Stargate&#8217; Is Adding a Familiar Face in a Surprising Way</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stargate-reboot-joe-flanagan-writing-2000720308</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720308</guid>
      <description>Plus, 'The Mummy 4' producer Tyler Gillett has high praise for the movie's script.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
