<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:51:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dyson&#8217;s powerful 360 Vis Nav robot vacuum is nearly 75 percent off today</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/870256/dyson-360-vis-nav-robot-vacuum-lego-lotr-balrog-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T13:48:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870256</guid>
      <description>In case you missed it, we recently overhauled our guides to the best budget robot vacuums and the best mopping vacs, both of which feature a slate of new picks from Roborock, Narwal, Dreame, and others. Dyson&#8217;s 360 Vis Nav Robot Vacuum didn&#8217;t technically make the cut, though it was once one of our top [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Robot Hand Pops Off and Crawls. I Hate It So Much.</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-robot-hand-pops-off-and-crawls-i-hate-it-so-much-2000715991</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715991</guid>
      <description>Like a robotic spider! But somehow worse!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest DDoS attack ever has been detected - but fortunately you probably barely noticed it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/the-biggest-ddos-attack-ever-has-been-detected-but-fortunately-you-probably-barely-noticed-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GgzmLyZmN3jpLHhXCKY6fL</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare mitigated a major attack on a telco which broke all previous records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This tree search framework hits 98.7% on documents where vector search fails</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/this-tree-search-framework-hits-98-7-on-documents-where-vector-search-fails</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1yaxE5ZdnN779Pf8JlHBpU</guid>
      <description>A new open-source framework called PageIndex solves one of the old problems of retrieval-augmented generation (RAG): handling very long documents.The classic RAG workflow (chunk documents, calculate embeddings, store them in a vector database, and retrieve the top matches based on semantic similarity) works well for basic tasks such as Q&amp;A over small documents.PageIndex abandons the standard "chunk-and-embed" method entirely and treats document retrieval not as a search problem, but as a navigation problem. But as enterprises try to move RAG into high-stakes workflows &#8212; auditing financial stat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;app France Identit&#233; teste une fonction pour prouver son &#226;ge en ligne</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/lapp-france-identite-teste-une-fonction-pour-prouver-son-age-en-ligne.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323541</guid>
      <description>Prouver son &#226;ge va devenir une contrainte de plus en plus pr&#233;sente &#224; mesure que les r&#233;gulateurs &#233;largissent la liste des sites et services en ligne tenus de v&#233;rifier que leurs utilisateurs sont bien des adultes certifi&#233;s. L'application France Identit&#233; pourrait avoir une carte &#224; jouer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook is destroying his own legacy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/870717/tim-cook-melania-minneapolis-tiktok-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T13:09:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870717</guid>
      <description>What responsibility do you have to speak up about bad things happening in the world? Does that responsibility change when speaking up might affect your business? What about if you're a sports creator, or the moderator of a deeply NSFW subreddit? What about if you're just a little ol' phone website? Ultimately, everyone has to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for the Galaxy S26? I have the perfect T-Mobile deal to tempt you into picking up a Google Pixel 10 Pro XL instead</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/network-providers/waiting-for-the-galaxy-s26-i-have-the-perfect-t-mobile-deal-to-tempt-you-into-picking-up-a-google-pixel-10-pro-xl-instead</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7wEZTYwXz8irtHFm3BQ8VJ</guid>
      <description>T-Mobile's current deal on the Google Pixel 10 Pro XL gets you this superb device for free with a new unlimited line - without a trade-in needed, either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sundance doc 'Ghost in the Machine' draws a damning line between AI and eugenics</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/sundance-doc-ghost-in-the-machine-draws-a-damning-line-between-ai-and-eugenics-180613367.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11f3334f-4881-48b9-97e7-07f459eda8bd</guid>
      <description>The Sundance documentary Ghost in the Machine boldly declares that the pursuit of artificial intelligence, and Silicon Valley itself, is rooted in eugenics.&#160;Director Valerie Veatch makes the case that the rise of techno-fascism from the likes of Elon Musk and Peter Thiel is a feature, not a bug. That may sound hyperbolic, but Ghost in the Machine, which is built around interviews with philosophers, AI researchers, historians and computer scientists, leaves little room for doubt.If you've been following the meteoric rise of AI, or Silicon Valley in general, Veatch's methodical deconstruction of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next &#8216;Fast and Furious&#8217; Movie Finally Has an Official Title and Release Date</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-next-fast-and-furious-movie-finally-has-an-official-title-and-release-date-2000716061</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716061</guid>
      <description>It's called 'Fast Forever' and will be in theaters on March 17, 2028.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic brings agentic plug-ins to Cowork</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/30/anthropic-brings-agentic-plugins-to-cowork/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087918</guid>
      <description>The company says you can use plug-ins to "tell Claude how you like work done, which tools and data to pull from, how to handle critical workflows, and what slash commands to expose so your team gets more consistent outcomes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 2026&#8217;s full &#8216;snow&#8217; moon comes with a side of free chips and queso: How and when to get yours</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482836/february-1-2026-full-moon-snow-free-chips-queso-dip-qdoba-when-what-day-to-see-it-tonight</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482836/february-1-2026-full-moon-snow-free-chips-queso-dip-qdoba-when-what-day-to-see-it-tonight</guid>
      <description>A major fast-food chain has a special deal to celebrate the &#8216;big cheese,&#8217; and stargazers can grab it this weekend.
This Sunday&#8217;s full moon, or &#8220;big cheese,&#8221; as it&#8217;s sometimes called, comes with a side of queso and chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The JBL Charge 5 is my most loyal travel buddy &#8212; and now this trusty Bluetooth speaker can be yours for almost &#163;90 off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/the-jbl-charge-5-is-my-most-loyal-travel-buddy-and-now-this-trusty-bluetooth-speaker-can-be-yours-for-almost-gbp90-off</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8EfnweYXSm6eUAGucKGSxa</guid>
      <description>My fave Bluetooth speaker for taking on adventures is at its lowest price yet &#8211; so grab it for nearly half off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: The Galaxy S26 lineup and everything else we expect</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-the-galaxy-s26-lineup-and-everything-else-we-expect-130000999.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company is expected to host its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year in February to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live, and we'll most likely have hands-on coverage of Samsung's new smartphones soon after they're announced. While we wait for an official invite, here's everything we expect Samsung will introduce at the first Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026.What is Unpacked 2026 taking place?But...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI IPO: What to know about the most anticipated stock listing in years amid rumors of a 2026 date</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484259/openai-ipo-chatgpt-maker-rumored-stock-listing-2026-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T17:48:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484259/openai-ipo-chatgpt-maker-rumored-stock-listing-2026-date</guid>
      <description>The ChatGPT maker and world&#8217;s most valuable startup could go public as soon as this year, according to a WSJ report.
It&#8217;s shaping up to be a busy year for initial public offerings from some of the most closely watched companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google's Project Genie lets you create your own 3D interactive worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/googles-project-genie-lets-you-create-your-own-3d-interactive-worlds-183646428.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f96776b3-9f86-4da3-a49e-ab792ecdecfc</guid>
      <description>This past summer, Google DeepMind debuted Genie 3. It&#8217;s what&#8217;s known as a world world, an AI system capable of generating images and reacting as the user moves through the environment the software is simulating. At the time, DeepMind positioned Genie 3 as a tool for training AI agents. Now, it&#8217;s making the model available to people outside of Google to try with Project Genie. To start, you&#8217;ll need Google&#8217;s $250 per month AI Ultra plan to check out Project Genie. You&#8217;ll also need to live in the US and be 18 years or older. At launch, Project Genie offers three different modes of interaction: Wo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos home theater gear is up to 20 percent off ahead of Super Bowl LX</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/sonos-home-theater-gear-is-up-to-20-percent-off-ahead-of-super-bowl-lx-174053619.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d95ac4b9-448d-4c43-906a-61793dfa0aef</guid>
      <description>Like many other companies during Super Bowl season, Sonos is discounting its home theater gear. Today, you can save $130 on the Beam (Gen 2) soundbar, bringing its price down to $369. You'll also find deals on the flagship Arc Ultra Soundbar, Sonos subwoofers, and more.
The Sonos Beam is the company's sub-$500 soundbar. Engadget's pick for the best midrange model, the compact speaker has impressive sound for its size. Part of that is its Dolby Atmos support. Although the soundbar lacks upward-firing speakers, it uses software tricks to compensate. Audio timing and frequency adjustments make so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save up to 81 percent on ExpressVPN two-year plans right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/save-up-to-81-percent-on-expressvpn-two-year-plans-right-now-180602273.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $88 for two years, plus four additional free months. The Basic plan is where you'll see the biggest discount: it's $68 for two years, plus the same four additional free months.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. On...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 175,000 publicly exposed Ollama AI servers discovered worldwide - so fix now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/over-175-000-publicly-exposed-ollama-ai-servers-discovered-worldwide-so-fix-now</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zzjTDwnSykoBBXUAUcHwp</guid>
      <description>Exposed servers are being used for LLMjacking, creating malicious content and being sold on the black market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The trust paradox killing AI at scale: 76% of data leaders can't govern what employees already use</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/the-trust-paradox-killing-ai-at-scale-76-of-data-leaders-cant-govern-what</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6A87OcEOazEOVNdwwB8oSb</guid>
      <description>The chief data officer (CDO) has evolved from a niche compliance role into one of the most critical positions for AI deployment. These executives now sit at the intersection of data governance, AI strategy, and workforce readiness. Their decisions determine whether enterprises move from AI pilots to production scale or remain stuck in experimentation mode.That's why Informatica's third annual survey &#8212; the largest survey yet of CDOs specifically on AI readiness, spanning 600 executives globally &#8212; carries particular weight. The findings expose a dangerous disconnect that explains why so many org...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE invades Minnesota and Minnesotans fight back</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/870315/ice-invades-minnesota-and-minnesotans-fight-back</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T12:32:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=870315</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration has flooded Minneapolis and other parts of Minnesota with federal agents as part of its immigration crackdown, Operation Metro Surge &#8212;&#160;detaining children, intimidating protestors and community organizers, and killing multiple people. Minnesotans have responded with mass community-level resistance, including mutual aid and tracking ICE operations, despite threats and surveillance &#8212;&#160;including through systems [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe is growing again, but the weaker dollar looms as a threat</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484360/europe-economy-q4-dollar-euro</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484360/europe-economy-q4-dollar-euro</guid>
      <description>Moderate growth has defied recession fears from earlier in the year.
The European economy recorded modest growth at the end of last year, pushing past&#160;turmoil over higher U.S. tariffs.&#160;Now the economy faces another hurdle: a stronger euro against the dollar that could weigh on exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgraced Crypto CEO Sam Bankman-Fried Seeks Trump Pardon With Republican Pivot</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disgraced-crypto-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-seeks-trump-pardon-with-republican-pivot-2000716037</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716037</guid>
      <description>SBF swears he was Republican-curious long before things went awry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluesky issues its first transparency report, noting rise in user reports and legal demands</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/30/bluesky-issues-its-first-transparency-report-noting-rise-in-user-reports-and-legal-demands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088209</guid>
      <description>Bluesky's first transparency reports tackle moderation, regulatory compliance, account takedowns, and more. The number of government legal requests went up fivefold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La tablette Honor Pad X8a qui chute sous les 100 &#8364; est une belle surprise de fin des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2961711_la-tablette-honor-pad-x8a-qui-chute-sous-les-100-e-est-une-belle-surprise-de-fin-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2961711_la-tablette-honor-pad-x8a-qui-chute-sous-les-100-e-est-une-belle-surprise-de-fin-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Joybuy d&#233;barque dans le paysage des e-marchands et attise la curiosit&#233; avec ses offres int&#233;ressantes, comme cette tablette Honor Pad X8a disponible pour seulement 98 euros contre 159 euros, prix classique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now use Nintendo&#8217;s wireless N64 controller with the Analogue 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/870968/analogue-3d-n64-nintendo-switch-online-wireless-controller-software-update</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T12:24:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870968</guid>
      <description>The Analogue 3D finally launched late last year with four controller ports on the front supporting the N64's original wired gamepads. If you wanted to go wireless, your best option was the 8BitDo 64 which offered a similar button and joystick layout as the N64's original controllers, but with a modernized design. For a more [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit&#8217;s Next AI Gadget Is a &#8216;Cyberdeck&#8217; for Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rabbits-next-ai-gadget-is-a-cyberdeck-for-vibe-coding-2000715970</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715970</guid>
      <description>Ah man, here we go again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1998 on the outside &#8212; 2026 inside': Maingear's Retro98 'nostalgic sleeper' PCs are power-packed and fabulously retro</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/1998-on-the-outside-2026-inside-maingears-retro98-nostalgic-sleeper-pcs-are-power-packed-and-fabulously-retro</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CQYzWikCYw5pGbotSRLmQH</guid>
      <description>Maingear's Retro98 PC looks like a boxy beige tower, but packs cutting-edge hardware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm excited for Fable, but worried about the combat &#8212; what do you think?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/im-excited-for-fable-but-worried-about-the-combat-what-do-you-think</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Gnvq94BTyLVHdJqFo7jrc4</guid>
      <description>Fable looks great, but the combat has me a little concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : voici les ultimes offres &#224; saisir pour le week-end de la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_soldes-dhiver-2026-voici-les-ultimes-offres-a-saisir-pour-le-week-end-de-la-derniere-demarque</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_soldes-dhiver-2026-voici-les-ultimes-offres-a-saisir-pour-le-week-end-de-la-derniere-demarque</guid>
      <description>
Il ne faut pas se le cacher, la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes est souvent le moment o&#249; l'on trouve les meilleures offres, car les e-commer&#231;ants comme Amazon, Fnac, Darty ou encore Boulanger veulent &#233;couler les derniers stocks. Avec cet article, vous serez s&#251;rs de ne manquer aucun deal Tech int&#233;ressant. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens tariffs on any country selling oil to Cuba</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484338/oil-cuba-tariffs-trump-mexico</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T17:06:31</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484338/oil-cuba-tariffs-trump-mexico</guid>
      <description>Since the Venezuela operation, Trump has said no more Venezuelan oil will go to Cuba and the Cuban government is ready to fall.
President Donald Trump on Thursday signed an executive order that would impose a tariff on any goods from countries that sell or provide oil to Cuba, a move that could&#160;further cripple an island&#160;plagued by a deepening energy crisis....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon se montre g&#233;n&#233;reux pour les derniers jours des soldes : voici les 20 meilleures offres qui valent le coup</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-se-montre-genereux-pour-les-derniers-jours-des-soldes-voici-les-20-meilleures-offres-qui-valent-le-coup</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933045_amazon-se-montre-genereux-pour-les-derniers-jours-des-soldes-voici-les-20-meilleures-offres-qui-valent-le-coup</guid>
      <description>
Plus que quelques jours avant la fin des soldes d&#8217;hiver&#8239;! Les bonnes affaires sont encore nombreuses, et certaines enseignes redoublent d&#8217;efforts pour marquer le coup. C&#8217;est le cas d&#8217;Amazon, qui transforme ce dernier week-end en v&#233;ritable grande braderie avec une multitude d&#8217;offres sur les produits Tech.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 of the most important iPhone apps to install first</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/5-of-the-most-important-iphone-apps-to-install-first</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GwP4xuqinan3RKTNwvLbg6</guid>
      <description>If you have an iPhone then these five apps are near-essential additions, that could make your life easier, drier, and more secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turtlemania Surges as &#8216;TMNT II: The Secret of the Ooze&#8217; Returns to Theaters</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/turtlemania-surges-as-tmnt-ii-the-secret-of-the-ooze-returns-to-theaters-2000715771</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715771</guid>
      <description>The cult-beloved sequel celebrates its 35th anniversary with a week-long run showcasing its new 4K restoration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This DIY kit turned my favorite mechanical keyboard into my favorite electrocapacitive keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/868153/dynacap-diy-electrocapacitive-keyboard-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868153</guid>
      <description>For my money, you simply cannot get a better electrocapacitive keyboard than the Bauer Lite with a DynaCap kit. [Editor's note: Huh?] You can get a nicer EC keyboard, without having to build it yourself, by simply spending $3,600 on a Norbauer Seneca. Or you can get a Happy Hacking Keyboard or a Realforce for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mario Kart World vs Mario Kart 8 Deluxe: which Nintendo racer stands atop the podium?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/mario-kart-world-vs-mario-kart-8-deluxe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8ngUnpKt4BhDC2whnNgsh</guid>
      <description>I love Mario Kart World, but is it actually better than Mario Kart 8 Deluxe? Here&#8217;s which Nintendo racer takes first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Spirits season 3 episode 4 is 'so unfamiliar that it's terrifying' as star warns of 'different show' to come</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/school-spirits-season-3-episode-4-is-so-unfamiliar-that-its-terrifying-as-star-warns-of-different-show-to-come</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pv4fEXtjPkHxM7WYDfU8CE</guid>
      <description>After its head-spinning three-episode premiere, School Spirits season 3 is officially in session. But according to one star, the next three episodes are 'a completely different show'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best cheap VPN in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/best-cheap-vpn-170000957.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aea9c33e-8a27-408b-81f7-8bb7b6712a8f</guid>
      <description>When talking about the best VPNs, I frequently warn about the dangers of trusting free VPNs without verifying them. Although there are a few free VPNs worth recommending, many other free providers are ineffective, malicious or looking to profit off their users (or sometimes all three). Even the best free VPNs work a lot better once you subscribe and access their full service.This can be frustrating if you want to enjoy the benefits of a VPN but don't have the budget for yet another subscription. To help you out, I put together a list of the best paid VPN services you can get cheaply. Every nam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Et si la vie existait tout pr&#232;s ? Cette plan&#232;te d&#233;couverte &#224; 40 ann&#233;es-lumi&#232;re relance l&#8217;espoir</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/exoplanete-si-vie-existait-tout-pres-cette-planete-decouverte-40-annees-lumiere-relance-espoir-w2t8-130541/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/exoplanete-si-vie-existait-tout-pres-cette-planete-decouverte-40-annees-lumiere-relance-espoir-w2t8-130541/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>&#192; environ 35 ann&#233;es-lumi&#232;re de la Terre, il y a une &#233;toile pas tout &#224; fait comme les autres. Toute petite, mais entour&#233;e de plusieurs plan&#232;tes rocheuses, dont une qui se r&#233;v&#232;le particuli&#232;rement int&#233;ressante.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entourer pour chercher&#160;: comment Google pourrait ruiner une de ses meilleures id&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/entourer-pour-chercher-comment-google-pourrait-ruiner-une-de-ses-meilleures-idees.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323514</guid>
      <description>Google teste un mode IA par d&#233;faut pour Circle to Search, sa fonctionnalit&#233; phare de recherche visuelle sur Android. Lanc&#233;e avec les Galaxy S24 de Samsung, elle pourrait bient&#244;t privil&#233;gier les r&#233;ponses g&#233;n&#233;r&#233;es par Gemini d&#232;s l'ouverture, tout en conservant l'acc&#232;s aux recherches classiques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reid Hoffman urges Silicon Valley leaders to stop bending the knee to President Trump</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/30/reid-hoffman-urges-silicon-valley-leaders-to-stop-bending-the-knee-to-president-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088202</guid>
      <description>Some Valley CEOs have condemned recent border patrol events, but Hoffman urges them to wield their influence more powerfully.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
