<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:30:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Halo Infinite is about to get its last major update</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/816960/halo-infinite-end</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-07T18:26:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=816960</guid>
      <description>On November 18th, Operation: Infinite will be released for Halo Infinite players with a battle pass and lots of new customizations, but according to the team, that&#8217;s it for this game&#8217;s content updates: With multiple Halo titles in development, we&#8217;ll need our whole team&#8217;s combined focus to deliver new experiences with the same passion and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminal-Bench 2.0 launches alongside Harbor, a new framework for testing agents in containers</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/terminal-bench-2-0-launches-alongside-harbor-a-new-framework-for-testing</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3F9CY5MGXMDKgNwozdCZR5</guid>
      <description>The developers of Terminal-Bench, a benchmark suite for evaluating the performance of autonomous AI agents on real-world terminal-based tasks, have released version 2.0 alongside Harbor, a new framework for testing, improving and optimizing AI agents in containerized environments. The dual release aims to address long-standing pain points in testing and optimizing AI agents, particularly those built to operate autonomously in realistic developer environments.With a more difficult and rigorously verified task set, Terminal-Bench 2.0 replaces version 1.0 as the standard for assessing frontier mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranking the New &#8216;Five Nights at Freddy&#8217;s 2&#8217; Popcorn Buckets From Cutest to Creepiest</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ranking-the-new-five-nights-at-freddys-2-popcorn-buckets-from-cutest-to-creepiest-2000682695</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000682695</guid>
      <description>A new round of eerie Freddy Fazbear's Pizza merch is coming to life at a theater near you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get a Fubo TV free trial</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/fubo-tv-free-trial</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yHpGmTyxAFxUpduToFj3k9</guid>
      <description>You can still get a Fubo TV free trial in 2025 &#8211; here are all the ways you can try out  the live TV streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Government Shutdown Is a Ticking Cybersecurity Time Bomb</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-government-shutdown-is-a-ticking-cybersecurity-time-bomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">690cca9f2e32add3a4a02c8c</guid>
      <description>Many critical systems are still being maintained, and the cloud provides some security cover. But experts say that any lapses in protections like patching and monitoring could expose government systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk says Tesla is "almost ready" to allow texting when behind the wheel with its Full Self-Driving system</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/elon-musk-says-tesla-is-almost-ready-to-allow-texting-when-behind-the-wheel-with-its-full-self-driving-system</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nkVeNkV9sAd8Qz6GaV2cYf</guid>
      <description>Musk claims Full Self-Driving will soon allow texting when at the wheel, but fails to explain how that will be legal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweet news:  Hershey Company announces new treats for the holiday 2025 season</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91436952/hershey-new-holiday-candy-2025-snickerdoodle-kisses-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-07T22:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91436952/hershey-new-holiday-candy-2025-snickerdoodle-kisses-and-more</guid>
      <description>Get ready for snickerdoodle-flavored Kisses, peppermint Kit Kats, Grinch chocolates, and more.
Now that Halloween has come and gone, you might have wrongly assumed that candy season is over. Not if the Hershey Company anything to say about it. In fact, the sweets are just getting started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Tatsuki Fujimoto 17-26&#8217; Is a Joyously Unhinged Look Into the Young Mind of Manga&#8217;s Wildest Auteur</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tatsuki-fujimoto-17-26-anime-anthology-review-prime-video-2000682427</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000682427</guid>
      <description>The Prime Video anthology tells eight of the 'Chainsaw Man' creator's earliest short stories, animated by six different studios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android could soon change in a big way thanks to the Google and Epic settlement &#8211; here&#8217;s what it means for you</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/android/android-could-soon-change-in-a-big-way-thanks-to-the-google-and-epic-settlement-heres-what-it-means-for-you</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BzGgNLfw6i9kyCyMVfzoph</guid>
      <description>The legal dispute between Google and Epic Games has been settled, with big changes coming to Android.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study Finds Around a Quarter of Polymarket Trades Are Fake</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/study-finds-around-a-quarter-of-polymarket-trades-are-fake-2000683231</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000683231</guid>
      <description>Surely, there's no potential for market manipulation here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayaneo d&#233;voile sa console-PC qui coutera plus de 1500 euros mais qui cache bien son jeu</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ayaneo/2860931_ayaneo-devoile-sa-console-pc-qui-coutera-plus-de-1500-euros-mais-qui-cache-bien-son-jeu</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ayaneo/2860931_ayaneo-devoile-sa-console-pc-qui-coutera-plus-de-1500-euros-mais-qui-cache-bien-son-jeu</guid>
      <description>
Voici une nouvelle console portable gaming &#224; plus de 1500 &#8364; : AYANEO d&#233;voile sa NEXT 2 avec le processeur Ryzen AI Max+ 395.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe Peloton is its own worst enemy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/816352/peloton-q1-2026-earnings-fitness</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-07T16:37:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=816352</guid>
      <description>For years - through its pandemic-fueled highs and its post-quarantine malaise - Peloton has held its earnings calls at a bright and bushy 8:30AM ET. Not yesterday. Instead, the company broke different news first thing in the morning: it issued yet another recall for 833,000 of its original Bike Plus units, before posting its Q1 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
