<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:26:44 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>New TV not looking as good as you hoped? Here are 3 settings I always change to get better picture quality</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/new-tv-not-looking-as-good-as-you-hoped-here-are-3-settings-i-always-change-to-get-better-picture-quality</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6hUTo934RVKbxMC2WozjWJ</guid>
      <description>While it's easier to leave your TV in its out-of-the-box settings, you'll be rewarded with a better picture if you take a trip to the menus. Here's my top 3 to get you started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar Grit X2 review: the Grit X2 Pro in a smaller, cheaper package</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/polar-grit-x2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sok74R7Mux8HnEBXp42555</guid>
      <description>A feature-packed fitness watch let down by limited smartwatch functionality and a clunky companion app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new Netflix series starring Ed Westwick and John Hannah is a throwback to classic pirate movies &#8211; here are 3 of the cast&#8217;s guilty pleasures</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/this-new-netflix-series-starring-ed-westwick-and-john-hannah-is-a-throwback-to-classic-pirate-movies-here-are-3-of-the-casts-guilty-pleasures</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hhz77nrRVE6h9VgEAScqeP</guid>
      <description>John Hannah, Ed Westwick and Alanah Bloor reveal the pirate movies they unapologetically love &#8211; and why their new Netflix series is a &#8216;classic adventure love story for the modern day&#8217;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Nikon pulling a Canon? What the Viltrox lawsuit rumors mean for the future of Z-mount lenses</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-lenses/is-nikon-pulling-a-canon-what-the-viltrox-lawsuit-rumors-mean-for-the-future-of-z-mount-lenses</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9z2xPtQLBhbm2jexKpnCEZ</guid>
      <description>Rumors suggest that Nikon has started legal action against the Chinese lens maker Viltrox, over alleged Z-mount patent infringements. Here's what that could mean moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google restores much-missed JPEG XL format to Chromium code base - better image compression and better bandwidth are on the way</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/google-restores-much-missed-jpeg-xl-format-to-chromium-code-base-better-image-compression-and-better-bandwidth-are-on-the-way</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bzPDiJ47br8RmcrVqS3dRM</guid>
      <description>Google restored JPEG XL support in Chromium, enabling native decoding after years of industry pressure and growing adoption elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS will not release any new smartphones this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/asus-will-not-release-any-new-smartphones-this-year-213043832.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fb175fd-b13e-4be4-985b-8280e9d884ad</guid>
      <description>ASUS appears to be shifting its business operations away from smartphones. According to translations of recent quotes from Chairman Jonney Shih, the company does not plan to release new phone models in the future. The chairman did not confirm whether smartphones would be completely phased out, but he did acknowledge that possibility. Whatever direction ASUS takes, its existing phones will continue to receive software updates and warranty assistance. Shih suggested that its future plans may include a shift into AI-related projects such as robotics or smartglasses.Previous reports hinted that AS...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I love this hidden feature on my Sony headphones, but you may not know it even exists</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/i-love-this-hidden-feature-on-my-sony-headphones-but-you-may-not-even-know-it-even-exists</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xTrxpJfrMp9XiimytVT2x3</guid>
      <description>I love this nifty feature on my Sony headphones, but a lot of users may not even know it&#8217;s there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s 2026 &#8216;focus&#8217; is &#8216;practical adoption&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864229/openai-focus-practical-adoption-sarah-friar</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T16:05:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864229</guid>
      <description>OpenAI plans to focus on "practical adoption" of AI in 2026, according to a blog post from CFO Sarah Friar. As the company spends a huge amount of money on infrastructure, OpenAI is working on "closing the gap" on what AI can do and how people actually use it. "The opportunity is large and immediate, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK agency questions Meta's policies for illegal gambling site ads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/uk-agency-questions-metas-policies-for-illegal-gambling-site-ads-210500714.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffc49933-c6b0-4df4-92f7-55ecc8fe6659</guid>
      <description>The UK Gambling Commission has raised concerns that Meta is ignoring advertisements by illegal gambling websites on its platforms. At a conference in Barcelona, the commission's Executive Director Tim Miller criticized Meta's behavior towards advertisements for online gambling on its Facebook and Instagram social networks."Companies like Meta will tell you that they don&#8217;t tolerate the advertising of illegal sites and will remove them if they are notified about them," Miller's speech transcript reads. "But that approach suggests that they don&#8217;t know about those ads unless alerted. That is simpl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Couldn&#8217;t Even Kill the Original &#8216;Galaxy&#8217;s Edge&#8217; Right</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-galaxys-edge-changes-disney-lucasfilm-2000711222</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711222</guid>
      <description>The 'Star Wars' sequels are out, and the original trilogy is in at Disneyland&#8212;but just as the parks failed to commit to what made 'Galaxy's Edge' so interesting in the first place, now they can't even commit to erasing that dream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much can a city take?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/864195/minneapolis-ice-invasion-organizing-immigration</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864195</guid>
      <description>I live in Minneapolis. I grew up not far from here, in a suburb of St. Paul; after stints on both coasts, my wife and I settled here to raise our daughters in a freezing state that had always welcomed us warmly. As the ongoing occupation by over 3,000 ICE agents stretches into its third [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TurboTax Deluxe is on sale for $45 ahead of tax season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/turbotax-deluxe-is-on-sale-for-45-ahead-of-tax-season-204848571.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d4b28c6-34f1-44bb-800a-eec732a96ded</guid>
      <description>With the spring approaching, it's time to start thinking about how you'll file your taxes. Unfortunately, with the recent demise of Direct File, there isn't a free, government-provided alternative to TurboTax in 2026, and you'll need to look to other federal programs, including IRS Free File, to file your paperwork. If you don't qualify for Free File, chances are you'll need to dish out cash for Intuit's software. And while we hate to suggest you give money to a company that has spent decades lobbying to ensure America's tax system remains a nightmare, we can at least save you some money if Tu...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
