<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:27:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot's spring sale has arrived &#8212; these are the backyard and home upgrades I'm buying</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/home-depots-spring-sale-has-arrived-these-are-the-backyard-and-home-upgrades-im-buying</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 20:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HxqFQaqXhbU8Bc7HdCwF5B</guid>
      <description>Home Depot's 2026 spring sale is live, and I'm rounding up everything that I'm buying for my backyard and home, including patio furniture, flowers, grills, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean Police Lose Seized Crypto By Posting Password Online</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/south-korean-police-lose-seized-crypto-by-posting-password-online-2000728191</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 20:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000728191</guid>
      <description>The digital equivalent of snatching coins from someone's outstretched hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portable Sonos Play speaker leaks on Canadian Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/887220/sonos-play-leak</link>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T15:10:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=887220</guid>
      <description>An unannounced Sonos speaker called Play has been spotted on the Canadian Best Buy site. The Sonos Play looks like a slightly shrunk-down version of the Move 2 with a loop on the back for toting it around. While nothing is confirmed yet, it's listed at CAD $399.99 with a release date of March 31st, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD is taking the fight to Intel with its most powerful Epyc chips yet &#8212; Sorano packs in 84 Zen5 cores and could supercharge the next generation of mobile networks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amd-is-taking-the-fight-to-intel-with-its-most-powerful-epyc-chips-yet-sorano-packs-in-84-zen5-cores-and-could-supercharge-the-next-generation-of-mobile-networks</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RBBuAcqCDkbso9RqCXcoab</guid>
      <description>AMD introduces 84-core Sorano Epyc chip for telecom networks, emphasizing efficiency and challenging Intel&#8217;s entrenched presence in virtualized infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon&#8217;s Claude Use in Iran Is a Reminder that Anthropic Never Objected to Military Use</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-pentagons-claude-use-in-iran-is-a-reminder-that-anthropic-never-objected-to-military-use-2000728150</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 20:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000728150</guid>
      <description>The company objected to hypothetical future use cases, not anything the military is currently doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blumhouse Wants to Be Perfectly Balanced for Horror Fans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/blumhouse-wants-to-be-perfectly-balanced-for-horror-fans-2000728153</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000728153</guid>
      <description>Jason Blum knows IP is the lifeblood of entertainment right now, but Blumhouse will keep pumping out originals on a regular basis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's Claude grabs top spot in App Store after Trump's ban</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/anthropics-claude-grabs-top-spot-in-app-store-after-trumps-ban-193610130.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1688b9b5-b570-4afb-9311-cb9078f326a7</guid>
      <description>Anthropic may have lost out on doing business with the US government, but it's gained enough popularity to earn the number one spot on the App Store's Top Free Apps leaderboard. At the top, Claude beat out both ChatGPT and Google Gemini, which respectively sit at the second and third spots on Apple's free apps charts.
The sudden surge in user downloads isn't random. It follows news that President Trump has barred any federal agency from using Anthropic's Claude or other AI tools after the AI company refused to concede on certain guardrails. After declining to have its AI models be used for mas...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
