<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:21:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>X says Grok will no longer edit images of real people into bikinis</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/x-says-grok-will-no-longer-edit-images-of-real-people-into-bikinis-231430257.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a86cee4d-ab97-42a1-98eb-82c59ed7404d</guid>
      <description>X says it is changing its policies around Grok&#8217;s image-editing abilities following a multi-week outcry over the chatbot repeatedly being accused of generating sexualized images of children and nonconsensual nudity. In an update shared from the @Safety account on X, the company said it has &#8220;implemented technological measures to prevent the Grok account from allowing the editing of images of real people in revealing clothing such as bikinis..&#8221;xAI is also moving all of Grok&#8217;s image-generating features behind its subscriber paywall so that non-paying users will no longer be able to create images. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stream Deck Plus is back to its lowest price</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/862274/elgato-stream-deck-plus-controller-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T18:04:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862274</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re looking for a simple way to streamline your workflow, the Elgato Stream Deck Plus is a handy productivity tool for automating everyday tasks. Right now, it&#8217;s on sale for $159.99 ($40 off) at Amazon, Best Buy, and B&amp;H Photo, which is its best price to date. Like the standard Stream Deck, the Stream [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get back-to-school-ready with up to AU$500 off Samsung monitors, tablets and phones</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/get-back-to-school-ready-with-up-to-au-500-off-samsung-monitors-tablets-and-phones</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wykLhNAUUSvyEqwVVgC7h</guid>
      <description>With school holidays slowly winding down, Samsung has discounted a slew of monitors, tablets and phones and here are the best deals we&#8217;ve found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Workers Are Condemning ICE Even as Their CEOs Stay Quiet</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/backlash-against-ice-policing-tactics-grows-in-silicon-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965510f7f460a0d99592638</guid>
      <description>The killing of George Floyd in 2020 prompted a wave of statements from tech companies and CEOs. Today, pushback against ICE is largely coming from employees, not executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix will air new video podcasts from Pete Davidson and Michael Irvin this month</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/netflix-will-air-new-video-podcasts-from-pete-davidson-and-michael-irvin-this-month-224353011.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1de232ac-0f3a-4086-a8c5-877068853ddd</guid>
      <description>Netflix is continuing to double down on podcasts, with the streaming service's announcement that it has hired talent to host two original shows for its platform. The first show stars NFL Hall of Famer-turned-analyst Michael Irvin and the second is a talk show for former Saturday Night Live cast member Pete Davidson.The White House with Michael Irvin premieres January 19. The abode in the title refers to a building near the Dallas Cowboys facilities rather than the seat of US presidential power, but the overlap was intentional. "In a crowded media landscape, recognition matters &#8212; and few names ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk denies awareness of Grok sexual underage images as California AG launches probe</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/musk-denies-awareness-of-grok-sexual-underage-images-as-california-ag-launches-probe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082852</guid>
      <description>The California attorney general has opened a formal investigation into Elon Musk's xAI after its chatbot Grok began generating nonconsensual sexual images of real women and even children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon outage: Voice and data services down for many customers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/verizon-outage-voice-and-data-services-down-for-many-customers-183048956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17d0339-fd27-40dc-a0a2-c153c9fb8655</guid>
      <description>Verizon&#8217;s network is experiencing technical issues that are impacting calls and wireless data. Verizon customers on X have reported seeing &#8220;SOS&#8221; rather than the traditional network bars on their smartphones, and even the network provider&#8217;s own status page struggled to load, likely due to the number of customers trying to access it.Based on the experience of Verizon users on Engadget&#8217;s staff, the services that are impacted appear to be calls and wireless data. Text messages continue to be delivered normally, at least for some users. On DownDetector, reports of a Verizon outage started growing a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;All You Need Is Kill&#8217; Director Felt Destined to Tackle the &#8216;Perfect&#8217; Sci&#8209;Fi Epic&#8217;s Anime Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/all-you-need-is-kill-director-felt-destined-to-tackle-the-perfect-sci%e2%80%91fi-epics-anime-adaptation-2000707823</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707823</guid>
      <description>Studio 4&#176;C's adaptation of Hiroshi Sakurazaka's adored novel, which inspired the Tom Cruise movie 'Edge of Tomorrow,' hits theaters January 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI signs deal, worth $10B, for compute from Cerebras</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/14/openai-signs-deal-reportedly-worth-10-billion-for-compute-from-cerebras/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082833</guid>
      <description>The collaboration will help OpenAI's models deliver faster response times for more difficult or time-consuming tasks, the companies said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Congressman Wants to Make ICE Agents Wear QR Codes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dem-congressman-wants-to-make-ice-agents-wear-qr-codes-2000710345</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710345</guid>
      <description>There's this analog device called a badge that has worked wonders for generations, maybe consider that too?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micron says it's 'trying to help consumers' in RAM crisis despite killing its Crucial brand &#8211; and PC owners have got even angrier as a result</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/micron-says-its-trying-to-help-consumers-in-ram-crisis-despite-killing-its-crucial-brand-and-pc-owners-have-got-even-angrier-as-a-result</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kJCVK3JXHyviNmt33UxnRB</guid>
      <description>Micron is even more unpopular after trying to defend its decision to shut down the Crucial brand of consumer RAM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ninja Slushi Max is down to a record-low price at Amazon &#8212; get it in time for football parties</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-ninja-slushi-max-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06K2slwk0zqyKVoWr4dtJDx</guid>
      <description>The Ninja Slushi Max is on sale at Amazon for $349.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jackery HomePower 3600 Plus is $1,200 off at Amazon &#8212; save big on a solution to your next power outage</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-14-jackery-homepower-3600-plus-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06aeTvfDTlhCWfrE2uwfdAF</guid>
      <description>The Jackery HomePower 3600 Plus portable power station is on sale at Amazon for $1,599, down from the list price of $2,799. That's a 43% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile takes jab at Verizon outage in service update</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/t-mobile-jabs-verizon-over-outage</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03r9FKPE8qG4IA7khoDFrGT</guid>
      <description>T-Mobile took a shot at Verizon over an outage affecting customers across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 advocacy groups call on Apple and Google to ban Grok, X over nonconsensual deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/28-advocacy-groups-call-on-apple-and-google-to-ban-grok-x-over-nonconsensual-deepfakes-215048460.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4e0f782-5b85-4fe4-b119-5b7e4576952a</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk isn't the only party at fault for Grok's nonconsensual intimate deepfakes of real people, including children. What about Apple and Google? The two (frequently virtue-signaling) companies have inexplicably allowed Grok and X to remain in their app stores &#8212; even as Musk's chatbot reportedly continues to produce the material. On Wednesday, a coalition of women's and progressive advocacy groups called on Tim Cook and Sundar Pichai to uphold their own rules and remove the apps.The open letters to Apple and Google were signed by 28 groups. Among them are the women&#8217;s advocacy group Ultravio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash and Uber Eats Cost Delivery Workers Millions of Dollars in Tips, NYC Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doordash-and-uber-eats-cost-delivery-workers-millions-of-dollars-in-tips-nyc-says-2000710487</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710487</guid>
      <description>A new report from the city claims app design changes made tipping harder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon support hints at phone bill discount for outage</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-customers-compensation-discounts-outage</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02koUZlR9clJcWYIzTD3r0F</guid>
      <description>A Verizon support team member made an interesting comment (and emoji choice) to a frustrated customer on X.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More worrying tech supply chain news - no, it's not more RAM troubles, but this vital material could be set to cause issues sooner than expected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/finally-some-good-supply-chain-news-no-its-not-more-ram-but-this-vital-material-is-set-to-enjoy-a-boom-year-which-should-be-great-news-for-everyone</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wRChMhP9PBHLgiNapmsxu6</guid>
      <description>Copper demand is rising fast due to electrification, data centers, and renewable energy, while supply struggles and recycling cannot meet needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon&#8217;s wireless network is down for many people nationwide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861956/verizon-is-down-outage-cell-wireless-service-sos-mode</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T16:40:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861956</guid>
      <description>The first big outage of 2026 is here, as Verizon customers across the US, including several of our phones, complain that service has been spotty or nonexistent starting at around noon ET, with phones switching to SOS Mode and being unable to connect. This cell service outage follows a "software issue" that cut off service [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Heads Say &#8216;Joker: Folie &#224; Deux&#8217; Was Good, You Guys Are Just Mean</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/joker-2-folie-a-deux-warner-bros-todd-phillips-joaquin-phoenix-2000710250</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710250</guid>
      <description>We're two years divorced from Todd Phillips' 'Joker' sequel, and the studio is still claiming the disappointing DC film was merely misunderstood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naya Connect is a modular mechanical keyboard system for the indecisive</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862123/naya-connect-modular-mechanical-keyboard-kickstarter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T16:38:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862123</guid>
      <description>Naya has already shipped one successful Kickstarter for a weird keyboard. The Naya Create was an ergonomic split deck with four swappable controller addons: a touchpad, a trackball, a rotary encoder, or a 6DoF spatial mouse. The Connect takes that modular concept, applies it to a more traditional flat keyboard form factor, and expands the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon breaks silence on massive outage. Heres what they said.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/verizon-outage-service-down-statement</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05FQVRD8Wv5jVZoKCSg1jpd</guid>
      <description>In a statement, Verizon acknowledged that its customers were impacted by a major disruption on Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.&#8217;s FDA Pulls Warning About Fake Autism Treatments</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rfk-jr-s-fda-pulls-warning-about-fake-autism-treatments-2000710367</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710367</guid>
      <description>The webpage previously noted that there is no cure for autism.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
