<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:39:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exodus is delayed to early 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/exodus-is-delayed-to-early-2027-032610665.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8293ee8-2bf0-40ca-8ee0-25669873ece3</guid>
      <description>
So there's good news and bad news about the highly anticipated Exodus coming out of The Game Awards this year. The good news is that there's a fresh trailer showcasing more of the game. The bad news is that the game won't be out until early 2027. The game was originally announced two years ago (also at The Game Awards) and had been pegged for release in 2026.
We may be waiting longer to get our hands on Exodus, but the substantial new trailer shows more of what the final product will entail, offering some backstory on main character Jun Aslan. He's the only human who can use the technology de...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider announces two new games</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/843260/tomb-raider-catalyst-trailer-tomb-raider-atlantis</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T22:11:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843260</guid>
      <description>While Geoff Keighley had already announced that Tomb Raider would be making a Game Awards appearance, the surprise was that instead of one game announcement there's two. Crystal Dynamics and Amazon Game Studios are releasing two Tomb Raider games back-to-back in 2026 and 2027. First up, coming in 2026 is Tomb Raider: Legacy of Atlantis. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluribus episode 7 ending explained: what happens to Carol and Manousos in the new Apple TV show?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/apple-tv-plus/pluribus-episode-7-ending-explained</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hhBUGFZnWbcx6Zn7LjmZaa</guid>
      <description>The antepenultimate episode of Pluribus season 1 puts two of its main characters through the physical and emotional wringer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Pips hints, answers for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pips-nyt-games-hints-answers-easy-medium-hard-december-12</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04AGCq4OWVyIjLTHFC6eETJ</guid>
      <description>The New York Times' latest game, Pips, brings domino fun to your desktop. How to play Pips as well as hints in case you get stuck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints today: Clues, answers for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nyt-connections-hint-answer-today-december-12-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03v0kRhd6d411Z52UtBb3op</guid>
      <description>Connections is a New York Times word game that's all about finding the "common threads between words." How to solve the puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints, answers for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/strands-nyt-hint-december-12-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06vVIhh4iSsAOUyQRau4YDM</guid>
      <description>The NYT Strands hints and answers you need to make the most of your puzzling experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordle today: Answer, hints for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wordle-today-answer-december-12-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06nLTxgoCMy8aCtPywDSTqa</guid>
      <description>Here's the answer for "Wordle" #1637 on December 12 as well as a few hints, tips, and clues to help you solve it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lara Croft will return in Tomb Raider: Catalyst and a new remake</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/lara-croft-will-return-in-tomb-raider-catalyst-and-a-new-remake-025859998.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85fa4c90-c029-478e-991d-30dd54f94a66</guid>
      <description>The last mainline Tomb Raider game was 2018&#8217;s Shadow of the Tomb Raider, and after spending a few years in video game purgatory, Lara Croft is coming back in two new games. At The Game Awards 2025, Amazon Game Studios announced that Tomb Raider: Legacy of Atlantis will reimagine of one of the hero&#8217;s early adventures in 2026, and Tomb Raider: Catalyst will continue the series in 2027.Catalyst is developed by Crystal Dynamics and follows Lara through Northern India &#8220;in the wake of a mythical cataclysm,&#8221; as she comes into competition with other treasure hunters. Legacy of Atlantis, developed by C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Christmas gifts we love under $50</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/802969/best-gifts-under-50-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:50:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=802969</guid>
      <description>One of the easiest things to do during the holidays is spend too much money. It happens to many of us, even when we swear that things are going to be different this year. We want to help you stay true to your intentions to save money when possible, and we're doing that with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Sweeney on the future of Fortnite after another win over Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843265/apple-epic-games-tim-sweeney-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:48:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843265</guid>
      <description>Shortly after appeals court judges ruled against Apple's contempt appeal in a years-long antitrust dispute against the makers of Fortnite, I got to talk to Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney in an interview. According to Sweeney, today's ruling "completely shuts down" Apple's App Store rules that allow it to collect "junk fees." The three-judge Ninth [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego Batman: Legacy of the Dark Knight swoops onto PC and consoles on May 29</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/lego-batman-legacy-of-the-dark-knight-swoops-onto-pc-and-consoles-on-may-29-024729940.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0f48c50-021d-49a6-9748-df2eb0ab1b8f</guid>
      <description>
It didn't take too long for a game that a whole bunch of people are excited about to swoop into Grand Theft Auto VI's old release week. Or maybe Rockstar had an idea of was what was coming and delayed its blockbuster by six months to get out of the way of Lego Batman: Legacy of the Dark Knight.&#160;
Either way, TT Games and Warner Bros. Games brought a new trailer to The Game Awards and revealed that the Caped Crusader's next adventure will hit PS5, Xbox Series X/S, Steam and the Epic Games Store on May 29. The base game will cost $70 and pre-orders are open as of 11PM ET on December 11.
Lego gam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Deadpool Is Also Coming to &#8216;Marvel Rivals&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/game-awards-2025-marvel-rivals-deadpool-release-date-2000698482</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698482</guid>
      <description>The merc with a mouth will be the next character to join Netease's Marvel comics shooter early next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Trailer for the New &#8216;Street Fighter&#8217; Movie Really Looks Like That</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/street-fighter-movie-trailer-2026-2000698804</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698804</guid>
      <description>Director Kitao Sakurai's 'Street Fighter' movie kicks its way into theaters in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South of Midnight is coming to PS5 and Switch 2 next spring</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/south-of-midnight-is-coming-to-ps5-and-switch-2-next-spring-022725892.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b949be1-4861-4d2c-b4f4-0c706affb82a</guid>
      <description>South of Midnight is heading to PlayStation 5 and Switch 2 in Spring 2026, developer Compulsion Games announced on X. The third-person action-adventure game launched as an Xbox and PC exclusive, but like plenty of Microsoft's other first-party games, it's heading to competitors' consoles.Mixing platforming with magic-infused combat in a unique setting inspired by the folklore of the South, Compulsion Games' South of Midnight &#160;was generally well-received when it was released in April 2025. The game likely reached sizable audience by launching on Game Pass and PC, but coming to PlayStation and S...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders creation of litigation task force to challenge state AI laws</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/trump-orders-creation-of-litigation-task-force-to-challenge-state-ai-laws-022657022.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1b08673-2410-4d85-8550-9a64ec4756a0</guid>
      <description>On Thursday evening, President Donald Trump signed an executive order calling for a single, nationwide regulatory framework governing artificial intelligence at the expense of the ability of different states to regulate the nascent technology. &#8220;To win, United States AI companies must be free to innovate without cumbersome regulation,&#8221; the order states. &#8220;But excessive State regulation thwarts this imperative.&#8221; As was expected after a draft of the order leaked earlier this week, the centerpiece of the document is an &#8220;AI Litigation Task Force whose sole responsibility shall be to challenge state ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The devs of SOMA are back with a spiritual successor called Ontos</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-devs-of-soma-are-back-with-a-spiritual-successor-called-ontos-021535060.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e5d0c28-80e3-43f6-b09b-1ac0b7f49174</guid>
      <description>Frictional Games is back with a new game that looks primed to carry on the studio's tradition of excellence in horror. It's called Ontos, and it's slated to launch on PC, PlayStation and Xbox next year. The trailer debuted during The Game Awards 2025.The company's past projects include Amnesia: The Dark Descent and SOMA, and this new title is also looking pretty dang creepy. It looks like things will take a philosophical turn, with a story of trying to piece together your father's past that leads you to questioning the meaning of life and reality. The team is going big with the casting, with S...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control Resonant steps into a larger world that's inspired by Neon Genesis Evangelion</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/control-resonant-steps-into-a-larger-world-thats-inspired-by-neon-genesis-evangelion-021310781.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f529d84-aec6-4ea6-b13c-5dbfffd3f081</guid>
      <description>Remedy Entertainment's Control is a bizarre yet totally captivating action game that feels like Die Hard by way of David Lynch. InControl: Resonant, players step into the role of the original game's most enigmatic and unsettling characters for their own jaunt through a 'new-weird' world outside The Oldest House.Just ahead of the reveal at The Game Awards, we got an early look at Control: Resonant, the next game in the Remedy Connected Universe. Along with learning why the developers wanted a new protagonist, they also explain why this Neon Genesis Evangelion-inspired sequel is the most expansi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control&#8217;s action-RPG sequel launches in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/841950/control-resonant-sequel-announce-ps5-xbox-steam</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:05:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841950</guid>
      <description>Remedy Entertainment is finally showing off the much-anticipated sequel to Control. The new game, dubbed Control Resonant, expands on the original with a new action-RPG framework. It takes place seven years later and shifts the setting from the unsettling Oldest House of the original to a more open Manhattan, while putting players in the role [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Landman season 2 episode 5 on Paramount+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/landman-season-2-episode-5-release-date-time</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RnMxqczA62k2TWyakLUUpg</guid>
      <description>After last week's emotional outing, Landman season 2 episode 5 could be a huge turning point. But when is it on Paramount+?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larian Studios is returning to the Divinity series with... Divinity</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/larian-studios-is-returning-to-the-divinity-series-with-divinity-015833088.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45e31f4d-0e8c-45a9-aaaa-d540e7cb85c8</guid>
      <description>Larian Studios didn&#8217;t rest on its laurels for long. Two years after taking home the Game of the Year prize for Baldur&#8217;s Gate III at The Game Awards, the developer popped up again at the 2025 edition of the ceremony to announce its upcoming project, which is the next entry in the Divinity series. Simply called Divinity, this will be the studio&#8217;s biggest game to date with &#8220;more breadth and depth than ever before,&#8221; according to TGA host Geoff Keighley.After 2017&#8217;s Divinity: Original Sin II, Larian took a break from the series with which it established itself to make BG3.  The rumor mill had been ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten years after The Witness, Jonathan Blow's next massive puzzle game is almost ready for primetime</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/ten-years-after-the-witness-jonathan-blows-next-massive-puzzle-game-is-almost-ready-for-primetime-015727378.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c002c8c-bd99-4424-aba9-7d2cf251554d</guid>
      <description>Many of the big announcements at The Game Awards are for completely new projects, some of which are total surprises (if you had an Okami sequel on your bingo card last year, you're either in the know or probably used up all your luck for the next few years). We'll often get updates on games that were previously announced too. The trailer for Order of the Sinking Star is something a little different, as it's a game that Braid designer Jonathan Blow has been working on fairly openly since releasing The Witness in 2016.&#160;The trailer revealed some new details, including confirmation of the expected...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next Star Wars game is the spiritual successor to Knights of the Old Republic</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/843188/star-wars-fate-of-the-old-republic-casey-hudson</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T20:48:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843188</guid>
      <description>The next Star Wars game is coming from the director of Mass Effect and Knights of the Old Republic. Star Wars: Fate of the Old Republic was revealed during The Game Awards with a brief trailer that got Geoff Keighley so excited his voice started cracking. Like any announcement trailer, it was brief, featuring a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World launches its &#8216;super app,&#8217; including crypto pay and encrypted chat features</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/world-launches-its-super-app-including-crypto-pay-and-encrypted-chat-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074899</guid>
      <description>Tools for Humanity, the company behind the app, is seeking to expand its "real human network."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coven of the Chicken Foot is the debut game from Naughty Dog alum Bruce Straley's indie studio</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/coven-of-the-chicken-foot-is-the-debut-game-from-naughty-dog-alum-bruce-straleys-indie-studio-014004553.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eae4a882-5cbf-42b2-857c-75b244e87cb1</guid>
      <description>Coven of the Chicken Foot has a lot of things going for it already, in my book. It stars a hero rarely seen in video games, an elderly woman, and it has gorgeous storybook-style art in a lush fantasy setting. It&#8217;s a single-player puzzle platformer, it relies on wordless storytelling and the woman, a witch named Gertie, travels with a creepy-cute companion. Plus, Gertie has chicken feet. I love her little chicken feet.Coven of the Chicken Foot is the first game from Wildflower Interactive, the independent studio founded by Naughty Dog veteran Bruce Straley. The game is coming to Steam and it&#8217;s ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
