<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:25:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>6 Best Dehumidifiers to Keep Your Home Mold-Free (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-dehumidifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f43e296f7834eb5344daad</guid>
      <description>If you care about good air, it&#8217;s time for a dehumidifier. These are the best ones we've tested for everything from basements to drying laundry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony&#8217;s First EV Collab With Honda Comes With PS Remote Play in Tow</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sonys-first-ev-collab-with-honda-comes-with-ps-remote-play-in-tow-2000702648</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702648</guid>
      <description>Sorry, a proper handheld console is too hard. How about a whole car with built-in Remote Play?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $450 RTX laptop deal is too good to ignore &#8212; Acer Nitro V packs RTX 5050, 16GB RAM and 13th Gen Core i5 power</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-usd450-rtx-laptop-deal-is-too-good-to-ignore-acer-nitro-v-packs-rtx-5050-16gb-ram-and-13th-gen-core-i5-power</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4rJ6U6aXnZmqhkUyMMcBVS</guid>
      <description>Deal alert: This RTX 5050 Acer Nitro V laptop just hit a record-low $450, a saving of 41%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&#8217;s yearly recap sums up your conversations with the chatbot</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849348/openai-chatgpt-2025-year-in-review-wrapped</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T17:12:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849348</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is joining the flood of apps offering yearly recaps for users. It's rolling out a "Year in Review" feature that will show you a bunch of stats - like how many messages you sent to the chatbot in 2025 - as well as give you an AI-generated pixel art-style image that encompasses some of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI says AI browsers may always be vulnerable to prompt injection attacks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/openai-says-ai-browsers-may-always-be-vulnerable-to-prompt-injection-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078400</guid>
      <description>OpenAI says prompt injections will always be a risk for AI browsers with agentic capabilities, like Atlas. But the firm is beefing up its cybersecurity with an 'LLM-based automated attacker.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo has huge discounts on Switch 2 games in its holiday sale</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/nintendo-has-huge-discounts-on-switch-2-games-in-its-holiday-sale-220058951.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f1c14a6-f48d-4198-a188-799b453dbf51</guid>
      <description>Nintendo is in a giving state of mind this season, offering some holiday deals on games in the eShop, including a few recent Switch 2 titles. For instance, the Switch 2 version of Ball x Pit, which was one of our staff's favorite games of 2025, is 20 percent off at $12. Final Fantasy Tactics: The Ivalice Chronicles is $40, down from the usual $50 on Switch 2, which is about as good a deal as you&#8217;ll get for a current-year game release.There are also a few older games that have gotten even steeper discounts. Cyberpunk 2077: Ultimate Edition for the Nintendo Switch 2 is a whopping 75 percent off,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Reveals the Predictably Epic Runtimes of Its Remaining Episodes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-reveals-the-predictably-epic-runtimes-of-its-remaining-episodes-2000702661</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702661</guid>
      <description>As expected, you'll be spending many hours in Hawkins before you see how the Netflix series ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozempic Is Quietly Reshaping Our Shopping Habits</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ozempic-is-quietly-reshaping-our-shopping-habits-2000702616</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702616</guid>
      <description>New research finds that people taking GLP-1 tend to spend less money grocery shopping, especially on snacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelloFresh Meal Kit's Discount Code for December 2025 Unlocks a Free Zwilling Knife</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/hellofresh-zwilling-chef-knife-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6949914b99c0a1026ea4beec</guid>
      <description>The Zwilling Four-Star chef's knife is the carbon steel blade WIRED recommends for most casual home chefs. It's free with HelloFresh meal kits, using this promo code</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 Flash is smart &#8212; but when it doesn&#8217;t know, it makes stuff up anyway</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/gemini-3-flash-is-smart-but-when-it-doesnt-know-it-makes-stuff-up-anyway</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CQPnf7kHbzuDybnBMjXCq4</guid>
      <description>Gemini 3 Flash frequently makes up answers rather than saying &#8220;I don&#8217;t know."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Starship Debris Came Closer to Airplanes Than SpaceX Admits</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/report-starship-debris-came-closer-to-airplanes-than-spacex-admits-2000702634</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702634</guid>
      <description>A new report by the Wall Street Journal reveals a failed SpaceX Starship test flight endangered three airplanes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can human-led AI spark a new era of generosity?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91464686/can-human-led-ai-spark-a-new-era-of-generosity</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T21:20:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91464686/can-human-led-ai-spark-a-new-era-of-generosity</guid>
      <description>The future of giving depends on technology designed around human values.
For 50 years, America&#8217;s generosity has been stuck in neutral with charitable giving frozen at 2.5% of GDP. But not because people stopped caring. In 2024, total giving hit record highs, and food banks saw donations surge as families faced delays in SNAP benefits. The heart is there. What&#8217;s missing is technology that turns generosity into lasting impact....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate group Anna's Archive says it has scraped Spotify in its entirety</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/pirate-group-annas-archive-says-it-has-scraped-spotify-in-its-entirety-211914755.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d44519-fbc3-48af-aa57-80d7b6387beb</guid>
      <description>Anna's Archive, the open-source search engine for shadow libraries, says it scraped Spotify's entire library of music. The group acquired metadata for around 256 million tracks, with 86 million actual songs, and is just under 300TB in total size.
"A while ago, we discovered a way to scrape Spotify at scale. We saw a role for us here to build a music archive primarily aimed at preservation," the group said in a blog post. The pirated treasure trove of music represents over 15 million artists with over 58 million albums.
The group intends to make all files available for download for anyone with ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet to buy Intersect Power to bypass energy grid bottlenecks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/alphabet-to-buy-intersect-power-to-bypass-energy-grid-bottlenecks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078399</guid>
      <description>Alphabet is set to pay $4.75 billion in cash, plus debt, for the data center and clean energy developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT &#8216;Wrapped&#8217; Is a Good Reminder to Check Your Privacy Settings</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openais-chatgpt-wrapped-is-a-good-reminder-to-check-your-settings-2000702643</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702643</guid>
      <description>A chatbot never forgets (unless you opt out of memories).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out, Nvidia - Qualcomm acquires Alphawave Semi in latest addition to its AI data center push</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/watch-out-nvidia-qualcomm-acquires-alphawave-semi-in-latest-addition-to-its-ai-data-center-push</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aXVJRwm9TcEU4VisxyPmn3</guid>
      <description>Qualcomm completes Alphawave Semi acquisition early, strengthening connectivity capabilities while advancing its strategy for scalable AI data center platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Weather Map Predicts Record-Breaking Heat Across the US</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/christmas-weather-map-predicts-record-breaking-heat-across-the-us-2000702663</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702663</guid>
      <description>In some areas, the weather could feel more like May than late December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The Mighty Nein&#8217; Wants You to Know Everyone&#8217;s Big Secrets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-mighty-nein-wants-you-to-know-everyones-big-secrets-2000702352</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702352</guid>
      <description>The creators of the Prime Video series explain why character-specific changes and reveals diverge from the source material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TechRadar Gaming's favorite gaming devices of 2025: personal picks from all the year's gear</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/techradar-gamings-favorite-gaming-devices-of-2025-personal-picks-from-all-the-years-gear</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NFoaeaAHEtWxXvrQ5PKco7</guid>
      <description>Read all about TechRadar Gaming's hardware products of the year right here, including everything from consoles to headsets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart scraps AI pricing tests after backlash over grocery price swings</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91464864/instacart-scraps-ai-pricing-tests-after-backlash-over-grocery-price-swings</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91464864/instacart-scraps-ai-pricing-tests-after-backlash-over-grocery-price-swings</guid>
      <description>The company says its Eversight pricing tests are over, following a federal probe and growing concern about algorithm-driven grocery costs.
Instacart said Monday that it will no longer allow retailers to use an AI-powered price testing program, two weeks after an extensive investigation showed wide discrepancies in the cost of groceries purchased through the platform....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The easiest way to search the new Epstein files</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465154/the-easiest-way-to-search-the-new-epstein-files</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465154/the-easiest-way-to-search-the-new-epstein-files</guid>
      <description>Even if the DOJ dump is incomplete and heavily redacted, at least Jmail makes them easy to access thanks to a familiar interface and AI.
The long-awaited release of Jeffrey Epstein&#8217;s files by the Department of Justice arrived on December 19 with a bureaucratic whimper and bang of public outrage. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty, Titanfall developer Vince Zampella has died at age 55</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849297/vince-zampella-dies-call-of-duty-titanfall-respawn-battlefield</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T15:57:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849297</guid>
      <description>Vince Zampella, who had a major hand in developing franchises like Medal of Honor, Call of Duty, and Battlefield, died in a car crash on Sunday, NBC Los Angeles reports. He was 55. NBC Los Angeles and CBS Los Angeles report California Highway Patrol responded to a single-car crash at around 12:45PM local time on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin halts 6 GW of offshore wind leases again</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/trump-admin-halts-6-gw-of-offshore-wind-leases-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078391</guid>
      <description>The move is the latest attempt by the Trump administration to delay the construction of 6 gigawatts of offshore wind near a hotspot of data center development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase buys The Clearing Company, doubling down on prediction markets</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465133/coinbase-clearing-company-prediction-markets</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T20:47:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465133/coinbase-clearing-company-prediction-markets</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, Coinbase launched its prediction markets platform.
Coinbase said on Monday it will buy prediction markets startup The Clearing Company, its tenth acquisition this year, as the crypto exchange looks to expand beyond its core digital assets business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty co-creator Vince Zampella killed in a car crash</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/call-of-duty-co-creator-vince-zampella-killed-in-a-car-crash-204046354.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d15b9ff-7ec9-4fc2-b968-425b5f8477e6</guid>
      <description>Game developer Vince Zampella, known for his work on many popular first-person shooter franchises, has died. According to Los Angeles news channel NBC4, Zampella was killed in a single-vehicle car crash on Sunday along with one other unnamed person. He was 55.Zampella has helmed several well-known first-person shooter titles. He was a founder of Infinity Ward, where he was a creator of the Call of Duty series. Zampella remained at the company for the launch of the hugely popular franchise's first few installments. In 2010, he co-founded Respawn Entertainment, the studio behind Titanfall, Titan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Magnetic Cloak Could Make Sensitive Tech Practically Invisible</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/proposed-magnetic-cloak-could-make-sensitive-tech-practically-invisible-2000702571</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702571</guid>
      <description>The cloak can shield objects of any shape from unwanted noise, the researchers say.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
