<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:26:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>True Classic Tees Deals for the 2025 Holidays: 25 Percent Off Crew Necks</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/true-classic-tees-flash-deals-december-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939c7358d85d77833f7b8a9</guid>
      <description>True Classic Tees is running holiday &#8220;flash deals&#8221; with some of the best prices we've seen in months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of South Korean retail giant Coupang resigns after massive data breach</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/ceo-of-south-korean-retail-giant-coupang-resigns-after-massive-data-breach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074924</guid>
      <description>The massive data breach at the South Korean retail giant Coupang affects more than half of the country's population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Week&#8217;s &#8216;Mighty Nein&#8217; Inherits the Beef Between Its 2 Best Characters</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-weeks-mighty-nein-inherits-the-beef-between-its-2-best-characters-2000694310</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694310</guid>
      <description>The Mighty Nein will become a great, well-oiled party someday, but first, they've got some kinks to work out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s favorite holiday gifts under $100</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/800440/best-gifts-under-100-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800440</guid>
      <description>Between all the new phones, smartwatches, and laptops we see throughout the year, it often feels like we're constantly being nudged toward shinier, more expensive gadgets. And I get it. As a self-professed gadget nerd, few things are more exciting than unboxing and setting up a new device. But the truth is, you can still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eufy&#8217;s Best Robot Vacuum Is $405 Off (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-best-robot-vacuum-deal-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939c384ac300a7f1db48d19</guid>
      <description>Eufy&#8217;s last-season robot vacuum-mop has a crazy price cut. Grab it before it&#8217;s gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify's new playlist feature gives users more control over their recommendation algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/spotifys-new-playlist-feature-gives-users-more-control-over-their-recommendation-algorithm-203237903.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d363f959-a9d1-4f31-9725-f863e4fe7a59</guid>
      <description>Spotify is attempting to give users more control over the music the streaming service recommends with a new playlist feature called "Prompted Playlist." The beta feature is rolling out in New Zealand starting on December 11, and will let users write a custom prompt that Spotify can use &#8212; alongside their listening history &#8212; to create a playlist of new music.By tapping on Prompted Playlist, Spotify subscribers participating in the beta will be presented with a prompt field where they can type exactly what they want to hear and how they want Spotify's algorithm to respond. And while past AI featu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finally! Another external USB4 SSD hit the market &#8212; and this one is likely to be far more affordable than rivals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/finally-another-external-usb4-ssd-hit-the-market-and-this-one-is-likely-to-be-far-more-affordable-than-rivals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QRXjtqQi2wYnPe7Ugt34ta</guid>
      <description>TeamGroup PD40 is a lightweight, travel-ready USB4 SSD offering strong performance, broad compatibility, and appealing value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best smart rings for tracking sleep and health</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/647901/best-smart-rings</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T15:29:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=647901</guid>
      <description>So, you&#8217;re thinking of buying a smart ring. Well, some good news. Picking the best of the lot is incredibly easy right now. The &#8220;bad&#8221; news is that, as far as trustworthiness and reliability, your choices are somewhat limited, as this is still a niche and emerging gadget category. Smart rings are in the middle [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Rubio Orders State Dept to Stop Using Calibri Font in Anti-DEI Push</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marco-rubio-orders-state-dept-to-stop-using-calibri-font-in-anti-dei-push-2000698012</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698012</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Switching to Calibri achieved nothing except the degradation of the department&#8217;s official correspondence," Rubio's memo said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The scramble to launch data centers into space is heating up</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841887/data-center-space-solar-power-aetherflux-lunch</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T15:13:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841887</guid>
      <description>A startup developing technologies to harness solar power in space is throwing its hat in with big tech companies attempting to build out data centers that orbit Earth. The US-based company, Aetherflux, announced on Tuesday that it plans to launch its first data center satellite in early 2027 - the first piece of a larger [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google adds prompt injection defenses to Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/google-adds-prompt-injection-defenses-to-chrome</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HnSZeSNLdGNKbCF6wJFtAR</guid>
      <description>There's an AI that checks what the other AIs are doing and makes sure they're not tricked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum severity React2Shell flaw exploited by North Korean hackers in malware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/maximum-severity-react2shell-flaw-exploited-by-north-korean-hackers-in-malware-attacks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HZLYE8hHenkVefvKukCQvF</guid>
      <description>Sysdig finds evidence of Contagious Interview actors abusing React2Shell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel loses its latest challenge to 16-year-old EU antitrust case</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/intel-loses-its-latest-challenge-to-16-year-old-eu-antitrust-case-200746004.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dde264b0-f2a7-4d22-933f-926286bfe1ba</guid>
      <description>Intel will have to pay up in an antitrust case dating back to 2009, Reuters reported on Wednesday. The company has lost its challenge against a &#8364;376 million ($438.7 million) regulatory fine levied by the European Commission. However, Intel managed to get the amount reduced to 237 million euros ($276.6 million).The case began in 2009, when mobile computing was in its infancy and netbooks (remember those?) were all the rage in the PC space. At the time, the EU ruled that Intel violated antitrust laws on multiple fronts. First, it used illegal hidden rebates to push rivals out of the PC processor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des essais &#233;tranges en orbite &#224; 36&#8239;000 km de la Terre : que pr&#233;paraient ces deux satellites chinois ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-essais-etranges-orbite-36-000-km-terre-preparaient-ces-deux-satellites-chinois-128412/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:03:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-essais-etranges-orbite-36-000-km-terre-preparaient-ces-deux-satellites-chinois-128412/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Alors que les &#201;tats-Unis viennent de d&#233;signer la Chine comme leur principal adversaire, cette derni&#232;re a r&#233;alis&#233; une avanc&#233;e technologique significative dans le domaine spatial. Deux satellites chinois ont en effet d&#233;montr&#233; des capacit&#233;s op&#233;rationnelles in&#233;dites en orbite, qui pourraient bien...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify tests more personalized, AI-powered &#8216;Prompted Playlists&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/spotify-tests-more-personalized-ai-powered-prompted-playlists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074868</guid>
      <description>The playlists can factor in world knowledge, go back to your listening history from day one, and be refreshed daily or weekly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Grinch Stole Modern Christmas</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-the-grinch-stole-modern-christmas-2000697520</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697520</guid>
      <description>From his storybook legacy to his modern-day anti-holiday influence, the Grinch has become an enduring face of the holidays&#8212;sincerely or otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best white elephant gifts worth fighting over for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-10-best-white-elephant-gifts-worth-fighting-over-for-2025-150516281.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">167b1092-71dd-42b0-b152-e8240159f089</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of competing ideas as to what a white elephant gift exchange really is. The origins of the term &#8220;white elephant&#8221; point to one definition: According to legend, the King of Siam would give a white elephant to courtiers who had upset them. It was a far more devious punishment than simply having them executed. The recipient had no choice but to simply thank the king for such an opulent gift, knowing that they likely could not afford the upkeep for such an animal. It would inevitably lead them to financial ruin.While that story is almost certainly untrue, it can inform one approach ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch New Zealand vs West Indies Test 2 on TVNZ+ &#8212; it's *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/new-zealand-vs-west-indies-test-2-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">h2tfxEyk9b9apwzEhrMns</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on how to watch New Zealand vs West Indies Test 2 on TVNZ+ for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world premieres and other hotness from The Game Awards 2025 Day of the Devs stream</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-world-premieres-and-other-hotness-from-the-game-awards-2025-day-of-the-devs-stream-200000447.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b31f45a5-f2c5-43c4-8442-3ad71203036e</guid>
      <description>You gotta love that post-Day of the Devs showcase feeling. The organization, founded by Double Fine Productions and iam8bit, consistently highlights top-tier games from independent developers across the globe, providing space for creators to share their stories in both online and in-person events. This year&#8217;s Day of the Devs: The Game Awards Digital Showcase was an hour-long celebration of 22 upcoming indie games, including six world premieres and three release date announcements.Settle in and bask in the afterglow with us:World PremieresVirtue and a Sledgehammer - DeconstructeamDeconstructeam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z is jealous of &#8216;millennial optimism&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457548/gen-z-is-jealous-of-millennial-optimism</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457548/gen-z-is-jealous-of-millennial-optimism</guid>
      <description>The youngest in the workforce are nostalgic for a period they didn&#8217;t experience. But was it really all that great?
Gen Z&#8217;s latest online fixation is the so-called &#8216;millennial optimism&#8217; era. The TikTok trend sees users posting early-2000s throwback snaps set to The Middle East&#8217;s 2009 song &#8220;Blood&#8221;. Think moustache tattoos, Apple Photo Booth selfies, and owl-print tops paired with galaxy leggings.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Wand just dropped four new vibes, and each one comes with a freebie</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-10-le-wand-classique-collection-free-gift-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05OJICuHeRljkc6mW299f82</guid>
      <description>Le Wand's new Classique line (which includes four vibrators) is luxe, affordable, and it comes with a freebie for your goodie drawer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI Answers the Question, &#8216;What if Product Placement was Significantly Worse?&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xai-answers-the-question-what-if-product-placement-was-significantly-worse-2000697957</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697957</guid>
      <description>Sometimes innovation is two steps back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. will require some tourists to hand over 5 years of social media</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458104/u-s-will-require-some-tourists-to-hand-over-5-years-of-social-media</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458104/u-s-will-require-some-tourists-to-hand-over-5-years-of-social-media</guid>
      <description>A new CBP proposal would make social media history, emails, phone numbers, and even selfies mandatory for certain foreign visitors.
Want to visit the U.S.? Be prepared to cough up your social media history.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I couldn&amp;#8217;t fix it with iFixit&#8217;s AI FixBot</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/841252/ifixit-fixbot-hands-on-ai-chatbot</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T14:44:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841252</guid>
      <description>My classic Sony CRT television won't power on. My living room is chilly because my Mitsubishi heat pump isn't putting out enough hot air. I want my Japanese N64 to play US games, too, but I've been too busy to pop the hood. What if I had an AI companion to talk me through? iFixit [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview Energy wants to beam energy from space to existing solar farms</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/overview-energy-wants-to-beam-energy-from-space-to-existing-solar-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074859</guid>
      <description>The stealthy startup plans to use a network of satellites to harvest sunlight and send it to Earth using infrared lasers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus Game Catalog additions for December include Assassin's Creed Mirage</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/ps-plus-game-catalog-additions-for-december-include-assassins-creed-mirage-193731745.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b23e575-f459-4042-bda4-a1f5f53f9470</guid>
      <description>Sony just announced December's Game Catalog additions for PS Plus subscribers and it's a pretty decent lineup. All of these titles will be ready to play on December 16, except Skate Story which is already available.

Speaking of Skate Story, it's a really weird skateboarding sim that's set in a glass-covered world. The reviews have been positive, with many people praising the outlandish story, surreal locations and the satisfying trick mechanics. It's made by Sam Eng, who was behind the indie shooter Zarvot. This new game is only available for PS5 subscribers.

Assassin's Creed Mirage will be ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit is testing verification</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/841879/reddit-verification-test</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T14:33:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841879</guid>
      <description>Reddit is starting to test verified profiles, the company announced today. Users who are verified as part of this "limited alpha test" will have a gray checkmark next to their username "across profiles, communities, feeds, post detail pages, and search results." For this "initial test," Reddit says it's "selected a group of public figures and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube TV Wants to Unbundle the Cable Package That Streamers Were Meant to Kill in the First Place</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youtube-tv-wants-to-unbundle-the-cable-package-that-streamers-were-meant-to-kill-in-the-first-place-2000697966</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697966</guid>
      <description>The video platform&#8217;s cable streaming service is introducing cheaper genre-specifying channel bundles next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only Core Ultra 265U laptop with a VGA port and a DVD writer just launched &#8212; and yes, it HAS to be in Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-only-core-ultra-265u-laptop-with-a-vga-port-and-a-dvd-writer-just-launched-and-yes-it-has-to-be-in-japan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UkAVPUjJ7MgpJbWfagxhtQ</guid>
      <description>Japan continues to welcome new laptops with retro features, and the NEC VersaPro VX-R blends modern Intel processors with aging connectors effectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Up That Hill returns for Season 5 of Stranger Things</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/running-up-that-hill-stranger-things-scene</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02FbnYlcVUKQs8YGRd7yI1l</guid>
      <description>Kate Bush's 'Running Up That Hill' returns and gives special meaning to Max's battle.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
