<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:40:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kilo CLI 1.0 brings open source vibe coding to your terminal with support for 500+ models</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/kilo-cli-1-0-brings-open-source-vibe-coding-to-your-terminal-with-support</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72XBkemR17bcKGCv5miIla</guid>
      <description>Remote-first AI coding startup Kilo doesn't think software developers should have to pledge their undying allegiance to any one development environment &#8212; and certainly not any one model or harness. This week, the startup &#8212; backed by GitLab co-founder Sid Sijbrandij &#8212; unveiled Kilo CLI 1.0, a complete rebuild of its command-line tool that offers support for more than 500 different underlying AI models from proprietary leaders and open source rivals like Alibaba's Qwen. It comes just weeks after Kilo launched a Slackbot allowing developers to ship code directly from Salesforce's popular messagin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A16z just raised $1.7B for AI infrastructure. Here&#8217;s where it&#8217;s going.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/a16z-just-raised-1-7b-for-ai-infrastructure-heres-where-its-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3089607</guid>
      <description>Andreessen Horowitz just raised&#160;a whopping&#160;&#8288;new&#160;$15 billion&#160;in funding&#8288;.&#160;And a&#160;$1.7 billion&#160;chunk&#160;of that is going to&#160;its&#160;&#8288;infrastructure&#160;team&#8288;,&#160;the one responsible for some of its biggest, most prominent&#160;AI investments including&#160;Black Forrest Labs, Cursor, OpenAI,&#160;&#8288;ElevenLabs&#8288;, Ideogram,&#160;&#8288;Fal&#8288;&#160;and dozens of others.&#160;&#160; A16z&#160;&#8288;general partner&#160;with the infra team Jennifer Li&#8288;&#160;(who oversees such&#160;investments&#160;as&#160;ElevenLabs&#160;&#8211; just valued at&#160;$11 billion);&#160;Ideagram&#160;and Fal, has a clear thesis on where&#160;the team is looking [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Town, 2.0</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/874050/regulator-shutdown-averted-crypto</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T15:20:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/874050/the-crypto-bill-is-falling-apart-in-congress</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers about the most ambitious crossover event of all time: the infinity war between technology and politics. Not subscribed yet? Come on, do it! Washington might seem slower than Silicon Valley. But that's because it's more turbulent. In order to achieve anything, one has to navigate [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Crown&#8217; Star Claire Foy Quit Caffeine After Living With Gut Parasite for Half a Decade</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/crown-star-claire-foy-quit-caffeine-after-living-with-a-gut-parasite-for-years-2000717999</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717999</guid>
      <description>The British actor claims to have struggled with gut parasites for at least five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post Lays Off Its Amazon Beat Reporter as Bezos Brings the Hammer Down</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/washington-post-lays-off-its-amazon-beat-reporter-as-bezos-brings-the-hammer-down-2000718027</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718027</guid>
      <description>The paper is reportedly cutting roughly a third of its staff while its billionaire owner sits on a $261 billion fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8217;What will people do in the year 2050, given the enormous intellectual power computers are likely to have?&#8217;: The man Google calls the spiritual father of AI asked big questions in 1991 &#8212; 35 years later, we&#8217;re still wrestling with the answers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-will-people-do-in-the-year-2050-given-the-enormous-intellectual-power-computers-are-likely-to-have-the-man-google-calls-the-spiritual-father-of-ai-asked-big-questions-in-1991-35-years-later-were-still-wrestling-with-the-answers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7H57F2P3hLcHFFJm5BNVdH</guid>
      <description>Ray Kurzweil&#8217;s 1991 AI predictions feel strikingly familiar today, revealing how progress advanced faster than our understanding of intelligence and purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best digital frames for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/best-digital-frame-120046051.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c6bd8ad-dfb7-4195-af8b-c278a7b1c8d7</guid>
      <description>A digital photo frame shouldn&#8217;t be complicated. At its best, it&#8217;s just a good-looking screen that can be set up quickly that reliably shows the photos you care about. Unfortunately, that&#8217;s not always how things play out. The market is flooded with cheap digital frames that promise simplicity but end up delivering washed-out displays, clunky apps and a frustrating experience &#8212; leading you to abandon it after a week.That&#8217;s a shame, because a good digital frame can be really enjoyable. Most of us have thousands of photos sitting on our phones that never make it beyond the camera roll, even though...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Bridgerton! It's Medieval Dynasty! No, it's The Sims 4 Royalty and Legacy, and I think it&#8217;s the best of both worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/its-bridgerton-its-medieval-dynasty-no-its-the-sims-4-royalty-and-legacy-and-i-think-its-the-best-of-both-worlds</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XT4Kri4NShf7FYzFFWYVSK</guid>
      <description>Scandals, dynasties and swordfighting make The Sims 4 Royalty and Legacy one of the most exciting storytelling packs in a while</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Season 2 Ends Pointing at the Big Bad You Already Knew Was Coming</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-season-2-ending-explained-colorado-liberty-prime-enclave-2000717889</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717889</guid>
      <description>Amazon's video game adaptation wraps up its sophomore season with plenty of nods to the 'Fallout' lore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch: all the news about Blizzard&#8217;s hit hero shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2022/6/14/23167853/overwatch-2-activision-blizzard-news</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T14:53:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/2022/6/14/603/overwatch-2-activision-blizzard-news</guid>
      <description>Overwatch 2, the sequel to Activision Blizzard&#8217;s hit hero shooter Overwatch, was announced in 2019 but didn&#8217;t arrive for another three years, eventually bringing a shift to five-on-five matches in PVP, and a few new characters, including Overwatch&#8217;s first Black female hero. After canceling planned PvE content and unlocking its hero pool, the game&#8217;s developers [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notepad++ Users, You May Have Been Hacked by China</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/notepad-plus-plus-china-hackers-update-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69836805afde988bb6796bae</guid>
      <description>Suspected Chinese state-backed hackers hijacked the Notepadd++ update infrastructure to deliver a backdoored version of the popular free source code editor and note-taking app for Windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Market in Shambles as Bitcoin Price Down 40% Since October High</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/crypto-market-in-shambles-as-bitcoin-price-down-40-since-october-high-2000717957</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717957</guid>
      <description>All muh apes, gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon wants Alexa+ to be the reason you keep Prime</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486821/amazon-wants-alexa-to-be-the-reason-you-keep-prime</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486821/amazon-wants-alexa-to-be-the-reason-you-keep-prime</guid>
      <description>Alexa+ costs $19.99 a month, but Amazon is bundling it into Prime at no extra charge, giving members a powerful new perk.
Amazon is rolling out a new feature in hopes of retaining, or perhaps attracting, new Prime members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games Done Quick's Back to Black 2026 event kicks off tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/games-done-quicks-back-to-black-2026-event-kicks-off-tomorrow-194147068.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02d88d9-a76b-4f41-9cab-c50afe458869</guid>
      <description>Hot on the heels of AGDQ in January, Games Done Quick is hosting its second speedrunning event of the year, Back to Black 2026, starting tomorrow, February 5. The four-day event is organized by Black in a Flash and is raising money for Race Forward, a nonprofit that works across communities to address systemic racism.Back to Black is timed to the start of Black History Month and highlights the deep bench of talent in the Black speedrunning community. A few runs, like ones for Hades II, Donkey Kong Country and Silent Hill 4, were teased when Back to Black 2026 was announced last year. The full ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea&amp;#8217;s cheap new smart home gear is struggling to get connected</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/873973/ikea-matter-thread-smart-home-connectivity-issues</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T14:35:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873973</guid>
      <description>I've spent the last couple of weeks trying - and mostly failing - to test Ikea's new Matter-over-Thread gear. These highly anticipated smart home devices include programmable buttons, smart bulbs, plugs, and temperature and motion sensors - all of which should work with any smart home platform and start at just $6. But I've hit [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rent-a-Human Site Lets AI Agents Hire an IRL Set of Opposable Thumbs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rent-a-human-site-lets-ai-agents-hire-an-irl-set-of-opposable-thumbs-2000717958</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717958</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the future, where you can do TaskRabbit for robots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Chinese data breach allegedly spills 8.7 billion records - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/massive-chinese-data-breach-allegedly-spills-8-7-billion-records-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PMfySdbANPMEewEir54GC9</guid>
      <description>Someone kept a gigantic database unlocked on the internet, allowing researchers (and likely, hackers, too) to find it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hinge tests facial recognition scans in these countries</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/hinge-testing-face-check-facial-recognition-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02EW3PAUEb6sGwb5jUSE6P8</guid>
      <description>Dating app Hinge is testing Face Check, the facial recognition scan already launched on Tinder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roblox&#8217;s '4D' creation toolset is now available in open beta</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/robloxs-4d-creation-toolset-is-now-available-in-open-beta-191510664.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9344a8-8b2a-4411-86f0-2bfe848750c6</guid>
      <description>Roblox launched an open-source AI model that generates 3D objects on the fly early last year and now that toolset is getting a massive boost. The platform has introduced a model that whips up "4D" objects. I put 4D in quotes because it doesn't actually allow access to the fourth dimension, but rather lets users make interactive 3D objects via prompts.
As suggested, these aren't static 3D models. They are fully functional and interactive objects that move and react to players. The beta toolset can't be used to make anything, as it's rather limited for now. There are just two templates for users...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman unloads on Elon Musk in latest X posts</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/sam-altman-elon-musk-feud-continues</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07aqtKFD65itrnYb6QPVJjF</guid>
      <description>Sam Altman is unloading on Elon Musk in latest X posts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenClaw&amp;#8217;s AI &amp;#8216;skill&amp;#8217; extensions are a security nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/874011/openclaw-ai-skill-clawhub-extensions-security-nightmare</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T14:03:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874011</guid>
      <description>OpenClaw, the AI agent that has exploded in popularity over the past week, is raising new security concerns after researchers uncovered malware in hundreds of user-submitted "skill" add-ons on its marketplace. In a post on Monday, 1Password product VP Jason Meller says OpenClaw's skill hub has become "an attack surface," with the most-downloaded add-on serving [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscar-Nominated &#8216;Avatar&#8217; Costume Designer Explains That Yes, Those Na&#8217;vi Outfits Are Real</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-oscar-nominated-avatar-costume-designer-explains-that-yes-those-navi-outfits-are-real-2000717959</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717959</guid>
      <description>James Cameron's 'Avatar: Fire and Ash' scored two Academy Award nominations: Best Visual Effects and Best Costume Design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wardrobe malfunctions to caged kids: A look at the most controversial Super Bowl halftime moments</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486961/super-bowl-controversial-halftime-moments</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-04T19:00:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486961/super-bowl-controversial-halftime-moments</guid>
      <description>The NFL has long maintained guardrails around the halftime show, particularly when performances edge toward political commentary.
For a show that lasts roughly 13 minutes, the&#160;Super Bowl&#160;halftime performance has fueled decades of conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New AI Math Startup Just Cracked 4 Previously Unsolved Problems</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/a-new-ai-math-ai-startup-just-cracked-4-previously-unsolved-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697cf0067c721427569fbace</guid>
      <description>Axiom says its AI found solutions to several long-standing math problems, a sign of the technology&#8217;s steadily advancing reasoning capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Ring Video Doorbell changed how I monitor my home &#8212; and 10,000+ people bought it last month</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/home-security/this-ring-video-doorbell-changed-how-i-monitor-my-home-and-10-000-people-bought-it-last-month</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">E5JSiRxBCSxeaV3pjgdUbY</guid>
      <description>The best-selling Ring Battery Doorbell has changed how I monitor my home, and over 10,000 people have bought it this month &#8211; it can be yours for just $59.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch will drop the '2' as Jetpack Cat and four other heroes arrive on February 10</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/overwatch-will-drop-the-2-as-jetpack-cat-and-four-other-heroes-arrive-on-february-10-184500327.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57a5ae71-c6f4-445a-a600-118a0f6f9ada</guid>
      <description>Blizzard is running a series of showcases for several of its major franchises and on Wednesday, it was time for Overwatch to step up to the plate. That&#8217;s Overwatch, by the way, and not Overwatch 2. The studio is formally nixing the number from the game's name.&#160;"Overwatch is more than just a digit: it's a living universe that keeps growing, keeps surprising, and keeps bringing players together from around the world," the Overwatch team said in a statement. "This year marks a huge turning point in how the development team envisions the future of Overwatch, so we are officially dropping the '2' a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
