<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:29:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Wi-Fi 8 is appearing at CES before most of us have switched to Wi-Fi 7</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856883/ces-2026-wi-fi-8-asus-broadcom-mediatek</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:26:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856883</guid>
      <description>The first Wi-Fi 8 routers and chips made a surprise appearance at CES 2026, and could launch this year, only a couple of years after Wi-Fi 7 debuted. So, if you don't already have a Wi-Fi 7 router - and many of us don't - you might want to consider holding off on upgrading. Rather [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just saw Roborock's new robot vacuum with legs, and it's going to make no-go zones a thing of the past</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/i-just-saw-roborocks-new-robot-vacuum-with-legs-and-its-going-to-make-no-go-zones-a-thing-of-the-past</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EDu6RLzs5rpA3g9RPXaxrd</guid>
      <description>Cleaning stairs is just the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California lawmaker proposes a four-year ban on AI chatbots in kid&#8217;s toys</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/california-lawmaker-proposes-a-four-year-ban-on-ai-chatbots-in-kids-toys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080435</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Our children cannot be used as lab rats for Big Tech to experiment on,&#8221; Senator Steve Padilla said. He just introduced a bill to ban AI chatbots in toys until safety regulations are developed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This RV will charge your electric truck after towing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/856487/this-rv-will-charge-your-electric-truck-after-towing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:20:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856487</guid>
      <description>Electric trucks seem to have hit a pothole recently, ignored by truck owners who say they're worried about losing too much ranging from towing. But what if the thing your towing could also pump electrons back into your truck's battery when all's said and done? That what California-company Evotrex is proposing with its new RV, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ralph Wiggum went from 'The Simpsons' to the biggest name in AI right now</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/how-ralph-wiggum-went-from-the-simpsons-to-the-biggest-name-in-ai-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2n4gRaKoSDaE3jlMJyiGRU</guid>
      <description>In the fast-moving world of AI development, it is rare for a tool to be described as both "a meme" and AGI, artificial generalized intelligence, the "holy grail" of a model or system that can reliably outperform humans on economically valuable work. Yet, that is exactly where the Ralph Wiggum plugin for Claude Code now sits. Named after the infamously high-pitched, hapless yet persistent character on "The Simpsons," this newish tool (released in summer 2025) &#8212; and the philosophy behind it &#8212; has set the developer community on X (formerly Twitter) into a tizzy of excitement over the last few wee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most bizarre tech announced so far at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/the-most-bizarre-tech-announced-so-far-at-ces-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080421</guid>
      <description>From an AI panda pet to an anime girl hologram for your desk, here are the wildest products at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok is undressing children &#8212; can the law stop it?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/855832/grok-undressing-children-csam-law-x-elon-musk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:08:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855832</guid>
      <description>Grok began 2026 as it began 2025: under fire for its AI-generated images. Elon Musk's chatbot has spent the last week flooding X with nonconsensual, sexualized deepfakes of adults and minors. Circulating screenshots show Grok complying with requests to put real women in lingerie and make them spread their legs, and to put small children [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Music signs a new AI deal with Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856849/universal-music-nvidia-ai-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:07:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856849</guid>
      <description>Universal Music Group is partnering with Nvidia to bring a new AI model to one of the world's largest music catalogs. Among other initiatives, Tuesday's announcement touts the extension of Nvidia's music AI model Music Flamingo, which is designed to mimic how humans understand music by recognizing nuanced elements like song structure, harmony, emotional arcs, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Least One &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Kid Thinks Eleven Is Actually Dead</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-ending-sadie-sink-eleven-2000706300</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706300</guid>
      <description>Sadie Sink has no problem taking a pessimistic view on the Netflix finale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 57 Best Shows on Disney+, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (January 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-shows-disney-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">632c75aa74ce5b82a68ef323</guid>
      <description>The End of an Era, Percy Jackson and the Olympians, and The Beatles Anthology are just a few of the shows you should be watching on Disney+ this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES promises the robot butler, but delivers better Roombas instead</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855329/rosey-robot-roomba-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855329</guid>
      <description>If you listen to the CES hype machine this year, you might think that robots are finally ready to take over your domestic duties. To some extent that's true, but take note of the plural: there's no single robot ready to take over all of your household chores yet, but an army of them just [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, Lego, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel is building a handheld gaming platform including a dedicated chip</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/intel-is-building-a-handheld-gaming-platform-including-a-dedicated-chip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080288</guid>
      <description>Intel has been building chips designed for gaming PCs for years but the company is now moving into handheld devices too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMArena lands $1.7B valuation four months after launching its product</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/lmarena-lands-1-7b-valuation-four-months-after-launching-its-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080354</guid>
      <description>LMArena, which started as a UC Berkeley research project, has raised about $250 million total and become a unicorn in about seven months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Google Pixel Buds Pro 2 earbuds are on sale for $165</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-google-pixel-buds-pro-2-earbuds-are-on-sale-for-165-193444491.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcfa8124-d118-4e0c-95ba-1799f6041da5</guid>
      <description>Google's Pixel Buds Pro 2 earbuds are on sale for $165 via Amazon. That's a nice discount of $64, which breaks down to 28 percent. There is a spot of bad news. The deal only applies to the hazel colorway. Other colors are discounted, but they aren't as cheap. It's not as if the hazel is hideous. These are standard dark brown-hued earbuds.
The device made our list of the best wireless earbuds, and this is particularly true for those tied into the Pixel ecosystem. These earbuds are on the smaller side and, more importantly, comfortable to wear for long periods of time. They also manage to delive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Luxurious Headphones Are Almost Half Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/bowers-wilkins-px8-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d458389c20eb7bcfd9ce0</guid>
      <description>The Bowers &amp; Wilkins Px8 feature premium materials and luxurious sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Bringing AI Slop Directly to TVs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/googles-bringing-ai-slop-directly-to-tvs-2000706245</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706245</guid>
      <description>The slop is inescapable at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest Nvidia announcements at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856439/nvidia-ces-2026-announcements-roundup</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T14:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856439</guid>
      <description>We're not even a full week into 2026 yet, but Nvidia has already announced several products and updates to start the new year. Nvidia's new Vera Rubin architecture was launched earlier than expected at CES, joined by announcements for its own Tesla-rivaling self-driving car technology, and the latest updates coming to DLSS, G-Sync display tech, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Luna's January lineup includes Madden NFL 26 for free</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/amazon-lunas-january-lineup-includes-madden-nfl-26-for-free-192500032.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7ee42cf-0491-467b-92d9-802d94fcb4a4</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced the next collection games that will be available to play through its Luna game streaming service in January. The highlight of the bunch is EA SPORTS Madden NFL 26, which will be available for a limited time on the service, but as in the past, Amazon is also giving away free PC games too if you'd prefer not to stream.Madden NFL 26 will be available to Prime members everywhere Luna currently streams, from January 10 through February 10. Luna is also getting several new "GameNight" games &#8212; Amazon's name for streaming games you can play with a smartphone &#8212; including multiplaye...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of spyware maker pcTattletale pleads guilty to hacking and advertising surveillance software</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/founder-of-spyware-maker-pctattletale-pleads-guilty-to-hacking-and-advertising-surveillance-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080222</guid>
      <description>Bryan Fleming, the founder of hacked stalkerware company pcTattletale, pleaded guilty to federal charges linked to the running of his now-defunct Michigan-based spyware company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best laptop deals you can get right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/good-deals/23161948/apple-macbook-lenovo-acer-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T14:20:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/good-deals/23161948/apple-macbook-lenovo-acer-deal-sale</guid>
      <description>If you want a great laptop, you&#8217;re going to have to fork over a ton of money, right? Not necessarily. There are dozens of good laptops on the market at various price points, with even more coming in 2026. However, it can feel overwhelming to find the right one for your needs (some are better [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosori's stainless steel air fryer wants to assuage your fear of microplastics</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/cosoris-stainless-steel-air-fryer-wants-to-assuage-your-fear-of-microplastics-191339820.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89064382-8f58-4b86-8df2-ea297bfd9563</guid>
      <description>Home appliance company Cosori has released a stainless steel air fryer because why not. The Iconic Air Fryer debuted in all its shiny glory at Pepcom this week, a media showcase event ahead of CES.
Cosori says the air fryer is meant to address a pain point in the market regarding consumer concern over heating food in plastic air fryers. The company's answer to this is a 6.5-quart stainless steel fryer with a ceramic, nonstick coating on all surfaces that come in contact with food. Iconic has a brushed metal finish that Cosori says is corrosion resistant.
The controls and display for the fryer ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Section 230 Doesn&#8217;t Cover Elon Musk&#8217;s Ass When It Comes to Deepfake Abuse, Senator Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/section-230-doesnt-cover-elon-musks-ass-when-it-comes-to-deepfake-abuse-senator-says-2000706234</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706234</guid>
      <description>"States must step in to hold X and Musk accountable, if Trump&#8217;s DOJ won&#8217;t," Wyden said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This WebUI vulnerability allows remote code execution - here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-webui-vulnerability-allows-remote-code-execution-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pqxNKMFhVzuc2XGMcHXzvB</guid>
      <description>Popular AI interface was plagued by an 8/10 bug, but a fix is now available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Went Into the Most Satisfying Scene in &#8216;Predator: Badlands&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/what-went-into-the-most-satisfying-scene-in-predator-badlands-2000705637</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705637</guid>
      <description>Elle Fanning and Dimitrius Schuster-Koloamatangi star in the sci-fi action film, which is now out on digital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI moves into the real world as companion robots and pets</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856207/ces-2026-trend-ai-companion-robot-pet</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856207</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence doesn't always want to optimize your life or steal your job. Sometimes, AI just wants to be your friend. And while robot pets weren't the biggest stars of CES 2026, they've become more than just noise and are signaling how AI is apparently leaving our screens and taking on a physical presence in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot Games' 2XKO will hit consoles on January 20</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/riot-games-2xko-will-hit-consoles-on-january-20-185627826.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cf995cf-86dc-401e-93b3-1530868bda63</guid>
      <description>Riot Games has a pretty long legacy as a PC gaming studio, but the company is spreading out into consoles with its newest title. 2XKO will land on consoles on January 20, to coincide with the start of its first season. The game will be available globally for the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S with cross-play support, allowing current players to access their existing progress on a PC account.&#160;&#160;The formula for most recent Riot projects (with the notable exception of Valorant), has been to take the extensive character roster from its long-standing League of Legends MOBA and place them into oth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested sleep earbuds for months: Here are the 3 Id buy, and the one Id skip</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/roundup/best-sleep-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01mtt5K1NAhb11M67rjRZQw</guid>
      <description>We tried sleep earbuds and earplugs from Ozlo, Anker Soundcore, 1More, and Loop &#8212; these are the three we'd buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Hits Pause on Ray-Ban Display Expansion to Europe and Canada</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meta-just-put-some-big-ray-ban-display-plans-on-pause-2000706268</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706268</guid>
      <description>The company says it's a victim of its own success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PC version of 007 First Light requires lots of expensive RAM and VRAM to run at recommended settings</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/the-pc-version-of-007-first-light-requires-lots-of-expensive-ram-and-vram-to-run-at-recommended-settings-184339040.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78e0c831-df66-4f90-b8e6-2693b54c1625</guid>
      <description>IO Interactive just revealed minimum and recommended specs for the PC build of 007 First Light. The company recommends 32GB of RAM and 12GB of VRAM. In a normal world, this wouldn't be news, as modern NVIDIA GPUs certainly have more than enough VRAM. However, we live in a world where AI companies gobble up lots of memory.
This has caused newer cards to tick up in price, with more hikes to come. Older cards like the RTX 3070 just won't cut it, as that one ships with 8GB of VRAM. Standard RAM is also getting much more expensive, putting that 32GB out of reach for many gamers. In other words, pla...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 4 coolest new products Acer announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-4-coolest-acer-announcements</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01uwZ0NGWhWLV6J48p19Ca2</guid>
      <description>Acer had a ton to show off at CES 2026, so we whittled it down to the best of the best for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNY is releasing slim-sized NVIDIA RTX GPUs just as PC building becomes prohibitively expensive</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/pny-is-releasing-slim-sized-nvidia-rtx-gpus-just-as-pc-building-becomes-prohibitively-expensive-183127305.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3773e2ff-7080-4509-b628-5b441c3d446f</guid>
      <description>If I were building a new PC today, I'd go for a small form factor mATX or ITX build. With companies like Fractal Design and Lian Li making cases that can fit modern GPUs without sacrificing on thermals, you don't need to settle for the old mid-tower monstrosities of yesteryear. And that's why PNY's new "Slim&#8221; model RTX 50-series designs caught my eye. All three variants, covering the 5070, 5070 Ti and 5080, are two slot cards with just a pair of 120mm fans for cooling. As a result, even the largest of the three new models, the 5080, is relatively svelte, coming in at 11.8-inches or 300mm long....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This robot pool cleaner lifts itself out of the water to charge</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854835/mammotion-spino-s1-pro-robot-pool-cleaner-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854835</guid>
      <description>Mammotion, the company best known for its line of robot lawnmowers, is launching a robot pool cleaner that can take itself out of the water. As shown during CES 2026, the Spino S1 Pro comes with a robotic arm mounted to a docking station that sits at the edge of your pool. When the bot [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
