<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:29:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Alliwava GH8 and rolling out the newer Ryzen technology delivers a truly useful mini PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/alliwava-gh8-mini-pc-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2MeWqid23KeP6qmraxfFoE</guid>
      <description>The Alliwava GH8 offers excellent performance and functionality at an affordable price</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Nobody can avoid AI - but it will not replace humans" - Lenovo CEO explains why your next work PC could be an AI-enabled device</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/nobody-can-avoid-ai-but-it-will-not-replace-humans-lenovo-ceo-explains-why-your-next-work-pc-could-be-an-ai-enabled-device</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cZDU6nP6hgs9QpaLwRcj8X</guid>
      <description>Exclusive - Lenovo CEO predicts more and more work PCs will be AI-boosted by the end of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've never tested a gaming laptop that offers so much for so little &#8212; but you&#8217;ll have to accept a few flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/medion-erazer-major-16-x1-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XrBRd9fx6QkXsLyUQUQAE</guid>
      <description>The Medion Erazer Major 16 X1 certainly has a promising spec &#8212; but does it deliver the goods?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget Podcast: Best of CES 2026 and a chat with Pebble's founder</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/engadget-podcast-best-of-ces-2026-and-a-chat-with-pebbles-founder-160000762.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87e5b9df-8707-4ec4-8287-4d38d2811610</guid>
      <description>That&#8217;s a wrap for CES 2026! In this episode, Devindra and Cherlynn chat about their favorite aspects of the show, as well as Engadget&#8217;s best of CES awards lineup. Also, Cherlynn chats with Pebble founder Eric Migicovsky about his Pebble smartwatch revival, as well as an intriguing new AI ring that&#8217;s built entirely around notetaking.Subscribe!iTunesSpotifyPocket CastsStitcherGoogle PodcastsTopicsTVs at CES 2026: all eyes on Micro RGB and LG&#8217;s super thin OLED &#8211; 1:48L'Or&#233;al debuts LED/Infrared face masks seem cool but needs some development &#8211; 5:46Engadget&#8217;s official Best of CES 2026: Lego&#8217;s Smart...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve never used a trackball, but Keychron&#8217;s Nape Pro looks like the perfect one</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/860178/ive-never-used-a-trackball-but-keychrons-nape-pro-looks-like-the-perfect-one</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T10:50:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860178</guid>
      <description>Keychron announced new mechanical keyboards with marathon battery life at CES, but this trackball stole the spotlight. The Nape Pro is Keychron's first trackball, and its slender frame means it can work on your desk in multiple ways. You can keep it to the right or left of a keyboard like a traditional trackball, or [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The robots we saw at CES 2026: The lovable, the creepy and the utterly confusing</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/the-robots-we-saw-at-ces-2026-the-lovable-the-creepy-and-the-utterly-confusing-153537930.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fc996a1-0ba1-4172-b0f2-2fd786941388</guid>
      <description>CES always has its share of attention-grabbing robots. But this year in particular seemed to be a landmark year for robotics. The advancement in AI technology has not only given robots better &#8220;brains,&#8221; it&#8217;s enabled new levels of autonomy and given rise to an ambitious, if sometimes questionable, vision for our robot-filled future.From sassy humanoids to AI-powered pets and chore-handling assistants, we sought out as many cute, strange and capable robots as we could find in Las Vegas. These are the ones that made the biggest impression. Agibot HumanoidsAgibot's X2 humanoid robot.Karissa Bell fo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Godzilla Minus Zero&#8217; Stomps Into Theaters This November</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/godzilla-minus-zero-stomps-into-theaters-this-november-2000708463</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708463</guid>
      <description>You won't just be carving turkey in November, you'll also be carving out time to see 'Godzilla Minus Zero' on the big screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are 15 TV deals for watching the Super Bowl that I recommend &#8212; $1,000 off 4K, QLED and OLED TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/here-are-15-tv-deals-for-watching-the-super-bowl-that-i-recommend-usd1-000-off-4k-qled-and-oled-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9JgLNA67qP43Hj9Efb63W8</guid>
      <description>If you're looking for a new TV for the Super Bowl, I've listed my top 15 recommendations, which include deals on best-rated 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu cette bo&#238;te de rangement qui charge votre Nintendo Switch 2  et j&#8217;aime beaucoup</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/belkin/2936081_jai-vu-cette-boite-de-rangement-qui-charge-votre-nintendo-switch-2-et-jaime-beaucoup</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/belkin/2936081_jai-vu-cette-boite-de-rangement-qui-charge-votre-nintendo-switch-2-et-jaime-beaucoup</guid>
      <description>
J'ai pu essayer bri&#232;vement la tr&#232;s pratique housse de rangement de Belkin, capable de recharger votre Nintendo Switch 2 par l'int&#233;gration d'une batterie de 10 000 mAh.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I replaced Windows with Linux and everything&#8217;s going great</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858910/linux-diary-gaming-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858910</guid>
      <description>Greetings from the year of Linux on my desktop. In November, I got fed up and said screw it, I'm installing Linux. Since that article was published, I have dealt with one minor catastrophe after another. None of that has anything to do with Linux, mind you. It just meant I didn't install it on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We tried to get humanoid robots to do the laundry</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/featured-video/860104/we-tried-to-get-humanoid-robots-to-do-the-laundry</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860104</guid>
      <description>At CES this year, humanoid robots appeared to be closer than ever to moving into our homes. LG introduced CLOiD, a household robot it says can handle chores like preparing food and loading the washing machine. SwitchBot showed off the Onero H1, another home helper built to tackle everyday tasks, and Boston Dynamics, WIRobotics, Zeroth, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From &#8216;Vibe Coding&#8217; to &#8216;Vibe Selling&#8217;: how AI is reshaping the art of selling</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/from-vibe-coding-to-vibe-selling-how-ai-is-reshaping-the-art-of-selling</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V6CjpZCHN5JiibrEPxBxFb</guid>
      <description>'Vibe selling' is a crucial tool in sellers&#8217; kits, but isn&#8217;t ready to be put directly in front of buyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Sunday, January 11 (game #1448)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-11-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4MRMCWBSjf99ZWz8gZi8w9</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Sunday, January 11 (game #945)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-11-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hhugs7E8ydB2AXvRKwbz9o</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Sunday, January 11 (game #679)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-11-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UZFeQAmgLMVv4HVGgunsB4</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA makes final preparations for its first crewed moon mission in over 50 years</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-makes-final-preparations-for-its-first-crewed-moon-mission-in-over-50-years-150000825.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">840cd11a-ecb0-45c7-8989-1ccf53d63d86</guid>
      <description>Back in 2024, NASA announced that the Artemis 2 mission was going to be pushed back to April 2026. Now, the agency says it could launch as early as February, with the first flight opportunity being on February 6. NASA is currently making the final preparations for the mission and will soon roll out the Space Launch System (SLS) rocket and the Orion spacecraft to their launch pad at the Kennedy Space Center in Florida. The spacecraft system&#8217;s four-mile journey from the assembly building to Launch Pad 39B will take up to 12 hours. NASA is targeting a date no earlier than January 17, with the exa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tottenham vs Aston Villa Free Streams: How to watch FA Cup 2025/26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/tottenham-vs-aston-villa-fa-cup-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sKD6Yx7LuvSj9JvRpPUtk9</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Tottenham vs Aston Villa online from anywhere for FREE, as football's oldest cup competition returns with giant-killings guaranteed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I can't stop playing Assassins Creed Shadows on Nintendo Switch 2 now it no longer crashes all the time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/assassins-creed-shadows-nintendo-switch-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FsoH8QBcF4ev57HnJuqS9Q</guid>
      <description>After a rocky start, I&#8217;m pleasantly surprised by how well Assassins Creed Shadows runs on Switch 2</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
