<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:22:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>From Spidey to Snoopy, Hollywood&#8217;s Acquisition Mania Has Come for &#8216;Peanuts&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-peanuts-snoopy-charlie-brown-2000701919</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701919</guid>
      <description>Sony just purchased a controlling stake in the iconic brand featuring Snoopy, Charlie Brown, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotspots Capable of Driving Catastrophic Mega-Hurricanes Are Spreading Across the Oceans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hotspots-capable-of-driving-catastrophic-mega-hurricanes-are-spreading-across-the-oceans-2000702025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702025</guid>
      <description>This process, driven by climate change, is increasing the risk of &#8220;Category 6&#8221; tropical cyclones making landfall in densely populated areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split View Tabs in Chrome are a game-changer &#8212; I can&#8217;t believe I wasn&#8217;t using this before</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/chrome/split-view-tabs-in-chrome-are-a-game-changer-i-cant-believe-i-wasnt-using-this-before</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MufQGHztUZHN3n3jobXj3j</guid>
      <description>Chrome's new Split View Tabs feature, introduced in the November update, is a game-changer that allows users to view two browser tabs simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React2Shell exploitation continues to escalate, posing 'significant risk'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/react2shell-exploitation-continues-to-escalate-posing-significant-risk</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wjHawdoUaRvYKfJ5RbMs5L</guid>
      <description>Several hundred machines across a diverse set of organizations already compromised, Microsoft says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sues web scraper for sucking up search results &#8216;at an astonishing scale&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/848365/google-scraper-lawsuit-serpapi</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T15:48:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848365</guid>
      <description>Google has filed a lawsuit against SerpApi, a company that offers tools to scrape content on the web, including Google's search results. SerpApi is accused of violating the Copyright Act by using "deceptive means" to automatically access and take Google's search results "at an astonishing scale" before selling the data to customers. Reddit also sued [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok | L&#8217;accord am&#233;ricain n&#8217;aura aucune incidence sur le Canada</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-19/tiktok/l-accord-americain-n-aura-aucune-incidence-sur-le-canada.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:48:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa8cc2bbd51a31f69e560b9f9a5c65a2</guid>
      <description>Les utilisateurs canadiens de TikTok ne devraient pas remarquer de changements sur l&#8217;application &#224; la suite de la signature d&#8217;un accord entre d&#8217;importants investisseurs am&#233;ricains pour la cr&#233;ation d&#8217;une nouvelle coentreprise TikTok, selon un expert en cybers&#233;curit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix is acquiring game avatar maker Ready Player Me</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/netflix-is-acquiring-game-avatar-maker-ready-player-me-204443001.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7822683-862a-4270-b2d5-2957d63862c2</guid>
      <description>Netflix is acquiring Estonian startup Ready Player Me, a company creating "cross-game avatar tech" that allows players to bring their digital personas with them to different games, the company's CEO Timmu T&#245;ke shared in a LinkedIn post. The acquisition is part of Netflix's new games strategy, which puts an emphasis on approachable multiplayer titles and adaptations of the streaming service's IP.Ready Player Me's team of around 20 employees will be incorporated into Netflix's staff, TechCrunch writes, though T&#245;ke is the only one of the startup's four founders who will continue on after the acqu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous messaging app NGL was acquired by &#8216;EarnPhone&#8217; startup Mode Mobile</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/anonymous-messaging-app-ngl-was-acquired-by-earnphone-startup-mode-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077874</guid>
      <description>Given NGL's track record of dubious growth hacking, this partnership with Mode Mobile seems like a good match.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;My Hero Academia&#8217; Carried the Shonen Anime Torch to a Triumphant Finish</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/my-hero-academia-boku-no-anime-review-series-finale-crunchyroll-kohei-horikoshi-2000701820</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701820</guid>
      <description>'My Hero Academia' earned its flowers as a superhero epic that never lost its way&#8212;and it also elevated the genre to new heights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Cisco customers are vulnerable to new Chinese hacking campaign, researchers say</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/hundreds-of-cisco-customers-are-vulnerable-to-new-chinese-hacking-campaign-researchers-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077895</guid>
      <description>Cisco warned that Chinese government hackers are exploiting a zero-day in some of its products. Researchers now say there are hundreds of vulnerable Cisco customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesses are hiring AI specialists instead of data engineers - and its a big problem</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/businesses-are-hiring-ai-specialists-instead-of-data-engineers-and-its-a-big-problem</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Va6JuvvurdTxocNhDYA2q</guid>
      <description>Yet again, we're being graced with a report stressing the importance of a solid data foundation to get the most out of AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequoia&#8217;s Shaun Maguire accused an innocent Palestinian of being the Brown shooter. Then he doubled down.</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463942/sequoia-shaun-maguire-brown-university-shooter-palestine</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T20:05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463942/sequoia-shaun-maguire-brown-university-shooter-palestine</guid>
      <description>Online sleuthing is not, it turns out, among the noted VC&#8217;s talents. 
The discovery of the body of Claudio Manuel Neves Valente, a Portuguese national who studied physics at Brown University, earlier this week in a New Hampshire storage facility brought closure to two alarming cases. Authorities say they believe Valente, a 48-year-old who recently arrived in Boston, was behind the December 13 mass shooting at Brown University, and the December 16 murder of MIT professor Nuno Loureiro....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to keep entrepreneurial energy alive as you scale</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463697/how-to-keep-entrepreneurial-energy-alive-as-you-scale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463697/how-to-keep-entrepreneurial-energy-alive-as-you-scale</guid>
      <description>Scale your business while keeping the entrepreneurial spirit that sparked your success.
Most businesses start with a spark, an idea fueled by hunger, resilience, or grit. But sustaining that energy through scale is the real challenge. Founders and leaders play a defining role in that journey. The same values, authenticity, and style that ignite early momentum can easily crush it. That&#8217;s why builders and entrepreneurs are essential to a new business. &#160;Think Steve Jobs, Jeff Bezos, or Sara Blakely. But that style is NOT for everyone, especially those who prefer less &#8220;out-front&#8221; leaders. These fo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even LinkedIn has hopped on the Spotify Wrapped train</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463793/even-linkedin-has-hopped-on-the-spotify-wrapped-train</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463793/even-linkedin-has-hopped-on-the-spotify-wrapped-train</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Where my 5% crew at??!!&#8221; wrote one power user. Others were reminded of their fruitless job search and felt humiliated.
First there was Spotify Wrapped. Then came Snapchat Wrapped, YouTube Wrapped, and even Uber Eats Wrapped&#8212;shortly after, SNL parodied the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony owns a majority stake in the &#8216;Peanuts&#8217; after $457 million buyout for WildBrain</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463935/sony-peanuts-majority-stake-wildbrain</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463935/sony-peanuts-majority-stake-wildbrain</guid>
      <description>Sony acquired its first stake in Peanuts Holdings LLC in 2018 from Toronto-based WildBrain.
Happiness is taking control of a beloved comic strip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get up to 78 percent off ExpressVPN two-year plans for the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-up-to-78-percent-off-expressvpn-two-year-plans-for-the-holidays-194912043.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5a0f70e-8a7d-42de-8d3c-2a4f80959c2d</guid>
      <description>It looks like the holidays aren't a bad time to shop for a VPN subscription. ExpressVPN, Engadget's pick for the best premium provider, currently has a less premium price. This deal gives you two years of the Advanced plan (with a bonus of four free months) for only $101. When it isn't on sale, the same subscription would cost $392.
Engadget's VPN guru, Sam Chapman, praised ExpressVPN's service. He described it as "high-performing" and having "very few flaws." The service received high marks for its speeds, easy-to-use interface and global network availability. The only significant mark agains...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration calls on white men to report job discrimination</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463796/trump-administration-calls-on-white-men-to-report-job-discrimination</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463796/trump-administration-calls-on-white-men-to-report-job-discrimination</guid>
      <description>Though white workers make up most of the workforce, their share of race-based discrimination claims remains small&#8212;at least for now.
The Trump administration is calling on white men who believe they faced discrimination at work to file their complaints to a federal civil rights agency.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart to Pay $60 Million in Refunds for Allegedly Deceiving Customers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/instacart-to-pay-60-million-in-refunds-for-allegedly-deceiving-customers-2000701915</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701915</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Federal Trade Commission accused Instacart of misleading costumers with promises of free deliveries and full refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up for a year of Crunchyroll Mega Fan and stream your favorite anime for the lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/sign-up-for-a-year-of-crunchyroll-mega-fan-and-stream-your-favorite-anime-for-the-lowest-price-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UvZmpB42eA5FMmsNmsg59c</guid>
      <description>Save $20 / &#163;12 off an annual subscription before the new year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers in China Are Using AI-Generated Images to Get Refunds</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/scammers-in-china-are-using-ai-generated-images-to-get-refunds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69433673a5f88b1c3aabf50b</guid>
      <description>From dead crabs to shredded bed sheets, fraudsters are using fake photos and videos to get their money back from ecommerce sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco email security products actively targeted in zero-day campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/cisco-email-security-products-actively-targeted-in-zero-day-campaign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bNkD8ZL6J7fKP3EZXQEJCJ</guid>
      <description>Two Chinese-nexus groups have been exploiting a newly discovered flaw to establish persistence and launch backdoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't think RAM is expensive enough yet? DDR5 sticks with a triple-fan cooler on top will be shown off at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/dont-think-ram-is-expensive-enough-yet-ddr5-sticks-with-a-triple-fan-cooler-on-top-will-be-shown-off-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xZYKzxquZMnFYGX3wZ3kaa</guid>
      <description>DDR5 memory sticks with a triple-fan cooler on top are going to leave your wallet quaking in fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube creator&#8217;s finance livestream mysteriously appears on White House website</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463929/white-house-website-youtube-creator-finance-livestream</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463929/white-house-website-youtube-creator-finance-livestream</guid>
      <description>The livestream was from Matt Farley, who posts as @RealMattMoney.
The livestream of a YouTube content creator talking about investments mysteriously appeared to take over a White House website, raising questions about whether the site was hacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Starlink Satellite Is Tumbling Toward Earth After a Strange Anomaly in Orbit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-starlink-satellite-is-tumbling-toward-earth-after-a-strange-anomaly-in-orbit-2000701874</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701874</guid>
      <description>The satellite suffered a sudden drop in altitude, suggesting there may have been a small explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yann LeCun confirms his new &#8216;world model&#8217; startup, reportedly seeks $5B+ valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/yann-lecun-confirms-his-new-world-model-startup-reportedly-seeks-5b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077797</guid>
      <description>Renowned AI scientist Yann LeCun confirmed on Thursday the worst-kept secret in the tech world: that he had indeed launched a new startup. Although he did say he will not be running the new company as its CEO.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
