<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:46:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An ice dance duo skated to AI music at the Olympics</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/olympics-czech-ice-dancers-duo-ai-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091561</guid>
      <description>Czech ice dancers Katerina Mrazkova and Daniel Mrazek are learning the hard way that LLMs sometimes spit out straight-up plagiarism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s new &#8216;Buy American&#8217; requirement for EV charging would dramatically curtail build-out</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/876703/trump-ev-charging-buy-american-nevi-funds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T17:30:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876703</guid>
      <description>It seems clear at this point to say that Donald Trump does not want to spend a single dime on EV charging. He tried to freeze $5 billion in funding for the National Electric Vehicle Infrastructure (NEVI) program, which was approved as part of the Bipartisan Infrastructure Law. And when a federal judge ordered the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Philips turntable with a CD player squirrelled away in its plinth and honestly, for this money it's hard to argue with the versatility</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/i-tested-the-philips-turntable-with-a-cd-player-squirrelled-away-in-its-plinth-and-honestly-for-this-money-its-hard-to-argue-with-the-versatility</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yPLwiaxiAqaK9ECcgbLwaB</guid>
      <description>In which Philips piles on the functionality without charging an arm and a leg &#8211;but is the Fidelio FT1 a music center for the 21st century?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Workers Circulate Open Letter Urging CEO Marc Benioff to Denounce ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/letter-salesforce-employees-sent-after-marc-benioffs-ice-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698b9c4b3b8fbecbbb8fcffc</guid>
      <description>The letter comes after Benioff joked at a company event on Monday that ICE was monitoring international employees in attendance, sparking immediate backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI upgrades its Responses API to support agent skills and a complete terminal shell</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/openai-upgrades-its-responses-api-to-support-agent-skills-and-a-complete</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1FJWgwlHKZ1jaa9voxzQJZ</guid>
      <description>Until recently, the practice of building AI agents has been a bit like training a long-distance runner with a thirty-second memory. Yes, you could give your AI models tools and instructions, but after a few dozen interactions &#8212; several laps around the track, to extend our running analogy &#8212; it would inevitably lose context and start hallucinating. With OpenAI's latest updates to its Responses API &#8212; the application programming interface that allows developers on OpenAI's platform to access multiple agentic tools like web search and file search with a single call &#8212; the company is signaling that t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barely any Microsoft 365 users are actually paying for Copilot - despite Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella claiming it is 'a true daily habit.'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/barely-any-microsoft-365-users-are-actually-paying-for-copilot-despite-microsoft-ceo-satya-nadella-claiming-it-is-a-true-daily-habit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Y5TMx3fRMD9qsjsteAzGYa</guid>
      <description>Microsoft claims rapid Copilot growth, yet only 3.3% of Microsoft 365 users pay, which raises questions over long-term AI investment returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checking in on Polymarket: Bets on Christ&#8217;s Return Jump on Bets That Bets on Christ&#8217;s Return Will Jump</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/checking-in-on-polymarket-bets-on-christs-return-jump-on-bets-that-bets-on-christs-return-will-jump-2000720298</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720298</guid>
      <description>Here's a prediction: this ends poorly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord will soon require age verification to access adult content</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/discord-will-soon-require-age-verification-to-access-adult-content-140000218.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16e72251-2944-4c39-8a63-dfa62eea200a</guid>
      <description>Discord is the latest company looking to bolster its child safety (again). Starting in March, all users will have a "teen-appropriate experience" by default. Unlocking adult content and age-gated spaces will require a (usually one-time) verification process. However, following blowback, the company appears to have pivoted. It now says its age prediction AI will verify the identities of &#8220;the majority of adult users&#8221; without requiring a manual age check.The platform's big safety update encompasses communication settings, restricted access to age-gated spaces and content filtering. Users who aren...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Founder&#8217;s Drone Startup Wins German Military Contracts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spotify-favorite-drone-startup-wins-german-military-contracts-2000720249</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720249</guid>
      <description>A Peter Thiel-backed drone maker is also in the contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is Using the &#8216;Game of Thrones&#8217; Theme Better Than &#8216;House of the Dragon&#8217; Ever Did</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-game-of-thrones-theme-2-2000720200</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720200</guid>
      <description>Even with the poop joke. Especially with the poop joke, even.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-Track Speed Skating at Winter Olympics 2026 Free Streams: TV Channels, Schedule, Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/short-track-speed-skating-at-winter-olympics-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CCFeQ6bEbZPz2fFD3VDfVA</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Winter Olympics Short-Track Speed Skating 2026 live streams for FREE, with William Dandjinou and Arianna Fontana headlining the action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to get started with your spring clean? IKEA has the perfect sunny accessories to give you the motivation you need &#8211; from $2</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/struggling-to-get-started-with-your-spring-clean-ikea-has-the-perfect-sunny-accessories-to-give-you-the-motivation-you-need-from-usd2</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5tYsm89jWNgPiZzG4F5zZc</guid>
      <description>Kit yourself out with these colorful caddies, cloths and cleaners to get your home in ship shape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NLRB just gave up on SpaceX workers who claim they were illegally fired</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-nlrb-just-gave-up-on-spacex-workers-who-claim-they-were-illegally-fired-215332847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73857ef4-b7ce-4232-8a6e-c99d0551893a</guid>
      <description>The National Labor Review Board (NLRB) has dropped a case accusing SpaceX of illegally firing eight employees who criticized the company's CEO Elon Musk, The New York Times. The employees were originally fired in 2022 after circulating a letter that referenced reports of Musk's sexual misconduct and called the executive "a frequent source of distraction and embarrassment." The NLRB filed a complaint claiming the firing was illegal in 2024.Originally, SpaceX's opposition to the NLRB's case was that the agency is unconstitutional, The New York Times writes. Complaints about the NLRB's independen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit&#8217;s AI health coach is now available on your iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876692/fitbit-ai-health-coach-public-preview-ios</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:42:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876692</guid>
      <description>Google announced on Tuesday that the public preview of Fitbit's AI personal health coach is rolling out to iOS users in the U.S. as well as both iOS and Android users in the UK, Canada, Australia, New Zealand, and Singapore. The update tests a major overhaul of Fitbit's app, introducing a conversational interface with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arm's owner and Intel say their Z-Angle Memory, HBM-rival, will hit the market in 2029 - but I hope it won't be another Optane/3D-Xpoint, which caused Micron to lose millions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/arms-owner-and-intel-say-their-z-angle-memory-hbm-rival-will-hit-the-market-in-2029-but-i-hope-it-wont-be-another-optane-3d-xpoint-one-that-caused-micron-to-lose-millions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PG4xgo5RyucDhdAtTqRPdg</guid>
      <description>Z-Angle Memory could rival HBM, yet previous failures like Optane show hundreds of millions in potential financial losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My most anticipated upcoming phone isn't this year's iPhone, it's a Chinese flagship filled with one-of-a-kind features</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/xiaomi-phones/my-most-anticipated-upcoming-phone-isnt-this-years-iphone-its-a-chinese-flagship-filled-with-one-of-a-kind-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ctCMzLQuj48dHNiDCDMziR</guid>
      <description>I'm not looking forward to the next iPhone, but this Chinese flagship has really caught my eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Now Lets Users Remove Explicit Images and Other Personal Info From Search Results</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-now-lets-users-remove-explicit-images-and-other-personal-info-from-search-results-2000720317</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720317</guid>
      <description>The search giant announced new tools aimed at giving people more control over how their information appears online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Observational memory' cuts AI agent costs 10x and outscores RAG on long-context benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/observational-memory-cuts-ai-agent-costs-10x-and-outscores-rag-on-long</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6VCkpGbTP1RX96miGVFRMw</guid>
      <description>RAG isn't always fast enough or intelligent enough for modern agentic AI workflows. As teams move from short-lived chatbots to long-running, tool-heavy agents embedded in production systems, those limitations are becoming harder to work around.In response, teams are experimenting with alternative memory architectures &#8212; sometimes called contextual memory or agentic memory &#8212; that prioritize persistence and stability over dynamic retrieval.One of the more recent implementations of this approach is "observational memory," an open-source technology developed by Mastra, which was founded by the engi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics CEO&#160;Robert Playter&#160;steps&#160;down after 30 years at the company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/boston-dynamics-ceo-robert-playter-steps-down-after-30-years-at-the-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091693</guid>
      <description>Robert Playter announcd he is leaving Boston Dynamics after 30 years at the company in various roles, including six years as CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok&#8217;s trinket trading trend taps into the joy of being offline</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490547/tiktok-trinket-trading-trend-joy-being-offline</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T21:14:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490547/tiktok-trinket-trading-trend-joy-being-offline</guid>
      <description>The viral swap boxes echo a broader push toward analog hobbies and small moments of surprise beyond the screen.
On a sidewalk, an unassuming junction box sits strapped to a fence. Inside, dozens of keychains, stickers, mini figurines, and other novelties wait to be discovered by eagle-eyed passersby or trinket traders who have traveled across the city to exchange their treasure....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VC Masha Bucher, Epstein associate and Day One founder, explains herself</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/vc-masha-bucher-epstein-associate-and-day-one-founder-explains-herself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091632</guid>
      <description>After numerous news reports documented Masha Bucher's close business and personal relationship with convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein, Bucher took to X to explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Phone Looks as Bad as It Sounds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-trump-phone-looks-as-bad-as-it-sounds-2000720184</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720184</guid>
      <description>The first real glimpse of the Trump phone confirms what we already suspected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F1 2026 Bahrain pre-season testing live streams: how to watch online from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/formula-one/f1-2026-bahrain-pre-season-testing-live-streams</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">p2ofJGp7wJjzCEyk6stP9B</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch the F1 2026 Bahrain pre-season testing. Stream all the live action from the two three-day tests at the Bahrain International Circuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayaneo&#8217;s new Windows handheld will cost up to $4,299 with maxed out specs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876521/ayaneo-next-2-windows-handheld-ryzen-ai-max-395-indiegogo-preorder</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:49:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876521</guid>
      <description>Ayaneo opened preorders for its next Windows 11 handheld and it looks like a powerhouse. The Ayaneo Next 2 is 13.45 inches wide, 10.3-inches tall, and weighs 3.14 pounds. That's more than twice as heavy as the original Ayaneo Next that launched back in 2022, and it easily outweighs the Steam Deck and Switch 2. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
