<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:38:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal user beware - experts warn subscriptions being abused to send fake purchase emails</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/paypal-user-beware-experts-warn-subscriptions-being-abused-to-send-fake-purchase-emails</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GAZGohYdmoNrqpo9fNae5X</guid>
      <description>A legitimate PayPal platform is being abused to bypass email protections and send phishing messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Loses the Oscars to the Home of MrBeast and &#8216;Hot Ones&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oscars-streaming-youtube-2029-2000700856</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700856</guid>
      <description>YouTube will stream the Super Bowl of the movies starting in 2029.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars will stream on YouTube in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846560/youtube-the-oscars-streaming-2029</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:30:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846560</guid>
      <description>The Oscars are headed to YouTube - in a few years. "Beginning in 2029, the Oscars will broadcast exclusively on YouTube for free globally and on YouTube TV in the U.S.," YouTube announced. YouTube's coverage will include the red carpet, behind the scenes content, and Governors Ball access. The deal runs through 2033, according to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 22 best gift ideas for the remote worker in your life</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-22-best-gift-ideas-for-the-remote-worker-in-your-life-140037336.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7354ab-106c-4b9a-ab03-3baa917ca395</guid>
      <description>For many folks, working from home is simply the new normal. If you&#8217;re looking to treat someone who spends most of their time in the home office, this holiday season is as good a time as any to make their daily routine a little more convenient. As a collection of remote workers ourselves, we at Engadget have rounded up a few gift ideas that should add a bit more delight to the WFH life.
Best gifts for remote workers












































Check out the rest of our gift ideas here. This article originally appeared on Engadget at https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars will exclusively air on YouTube starting in 2029</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/the-oscars-will-exclusively-air-on-youtube-starting-in-2029-181545531.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aadd9da4-bf4f-4282-81c6-149564519e84</guid>
      <description>The entertainment industry&#8217;s most well-known awards show is heading to streaming. The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences (AMPAS) has announced that the Academy Awards, popularly known as the Oscars, will exclusively air on YouTube starting in 2029. The new deal means the awards show is abandoning its long-time partnership with ABC (owned by frequent Oscars heavyweight, The Walt Disney Company), though the Oscars will continue to air on the network through its 100th anniversary in 2028.The Academy Awards will be joined by other Academy events and programming on the Oscars YouTube chann...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is testing a link posting limit for professional accounts and pages</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/facebook-is-testing-a-link-posting-limit-for-professional-accounts-and-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076954</guid>
      <description>Meta said that the test impacts professional accounts and pages on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Bets on Small Drones to Expand US Surveillance Reach</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/border-patrol-bets-on-small-drones-to-expand-us-surveillance-reach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6941a9ca898599d8134eb0d0</guid>
      <description>Federal records show CBP is moving from testing small drones to making them standard surveillance tools, expanding a network that can follow activity in real time and extend well beyond the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon appoints longtime AWS exec Peter DeSantis to lead new AI org</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/amazon-appoints-longtime-aws-exec-peter-desantis-to-lead-new-ai-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076946</guid>
      <description>DeSantis has spent 27 years at Amazon, including eight years as an SVP for AWS, the cloud provider that powers about one-third of the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 best last-minute Christmas gifts for 2025 that will arrive by December 24</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-12-best-last-minute-christmas-gifts-for-2025-that-will-arrive-by-december-24-140037753.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f10f3474-8a9f-4844-b943-494ef9bdc916</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re almost out of time &#8212; the holidays are just about here, and if you&#8217;re still doing your holiday shopping, you&#8217;re not alone. Between wrapping things up at work before some well-deserved time off and making sure you have everything you need to host family and friends, it can be hard to find the time to go shop for some gifts. And if you&#8217;re going to physical stores right now, you&#8217;re probably being met with half-empty shelves. But the internet remains an option, even this late in the game: you still have time to buy holiday gifts online.USPS, UPS and FedEx have laid out their holiday shipping ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximus is more important than ever in Fallout season 2</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/846429/fallout-season-2-maximus-aaron-moten-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:02:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846429</guid>
      <description>As we tuck into Fallout season 2, eager to see Amazon bring New Vegas to life, there's one person who stands out - and not just because of his power armor. Knight Maximus of the Brotherhood of Steel is the most important of Fallout's three main characters, and I'm glad the new season is finally [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla would have to rein in FSD under new Democratic bill</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846387/level-2-operational-design-domain-markey-bill</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846387</guid>
      <description>Tesla and other automakers working on Level 2 and higher driving systems would be required to restrict their vehicles to specific road types or clearly defined operational domains under a new bill introduced today by Massachusetts Senator Ed Markey (D). Operational design domains, or ODDs, are a set of conditions, either geographic or weather-related, in [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Newcastle vs Fulham for *FREE* &#8212; Stream Carabao Cup Quarter-Final 25/26</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/newcastle-vs-fulham-carabao-cup-quarter-final-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iSdXBDHrWR8RhUsajqMoHE</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on how to watch Newcastle vs Fulham for free in the Carabao Cup 2025/26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IO Interactive's 007 First Light reimagines James Bond as a young and reckless spy</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/io-interactives-007-first-light-reimagines-james-bond-as-a-young-and-reckless-spy-180000758.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57fdd544-194b-467d-8745-ffaad8cc4055</guid>
      <description>The creators of the Hitman series have honed their style of- open-ended and spectacle-driven sandboxes across several games, and now they're taking their signature immersive gameplay to the world of James Bond. With 007 First Light, developer IO Interactive is crafting an origin story for the globetrotting British spy, showing how he undertook daring missions at the start of his career to eventually become the world's most infamous agent.Before the reveal at The Game Awards of 007 First Light's newest villain, played by Lenny Kravitz, we had an early look at the latest bits of plot for James B...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette manette transforme votre smartphone en GameBoy</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/manette-de-jeu/2914269_cette-manette-transforme-votre-smartphone-en-gameboy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/manette-de-jeu/2914269_cette-manette-transforme-votre-smartphone-en-gameboy</guid>
      <description>
GameSir s&#8217;appr&#234;te &#224; lancer la Pocket 1, une manette au format vertical in&#233;dit qui promet de m&#233;tamorphoser votre smartphone en console r&#233;tro, le tout &#224; un prix particuli&#232;rement agressif.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argos launches a final pre-Christmas sale &#8212; save up to 50% on tech, appliances, toys, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/argos-launches-a-final-pre-christmas-sale-save-up-to-50-percent-on-tech-appliances-toys-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95bvFLpiznVjQ3qrqYEFNF</guid>
      <description>Argos has launched one last sale before Christmas, featuring savings of up to 50% across tech, appliances, furniture, toys, and more &#8211; I've rounded up the 11 best deals right here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires want data centers everywhere, including space</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/845453/space-data-centers-astronomers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:48:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845453</guid>
      <description>Tech billionaires have been obsessed with space for a long time. Now, as the largest AI companies race to build more data centers in a frenzied pursuit of profitability, space is looking less like a pet project and more like a commercial opportunity. In 2025 alone, six proposals for giant AI data centers needing multiple [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Gerard Butler vs. the Post-Apocalypse in the Fiery New &#8216;Greenland 2: Migration&#8217; Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/its-gerard-butler-vs-the-post-apocalypse-in-the-fiery-new-greenland-2-migration-trailer-2000700813</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700813</guid>
      <description>He and his family survived the comet&#8212;but what comes next? Find out in the sequel hitting theaters in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The age of satellite TV is ending &#8212; Sky Q is finished, and Sky Stream is the future</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-age-of-satellite-tv-is-ending-sky-q-is-finished-and-sky-stream-is-the-future</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SSF6gM2v8v7gG4nuP3WbSR</guid>
      <description>Hey satellite man, your time has come: Sky Q is now 'unplugged' from new orders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN is debuting a new data-filled Monday Night Football stream next week</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846478/espn-monday-night-football-playbook-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:35:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846478</guid>
      <description>A new Monday Night Football broadcast will offer an alternate telecast that presents the game live from the All-22 camera angle that shows the entire field, coupled with on-screen analytics and commentary. It's called MNF Playbook with Next Gen Stats, and it premieres next week. To develop the show, ESPN partnered with sports data analytics [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Votre smartphone devient une cl&#233; avec cette serrure connect&#233;e &#224; moiti&#233; prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913669_votre-smartphone-devient-une-cle-avec-cette-serrure-connectee-a-moitie-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913669_votre-smartphone-devient-une-cle-avec-cette-serrure-connectee-a-moitie-prix</guid>
      <description>
Si vous avez l'habitude d'oublier ou d'&#233;garer vos cl&#233;s, voici une serrure connect&#233;e qui devrait r&#233;soudre ce probl&#232;me puisqu'elle transforme votre smartphone en cl&#233;. D&#233;couvrez-la chez PC Componentes pour 64,99 euros au lieu de 139 euros habituellement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VID&#201;O &#8211; Voici les meilleurs produits tech de l&#8217;ann&#233;e : Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/video-podcast/2911809_video-voici-les-meilleurs-produits-tech-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/video-podcast/2911809_video-voici-les-meilleurs-produits-tech-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
D&#233;couvrez notre vid&#233;o &#233;v&#233;nement sp&#233;cialement d&#233;di&#233;e aux Frandroid Awards 2025 avec Delos. Un v&#233;ritable court-m&#233;trage pour vous informer et vous faire rire.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is exploiting US-funded research on nuclear technology</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461998/china-exploiting-us-funded-research-nuclear-tech-congressional-report</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T17:30:45</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461998/china-exploiting-us-funded-research-nuclear-tech-congressional-report</guid>
      <description>Investigators found that federal funds went to research collaborations with Chinese state-owned laboratories and universities that work directly for China&#8217;s military.
China is exploiting partnerships with U.S. researchers funded by the Department of Energy to provide the Chinese military with access to sensitive nuclear technology and other innovations with economic and national security applications, according to a congressional report published Wednesday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rad Power Bikes files for bankruptcy and is looking to sell the business</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/17/rad-power-bikes-files-for-bankruptcy-and-is-looking-to-sell-the-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076928</guid>
      <description>It's the latest e-bike company to seek bankruptcy protection after pandemic-era excitement for the category wore off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban VPN Proxy is the latest free VPN spying on users &#8211; here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/urban-vpn-proxy-is-the-latest-free-vpn-spying-on-users-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HrSptpme5gMVzwaQZ6q2oC</guid>
      <description>The free Urban VPN Proxy Chrome extension has recently made headlines after being caught silently stealing users' AI chats. Yet, it's not an isolated incident but rather a stark reminder to use only reputable VPN apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out, Apple &#8211; the OnePlus Pad Go 2 just raised the bar for all mid-range tablets</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tablets/oneplus-pad-go-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de28bnZGvSEn6L27XcKiei</guid>
      <description>With a faster chipset, larger battery, and more expansive software features, the OnePlus Pad Go 2 is the new mid-range tablet to beat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google d&#233;ploie Gemini 3 Flash : le nouveau mod&#232;le par d&#233;faut qui surpasse GPT-5.2 sur certains points</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/google-gemini/2913729_gemini-3-0-flash-arrive-trois-nouveaux-modes-de-reflexion</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/google-gemini/2913729_gemini-3-0-flash-arrive-trois-nouveaux-modes-de-reflexion</guid>
      <description>
Google vient de presser le bouton "d&#233;ploiement" pour Gemini 3.0 Flash sur nos smartphones. Une mise &#224; jour qui semble anodine, mais qui cache une refonte totale de la mani&#232;re dont votre IA r&#233;fl&#233;chit avant de vous r&#233;pondre.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS systems targeted by crypto mining scam using hijacked IAM credentials</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/aws-systems-targeted-by-crypto-mining-scam-using-hijacked-iam-credentials</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aYZeTQbbbYvjz93E5Y2PqH</guid>
      <description>The attacks were stopped, but they could always return - if users don't strengthen their passwords.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waze could soon fix its biggest weakness to tempt you from Google Maps</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/waze-could-soon-fix-its-biggest-weakness-to-tempt-you-from-google-maps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kBJswdEV3CtTmG5fnxaLtA</guid>
      <description>Waze is reportedly testing traffic light indication during navigation, with the feature due to be rolled out in the coming months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of our favorite budgeting apps has 50 percent off annual subscriptions right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/one-of-our-favorite-budgeting-apps-has-50-percent-off-annual-subscriptions-right-now-154056535.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9cd69a7-2172-4476-a391-04d87e530174</guid>
      <description>With a new year just around the corner, now is the perfect time to take stock of your finances. A budgeting app can help with that, and right now you can get 50 percent off your first year of a Monarch Money plan. All you need to do is enter the code MONARCHVIP at checkout and you&#8217;ll pay $50 for the initial 12 months instead of the regular price of $100. Note that the offer only applies to new users.


Monarch Money was the runner-up in our guide to the best budgeting apps in 2025, and it was definitely a grower. Initially we found the experience of using the app to be needlessly complicated c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz discontinues feature that syncs music to driving</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846367/mercedes-benz-discontinues-feature-that-syncs-music-to-driving</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:04:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846367</guid>
      <description>Mercedes-Benz sent out a notice to customers recently announcing its plans to discontinue MBUX Sound Drive, an interactive audio feature that syncs music to the car's actions. The feature was first announced less than a year ago at CES in partnership with Black Eyed Peas frontman Will.i.am. Notices went out recently to customers that MBUX [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Chine tient-elle son Nvidia ? Qui est MetaX qui affole les march&#233;s financiers avec ses GPU</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/cartes-graphiques/2914179_la-chine-tient-elle-son-nvidia-qui-est-metax-qui-affole-les-marches-financiers-avec-ses-gpu</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/cartes-graphiques/2914179_la-chine-tient-elle-son-nvidia-qui-est-metax-qui-affole-les-marches-financiers-avec-ses-gpu</guid>
      <description>
C'est la troisi&#232;me plus grosse introduction en bourse de l'ann&#233;e sur le Star Market. MetaX, une jeune pousse fond&#233;e par des anciens d'AMD, promet de rivaliser avec les puces IA de Nvidia. Le march&#233; y croit dur comme fer : l'action est pass&#233;e de 104 &#224; 829 yuans en une journ&#233;e. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This iPhone case with a second screen lets you snap selfies with its rear cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/846408/dockcase-selfix-selfie-smartphone-iphone-17-pro-case-kickstarter</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:00:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846408</guid>
      <description>Smartphones with secondary screens on the back aren't a new idea. Most recently the Xiaomi 17 series launched in September with a smaller rear display and while the company suggests using it for widgets or gaming, the most practical use is as a way to frame selfies captured with the phone's superior rear cameras. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Discovery wants its shareholders to reject Paramount&#8217;s latest offer</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/846425/warner-bros-discovery-board-rejection-paramount-skydance-hostile-bid</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:00:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846425</guid>
      <description>Though Paramount Skydance was trying to buy Warner Bros. Discovery for much more money than Netflix is offering, David Zaslav and the rest of WBD's board are urging their shareholders to give Oracle scion David Ellison the cold shoulder. Today, WBD's board announced that it has unanimously decided that its shareholders would be much better [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 unmissable Apple deals that arrive before Christmas &#8211; AirPods, iPads, AirTags, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/here-are-10-apple-deals-that-are-on-sale-and-arrive-before-christmas</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uyoibt3tE8qjdBf2EgRzf4</guid>
      <description>I'm rounding up every single Apple device, including AirPods, iPads, MacBooks, and more, that are on sale and arrive before Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Wales trusts the process</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/846184/jimmy-wales-trusts-the-process</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846184</guid>
      <description>Wikipedia will be 25 years old in January. During that time, the encyclopedia has gone from a punchline about the unreliability of online information to the factual foundation of the web. The project's status as a trusted source of facts has made it a target of authoritarian governments and powerful individuals, who are attempting to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official Proton VPN app lands on even more Linux devices</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/official-proton-vpn-app-lands-on-even-more-linux-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Pok3Yqw6VeRpLSgekYd3rD</guid>
      <description>Linux users rejoice! Proton VPN has officially released its new command-line interface for Arch, Debian, Ubuntu, and Fedora. Here is what you need to know about the new tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikon ZR review: cinema cameras just got a major new player</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/video-cameras/nikon-zr-review-cinema-cameras-just-got-a-major-new-player</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7YKs7Cd6eRfRRM7RuxzwUG</guid>
      <description>The ZR is the first in a new line of cinema cameras by Nikon / RED, with stabilized 24MP full-frame sensor, 6K 60fps video, internal RAW recording, RED color profiles, mega 4-inch screen and 32-bit float audio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici la meilleure carte graphique de l&#8217;ann&#233;e &#8211; Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/cartes-graphiques/2906303_voici-quelle-est-la-meilleure-carte-graphique-de-2025-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/hardware/cartes-graphiques/2906303_voici-quelle-est-la-meilleure-carte-graphique-de-2025-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
Pour cet exercice 2025, la r&#233;daction a choisi de consacrer l'AMD Radeon RX 9060 XT comme la meilleure carte graphique de l'ann&#233;e. D&#233;couvrez pourquoi ce GPU a re&#231;u le Frandroid Awards de sa cat&#233;gorie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile's latest prepaid plan deal gets you a two-line unlimited plan for just $75/mo</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/network-providers/t-mobiles-latest-prepaid-plan-deal-gets-you-a-two-line-unlimited-plan-for-just-usd75-mo</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pj9dNx2y32RVDSVTBBFSS7</guid>
      <description>Looking for a cheap two-line unlimited plan? T-Mobile's latest deal gets you an unlimited data plan with perks for just $75/mo - much cheaper than the competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FrandroidOffreMoi un &#233;norme espace de stockage &#224; vie sur pCloud (2 To)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2914093_frandroidoffremoi-un-enorme-espace-de-stockage-a-vie-sur-pcloud-2-to</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2914093_frandroidoffremoi-un-enorme-espace-de-stockage-a-vie-sur-pcloud-2-to</guid>
      <description>
Le calendrier de l&#8217;Avent #FrandroidOffreMoi se poursuit avec encore un cadeau de taille sur cette 17e journ&#233;e. Aujourd'hui, c'est 2 To de stockage &#224; vie qui sont &#224; la cl&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Kushner&#8217;s Affinity Partners pulls out of Paramount&#8217;s bid for Warner Bros. Discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461992/jared-kushners-affinity-partners-pulls-out-paramounts-bid-warner-bros-discovery</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T16:50:04</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461992/jared-kushners-affinity-partners-pulls-out-paramounts-bid-warner-bros-discovery</guid>
      <description>Paramount&#8217;s latest SEC filings do not disclose the amount Affinity Partners was contributing to the bid.
A private equity firm owned by President Donald Trump&#8217;s son-in-law, Jared Kushner, is no longer backing Paramount&#8217;s hostile acquisition bid for Warner Bros. Discovery, the firm confirmed Tuesday.Days after Warner agreed to be bought by Netflix in early December, Paramount launched a rival bid that seeks to bypass Warner&#8217;s management and appeal directly to its shareholders with more money. Paramount is offering $30 per Warner share to Netflix&#8217;s $27.75.Warner, one of the &#8220;big five&#8221; Hollywood ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Xiaomi SU7 va d&#233;j&#224; changer : un &#171;&#160;refresh &#187; avec une augmentation de prix et quelques changements attendus</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2914007_la-xiaomi-su7-va-deja-changer-un-refresh-avec-une-augmentation-de-prix-et-quelques-changements-attendus</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2914007_la-xiaomi-su7-va-deja-changer-un-refresh-avec-une-augmentation-de-prix-et-quelques-changements-attendus</guid>
      <description>
Xiaomi pr&#233;parerait une nouvelle version de la SU7 pour le printemps 2026. Mauvaise nouvelle : le prix pourrait grimper.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des &#233;couteurs ouverts &#224; conduction a&#233;rienne pour les sportifs &#224; moins de 30 euros, cela existe bien</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/audio/ecouteurs-true-wireless/2914005_des-ecouteurs-ouverts-a-conduction-aerienne-pour-les-sportifs-a-moins-de-30-euros-cela-existe-bien</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/audio/ecouteurs-true-wireless/2914005_des-ecouteurs-ouverts-a-conduction-aerienne-pour-les-sportifs-a-moins-de-30-euros-cela-existe-bien</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s avoir commercialis&#233; ses premiers &#233;couteurs tour de cou &#224; conduction osseuse en octobre 2025, la marque fran&#231;aise Muse &#233;largit son catalogue d&#233;di&#233; aux sportifs et aux utilisateurs urbains avec le lancement du M-228 AC, son premier mod&#232;le exploitant la technologie de conduction a&#233;rienne. Il est propos&#233; &#224; moins de 30 euros seulement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s how much you racked up on Uber Eats in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462137/uber-eats-snl-spotify-wrapped</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T16:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462137/uber-eats-snl-spotify-wrapped</guid>
      <description>&#8220;If you rank in the top 1% of a restaurant&#8217;s customers, YOUBER will let you know, whether or not that realization fills you with pride or shame.&#8221;
Want to know how much you spent on Uber Eats this past year? If the answer is no, bad luck.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les nouveaux tarifs de Free sont l&#224; : il y a une bonne et une mauvaise nouvelle</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2913865_les-nouveaux-tarifs-de-free-sont-la-il-y-a-une-bonne-et-une-mauvaise-nouvelle</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2913865_les-nouveaux-tarifs-de-free-sont-la-il-y-a-une-bonne-et-une-mauvaise-nouvelle</guid>
      <description>
L'op&#233;rateur Free publie sa derni&#232;re brochure tarifaire avec entr&#233;e en vigueur le 17 d&#233;cembre 2025. Voyons ce qu'elle nous r&#233;serve.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The very giftable Dyson Airwrap i.d. is down to its best-ever price at Amazon &#8212; save over $100</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-17-dyson-airwrap-id-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03wuaqmsGOi15hkTF7rKy7d</guid>
      <description>The Dyson Airwrap i.d. is down to just $479 at Amazon in both the straight and curly models &#8212; its lowest price ever at 26% off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI Neo 2 : ce nouveau petit drone 4K baisse d&#233;j&#224; son prix dans ce pack avec radiocommande et batteries suppl&#233;mentaires</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913391_dji-neo-2-ce-nouveau-petit-drone-4k-baisse-deja-son-prix-dans-ce-pack-avec-radiocommande-et-batteries-supplementaires</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2913391_dji-neo-2-ce-nouveau-petit-drone-4k-baisse-deja-son-prix-dans-ce-pack-avec-radiocommande-et-batteries-supplementaires</guid>
      <description>
Le DJI Neo 2 est un petit drone pouvant &#234;tre pris en main sans aucune formation. Pour am&#233;liorer sa maniabilit&#233;, la marque propose une &#233;dition dot&#233;e d'une radiocommande qui passe de 399 euros &#224; 364 euros chez Joybuy.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 big rail unions oppose $85 billion Union Pacific-Norfolk Southern merger</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461990/rail-unions-oppose-union-pacific-norfolk-southern-merger</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T16:42:13</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461990/rail-unions-oppose-union-pacific-norfolk-southern-merger</guid>
      <description>The unions worry that safety could deteriorate after a merger and say there&#8217;s nothing to keep the companies from transferring jobs.
The&#160;proposed $85 billion merger&#160;of Union Pacific and Norfolk Southern railroads has lost the support of two unions that represent more than half their workers over concerns it will jeopardize safety and jobs, raise shipping rates and consumer prices, and cause significant disruptions....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit check company breached, 5.6 million customers info exposed</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/credit-check-company-breach-5-6-customers-expose</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03fmugJ5j06eNLqxeaRIk8z</guid>
      <description>Millions of customers had very sensitive financial information stolen in a breach of a credit check company.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
