<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:26:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Legacy of the &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Ending Debate Goes Back to &#8216;Mass Effect&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-conformity-gate-mass-effect-indoctrination-theory-2000708251</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708251</guid>
      <description>I remember when Conformity Gate was called the Indoctrination Theory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Watch Is Discounted on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-galaxy-watch8-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69613a804169e08c999c69d6</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Watch8 gets marked down across a variety of colors, sizes, and feature sets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's time for Apple to reinstate ICEBlock</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/its-time-for-apple-to-reinstate-iceblock-220802356.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db1c945f-64db-4519-9c58-c6c65586ef02</guid>
      <description>In October, Apple caved to pressure from the Trump administration and removed ICEBlock &#8212; and similar apps which crowdsourced the location of Immigrations and Customs Enforcement activity &#8212; from its App Store. Apple's stated rationale? The apps could "be used to harm law enforcement officers."  But armed-to-the-teeth ICE officers don&#8217;t need protection from civilians. Apple had that exactly backward.That became impossible to ignore on Wednesday, when ICE agent Jonathon Ross killed 37-year-old Renee Nicole Good in cold blood. By now, you don't need me to recount her brutal last moments. But the f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alamo Drafthouse Moves to Mobile Food Ordering in the Movie Theater</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alamo-drafthouse-moves-to-mobile-food-ordering-in-the-movie-theater-2000708311</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708311</guid>
      <description>The small screen meets the big screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solawave Wand Fans: Don't Miss This Buy One, Get One Free Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/solawave-wand-fans-this-buy-one-get-one-free-deal-is-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6961636dc0c7d7edb18e6e76</guid>
      <description>Double up on LED therapy, because sharing is caring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orchestral replaces LangChain&#8217;s complexity with reproducible, provider-agnostic LLM orchestration</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/orchestral-replaces-langchains-complexity-with-reproducible-provider</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75B1rgngQYodzdg5a5mFMq</guid>
      <description>A new framework from researchers Alexander and Jacob Roman rejects the complexity of current AI tools, offering a synchronous, type-safe alternative designed for reproducibility and cost-conscious science.In the rush to build autonomous AI agents, developers have largely been forced into a binary choice: surrender control to massive, complex ecosystems like LangChain, or lock themselves into single-vendor SDKs from providers like Anthropic or OpenAI. For software engineers, this is an annoyance. For scientists trying to use AI for reproducible research, it is a dealbreaker.Enter Orchestral AI,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes Bets Its Credibility on New Polymarket Partnership</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/golden-globes-bets-its-credibility-on-new-polymarket-partnership-2000708316</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708316</guid>
      <description>The awards show is teaming up with a controversial prediction marketplace that is facing growing scrutiny over insider trading concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is apparently planning a big box store in the Chicago suburbs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/amazon-is-apparently-planning-a-big-box-store-in-the-chicago-suburbs-213451978.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fa47371-d78c-4495-8719-c8823bf845ac</guid>
      <description>Amazon is making a return, of sorts, to physical retail via plans to build a big-box retail store in the Chicago suburbs, The Information reports. The 225,000-square foot retail space will open in Orland Park, Illinois, and give the company the opportunity to sell more than just groceries after it closed most of its physical bookstores and gift shops in 2022.The new store will offer in-store shopping, but also act as a fulfillment center for online orders, which could make it similar to competitors like Target and Walmart, and some of Amazon's existing Whole Foods and Amazon Fresh locations. "...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook and Sundar Pichai are cowards</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/859902/apple-google-run-by-cowards</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T16:24:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859902</guid>
      <description>Since X's users started using Grok to undress women and children using deepfake images, I have been waiting for what I assumed would be inevitable: X getting booted from Apple's and Google's app stores. The fact that it hasn't happened yet tells me something serious about Silicon Valley's leadership: Tim Cook and Sundar Pichai are [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You Love &#8216;Cloud Atlas,&#8217; You&#8217;ve Got to See This New Documentary</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cloud-atlas-4k-documentary-tom-hanks-halle-berry-2000707632</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707632</guid>
      <description>The new 4K release has an excellent, star-studded, two-hour look back at the film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer launches 40th Ryzen AI Max+ 395 system as it pitches Veriton RA100 mini PC as an AI workstation &#8212; but unless it is keenly priced, it will struggle against better value competitors</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/acer-launches-40th-ryzen-ai-max-395-system-as-it-pitches-veriton-ra100-mini-pc-as-an-ai-workstation-but-unless-it-is-keenly-priced-it-will-struggle-against-better-value-competitors</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9k4dfV2HRi6gp8CnSzRu8</guid>
      <description>Acer targets creators and developers building and running local models with its Veriton RA100 Ryzen AI Max+ 395 mini PC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've looked at every Samsung Galaxy S26 price and release date rumor so far &#8212; here's what I think will happen</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/ive-looked-at-every-samsung-galaxy-s26-price-and-release-date-rumor-so-far-heres-what-i-think-will-happen</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eHYJpEHUuqwxXibneTgzzj</guid>
      <description>I've predicted the announcement, pre-order, and on-sale dates for the Samsung Galaxy S26 series, along with the possible prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facture d&#8217;&#233;lectricit&#233; : une (petite) baisse automatique confirm&#233;e pour le 1er f&#233;vrier, voici ce que vous allez gagner</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/2936473_facture-delectricite-une-petite-baisse-automatique-confirmee-pour-le-1er-fevrier-voici-ce-que-vous-allez-gagner</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/2936473_facture-delectricite-une-petite-baisse-automatique-confirmee-pour-le-1er-fevrier-voici-ce-que-vous-allez-gagner</guid>
      <description>
Une baisse automatique sera bient&#244;t appliqu&#233;e sur les factures d&#8217;&#233;lectricit&#233; en France. Le gouvernement a en effet d&#233;cid&#233; de r&#233;duire l&#8217;une des taxes qui les alourdissent. Une bonne nouvelle pour commencer l&#8217;ann&#233;e, certes, mais dont l&#8217;impact restera limit&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a pris en main les batteries solaires et les piles rechargeables en USB-C de Marstek : un prix qui promet de d&#233;fier la concurrence</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2938175_on-a-pris-en-main-les-batteries-solaires-et-les-piles-rechargeables-en-usb-c-de-marstek-un-prix-qui-promet-de-defier-la-concurrence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2938175_on-a-pris-en-main-les-batteries-solaires-et-les-piles-rechargeables-en-usb-c-de-marstek-un-prix-qui-promet-de-defier-la-concurrence</guid>
      <description>
Le fabricant chinois de batteries, Marstek, d&#233;voile au CES 2026 trois produits, dont un tr&#232;s int&#233;ressant. Une batterie solaire compacte, puissante et plut&#244;t abordable. Nous &#233;tions sur place, voici notre premier avis.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecovacs wants to make self-clean window-bots happen, but I don't think they're going to happen</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/ecovacs-wants-to-make-self-clean-window-bots-happen-but-i-dont-think-theyre-going-to-happen</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TjMKpDYec25Gbe6uTkU9J6</guid>
      <description>I'm not sure my window bot really needs its own tiny washing machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Is Making a Big Bet on Nuclear With Oklo</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/meta-is-making-a-big-bet-on-nuclear-with-oklo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695fb7f6523ced0d2271f7d9</guid>
      <description>Meta will finance Oklo&#8217;s purchase of uranium for its reactors. It&#8217;s a massive vote of confidence for both the startup and nuclear power, but challenges remain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The older but still excellent Garmin Vivoactive 5 tumbles to a record-low price on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/the-older-but-still-excellent-garmin-vivoactive-5-tumbles-to-a-record-low-price-on-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ih94n5kpEjBwJPg23VMWJb</guid>
      <description>The Garmin Vivoactive 5 crashes to $184.99 at Amazon, making it an excellent buy if you're after a cheap running watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This semi-secret Lego Smart Brick feature gives it even more potential</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859740/this-semi-secret-lego-smart-brick-feature-gives-it-even-more-potential</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T15:50:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859740</guid>
      <description>We just gave the Lego Smart Brick our Best In Show award at CES 2026, and I wanted to stop by The Lego Group's suite to get a last glimpse before I left Las Vegas. To my surprise, the company showed off one more feature I didn't see during my first demo, perhaps the most [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monarch Money's budgeting app is 50 percent off for new users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/monarch-moneys-budgeting-app-is-50-percent-off-for-new-users-204507740.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764214b-3509-4628-8631-8692fa12e904</guid>
      <description>A new year is the perfect time to get your spending in order, and if you're not trying to build your own spreadsheet, budgeting apps are one of the best ways to do it. To save yourself some money in the process, you can pick up a year-long subscription to Monarch Money, one of Engadget's favorite budgeting apps, for just $50 if you use code NEWYEAR2026 at checkout and you're a new subscriber. That's a 50 percent discount on the service's normal $100 price.
Monarch Money makes for a capable and detailed budgeting companion. You can use the service via apps for iOS, Android, iPadOS or the web, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla baisse le prix de la Model 3 jusqu&#8217;au 31 mars 2026 : moins de 33 400 &#8364;, c&#8217;est du jamais vu</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2938177_tesla-baisse-le-prix-de-la-model-3-jusquau-31-mars-2026-moins-de-34-000-e-cest-du-jamais-vu</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2938177_tesla-baisse-le-prix-de-la-model-3-jusquau-31-mars-2026-moins-de-34-000-e-cest-du-jamais-vu</guid>
      <description>
La strat&#233;gie de Tesla est pr&#233;visible, mais elle fonctionne toujours. Pour gonfler ses chiffres du premier trimestre 2026, Elon Musk brade la Model 3. 3500 &#8364; de r&#233;duction imm&#233;diate. Une aubaine pour les acheteurs, un cauchemar pour ceux qui ont achet&#233; le mois dernier.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did you know that Gmail has emoji reactions?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/859865/gmail-emoji-reaction-workspace-rollout-default</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T15:42:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859865</guid>
      <description>Google rolled out emoji reactions to personal Gmail accounts a little over two years ago, and I completely forgot about it until now - probably because the option is hidden within a small, smiley face icon beside the Forward button. But now, Google is bringing emoji reactions to all Workspace users by default on February [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean hackers using malicious QR codes in spear phishing, FBI warns</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/north-korean-hackers-using-malicious-qr-codes-in-spear-phishing-fbi-warns</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QhztNSoUTTFWPEUPgbf5jY</guid>
      <description>Kimsuky's latest attacks can bypass email protections and MFA to steal M365 and VPN accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The era of 6K monitors has come: after Dell, Acer launches another 20-megapixel screen &#8212; 32-inch PE320QX has 7 ports and a webcam but no KVM</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-era-of-6k-monitors-has-come-after-dell-acer-launches-another-20-megapixel-screen-32-inch-pe320qx-has-7-ports-and-a-webcam-but-no-kvm</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KN8PGribBMqYZxBDphwmQR</guid>
      <description>Acer&#8217;s new ProDesigner PE320QX monitor packs real 6K resolution in a 32-inch display with a generous selection of ports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenes from the anti-ICE march in New York City</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/859550/anti-ice-protest-photos-new-york</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T15:30:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859550</guid>
      <description>On Thursday evening in Manhattan's Financial District, hundreds of protesters braved the cold to protest US Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), after an agent fatally shot a woman at close range on Wednesday. Earlier that day, Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kristi Noem's visit to One World Trade Center in Lower Manhattan sparked protests outside [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weight Loss Drugs Like Zepbound Could Help Treat Arthritis, Trial Shows</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/weight-loss-drugs-like-zepbound-could-help-treat-arthritis-trial-shows-2000708246</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708246</guid>
      <description>People who took both Zepbound and an anti-inflammatory drug saw a greater improvement of their psoriatic arthritis symptoms.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
