<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:29:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s Even More Rumors About Sebastian Stan&#8217;s &#8216;The Batman, Part II&#8217; Role</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/batman-part-ii-sebastian-stan-two-face-dc-2000707847</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707847</guid>
      <description>Plus, Sam Raimi's return to horror teases some genre-bending elements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vergecast Live at CES 2026: What is the point of a robot that falls over?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/859370/ces-2026-best-tech-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T09:23:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859370</guid>
      <description>This year's CES was an odd one. This is a conference usually dominated by futuristic, expensive TVs and futuristic, expensive cars, but those things weren't what dominated CES 2026. Instead, Las Vegas was filled with new ideas about old gadgets, and showed us a whole lot of really impressive hardware waiting on software to catch [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU goes soft on Big Tech in digital rules overhaul</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/eu-goes-soft-on-big-tech-in-digital-rules-overhaul</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LfjMgNGur85rnTaBN83Arh</guid>
      <description>EU Digital Networks Act will require telecoms firms to modernize their networks, but Big Tech is mostly immune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger lance une grande braderie lors des soldes : les 20 deals qui m&#233;ritent votre argent ce week-end</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-lance-une-grande-braderie-lors-des-soldes-les-20-deals-qui-meritent-votre-argent-ce-week-end</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-lance-une-grande-braderie-lors-des-soldes-les-20-deals-qui-meritent-votre-argent-ce-week-end</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver viennent tout juste de d&#233;buter et Boulanger n&#8217;a pas perdu de temps pour lancer de belles promotions. L&#8217;enseigne met en avant ses meilleures offres Tech pour le week-end. De quoi bien commencer l&#8217;ann&#233;e 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La g&#233;n&#233;ration d&#8217;images de Grok maintenant payante&#160;: un cache-mis&#232;re qui n&#8217;emp&#234;che pas les d&#233;rives</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/la-generation-dimages-de-grok-maintenant-payante-un-cache-misere-qui-nempeche-pas-les-derives.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319143</guid>
      <description>Suite, et certainement pas fin, du feuilleton Grok. xAI, la start-up IA d'Elon Musk, limite d&#233;sormais la g&#233;n&#233;ration d'images aux utilisateurs payants de X (anciennement Twitter). Une contrainte qui ne va pas faire grand chose pour r&#233;duire le volume d'images sexualis&#233;es de femmes et d'enfants sur le r&#233;seau social.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirTag deal: Get four of the Bluetooth trackers for only $65</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airtag-deal-get-four-of-the-bluetooth-trackers-for-only-65-202333516.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Apple keeps most of its product pricing on a tight leash, but we do see the company's AirTags go on sale pretty frequently. Another cost cut has come around for this item just in time for the holidays. Amazon is currently selling a four-pack of AirTags for $65. At a third off the regular cost, that price is pretty close to the record low discount of $63 we've seen for these Bluetooth trackers.


AirTags can be useful for people who travel frequently, helping you to keep track of essentials like your passport as well as a way to keep tabs on luggage while you're on the go. If you do purchase so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kia&#8217;s EV2 is its smallest and most affordable EV for Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/858912/kia-ev2-announce-specs-range-europe</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T09:07:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858912</guid>
      <description>Kia unveiled the EV2, a small and affordably priced electric vehicle built for the European market. The EV2 made its debut at the Brussels Auto Show, where executives touted it as its "most compact" EV to date. Of course, it was another in a long line of affordable, capable, and impressively designed EVs that won't [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : la 4K est &#224; petit prix dans cette s&#233;lection des meilleures offres sur les TV et les vid&#233;oprojecteurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933417_soldes-dhiver-2026-la-4k-est-a-petit-prix-dans-cette-selection-des-meilleures-offres-sur-les-tv-et-les-videoprojecteurs</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933417_soldes-dhiver-2026-la-4k-est-a-petit-prix-dans-cette-selection-des-meilleures-offres-sur-les-tv-et-les-videoprojecteurs</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver font moins de bruit que le Black Friday, mais cela reste une occasion de d&#233;nicher de belles affaires. Sur les TV 4K et les vid&#233;oprojecteurs par exemple, pour remplacer son &#233;cran poussi&#233;reux par une dalle OLED flambant neuve ou un vid&#233;oprojecteur dernier cri.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Chair X-Tech review: My kids called this an office chair built for the boss - and with its cooling, heating, and massaging features, I agree</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/x-chair-x-tech-office-chair-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2eFL9hnKYNVAPrGVfsX79</guid>
      <description>The X-Chair X-Tech is a fantastic ergonomic option for those who desire massaging, cooling, and heating, plus the comfortable seat, great ergonomics, leg rest, and flexible armrests, all of which result in a fantastic bang for your buck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We might see a successor to the MSI Claw 8 AI+ soon, as Intel promises plenty of gaming handhelds with Panther Lake CPUs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cpu/we-might-see-a-successor-to-the-msi-claw-8-ai-soon-as-intel-promises-plenty-of-gaming-handhelds-with-panther-lake-cpus</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2hx36iDXzg6qnVC3ztbwvL</guid>
      <description>Intel isn't slowing down with its handheld ambitions, and it's promising a clutch of new portables for later in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The weirdest tech we've seen at CES 2026 so far</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-weirdest-tech-weve-seen-at-ces-2026-so-far-134056504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a400df8-3389-4aee-8595-d1a0f59b424f</guid>
      <description>CES is a launchpad for serious tech, but it&#8217;s also where companies proudly unveil devices that make you stop mid-scroll and whisper, &#8220;Wait, this is real?&#8221; We&#8217;ve been keeping a running list of the strangest, funniest and most unexpectedly compelling gadgets we&#8217;ve spotted in Las Vegas, from bathroom computers to robots that look like they escaped a Pixar pitch meeting. Also, be sure to check out our list of the best CES tech we saw this year at the show.Dreame Cyber X robot vacuumDreame Cyber XEngadgetRobot vacuums can be a little unsettling already, but Dreame&#8217;s Cyber X takes it up a level by s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the tech and gadgets announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/all-the-tech-and-gadgets-announced-at-ces-2026-130124023.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown off a wide ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spartacus: House of Ashur episode 7's fatal fallout is 'heavier than anyone expected' &#8212; and that's for good reason</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/spartacus-house-of-ashur-episode-7s-fatal-fallout-is-heavier-than-anyone-expected-and-thats-for-good-reason</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dSNSX5uXR3A4cuUJ7pyCHm</guid>
      <description>With Opiter dead, Korris is rightly on the war path. For the Brothers Ferox in Spartacus: House of Ashur episode 7, that's a near-death experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA is ending Crew-11 astronauts' mission a month early</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-is-ending-crew-11-astronauts-mission-a-month-early-140000750.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ad2404-ea52-4c0b-8d5c-462cb7597a55</guid>
      <description>NASA has decided to bring the Crew-11 astronauts home a month earlier than originally planned due to a &#8220;medical concern&#8221; with one of them. This is the first time in its history that the space agency is cutting a mission short due to a medical issue, but it didn&#8217;t identify the crew member or divulge the exact situation and its severity. The astronauts will be heading back to Earth in the coming days. NASA Administrator Jared Isaacman said the agency will be releasing more details about their flight back home within 48 hours. The agency previously postponed an International Space Station (ISS) s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolby Vision 2 is coming this year, here&#8217;s what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/dolby-vision-2-is-coming-this-year-heres-what-you-need-to-know-140000034.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6964b774-6238-4f0c-9dd2-c1b368d37b3d</guid>
      <description>Dolby may have announced Dolby Vision 2 a few months ago, but the company gave the new platform its first big reveal at CES 2026. I got the chance to see the improvements in person for the first time, thanks to a variety of demos and Q&amp;A sessions. Dolby Vision 2 will be available this year, but initially, it will be limited. As such, I&#8217;ve compiled the info on where the image engine will be available first, and what&#8217;s likely to come next in terms of where and how you can use it. But first, let&#8217;s quickly summarize what Dolby Vision 2 will even do for your TV.&#160;What is Dolby Vision 2?Dolby Vision ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy just launched a weekend sale &#8212;clearance prices from Apple, Samsung, HP, and Fitbit</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/best-buy-just-launched-a-weekend-sale-clearance-prices-from-apple-samsung-hp-and-fitbit</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BENftp4dXCYuKQdCdBy8pV</guid>
      <description>Best Buy just launched a huge weekend sale with clearance prices on best-selling TVs, headphones, and laptops, and Apple devices - here's everything I recommend buying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X restricts Grok&#8217;s image generation to paying subscribers only after drawing the world&#8217;s ire</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/09/x-restricts-groks-image-generation-to-paying-subscribers-only-after-drawing-the-worlds-ire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081409</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's AI company has restricted Grok's controversial AI image-generation feature to only paying subscribers on X, after the tool invited heated criticism from across the world for letting users generate sexualized images of women and children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une carte in&#233;dite de l&#8217;Univers vient d&#8217;&#234;tre r&#233;v&#233;l&#233;e par la NASA avec SPHEREx</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-carte-inedite-univers-vient-etre-revelee-nasa-spherex-129941/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:57:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-carte-inedite-univers-vient-etre-revelee-nasa-spherex-129941/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>SPHEREx, le t&#233;lescope spatial de la Nasa, vient de faire une premi&#232;re cartographie nouvelle du ciel en infrarouge.&#160;Son but, percer les secrets de l'inflation cosmique, de la formation des galaxies et de l'origine de l'eau dans le Syst&#232;me solaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antivol qui pue le cadavre et v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique sans batterie : qu&#8217;ont donn&#233; leur passage sur &#171; Qui veut &#234;tre mon associ&#233; &#187; ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2937089_antivol-qui-pue-le-cadavre-et-velo-electrique-sans-batterie-quont-donne-leur-passage-sur-qui-veut-etre-mon-associe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2937089_antivol-qui-pue-le-cadavre-et-velo-electrique-sans-batterie-quont-donne-leur-passage-sur-qui-veut-etre-mon-associe</guid>
      <description>
Novateurs, le v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique Pi-Pop qui se recharge en roulant et l&#8217;antivol v&#233;lo CactUs qui sent le cadavre n&#8217;ont pas convaincu le jury malgr&#233; leurs qualit&#233;s.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best tech announced at CES 2026 so far</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854159/ces-2026-best-tech-gadgets-smartphones-appliances-robots-tvs-ai-smart-home</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:53:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854159</guid>
      <description>The CES show floor officially closes its doors at the end of the day, but there's still a trickle of announcements and reveals coming out of Las Vegas. If you're struggling to stay on top of all the new tech, gadgets, concepts, and AI-powered devices as the final day of CES gets underway, we're still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's Kindle is $20 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/amazons-kindle-is-20-off-right-now-183302861.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9865d5d-82c0-47b4-858f-2d61df88bf8c</guid>
      <description>If you're one of the many who made a New Year's resolution to read more, an ereader can help by putting your whole library (and more) at your fingertips wherever you are. While not as expensive as an iPad or another flagship tablet, these e-paper devices can be more expensive than you think, but right now you can save on one of our favorites. Amazon's base Kindle is on sale for $90 &#8212; that's $20 less than usual and only $10 more than its record-low price.
This made our list of the best ereaders, and for good reason. It's an iconic device that gets the job done. It doesn't have much by way of mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 Day 3: The most interesting tech that's still on the show floor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-day-3-the-most-interesting-tech-thats-still-on-the-show-floor-134724231.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">609a8caa-f93b-40af-b9db-b9fd1ad0d03d</guid>
      <description>Even as CES 2026 wraps up soon, there&#8217;s no shortage of standout hardware hiding in plain sight. From genuinely quieter yard tools to ultra-light EVs and companion robots that want to remember your family, Day 3 was all about tech that felt a little more considered &#8212; and in some cases, refreshingly practical.If you can&#8217;t get enough of CES, be sure to check out our picks for best of CES 2026, which highlights the most impressive new tech we&#8217;ve seen in Las Vegas. We&#8217;ve also rounded up the CES gadgets you can buy right now if you&#8217;re itching to place an order, along with a look at the weirdest tech...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Eintracht Frankfurt vs. Borussia Dortmund online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/eintracht-frankfurt-borussia-dortmund-bundesliga-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04Yo4FqrMZogec3df4IKMBg</guid>
      <description>How to watch Bundesliga for free. Watch Eintracht Frankfurt vs. Borussia Dortmund in the Bundesliga for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Mali vs. Senegal online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/mali-senegal-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01zypeWnOXiQNmbcp9pm86R</guid>
      <description>How to watch AFCON for free. Live stream Mali vs. Senegal in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for a record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-apple-watch-series-11-is-on-sale-for-a-record-low-price-154609244.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9398dfc3-7cc2-4fa1-ba51-8f9fa52c78af</guid>
      <description>The Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for the lowest price we've ever seen. You can pick up the smartwatch for $299, which is 25 percent off its regular price, a discount of $100. Discounts tend to increase as we get closer to September, when the next generation of Apple Watch is typically announced.


The Series 11 is our best overall smartwatch pick, and we gave it a score of 90 out of 100 in our hands-on review. We were impressed with the battery life, which lasted longer than the 24 hours it's rated for in our testing. We also liked how lightweight and thin the watch is. The 9.7mm thick cas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : les iPhone d&#8217;Apple, Samsung Galaxy et Google Pixel sont &#224; prix cass&#233; dans cette liste des meilleurs bons plans</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-soldes-dhiver-2026-demarrent-aujourdhui-voici-les-meilleures-offres-sur-les-smartphones-apple-samsung-et-xiaomi</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-soldes-dhiver-2026-demarrent-aujourdhui-voici-les-meilleures-offres-sur-les-smartphones-apple-samsung-et-xiaomi</guid>
      <description>
Du 7 janvier au 3 f&#233;vrier, les soldes d'hiver promettent de faire de bonnes affaires dans la tech, particuli&#232;rement aupr&#232;s des e-commer&#231;ants fran&#231;ais. C'est par exemple l'occasion de mettre la main sur un smartphone que le P&#232;re No&#235;l aurait oubli&#233; de d&#233;poser au pied du sapin.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; la nouvelle version des Ray-Ban Meta et leur bracelet neuronal qui ne sont pas encore disponibles en France</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/on-a-teste-la-nouvelle-version-des-ray-ban-meta-et-leur-bracelet-neuronal-qui-ne-sont-pas-encore-disponibles-en-france.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318980</guid>
      <description>Au CES 2026 Meta et Ray Ban ont d&#233;voil&#233; la derni&#232;re mise &#224; jour des lunettes et de leur Neural Band, le bracelet connect&#233; qui les accompagne. Dot&#233;es de nouvelles fonctionnalit&#233;s, elles s&#8217;imposent comme le mod&#232;le le plus avanc&#233; du march&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the tech trends we saw at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859244/ces-2026-highlights-trends</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:27:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=859244</guid>
      <description>CES&#160;is a lot &#8212; a deluge of consumer tech surrounded by lots of bad carpeting.&#160;The Verge&#8217;s on-the-ground team of super nerds covered so many new products and technologies that it&#8217;s understandable if it was all a little overwhelming. That&#8217;s why we&#8217;ve gathered up a collection of trend reports from the show to help make sense [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macy&#8217;s store closures 2026: See the full list of doomed locations in 12 states as clearance sales begin</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471941/macys-stores-closing-in-2026-full-list-of-doomed-locations-states</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T13:25:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471941/macys-stores-closing-in-2026-full-list-of-doomed-locations-states</guid>
      <description>The department store chain continues to reduce its physical footprint as part of a &#8220;Bold New Chapter.&#8221; Shares have risen 48% over the last 12 months.
Fans of Macy&#8217;s Inc. will be disappointed to learn that the iconic department store has announced its next round of store closures. Fourteen Macy&#8217;s locations in 12 states will shutter as a result of this move. Here&#8217;s why and when the closures will take place....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernize your business communication for less with Quo&#8217;s all-in-one phone system</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/phone-communications/modernize-your-business-communication-for-less-with-quos-all-in-one-phone-system</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EVddNF6oS3tumvLqxVGhec</guid>
      <description>Try the platform&#8217;s bells and whistles risk-free and get an exclusive 20% discount on your first three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-blog-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03weFCUbfFvR5jPHEa0V0Ce</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cornichon, phare, m&#233;t&#233;orite&#160;: voici les futurs emojis d&#8217;iOS et d&#8217;Android</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/cornichon-phare-meteorite-voici-les-futurs-emojis-dios-et-dandroid.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319118</guid>
      <description>Nouvelle ann&#233;e, nouveaux &#233;mojis : le consortium Unicode a publi&#233; la liste des nouveaux emojis qui seront (probablement) int&#233;gr&#233;s dans de futures versions d'iOS, d'Android, dans les applications de messageries et ailleurs. Au menu : un cornichon, un phare, une m&#233;t&#233;orite ou encore un visage qui plisse les yeux.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"I have never seen such a thing in my life" &#8211; Iran completely shuts down the internet amid protests, Starlink also affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/i-have-never-seen-such-a-thing-in-my-life-iran-completely-shuts-down-the-internet-amid-protests-starlink-also-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xxt8hvS4hXgFNuSA9NsCNg</guid>
      <description>Iranians have been offline for over 12 hours, with broadband, mobile and Starlink services affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, Grok hasn&amp;#8217;t paywalled its deepfake image feature</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/859309/grok-undressing-limit-access-gaslighting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:09:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859309</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's X has partially restricted access to Grok's image editing capabilities amid growing backlash to the flood of nonconsensual, sexualized deepfakes of adults and minors generated by the platform. As of this writing, it no longer generates images as @grok replies for free, but Grok's image editing tools remain readily available for any X [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft simplifie &#224; l&#8217;extr&#234;me l&#8217;ajout d&#8217;un lien dans un document Word</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/microsoft-simplifie-a-lextreme-lajout-dun-lien-dans-un-document-word.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319113</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;entreprise de Redmond est en train de tester un nouveau syst&#232;me, beaucoup plus simple, pour ins&#233;rer un lien hypertexte dans un document Word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where is the Trump phone? Golden iPhone rival misses another release date &#8211; as experts suggest it may never arrive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/where-is-the-trump-phone-golden-iphone-rival-misses-another-release-date-as-experts-suggest-it-may-never-arrive</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">phqSUwbLnLF5RZwKFwecFW</guid>
      <description>The Trump Mobile T1 Phone still hasn&#8217;t shipped and its future appears to be uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu la nouvelle Peugeot 408 &#233;lectrique : elle a de la gueule, mais voici pourquoi &#231;a ne suffira pas</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2936113_on-a-vu-la-nouvelle-peugeot-408-electrique-elle-a-de-la-gueule-mais-voici-pourquoi-ca-ne-suffira-pas</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2936113_on-a-vu-la-nouvelle-peugeot-408-electrique-elle-a-de-la-gueule-mais-voici-pourquoi-ca-ne-suffira-pas</guid>
      <description>
C'est le probl&#232;me des voitures "coup de c&#339;ur" : on a tendance &#224; leur pardonner beaucoup. La nouvelle Peugeot 408, d&#233;voil&#233;e ce matin, mise tout sur son physique ravageur pour vous s&#233;duire. Le souci ? En 2026, face &#224; une Tesla Model 3 ou une Mercedes CLA, avoir de beaux yeux ne suffit plus. Surtout quand la technique fait du surplace.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idris Elba casually watches Arsenal game on iPad during Seth Meyers interview</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/idris-elba-arsenal-game-seth-meyers</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02XazkcPTHRW1vFFeEt3kIY</guid>
      <description>Idris Elba wanted to watch the Arsenal-Liverpool game during his "Late Night" interview with Seth Meyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should you upgrade to Gemini for Home? Tread carefully &#8211; some users are still reporting major bugs and problems</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/should-you-upgrade-to-gemini-for-home-tread-carefully-some-users-are-still-reporting-major-bugs-and-problems</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uLDTJMCtjUXATJ7hs7zCpU</guid>
      <description>Users who've made the jump to Gemini on their smart home are reporting several issues with functionality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify pulls its ICE recruitment ads</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/spotify-ice-ads-removed</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01g2o11rg5h3ynWwJzREhVI</guid>
      <description>Spotify says its ICE recruitment ads have been removed from the platform by the company, following backlash and boycotts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Tangled&#8217; Casts Its Villain, and It Was Agatha All Along</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tangled-casts-its-villain-and-it-was-agatha-all-along-2000707887</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707887</guid>
      <description>Marvel's own Kathryn Hahn is in talks to play Mother Gothel in the live-action 'Rapunzel' remake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kia's budget EV2 arrives with up to 240 miles of range</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/kias-budget-ev2-arrives-with-up-to-240-miles-of-range-130038144.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc213d6-9e25-48cd-a9b4-512be70476b3</guid>
      <description>Kia has unveiled its new entry level electric vehicle, the EV2. The boxy model strongly resembles the company's Soul (Kia did make an electric Soul at one point) and has very similar dimensions, though it's slightly shorter in height and length. It's not exactly a range monster and will charge a bit slower than the competition. The EV2 launched at the Brussels Motor Show and the company said it has no plans for US availability at this point.&#160;
The EV2 uses Kia/Hyundai's E-GMP platform and slots into the bottom of its EV lineup as an "entry point to electric mobility," according to the automaker...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality still matters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/859055/minneapolis-renee-good-ice-shooting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859055</guid>
      <description>The first video I saw of the Minneapolis shooting was bad enough. Shortly after I saw it, I had the terrible realization that there were multiple people in the clip holding their phones up - another angle was bound to surface. Within minutes, a second video was all over social media, and it was even [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The venture firm that ate Silicon Valley just raised another $15 billion</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/09/the-venture-firm-that-ate-silicon-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081401</guid>
      <description>In a blog post published Friday morning, Ben Horowitz writes that "as the American leader in Venture Capital, the fate of new technology in the United States rests partly on our shoulders." It's the kind of statement certain to cause agita at rival firms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego is trying to make tech invisible with Smart Play</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/lego-is-trying-to-make-tech-invisible-with-smart-play-130000979.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a9113c-bd2c-4f18-a977-5b967ad4c25e</guid>
      <description>Probably my favorite thing about the Lego Smart Play system unveiled this week at CES is that it was designed for kids, first and foremost. In the past 10 years or so, Lego has increasingly courted an older audience with more expensive and elaborate sets. But when it was time to bring more advanced technology to Lego, the idea right from the beginning was more social and interactive play.&#160;If you haven&#8217;t heard about Smart Play yet, its a way for Lego to make its sets more interactive. A Smart Brick filled with sensors makes it so sets can respond to each other, know when they&#8217;re moving, play so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify is no longer running ads for ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/spotify-is-no-longer-running-ads-for-ice-130000672.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a2fcac3-5bc8-430d-87b7-0bb821f33b35</guid>
      <description>There are no recruitment ads for Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) running on Spotify at the moment, the streaming service has told Variety. A spokesperson has confirmed the news after an ICE agent fatally shot Renee Good in Minneapolis, but they also clarified that the ads stopped running in late 2025. &#8220;The advertisements mentioned were part of a US government recruitment campaign that ran across all major media and platforms,&#8221; they explained. Spotify caught flak back in October for playing ICE ads, asking people to &#8220;join the mission to protect America,&#8221; in between songs for users on ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 hands-on: Xreals world-first 240 Hz AR smart glasses made my jaw drop</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-xreal-1s-asus-r1-ar-smart-glasses-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06PYs8wMBypvN34Ko0Tk21G</guid>
      <description>Xreal brought out the big guns for CES 2026. The brand debuted the world's first AR glasses with a 240 Hz refresh rate, plus a new 3D conversion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigabyte may have just solved my biggest issue with OLED monitors at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/monitors/gigabyte-may-have-just-solved-my-biggest-issue-with-oled-monitors-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4WzRtRBT5JA5wAhCtjxLS</guid>
      <description>OLED monitors need fine tuning with brightness dimming issues, and Gigabyte may just have cracked this at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take five! Soundpeats&#8217; new affordable audiophile earbuds up the H3's driver count by two</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/our-favorite-affordable-audio-brands-new-earbuds-have-more-drivers-than-a-horse-has-legs</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wpJiD824WqvzygpqhwapuU</guid>
      <description>Soundpeats' Aura Nebula features a five-driver design for a temptingly low price</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce SSD de Samsung avec une vitesse de lecture de 14,8 Go/s s&#8217;offre une baisse de 50 euros chez Amazon &#224; l&#8217;occasion des soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936687_ce-ssd-de-samsung-avec-une-vitesse-de-lecture-de-148-go-s-soffre-une-baisse-de-50-euros-chez-amazon-a-loccasion-des-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936687_ce-ssd-de-samsung-avec-une-vitesse-de-lecture-de-148-go-s-soffre-une-baisse-de-50-euros-chez-amazon-a-loccasion-des-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Chez Amazon, ce SSD 9100 Pro s'offre une baisse de 21 % et tombe &#224; 190,99 euros. L'occasion est donc parfaite pour se ruer sur un SSD capable de lire vos fichiers ou de lancer vos jeux favoris en un rien de temps.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brick-and-mortar bookshops look better than ever in the Amazon age</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468520/amazon-vs-local-bookstores</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T12:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468520/amazon-vs-local-bookstores</guid>
      <description>Digital books haven&#8217;t killed print ones. And even the smallest local stores can transcend Amazon&#8217;s increasingly chaotic shopping experience.
Welcome to the first Fast Company&#8217;s Plugged In of 2026, and Happy New Year to you.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
