<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 22:29:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Can the creator economy stay afloat in a flood of AI slop?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/22/can-the-creator-economy-stay-afloat-in-a-flood-of-ai-slop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 22:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095534</guid>
      <description>On the latest episode of Equity, we debated what&#8217;s next for the creator economy, and whether there will be any room for the next generation of creators to stand out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung is adding Perplexity to Galaxy AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/882921/samsung-is-adding-perplexity-to-galaxy-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T17:15:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882921</guid>
      <description>In addition to summoning Bixby or Gemini, Galaxy S26 users will be able to call on Perplexity by saying "hey, Plex." The integration of Perplexity into Galaxy AI is just one element of the company's embrace of a "multi-agent ecosystem." Often, people will use different AI agents for different tasks, depending on where their strengths [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman: Know What Else Used a Lot of Energy? Human Civilization</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altman-know-what-else-used-a-lot-of-energy-human-civilization-2000725167</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 21:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725167</guid>
      <description>The OpenAI CEO, very smart, brushed away concerns about AI's environmental impact with one hell of a take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You need to listen to Laurie Spiegel&#8217;s masterpiece of early ambient music</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/882915/laurie-spiegel-the-expanding-universe-review-masterpiece-ambient-music</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T16:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882915</guid>
      <description>I recently had the pleasure of interviewing Laurie Spiegel for the site. As preparation for the interview, I spent a lot of time over the last couple of weeks revisiting Spiegel's records, most notably The Expanding Universe, her 1980 masterpiece that blends synth experimentalism with early examples of what would eventually be called ambient music, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado is working on a bill that would make it illegal to 3D print firearms and gun parts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/colorado-is-working-on-a-bill-that-would-make-it-illegal-to-3d-print-firearms-and-gun-parts-211508169.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 21:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8866bdb5-4ba8-4f58-b56b-c6a59403289b</guid>
      <description>A collective of Colorado lawmakers wants to put an end to "ghost guns" and their rising popularity. Earlier this week, the state's House Judiciary Committee voted in a 7-4 majority to pass the bill, HB26-1144, along for a decision with the full House of Representatives. The proposed law would "prohibit the use of a three-dimensional printer, or similar technology, to make a firearm or a firearm component."
Ghost guns are typically made from 3D printers or similar machines without serial numbers, making them virtually impossible to trace and allowing users to skirt the federal requirements for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The Mummy Returns&#8217; To Theaters in March</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-mummy-returns-to-theaters-in-march-2000725066</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 21:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725066</guid>
      <description>Universal's pretty sure your love of 'The Mummy' movies is so strong, you're willing to see bad Dwayne Johnson CG again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gurley says that right now, the worst thing you can do for your career is play it safe</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/22/bill-gurley-says-that-right-now-the-worst-thing-you-can-do-for-your-career-is-play-it-safe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 21:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095524</guid>
      <description>"The number one thing is to get out of your head this ideal that gets passed around in the self-help world: 'go get a mentor,' and everyone runs out and cold calls someone that's ridiculously too high and unachievable, and it doesn't work."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't trust AI to come up with a strong new password for you &#8212; LLMs are pretty poor at creating new logins, experts warn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/dont-trust-ai-to-come-up-with-a-new-strong-password-for-you-llms-are-pretty-poor-at-creating-new-logins-experts-warn</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nc4Ba9tCZdQHhtLxVctRqD</guid>
      <description>AI-generated passwords appear complex yet follow predictable statistical patterns, significantly reducing entropy and increasing brute force vulnerability risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung is adding Perplexity to Galaxy AI for its upcoming S26 series</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/samsung-is-adding-perplexity-to-galaxy-ai-for-its-upcoming-s26-series-203729539.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 20:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb9206e-030f-4858-965b-c4c9ac1e8da8</guid>
      <description>Samsung's next flagship devices will offer Perplexity as part of an expansion to support multiple AI agents in Galaxy AI. Perplexity's AI agent will work with apps including Samsung Notes, Clock, Gallery, Reminder and Calendar, according to the announcement. And, some third-party apps will support it, though Samsung hasn't yet said which. The news comes just a few days before Samsung's Galaxy Unpacked event, so we can expect to find out more about that integration and how it fits in with Samsung's revamped Bixby very soon.&#160;What we know so far is that the Perplexity agent will respond to the wa...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
