<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:30:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>You can turn this modular clamp-on controller into an N64 or GameCube gamepad</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857428/hyperkin-gamesir-x5-alteron-clamp-bluetooth-wireless-controller</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T10:19:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857428</guid>
      <description>Hyperkin announced a new clamp-on style wireless controller created in collaboration with GameSir. The X5 Alteron features similar functionality to GameSir's GameSir G8 Plus that debuted in 2024 with an expanding telescopic mechanism that can clamp onto smartphones, tablets, and several versions of the Nintendo Switch, replacing the Joy-Cons. What sets the X5 Alteron apart [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify now lets you share what you&#8217;re streaming in real time with friends</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/spotify-now-lets-you-share-what-youre-streaming-in-real-time-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080645</guid>
      <description>You can tap a friend&#8217;s listening activity to play the track, save it, open the menu, or react with an emoji.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego Smart Play hands-on: Using Smart Brick technology to get kids to play together</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/lego-smart-play-hands-on-using-smart-brick-technology-to-get-kids-to-play-together-133000740.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27c066b4-5f4b-4b62-9099-8412c652c6c9</guid>
      <description>Lego&#8217;s Smart Play system announced at CES 2026 earlier this week is a new embrace of digital technology that we haven&#8217;t seen from the company before. While the demo Lego gave at its press conference on Monday was a good start to showing what Smart Bricks are capable of, it really isn&#8217;t a substitute for seeing it in person. I was able to get an extended demo that answered many of my questions about how the system will work once Lego fans of all ages get their hands on the first Smart Play sets.As I detailed yesterday, the Smart Play system contains three elements. The Smart Brick is packed with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This critical severity flaw in D-Link DSL gateway devices could allow for remote code execution</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-critical-severity-flaw-in-d-link-dsl-gateway-devices-could-allow-for-remote-code-execution</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ANDzegb6EoSQicW7pS5pM9</guid>
      <description>Users are advised to replace outdated gear to avoid being targeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Expedition X season 11 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/expedition-x-season-11-online</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K6xJotUohH3kbMvfuD8SS8</guid>
      <description>Josh and his team set out to uncover long-standing mysteries. Here&#8217;s how you can watch Expedition X season 11 online and from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown off a wide ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If the rumored OnePlus 16 Pro is anything like the Oppo Find X9 Pro, I'll be recommending it to every Android fan</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/oneplus-phones/if-the-rumored-oneplus-16-pro-is-anything-like-the-oppo-find-x9-pro-ill-be-recommending-it-to-every-android-fan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5RxgpdVbKzqA3y2Jfy7RDR</guid>
      <description>OnePlus hasn&#8217;t released a &#8216;Pro&#8217; version of its flagship handset for years &#8211; but new rumors have got me excited to see how the brand could improve on its recent five-star flagship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia DLSS 4.5 : la mise &#224; jour qui fait mal aux propri&#233;taires de RTX 3000 et 2000</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2933657_nvidia-dlss-4-5-la-mise-a-jour-qui-fait-mal-aux-proprietaires-de-rtx-3000-et-2000</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2933657_nvidia-dlss-4-5-la-mise-a-jour-qui-fait-mal-aux-proprietaires-de-rtx-3000-et-2000</guid>
      <description>
Nvidia promettait des images plus propres avec le DLSS 4.5, et sur ce point, la nouvelle version tient parole. Mais si vous jouez avec une RTX 2000 ou 3000, la facture c&#244;t&#233; performances risque de piquer un peu plus que pr&#233;vu.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can still save $100 on those excellent Fortnite PS5 bundles right now &#8212; but the deals might not be around for much longer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/you-can-still-save-usd100-on-those-excellent-fortnite-ps5-bundles-right-now-but-the-deals-might-not-be-around-for-much-longer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeyLnczjx3pcRb9wc4LQr3</guid>
      <description>The PS5 Cobalt Star Bundle is the perfect place to begin a PS5 or Fortnite journey, and you can currently save $100 on bundles with both at PlayStation Direct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the laptops that caught our eye at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/all-the-laptops-that-caught-our-eye-at-ces-2026-160610752.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9affd700-e6e7-44a9-a3d0-4169004caad8</guid>
      <description>CES remains a key stage for laptop makers to lay out their plans for the year ahead. At CES 2026, that meant new flagship productivity machines, reconsidered gaming notebooks and solid incremental updates across several major lineups. While we&#8217;re still seeing embargoes lift and hands-on time on the show floor, the announcements below reflect the most significant laptops we&#8217;ve seen so far. Plus, the list will grow as more companies reveal details throughout January 6 and beyond.Lenovo Legion Pro RollableLenovo Legion Pro RollableEngadgetLenovo came prepared for CES 2026 with a ton of laptops &#8212; ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le nouvel aspirateur robot de Roborock monte les escaliers avec ses deux pattes</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-nouvel-aspirateur-robot-de-roborock-monte-les-escaliers-avec-ses-deux-pattes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318630</guid>
      <description>Les robots domestiques font peut-&#234;tre fureur au CES, mais sans attendre ni d&#233;penser des sommes folles, les consommateurs qui le souhaitent peuvent d&#233;j&#224; en avoir un avant-go&#251;t : apr&#232;s tout, les aspirateurs robots sont en quelque sorte les pr&#233;curseurs de ces futurs majordomes &#224; tout faire ! Et Roborock s'emploie &#224; brouiller les fronti&#232;res avec son nouveau concept, le Saros Rover....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify is finally bringing your friends&#8217; Listening Activity to mobile</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/857404/spotify-listening-activity-mobile</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T10:02:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857404</guid>
      <description>Since almost day one, Spotify has offered the ability to creep on your friends' listening habits - but you could mostly only uncover those guilty pleasures on the desktop app. The company experimented with a community feature on the mobile app back in 2022, but it never officially launched. Now the company is finally bringing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These five-star Nothing Ear (a) budget are down to a record-low price on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/these-five-star-nothing-ear-a-budget-are-down-to-a-record-low-price-on-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4BYfdXrzAENAcpCrNBEDhF</guid>
      <description>The Nothing Ear (a) are great budget earphones which are both stylish and sound great. They're on sale now at Amazon. Here's why you should buy them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Ahead in Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-year-ahead-in-movies-2026-2000705746</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705746</guid>
      <description>In 2026, we might finally get some new mega franchises to go along with the usual ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xthings&#8217; New Ultraloq Smart Lock Doesn&#8217;t Care What Your Phone Brand Is</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xthings-new-ultraloq-smart-lock-doesnt-care-what-your-phone-brand-is-2000705751</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705751</guid>
      <description>It will use Aliro, a standard that&#8217;s like Matter but for smartphone digital keys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Thursday, January 8 (game #676)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-8-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XVrLXPVv7HXeNvS8BSjRg5</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Thursday, January 8 (game #1445)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-8-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ewDE6U2ab94z7gwnKBnpdZ</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Thursday, January 8 (game #942)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-8-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gyhXWZk56CRik7MoK5rHNU</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Masked Singer season 14 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/the-masked-singer-season-14</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Ux6FMFm8RpnzyKQhX6SVE4</guid>
      <description>The silliest singing show on TV returns with a new twist Here&#8217;s how you can watch The Masked Singer season 14 online and from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throne, from the co-founder of Whoop, uses computer vision to study your poop</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/throne-from-the-co-founder-of-whoop-uses-computer-vision-to-study-your-poop-150000606.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2108d8ce-9e68-4173-b89e-dc797e622396</guid>
      <description>Throne has rocked up to CES 2026 to show off its forthcoming toilet computer which uses computer vision to study your poop. It hangs from the side of the bowl and has a camera and microphone to track bowel motions and urination and offer feedback. It was co-founded by (activity tracker) Whoop co-founder John Capodilupo, who explained the hardware is designed to understand what your base state is to be able to identify when you fall out of that pattern.&#160;
Capodilupo explained the hardware will look at how often you go, the texture and size of your motions, as well as the volume. The eventual aim...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le t&#233;lescope James-Webb est tomb&#233; sur des &#171;&#160;galaxies ornithorynques&#160;&#187; dans l&#8217;Univers primitif qui d&#233;routent les astronomes</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/cosmologie-telescope-james-webb-tombe-galaxies-ornithorynques-univers-primitif-deroutent-astronomes-129886/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:57:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/cosmologie-telescope-james-webb-tombe-galaxies-ornithorynques-univers-primitif-deroutent-astronomes-129886/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>&#171;&#8201;On se dit que ces choses ne devraient pas exister ensemble, mais elles sont l&#224;, juste devant vous, et c&#8217;est ind&#233;niable.&#8201;&#187; C&#8217;est ce que des biologistes pourraient bien dire &#224; propos de l&#8217;ornithorynque. C&#8217;est surtout ce que des astronomes rapportent aujourd&#8217;hui d&#8217;une poign&#233;e d&#8217;objets...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics unveils production-ready version of Atlas robot at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/boston-dynamics-unveils-production-ready-version-of-atlas-robot-at-ces-2026-234047882.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">207c5a82-d64f-4628-b6d7-ef00999cd1c5</guid>
      <description>Boston Dynamics' Atlas is finally entering production. After years of testing this humanoid robot (and forcing it to dance), the robotics company announced at CES 2026 that the final version of the machine is being built now. The first companies to receive deployments will be Hyundai, Boston Dynamics' majority shareholder, and Google DeepMind, the firm&#8217;s new AI partner.This final enterprise version of Atlas "can perform a wide array of industrial tasks," according to Boston Dynamics, and is specifically designed with consistency and reliability in mind. Atlas can work autonomously, via a teleo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pr&#233;cision cardio, triathlon et capteurs externes : pourquoi cette mise &#224; jour Suunto est une excellente nouvelle pour les sportifs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/suunto/2933635_precision-cardio-triathlon-et-capteurs-externes-pourquoi-cette-mise-a-jour-suunto-est-une-excellente-nouvelle-pour-les-sportifs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/suunto/2933635_precision-cardio-triathlon-et-capteurs-externes-pourquoi-cette-mise-a-jour-suunto-est-une-excellente-nouvelle-pour-les-sportifs</guid>
      <description>
La marque finlandaise Suunto vient de d&#233;ployer une mise &#224; jour massive pour ses montres de sport. Au programme, une meilleure gestion des capteurs externes, une plus grande pr&#233;cision du suivi cardio ou de nouveaux modes multisport. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Discovery rejects Paramount&#8217;s bid again, calls it a &#8216;leveraged buyout&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/warner-bros-discovery-rejects-paramounts-bid-again-calls-it-a-leveraged-buyout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080644</guid>
      <description>The studio's board unanimously rejected Paramount Skydance's revised $108.4 billion bid, calling the proposal a "leveraged buyout" that would saddle the company with $87 billion in debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's latest 25W MagSafe charger drops to only $30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-latest-25w-magsafe-charger-drops-to-only-30-141707024.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ce1496f-1e48-428a-bb64-aefda025bc79</guid>
      <description>One way you can reduce the number of cables you have to deal with on the regular is by investing in a few wireless chargers. Those with iPhones should consider Apple's own MagSafe charger not only because of its sleek and effective design, but also because it's on sale right now at Amazon. The Qi2.2-rated MagSafe charger is down to $30 for the one-meter version, or $40 for the two-meter version.&#160;


If you have an iPhone 16, iPhone 17 or iPhone Air, this cable can charge your device at 25W as long as it's connected to a 30W power adapter on the other end. While you'll need a more recent iPhone ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a good idea': Jensen Huang hints that Nvidia could consider bringing back older graphics cards to solve GPU pricing crisis</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/its-a-good-idea-jensen-huang-hints-that-nvidia-could-consider-bringing-back-older-graphics-cards-to-solve-gpu-pricing-crisis</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z8HQW6YsKuYkUu7YZMmEyY</guid>
      <description>Fed up with high gaming GPU prices caused by AI demand? Nvidia's solution could be AI, ironically &#8211; or even to bring back older GPUs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belkin Now Has an Even Better Switch 2 Charging Case</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/belkin-now-has-an-even-better-switch-2-charging-case-2000706639</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706639</guid>
      <description>This time, the case is a charging stand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le sublime &#233;cran OLED de la Nintendo Switch s&#8217;offre une r&#233;duction lors des soldes chez Leclerc</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933307_le-sublime-ecran-oled-de-la-nintendo-switch-soffre-une-reduction-lors-des-soldes-chez-leclerc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933307_le-sublime-ecran-oled-de-la-nintendo-switch-soffre-une-reduction-lors-des-soldes-chez-leclerc</guid>
      <description>
La Nintendo Switch OLED prend ce qui avait fonctionn&#233; sur la version standard et ajoute des nouveaut&#233;s int&#233;ressantes comme cet &#233;cran OLED et chez E.Leclerc, elle perd 23 euros de son prix et est affich&#233;e &#224; 312,90 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 Day 1: The biggest tech news and gadgets you missed from the first official day of the show</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-day-1-the-biggest-tech-news-and-gadgets-you-missed-from-the-first-official-day-of-the-show-144040174.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">575be6e0-75bb-4085-b3ba-227a0e8e943d</guid>
      <description>CES 2026&#8217;s first official show day kept the pace up with a mix of near-term gaming upgrades, ambitious new form factors and a few reminders that not every gadget needs to do everything. NVIDIA announced important gaming news, we caught up with Samsung&#8217;s tri-fold phone and Lenovo marched out an army of impressive looking gaming laptops and concept tech. Here are the biggest stories from January 6.NVIDIANVIDIA's G-Sync Pulsar is the next evolution of its VRR technology.NVIDIANVIDIA&#8217;s gaming updates focused on making motion look cleaner and boosting performance without forcing developers to rebui...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best 75-inch TVs, all tested by our big-screen experts.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-best-75-inch-tvs-all-tested-by-our-big-screen-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fzSXPFgPNhC9kPPCToHKtV</guid>
      <description>The best 75-inch TVs offer a true big-screen experience, with a size befitting the greatest films and the most nail-biting sports matches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What surprised us the most at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857406/ces-2026-surprises</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T09:34:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857406</guid>
      <description>There are some things you can reliably expect to see at the Consumer Electronics Show every year. Companies will announce big splashy TVs, there's going to be a bunch of new gadgets for charging your other gadgets, and the odds are good that a robot or two is going to hilariously malfunction. But CES always [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap x Loewe, Herm&#232;s x Adidas: Experts spill their dream collabs for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91464951/dream-collabs-that-would-actually-excite-fashion-people-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T14:32:33</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91464951/dream-collabs-that-would-actually-excite-fashion-people-in-2026</guid>
      <description>Stylish industry insiders share unexpected brand link-ups they&#8217;d like to see, but never have.
Fashion collaborations are nothing new, but 2025 felt like a year particularly stuffed with branding matchups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini les c&#226;bles&#160;: LG ressuscite son TV OLED &#171;&#160;papier peint&#160;&#187; au CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fini-les-cables-lg-ressuscite-son-tv-oled-papier-peint-au-ces-2026.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318623</guid>
      <description>Le surprenant TV Wallpaper revient au CES 2026. &#201;paisseur de 9mm, bo&#238;tier sans fil et luminosit&#233; record : le r&#234;ve devient r&#233;alit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre s&#233;lection des meilleures TV pas ch&#232;res (&#224; moins de 600 euros) en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-tv/1669623_quelle-tv-pas-chere-choisir-notre-selection-de-petit-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-tv/1669623_quelle-tv-pas-chere-choisir-notre-selection-de-petit-prix</guid>
      <description>
Vous &#234;tes &#224; la recherche d&#8217;un TV pas cher pour vous &#233;quiper correctement sans exploser votre budget&#8201;? Voici une s&#233;lection des meilleurs mod&#232;les disponibles &#224; petit prix. Pour ce faire, nous avons plac&#233; une limite de budget en dessous de 600&#160;euros et propos&#233; quelques technologies d&#8217;&#233;cran.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WheelMove gives manual wheelchairs the power and height to handle rough terrain</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/wheelmove-gives-manual-wheelchairs-the-power-and-height-to-handle-rough-terrain-143000560.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65429579-0444-4861-ab69-e3c58adf4dae</guid>
      <description>French startup WheelMove demonstrated a compact motorized wheelchair add-on at CES 2026 that not only acts as a power-assist device, but can also lift up a chair's small front wheels so it can ride over rough terrain. The accessory upgrades a manual wheelchair with a 10-inch extra wheel and a 250W motor that can drive at up to six miles per hour (10 kilometers per hour) and handle slopes up to 10 percent, with a range of 15.5 miles (25km). The battery is swappable, too, so a person could pack an extra for a longer outing to avoid having to stop and recharge.&#160;As the WheelMove team showed at its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn is expanding its AI-powered job search features</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467930/linkedin-ai-powered-job-search</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T14:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467930/linkedin-ai-powered-job-search</guid>
      <description>The platform continues to grow as a hub for&#160;seeking jobs and holding professional discussions.&#160;&#160;
LinkedIn&#8217;s AI-powered job search feature is expanding to new audiences.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to find a job in the age of AI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469887/how-to-find-a-job-in-the-age-of-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T14:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469887/how-to-find-a-job-in-the-age-of-ai</guid>
      <description>A LinkedIn Career Expert weighs in on how to crack the job market when competition is stiff and AI is changing the hiring process. 
If you&#8217;re job searching right now, it can feel like your efforts and outcomes aren&#8217;t lining up. The job search is changing, and competition isn&#8217;t easing. The result: nearly 80% of job seekers say they feel unprepared to find a new job this year. At the same time, two-thirds of recruiters say it&#8217;s become harder to find qualified talent over the last year. This tension has become a defining feature of the job hunt....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les plus grosses nouveaut&#233;s &#233;lectriques du CES 2026 sont &#224; d&#233;couvrir dans notre &#233;mission Survolt&#233;s du jour : il va y en avoir pour tout le monde</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2932709_les-plus-grosses-nouveautes-electriques-du-ces-2026-sont-a-decouvrir-dans-notre-emission-survoltes-du-jour-il-va-y-en-avoir-pour-tout-le-monde</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2932709_les-plus-grosses-nouveautes-electriques-du-ces-2026-sont-a-decouvrir-dans-notre-emission-survoltes-du-jour-il-va-y-en-avoir-pour-tout-le-monde</guid>
      <description>
L&#8217;&#233;quipe Survolt&#233;s (Frandroid) et Vroom (Numerama) vous donnent rendez-vous ce mercredi 7 janvier, d&#232;s 18h, pour une &#233;mission sp&#233;ciale CES 2026. Au menu du jour : des nouveaut&#233;s &#233;lectriques tr&#232;s excitantes et un duplex en direct de Las Vegas.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Prime lawsuit settlement: Eligibility guidelines, refund amounts, and how to file a claim</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470384/amazon-prime-lawsuit-settlement-eligibility-refund-amounts-file-claim</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T14:26:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470384/amazon-prime-lawsuit-settlement-eligibility-refund-amounts-file-claim</guid>
      <description>The company has reached a settlement with the FTC to refund customers who signed up via &#8216;challenged enrollment flows.&#8217; Here&#8217;s what that means.
If you signed up for an Amazon Prime membership between June 23, 2019, and June 23, 2025, Amazon might owe you as much as $51. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get a four-pack of AirTags for only $65 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-a-four-pack-of-airtags-for-only-65-right-now-202333162.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Most Apple products are pretty expensive, but some of the most affordable (and useful) ones are AirTags. The Bluetooth trackers are priced pretty reasonably even when not on sale, but they can be a steal if you can get them on a discount &#8212; like right now. A four pack of AirTags is on sale for $65 at Amazon, which is only a few dollars more than the record-low price we saw during Black Friday this year.


AirTags can be useful for people who travel frequently, helping you to keep track of essentials like your passport as well as a way to keep tabs on luggage while you're on the go. If you do pu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions escalate as Denmark and Greenland seek meeting with U.S. Secretary of State Rubio</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470443/tensions-escalate-denmark-greenland-seek-meeting-u-s-secretary-state-rubio</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T14:23:06</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470443/tensions-escalate-denmark-greenland-seek-meeting-u-s-secretary-state-rubio</guid>
      <description>Takeover talks are once again intensifying in the Trump White House.
Denmark and Greenland are seeking a meeting with U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio after the Trump administration doubled down on its intention to take over the strategic Arctic island, a Danish territory.Tensions escalated after the White House said Tuesday that the &#8220;U.S. military is always an option.&#8221; President Donald Trump has argued that the U.S. needs to control the world&#8217;s largest island to ensure its own security in the face of rising threats from China and Russia in the Arctic.Danish Prime Minister Mette Frederiksen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger brade un tas de produit Tech durant les soldes d&#8217;hiver : voici le TOP 15 des deals &#224; saisir</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-degaine-de-belles-offres-pour-les-soldes-dhiver-les-10-offres-qui-meritent-votre-argent</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-degaine-de-belles-offres-pour-les-soldes-dhiver-les-10-offres-qui-meritent-votre-argent</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 viennent tout juste de commencer, donnant une excellente opportunit&#233; d'optimiser ses achats Tech. Pour bien entamer l&#8217;ann&#233;e, le site Boulanger d&#233;ploie une s&#233;rie de remises attractives sur une large gamme de produits. D&#233;couvrez en temps r&#233;el notre s&#233;lection des meilleures offres &#224; ne pas manquer.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jouer gratuitement aux jeux Android payants ? Ce serait (presque) possible gr&#226;ce &#224; Google</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2933517_jouer-gratuitement-aux-jeux-android-payants-ce-serait-presque-possible-grace-a-google</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2933517_jouer-gratuitement-aux-jeux-android-payants-ce-serait-presque-possible-grace-a-google</guid>
      <description>
Google travaille &#224; une fonctionnalit&#233; qui ravirait bon nombre de joueurs sur Android. Surtout ceux qui h&#233;sitent avant de payer pour le titre qui les int&#233;resse.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : les meilleures offres &#224; ne pas rater pour cette premi&#232;re journ&#233;e de promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931731_top-depart-soldes-dhiver-2026-les-meilleures-offres-en-direct</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931731_top-depart-soldes-dhiver-2026-les-meilleures-offres-en-direct</guid>
      <description>
On a bien mang&#233; pendant les f&#234;tes, la nouvelle ann&#233;e est pass&#233;e et il a neig&#233; dans presque toute la France : c'est maintenant l'heure des soldes d'hiver. De plus, cette &#233;dition risque d'&#234;tre particuli&#232;rement int&#233;ressante pour s'&#233;quiper &#224; de bons prix avant la hausse annonc&#233;e en 2026. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer a fait plaisir &#224; Elon Musk : le Project AVA est une &#171;&#160;waifu&#160;&#187; holographique qui vous juge quand vous jouez</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2932591_razer-project-ava-le-tamagotchi-du-futur-est-une-waifu-holographique-qui-vous-juge-quand-vous-jouez</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2932591_razer-project-ava-le-tamagotchi-du-futur-est-une-waifu-holographique-qui-vous-juge-quand-vous-jouez</guid>
      <description>
C'est un peu effrayant. Razer vient de d&#233;voiler Project AVA, un compagnon IA enferm&#233; dans un &#233;cran transparent de 5,5 pouces. Il tourne sous Grok (xAI), analyse votre &#233;cran en temps r&#233;el et promet de vous aider &#224; gagner vos parties class&#233;es.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warners Bros. Discovery board urges shareholders to reject amended Paramount bid</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/warners-bros-discovery-board-urges-shareholders-to-reject-amended-paramount-bid-141513357.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d85764d-4fa7-4514-8838-b36076c55171</guid>
      <description>In a unanimous written determination, the Warner Bros. Discovery's board is advising shareholders to once again reject Paramount Skydance's "inadequate" hostile takeover bid. The letter to shareholders cites a number of concerns with the offer and reiterates its position that Netflix's offer remains superior. Netflix and WBD have entered into a merger agreement in early December after the WBD board selected its offer over other bidders.
There are two key differences between the two options: Netflix is willing to pay $82 billion, but only for the Warner Bros., HBO and HBO Max divisions; Paramou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Wi-Fi extenders in 2025: top devices for boosting your WiFi network.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/wi-fi-broadband/the-best-wi-fi-extenders-in-2025-top-devices-for-boosting-your-wifi-network</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8rnybWysHFd3Wrjbh8nkd</guid>
      <description>The best Wi-Fi extenders will make sure you can get online anywhere in your house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gaming TV for all budgets, all real-world tested by our experts.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-best-gaming-tv-for-all-budgets-all-real-world-tested-by-our-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zV9tGwHLr45KCjZ6GNCvsM</guid>
      <description>Our guide to finding the best gaming TV for your PS5, Xbox Series X, PC or even last-gen console that will suit all budgets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;m a trained TV calibrator, and here are the best TVs you can buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/im-a-trained-tv-calibrator-and-here-are-the-best-tvs-you-can-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">grVvX3GVPDiFj2oPnXx4AD</guid>
      <description>Top OLED and QLED sets to consider, from elite TVs to wallet-friendly options &#8211; all tested by us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le mini PC beige triste est mort : place au r&#233;tro-cool</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/pc-fixes/mini-pc/2933567_le-mini-pc-beige-triste-est-mort-place-au-retro-cool</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/pc-fixes/mini-pc/2933567_le-mini-pc-beige-triste-est-mort-place-au-retro-cool</guid>
      <description>
Vous cherchez un mini PC qui a de la gueule ? Regardez &#231;a. Le AYANEO AM03 mise tout sur le style avec son look cubique et ses d&#233;tails soign&#233;s. Sous le capot, la marque fait un choix pragmatique : un Intel Core i9-12900H. C'est de l'ancien, oui, mais &#224; moins de 400 &#8364;, &#231;a limite la casse.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wi-Fi sur MacBook et iPad : pourquoi vous devriez peut-&#234;tre changer les r&#233;glages de votre box internet</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2933495_wi-fi-sur-macbook-et-ipad-pourquoi-vous-devriez-peut-etre-changer-les-reglages-de-votre-box-internet</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2933495_wi-fi-sur-macbook-et-ipad-pourquoi-vous-devriez-peut-etre-changer-les-reglages-de-votre-box-internet</guid>
      <description>
Apple a discr&#232;tement am&#233;lior&#233; les performances Wi-Fi de ses derniers iPad et MacBook sur iPadOS 26 et macOS 26. Mais il faudra poss&#233;der un routeur compatible pour pouvoir en profiter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable AI is coming &#8212; and Razer&#8217;s Project Motoko is leading the charge with smart headphones</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/wearable-ai-is-coming-and-razers-project-motoko-is-leading-the-charge-with-smart-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hwgEFZTEZUimmJ5LCNfCpc</guid>
      <description>Razer&#8217;s Project Motoko reimagines headphones as intelligent, camera-equipped AI companions that respond to your environment and needs without a screen in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flamb&#233;e de la RAM&#160;: les prix vont augmenter chez Samsung aussi</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/flambee-de-la-ram-les-prix-vont-augmenter-chez-samsung-aussi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318619</guid>
      <description>Il n'y aura pas de miracles chez Samsung. Malgr&#233; sa position dominante sur le march&#233; des semi-conducteurs, le groupe cor&#233;en pr&#233;vient que la hausse des co&#251;ts finira par se retrouver sur les &#233;tiquettes de ses propres produits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Familiar Face Might Take the Long Away Round to &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chris-pratt-avengers-doomsday-vision-quest-star-lord-2000706396</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706396</guid>
      <description>Plus, Kristen Stewart wants a lot of money and a lot of love for a new 'Twilight' remake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aqara&#8217;s New Thermostat Is Also a Home Hub, Presence Sensor, and Video Doorbell Monitor</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/aqaras-new-thermostat-is-also-a-home-hub-presence-sensor-and-video-doorbell-monitor-2000705839</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705839</guid>
      <description>The Thermostat Hub W200 combines many of the best features of Aqara's lineup to make a very compelling smart home thermostat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea is expanding its Matter support to two stylish lamps</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853143/ikea-smart-home-matter-varmblixt-donut-color-changing-pendant-lamp</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853143</guid>
      <description>After debuting 21 new Matter-compatible smart home devices last November, Ikea is expanding Matter support to some of its existing home furnishings starting with two upgraded lamps at CES 2026. The Varmblixt donut lamp is getting a small redesign to complement its new color-changing smart home capabilities, while the new Varmblixt pendant lamp will let [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix is bringing back some big franchises in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/856756/netflix-2026-releases-bridgerton-one-piece-3-body</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856756</guid>
      <description>Last year was a pivotal one for Netflix, as it saw arguably the streamer's two most prominent series - Stranger Things and Squid Game - come to an end. And while Netflix has a number of competing priorities now, its lineup for 2026 also shows it's not quite done with blockbuster franchises just yet. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea&#8217;s $10 Kallsup speakers are tiny, colorful, and surprisingly loud</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/857403/ikea-kallsup-bluetooth-speaker-price-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857403</guid>
      <description>Ikea's new cute, colorful Kallsup Bluetooth speakers cost just $10 (&#8364;5 in Europe) each and feature instant Bluetooth pairing. Pair one to your phone, then, with a two-button sequence, another Kallsup can join the party. You can theoretically pair up to 100. The team I chatted with at CES - where Ikea is making its [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify lowers monetization threshold for video podcasts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/spotify-lowers-monetization-threshold-for-video-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080635</guid>
      <description>Spotify is dropping the minimum episode requirement to three, minimum consumption hours to 2,000, and engaged audience member threshold to 1,000 over the last 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA just revealed a new donut-shaped smart light &#8211; and it'll look sweet on your tables or walls</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/ikea-just-revealed-a-new-donut-shaped-smart-light-and-itll-look-sweet-on-your-table-or-wall</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fAVTtVb6iV5VhHqQEHpRhJ</guid>
      <description>The lights can be controlled using a remote, or connected to IKEA's Wi-Fi hub and linked to your smart home system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clear Drop is trying to do something about all those plastic bags under your sink</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/clear-drop-is-trying-to-do-something-about-all-those-plastic-bags-under-your-sink-140000254.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61d49e20-3d2e-4d6f-92a1-8472a751ccc5</guid>
      <description>Even if you bring home as few bags as possible &#8212; using reusable bags, carrying purchases home with your own two hands &#8212; soft plastics sill accumulate. I certainly have a collection with one flimsy plastic sack filled with dozens or hundreds of others. I plan to do something with it&#8230; eventually. 
Unfortunately, there aren&#8217;t a ton of options for what to do with those soft plastics, as most recycling facilities can&#8217;t accept them. But no one likes seeing them end up in oceans and rivers and stuck up in trees. So I was excited to see the Clear Drop Soft Plastic Compactor (CPC) at CES. It&#8217;s a pre-re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce vid&#233;oprojecteur Xgimi 4K ultra lumineux qui co&#251;te 500 &#8364; pendant les soldes de moins est parfait pour les amateurs de cin&#233;ma</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2520229_ce-videoprojecteur-xgimi-4k-ultra-lumineux-qui-coute-500-euros-pendant-les-soldes-de-moins-est-parfait-pour-les-amateurs-de-cinema</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2520229_ce-videoprojecteur-xgimi-4k-ultra-lumineux-qui-coute-500-euros-pendant-les-soldes-de-moins-est-parfait-pour-les-amateurs-de-cinema</guid>
      <description>
Si vous voulez profiter d'un v&#233;ritable home cin&#233;ma, vous pouvez vous tourner vers le Xgimi Horizon S Max. Un vid&#233;oprojecteur 4K ultra lumineux qui voit son prix s'adoucir en passant de 1 999 euros &#224; 1 499 euros gr&#226;ce aux promotions des soldes. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The base Kindle is on sale for $20 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-base-kindle-is-on-sale-for-20-off-right-now-183302578.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9865d5d-82c0-47b4-858f-2d61df88bf8c</guid>
      <description>The latest entry-level Kindle ereader is on sale for $90 via Amazon. This is a nice discount of $20. It's not a record-low price, but it's certainly a budget-friendly way to keep that New Year's resolution to read more.
This made our list of the best ereaders, and for good reason. It's an iconic device that gets the job done. It doesn't have much by way of modern bells and whistles, but it ships with 16GB of storage and comes in two snazzy colorways. 


The build is compact and durable. It's also light, which makes it easy to pack and easy to hold up with one hand. It allows access to the vast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le moins cher des Tesla Model Y pourrait bient&#244;t gagner 100 km d&#8217;autonomie gr&#226;ce &#224; une nouvelle batterie myst&#232;re</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2933431_le-moins-cher-des-tesla-model-y-pourrait-bientot-gagner-100-km-dautonomie-grace-a-une-nouvelle-batterie-mystere</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2933431_le-moins-cher-des-tesla-model-y-pourrait-bientot-gagner-100-km-dautonomie-grace-a-une-nouvelle-batterie-mystere</guid>
      <description>
Quelques mois apr&#232;s la pr&#233;sentation du Model Y "pas cher", &#224; savoir la version Standard &#224; 39 990 euros en Europe, Tesla pourrait d'ores et d&#233;j&#224; lui proposer une plus grosse batterie pour porter son autonomie &#224; plus de 650 km.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker's new 45W Nano charger with smart display from CES is already $10 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/ankers-new-45w-nano-charger-with-smart-display-from-ces-is-already-10-off-160707191.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker introduced a nifty little charger at CES 2026, which is a refresh of the pre-existing Nano Charger. It's already on sale for $30, which is a discount of $10. These are preorders, however, with shipments officially going out on January 20.
The 45W charger includes a smart display that shows real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to ensure a longer battery lifespan. 


To that end, it works with just about everything....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apr&#232;s les montres, Amazfit s&#8217;attaque &#224; votre assiette et aux lunettes avec deux innovations surprenantes au CES</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazfit/2933461_apres-les-montres-amazfit-sattaque-a-votre-assiette-et-aux-lunettes-avec-deux-innovations-surprenantes-au-ces</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazfit/2933461_apres-les-montres-amazfit-sattaque-a-votre-assiette-et-aux-lunettes-avec-deux-innovations-surprenantes-au-ces</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES de Las Vegas, Amazfit a d&#233;voil&#233; sa ligne directrice dans le domaine du sport et de la sant&#233; connect&#233;e, notamment avec une cam&#233;ra pour analyser l'alimentation et des lunettes connect&#233;es Amazfit Helio Glasses. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Ni une d&#233;cision arbitraire, ni un choix politique&#160;&#187; : le patron de l&#8217;Anssi revient sur la certification SNC de l&#8217;alliance Google-Thal&#232;s</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/ni-une-decision-arbitraire-ni-un-choix-politique-le-patron-de-lanssi-revient-sur-la-certification-snc-de-lalliance-google-thales.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318523</guid>
      <description>Vincent Strubel, &#224; la t&#234;te de l'Anssi, a pris son b&#226;ton de p&#232;lerin pour rappeler ce qu'est le label SecNumCloud (SNC), apr&#232;s la certification SNC de l'offre de cloud hybride de Google et de Thal&#232;s. Pour la premi&#232;re fois mi-d&#233;cembre, une offre associant un g&#233;ant am&#233;ricain &#224; une entreprise fran&#231;aise a re&#231;u cette certification qui n'&#233;tait, jusqu'ici, qu'accord&#233;e &#224; des entreprises fran&#231;aises : un toll&#233; pour les d&#233;fenseurs d'une souverainet&#233; num&#233;rique fran&#231;aise et europ&#233;enne....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. rejects takeover bid from Paramount, siding with Netflix&#8217;s offer</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470407/warner-bros-rejects-takeover-bid-paramount-siding-netflixs-offer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T13:37:33</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470407/warner-bros-rejects-takeover-bid-paramount-siding-netflixs-offer</guid>
      <description>Shareholders were once again urged to back Netflix&#8217;s offer for $72 billion.
Warner Bros. again rejected Paramount&#8217;s latest takeover bid and told shareholders Wednesday to stick with a rival offer from Netflix.Warner&#8217;s leadership has repeatedly rebuffed Skydance-owned Paramount&#8217;s overtures&#8212;and urged shareholders just weeks ago to back its the sale of its streaming and studio business to Netflix for $72 billion. Paramount, meanwhile, has sweetened its $77.9 billion offer for the entire company and gone straight to shareholders with a hostile bid.Warner Bros. Discovery said Wednesday that its boa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick up the Apple Watch Series 11 while it's $100 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/pick-up-the-apple-watch-series-11-while-its-100-off-154609513.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9398dfc3-7cc2-4fa1-ba51-8f9fa52c78af</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to get in shape in the new year, a wearable that tracks your daily activity and workouts can help with that. Our current favorite smartwatch is the Apple Watch Series 11, and it's on sale for $100 off right now. That brings it down to $299, which is the lowest price we've seen it so far since its release last September.


The Series 11 is our best overall smartwatch pick, and we gave it a score of 90 out of 100 in our hands-on review. We were impressed with the battery life, which lasted longer than the 24 hours it's rated for in our testing. We also liked how lightweight and...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
