<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:38:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PNY is releasing slim-sized NVIDIA RTX GPUs just as PC building becomes prohibitively expensive</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/pny-is-releasing-slim-sized-nvidia-rtx-gpus-just-as-pc-building-becomes-prohibitively-expensive-183127305.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3773e2ff-7080-4509-b628-5b441c3d446f</guid>
      <description>If I were building a new PC today, I'd go for a small form factor mATX or ITX build. With companies like Fractal Design and Lian Li making cases that can fit modern GPUs without sacrificing on thermals, you don't need to settle for the old mid-tower monstrosities of yesteryear. And that's why PNY's new "Slim&#8221; model RTX 50-series designs caught my eye. All three variants, covering the 5070, 5070 Ti and 5080, are two slot cards with just a pair of 120mm fans for cooling. As a result, even the largest of the three new models, the 5080, is relatively svelte, coming in at 11.8-inches or 300mm long....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This robot pool cleaner lifts itself out of the water to charge</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854835/mammotion-spino-s1-pro-robot-pool-cleaner-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854835</guid>
      <description>Mammotion, the company best known for its line of robot lawnmowers, is launching a robot pool cleaner that can take itself out of the water. As shown during CES 2026, the Spino S1 Pro comes with a robotic arm mounted to a docking station that sits at the edge of your pool. When the bot [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia to accelerate Siemens chip-design tools using its GPUs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/nvidia-to-accelerate-siemens-chip-design-tools-using-its-gpus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080306</guid>
      <description>Nvidia announced today at CES 2026 that it would help Siemens&#8217; electronic design automation (EDA) software run on its GPUs in an attempt to speed up the chip-design process. Nearly all computer chips today are designed using EDA tools, and as chip features get smaller and transistors more numerous, the process has grown more computationally [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of organizations fall victim to infostealers after failing to enforce MFA</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/dozens-of-organizations-fall-victim-to-infostealers-after-failing-to-enforce-mfa</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HgWVAGANimokFDbZy8UX4d</guid>
      <description>50 companies allowed access to cloud instances with just a password and were compromised with infostealers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident Evil Village and Star Wars Outlaws join January's Game Pass additions</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/resident-evil-village-and-star-wars-outlaws-join-januarys-game-pass-additions-182500938.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">711bfbc9-e0cc-48c4-9f0a-94ec88e1f749</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Microsoft announced the first batch of incoming Game Pass titles for 2026. Star Wars Outlaws and Resident Evil Village headline the first wave of the January lineup.If you (perhaps wisely) held off on spending $70 on Ubisoft's first stab at a Star Wars game, here's your chance to try it for less. Star Wars Outlaws sets you loose in an open world as the young thief Kay Vess. The third-person action title includes melee, shooting and stealth. There&#8217;s even some speeder chases and space dogfights to scratch your (boilerplate) Star Wars itch. Does it do anything novel or innovative to j...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How World Cup champion Mario G&#246;tze built a parallel career as an angel investor</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/how-world-cup-champion-mario-gotze-built-a-parallel-career-as-an-angel-investor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080196</guid>
      <description>Mario G&#246;tze will go down in soccer history as the player who scored the winning goal that made Germany the 2014 FIFA World Cup champion. But he is also an increasingly seasoned angel investor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I had my hormones checked at CES 2026 &#8212; and it turns out I'm doing great</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/i-had-my-hormones-checked-at-ces-2026-and-it-turns-out-im-doing-great</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jjuBbu76infhKS2wgEstdC</guid>
      <description>The Eli Hormometer checks your cortisol and progesterone levels and gives you your results in minutes. Here's how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG has released pricing for its new Sound Suite speaker lineup</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/lg-has-released-pricing-for-its-new-sound-suite-speaker-lineup-181053832.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d615601-adcc-4281-a201-ab5efe07476c</guid>
      <description>On Monday, we went hands-on at CES with LG's new Sound Suite speakers featuring Dolby Atmos FlexConnect and now we have pricing for the entire lineup. The modular home audio system consists of four speakers that include a soundbar, surround speakers and a subwoofer.
The centerpiece of the group is the H7 soundbar, which will retail for $1,000. The soundbar uses FlexConnect to optimize sound based on the layout of a room and its location therein. This is intended to solve for when a speaker can't be perfectly placed to deliver optimal sound, especially spatial audio.
The H7 also has a feature L...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What It&#8217;s Like to Sit in a $12,000 AI Massage Chair?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/what-its-like-to-sit-in-a-12000-ai-massage-chair-2000706025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706025</guid>
      <description>I got to try a chair that's worth more than my (admittedly old) minivan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker unveils a new lineup of chargers and docks at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/anker-unveils-a-new-lineup-of-chargers-and-docks-at-ces-2026-160021195.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a59925-1c86-46f9-b8b4-44c46f9069f6</guid>
      <description>Anker dove into CES 2026 with a slew of announcements that bring new chargers and accessories under its umbrella. The new accessories include improved visual interfaces, faster Qi2 wireless charging and &#8220;upgraded ecosystems&#8221; that support the latest iPhones. Some of the latest devices are even available to buy right now.
First up is the Anker Nano Charger with smart display, which features a tiny screen, 180-degree foldable prongs and provides up to 45W of power. The plug can identify the exact iPhone model connected and then deliver the right amount of power for your phone. Anker says the Nano...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#201;crire sur une table avec vos Ray-Ban&#160;? La fonction bluffante d&#233;voil&#233;e par Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/ecrire-sur-une-table-avec-vos-ray-ban-la-fonction-bluffante-devoilee-par-meta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318468</guid>
      <description>Meta profite du CES 2026 pour muscler ses Ray-Ban Display. Au menu : un t&#233;l&#233;prompteur personnel dans le champ de vision et la capacit&#233; d'&#233;crire des messages du bout des doigts sur n'importe quelle surface. Le futur est l&#224;, mais il faudra &#234;tre patient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The Batman Part II&#8217; Keeps Poaching MCU Alums</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-batman-part-ii-sebastian-stan-dc-marvel-2000706269</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706269</guid>
      <description>The Winter Soldier himself, Sebastian Stan, is reportedly joining his fellow 'Avengers' alum Scarlett Johansson in DC's Robert Pattinson-starring sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beatbot&#8217;s New Pool Cleaning Robot Uses AI to Find Pool Debris</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/beatbots-new-pool-cleaning-robot-uses-ai-to-find-pool-debris-2000705768</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705768</guid>
      <description>Also, the company has updates on its sea turtle robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power bank feature creep is out of control</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856225/power-banks-are-the-latest-victims-of-feature-creep</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856225</guid>
      <description>There was a time not too long ago when buying a power bank was as easy as choosing the cheapest portable battery that could charge your phone and quickly slip into your pocket, purse, or backpack. The hardest part was deciding whether it was time to ditch USB-A ports. Recently, however, brands have been slathering [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navee's CES lineup includes a speedy e-scooter, a golf cart and... a seaplane?</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/navees-ces-lineup-includes-a-speedy-e-scooter-a-golf-cart-and-a-seaplane-180000473.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edf4be96-670d-44a8-9d4d-180b61e32664</guid>
      <description>The Chinese micromobility company Navee has some wild new stuff at CES 2026. The lineup is headlined by the UT5 Ultra X, a dual-motor e-scooter with an advertised top speed of 43 mph. And who among us isn't in the market for an auto-following golf cart and a seaplane?The flagship UT5 Ultra X is a sleek-looking e-scooter with a pair of 2,400W motors. Navee says it can reach a top speed of 43 mph and has a max range of 87 miles. (However, in the world of e-scooters, it's safe to expect the real-world range to be around half of what manufacturers promise.) It has a front and rear hydraulic suspen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#201;nergie noire : et si l&#8217;Univers changeait de destin sous nos yeux ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-energie-noire-si-univers-changeait-destin-sous-nos-yeux-w2t8-129794/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-energie-noire-si-univers-changeait-destin-sous-nos-yeux-w2t8-129794/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Une &#233;quipe de chercheurs parmi lesquels se trouve l'un des d&#233;couvreurs de l'&#233;nergie noire, ou pour le moins de l'expansion acc&#233;l&#233;r&#233;e de l'espace, a trouv&#233; une fa&#231;on plus rigoureuse de l'&#233;tudier. Les nouveaux r&#233;sultats obtenus vont toujours dans le sens d'une remise en cause du destin du cosmos...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les trois meilleurs smartphones de l&#8217;ann&#233;e 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2928987_les-trois-meilleurs-smartphones-de-lannee-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2928987_les-trois-meilleurs-smartphones-de-lannee-2025</guid>
      <description>
L'ann&#233;e 2025 a &#233;t&#233; un tournant, marqu&#233;e par l'int&#233;gration massive de l'IA dans nos smartphones. Apr&#232;s avoir test&#233; et compar&#233; des dizaines de mod&#232;les cette ann&#233;e, nous avons s&#233;lectionn&#233; la cr&#232;me de la cr&#232;me. Voici notre podium des trois smartphones incontournables de 2025.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock lance le F25 Ace Pro : 25 000 Pa et une technologie de mousse in&#233;dite</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/roborock/2926473_roborock-lance-le-f25-ace-pro-25-000-pa-et-une-technologie-de-mousse-inedite</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/roborock/2926473_roborock-lance-le-f25-ace-pro-25-000-pa-et-une-technologie-de-mousse-inedite</guid>
      <description>
Le probl&#232;me des aspirateurs-laveurs, c'est souvent l'humidit&#233; r&#233;siduelle. Avec le F25 Ace Pro, Roborock change de fusil d'&#233;paule. Au lieu d'inonder le sol, il projette une mousse ultra-dense. Ajoutez &#224; cela une puissance brute de 25 000 Pa, et vous avez sur le papier une machine de guerre contre les taches de gras.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Morning After: Sony Honda&#8217;s new car, Lego&#8217;s first CES press event and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/the-morning-after-engadget-newsletter-ces-2026-press-day-174444560.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fc60d43-0935-486f-985b-3903fd0092ae</guid>
      <description>Welcome to your first CES edition of TMA, attempting (almost futilely) to distill the biggest product reveals and announcements. Despite two days of briefings and conferences, today is merely day one. However, we&#8217;ve already seen Sony Honda reveal its next car &#8212; and the Afeela 1 isn&#8217;t yet on sale. We&#8217;ve got a deep dive on what we&#8217;ve seen so far, right here.
AMD announced new Ryzen AI 400 laptop processors and updated desktop chips, including the Ryzen 7 9850X3D, with a new focus broadly on AI processing improvements. NVIDIA had a lengthy, dense press conference showing off its dominance in AI t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report on AI adoption warns workers could face more complex responsibilities for lower pay</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/new-report-on-ai-adoption-warns-workers-could-face-more-complex-responsibilities-for-lower-pay</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JXp73veu97ZyfkDdTxtWem</guid>
      <description>AI could lead to productivity, unemployment, and health gaps &#8211; we should focus on sustainable human-AI collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads is developing in-message games</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/threads-is-developing-in-message-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080274</guid>
      <description>Launching in-message games would give Threads an edge over competitors like X and Bluesky, which don&#8217;t offer built-in games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quand le tableau de bord devient une toile g&#233;ante : comment ces mini-projecteurs pourraient &#233;liminer les &#233;crans des voitures</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2931261_quand-le-tableau-de-bord-devient-une-toile-geante-comment-ces-mini-projecteurs-pourraient-eliminer-les-ecrans-des-voitures</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2931261_quand-le-tableau-de-bord-devient-une-toile-geante-comment-ces-mini-projecteurs-pourraient-eliminer-les-ecrans-des-voitures</guid>
      <description>
Au CES de Las Vegas, l'&#233;quipementier Aumovio d&#233;voile un syst&#232;me de projection qui transforme radicalement l'habitacle. Exit les &#233;crans : place &#224; une surface d'affichage qui s'&#233;tend sur toute la largeur de la planche de bord, promettant une exp&#233;rience visuelle immersive.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazons 55-inch 4-Series Fire TV is $100 off for the first time ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-amazon-4-series-fire-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03EpYGnueLqK4m6SMy9NPhP</guid>
      <description>The Amazon 55-inch 4-Series 4K TV is down to its best price ever of $359.99 at Amazon. Use the code SAVE100 at checkout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenbook et Vivobook 2026&#160;: comment Asus veut contrer le MacBook Air avec l&#8217;IA</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/zenbook-et-vivobook-2026-comment-asus-veut-contrer-le-macbook-air-avec-lia.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318143</guid>
      <description>Poids plume de moins d'un kilo, autonomie solide et puces Snapdragon X2 Elite : Asus bouscule les codes de la mobilit&#233; avec sa nouvelle gamme Zenbook et Vivobook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finis les PC pros moches&#160;? Asus l&#232;ve le voile sur l&#8217;ExpertBook Ultra</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/finis-les-pc-pros-moches-asus-leve-le-voile-sur-lexpertbook-ultra.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318439</guid>
      <description>Moins d'un kilo, &#233;cran OLED Tandem et finitions c&#233;ramique : Asus veut r&#233;inventer le PC pro avec l'ExpertBook Ultra, une machine &#233;l&#233;gante taill&#233;e pour l'&#232;re de l'IA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm Wants You to Know That Its New Car Chip Has Multitasking Baked In</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/qualcomm-wants-you-to-know-that-its-new-car-chip-has-multitasking-baked-in-2000706140</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706140</guid>
      <description>Qualcomm demoed its Flex SoC that controls driver assistance and safety features at the same time as in-car entertainment in cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aqara&#8217;s Latest Presence Sensor Knows When You&#8217;re Lying Down or Sitting Up</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/aqaras-latest-presence-sensor-knows-when-youre-lying-down-or-sitting-up-2000706039</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706039</guid>
      <description>The Spatial Multi-Sensor FP400 takes mmWave presence sensing a step further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu les nouveau Zenbook DUO, le g&#233;nial PC d&#8217;Asus &#224; deux &#233;crans qui s&#8217;am&#233;liore grandement</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/on-a-vu-les-nouveau-zenbook-duo-le-genial-pc-dasus-a-deux-ecrans-qui-sameliore-grandement.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1316890</guid>
      <description>&#192; l&#8217;approche du CES 2026, Asus d&#233;voile un Zenbook DUO repens&#233;&#8239;: double &#233;cran OLED, ch&#226;ssis affin&#233; et charni&#232;re revue pour plus de confort et de robustesse. Ce PC portable &#224; deux &#233;crans vise toujours la productivit&#233; maximale, mais avec un design bien plus abouti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Asus new 16-inch laptop is lighter than a 13-inch MacBook Air</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-asus-zenbook-a16-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00UTqu7r73wiPi7Cz80AURN</guid>
      <description>The ultralight Asus Zenbook A16 debuted at CES 2026 Tuesday. It's a 16-inch version of the company's award-winning MacBook Air competitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 16-inch laptop is so light I can easily lift it with three fingers</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852034/asus-zenbook-a16-thin-light-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852034</guid>
      <description>Asus' Zenbook A14 that debuted at last year's CES is now getting a bigger sibling for CES 2026. The new Asus Zenbook A16 is a 16-inch counterpart to refreshed Zenbook A14, both packing Qualcomm Snapdragon X2 Elite processors. The two Zenbook A models are very similar, both sporting OLED displays, two USB 4 ports, one [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus&#8217; Zenbook Duo dual-screen laptop gets Intel&#8217;s new chip and a more seamless hinge</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852067/asus-zenbook-duo-dual-screen-laptop-intel-new-chip</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852067</guid>
      <description>The Asus Zenbook Duo is getting a chip upgrade, an overhauled hinge design, and a big battery upgrade for CES 2026. The new dual-screen laptop will get Intel Panther Lake when it launches later in Q1 2026, though its pricing isn't finalized. But the most noticeable change is to its finish and its hinge. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus made a GoPro-inspired ProArt PX13 laptop</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852109/asus-gopro-inspired-proart-px13-laptop</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852109</guid>
      <description>Asus is announcing a new ProArt PX13 convertible laptop and ProArt PZ14 detachable tablet for CES 2026. The PX13 comes in two versions: a standard model and a GoPro Edition. Both feature a stylus-compatible 13.3-inch 2880 x 1800 OLED display, dial pad control built into the trackpad, and AMD's "Strix Halo" Ryzen AI Max APU [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI's newest laptop beats Apple's MacBook Pro on an all-important metric &#8212; Prestige 16 lasts 30+ hours on video playback and weighs only 1.59kg</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/msis-newest-laptop-beats-apples-macbook-pro-on-an-all-important-metric-prestige-16-lasts-30-hours-on-video-playback-and-weighs-only-1-59kg</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q6cBuAAyntNAyMFsMRsJrN</guid>
      <description>MSI&#8217;s Prestige 16 offers professional performance with long battery life, OLED display, lightweight aluminum chassis, and advanced input including keyboard and stylus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ASUS Zenbook Duo got a fantastic redesign for CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/the-asus-zenbook-duo-got-a-fantastic-redesign-for-ces-2026-173000392.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0875ad95-000b-4b2d-b99d-9cebb935fc7a</guid>
      <description>The ASUS Zenbook Duo was easily one of my favorite laptops of 2024 as it was the first dual-screen notebook actually worth buying. But now at CES 2026, ASUS has given the second-gen model a complete revamp with practically all the upgrades and tweaks I&#8217;ve been hoping for.&#160;Like the rest of the Zenbook line, the 2026 Duo is getting ASUS&#8217; Ceraluminum treatment on its lid, bottom and kickstand, which not only looks great but it adds an extra bit of durability and scratch resistance. There&#8217;s also an improved magnetic latch system and Bluetooth connection for its detachable keyboard to help keep it ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus ExpertBook Ultra : le PC de moins de 1 kg qui veut faire oublier le MacBook Air</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2928123_asus-expertbook-ultra-le-pc-de-moins-de-1-kg-qui-veut-faire-oublier-le-macbook-air</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2928123_asus-expertbook-ultra-le-pc-de-moins-de-1-kg-qui-veut-faire-oublier-le-macbook-air</guid>
      <description>
D&#233;sireux de d&#233;poussi&#233;rer sa gamme ExpertBook pour les professionnels, Asus a d&#233;voil&#233; un nouveau mod&#232;le au suffixe "Ultra" lors du CES 2026 de Las Vegas. Un ultraportable avec &#233;cran Oled qui pourrait bien relancer Asus sur ce segment.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quand deux &#233;crans Oled qui n&#8217;en font plus qu&#8217;un : on a vu le nouveau Zenbook Duo d&#8217;Asus</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2927587_quand-deux-ecrans-oled-qui-nen-font-plus-quun-on-a-vu-le-nouveau-zenbook-duo-dasus</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2927587_quand-deux-ecrans-oled-qui-nen-font-plus-quun-on-a-vu-le-nouveau-zenbook-duo-dasus</guid>
      <description>
Le Zenbook Duo de chez Asus se refait une sant&#233; en 2026 avec deux nouvelles dalles Oled encore plus lumineuses, un nouveau ch&#226;ssis plus fin et une fiche technique dernier cri.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We now know the first TV brands that will support Dolby Vision 2 &#8211; and one has been very prolific at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/we-now-know-the-first-tv-brands-that-will-support-dolby-vision-2-and-one-has-been-very-prolific-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XLrpMUReHNnQSua9cCWAwV</guid>
      <description>After being revealed in 2025, Dolby Vision 2 plans have been announced at CES 2026, including which TV brands will get the new HDR format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new Skims Team USA collection is the &#8216;Juicy Couture&#8217; of Olympic partnerships</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469849/skims-team-usa-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T17:24:25</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469849/skims-team-usa-2026</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s Team USA&#8217;s cheekiest collection yet.
Kim Kardashian&#8217;s apparel brand Skims is outfitting American athletes at the Olympics for the fourth time in a row, and this year&#8217;s collection is its cheekiest one yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We&#8217;re really pleased with the reception.&#8217; Meta&#8217;s Display smart glasses are a hit &#8212; but that&#8217;s not good news if you want a pair</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/were-really-pleased-with-the-reception-metas-display-smart-glasses-are-a-hit-but-thats-not-good-news-if-you-want-a-pair</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RyRiNi3wuMKX6XNGCiqaMm</guid>
      <description>The Meta Ray-Ban Display glasses are so popular that their international launch is on &#8216;pause&#8217;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immerse yourself in your favorite games with the 27-inch Alienware gaming monitor at its lowest price</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-alienware-gaming-monitor-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05p42bjccxB7rqiUVRKsLar</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 6, get the 27-inch Alienware gaming monitor for its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huawei Watch GT 6 Pro : d&#233;j&#224; plus de 100 &#8364; de remise pour cette r&#233;cente montre connect&#233;e qui combine &#233;l&#233;gance et fonctions sportives</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2918551_huawei-watch-gt-6-pro-deja-plus-de-100-euros-de-remise-pour-cette-recente-montre-connectee-qui-combine-elegance-et-fonctions-sportives</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2918551_huawei-watch-gt-6-pro-deja-plus-de-100-euros-de-remise-pour-cette-recente-montre-connectee-qui-combine-elegance-et-fonctions-sportives</guid>
      <description>
Endurante, pr&#233;cise dans ses donn&#233;es et tr&#232;s styl&#233;e, la Huawei Watch GT 6 Pro est une montre connect&#233;e r&#233;ussie. Actuellement, AliExpress la vend &#224; 273,96 euros au lieu de 379,99 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; un code promo. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valve announced the 2025 Steam Awards winners (and shockingly Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 didn't win everything)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/valve-announced-the-2025-steam-awards-winners-and-shockingly-clair-obscur-expedition-33-didnt-win-everything</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">my44Qk9bGMvGEpAKF7ZLeZ</guid>
      <description>Valve has revealed the winners of the 2025 Steam Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP just squeezed a desktop computer into a keyboard &#8211; and it's powerful enough to be a Copilot+ PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/keyboards/hp-just-squeezed-a-desktop-computer-into-a-keyboard-and-its-powerful-enough-to-be-a-copilot-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ESKYJFt7rENePtczKS8gH5</guid>
      <description>HP packed a powerful Ryzen CPU, DDR5 RAM and storage into a peripheral to make the world's first keyboard that's a Copilot+ PC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida&#8217;s Surgeon General Is Now Peddling Fake Water</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/floridas-surgeon-general-is-now-peddling-fake-water-2000705629</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705629</guid>
      <description>In a recent social media post, Joseph Ladapo endorsed the use of structured water, which doesn't actually seem to exist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The long-rumored Assassin's Creed Black Flag remake could finally be announced soon, as leaked domain registration surfaces online</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-long-rumored-assassins-creed-black-flag-remake-could-finally-be-announced-soon-as-leaked-domain-registration-surfaces-online</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aCdSysvTV8vAcv3F85R5z4</guid>
      <description>The domain registration for the long-rumored Assassin's Creed Black Flag remake has seemingly been leaked online, suggesting Assassin's Creed Black Flag Resynced could be announced imminently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preorder the new Soundcore Sleep A30 Special earbuds to get better rest by the end of the month</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/soundcore-sleep-a30-special-where-to-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06swZs3cQxfqju9C0GuhIgI</guid>
      <description>Anker is now taking preorders for the new Soundcore Sleep A30 Special sleep earbuds for $199.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth Targets Retired Astronaut&#8217;s Pension for &#8216;Illegal Orders&#8217; Video</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pete-hegseth-targets-retired-astronauts-pension-for-illegal-orders-video-2000706202</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706202</guid>
      <description>The 90-second video urging U.S. military personnel to refuse to follow illegal orders was deemed "punishable by DEATH!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures montres connect&#233;es de 2026&#8201;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-wearables/321259_7-suggestions-de-montres-connectees-en-2018</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-wearables/321259_7-suggestions-de-montres-connectees-en-2018</guid>
      <description>
Vous voulez craquer sur une smartwatch ? Galaxy Watch, Pixel Watch, Apple Watch, Garmin ou encore Withings. Voici notre s&#233;lection des meilleures montres connect&#233;es&#160;test&#233;es par notre r&#233;daction pour accompagner votre smartphone Android ou votre iPhone.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Smart Play : explications techniques sur le fonctionnement des briques connect&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/2930409_lego-smart-play-explications-techniques-sur-le-fonctionnement-des-briques-connectees</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/2930409_lego-smart-play-explications-techniques-sur-le-fonctionnement-des-briques-connectees</guid>
      <description>
On a vu les jolis vaisseaux Star Wars. Mais le vrai sujet n'est pas l&#224;. Le vrai sujet, c'est comment LEGO a r&#233;ussi &#224; faire entrer un ASIC, des capteurs et une batterie dans une brique standard de 2x4 tenons. Pas d'&#233;cran, pas de smartphone : c'est la technologie Smart Play.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This portable triple laptop monitor can quadruple your total screen resolution to 4K &#8212; and unlike others, it only requires a single USB-C cable to make it all work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-portable-triple-laptop-monitor-can-quadruple-your-total-screen-resolution-to-4k-and-unlike-others-it-only-requires-a-single-usb-c-cable-to-make-it-all-work</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oCysW38JiJMLMhPRSVWbA3</guid>
      <description>This KYY monitor extender gives your laptop a full four-screen workspace from a single USB-C cable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Mobile&#8217;s golden phone delayed despite promises</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469662/trump-mobile-t1-golden-phone-delayed</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T17:04:24</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469662/trump-mobile-t1-golden-phone-delayed</guid>
      <description>Trump Mobile&#8217;s website continues to list the T1&#8217;s targeted release date as &#8216;later this year.&#8217;
A golden phone that President Donald Trump&#8216;s family business promised to release last year remains mysteriously under wraps as the technology industry serves up a glut of&#160;new gadgets at CES&#160;in Las Vegas this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas firm hit with a record $9.6 million fine after a Gulf of Mexico oil spill</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469673/texas-firm-hit-record-9-6-million-fine-after-gulf-mexico-oil-spill</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T17:04:04</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469673/texas-firm-hit-record-9-6-million-fine-after-gulf-mexico-oil-spill</guid>
      <description>The fine represents less than 3% of Third Coast&#8217;s annual earnings. 
Pipeline safety regulators on Monday assessed their largest fine ever against the company responsible for leaking 1.1 million gallons of oil into the Gulf off the coast of Louisiana in 2023. But the $9.6 million fine isn&#8217;t likely to be a major burden for Third Coast to pay.This single fine is close to the normal total of $8 million to $10 million in all fines that the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration hands out each year. But Third Coast has a stake in some 1,900 miles of pipelines, and in September, the H...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon just unveiled its first Fire TV Stick interface upgrade in five years &#8211; and it could spell trouble for Google TV</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/amazon-just-unveiled-its-first-fire-tv-stick-interface-upgrade-in-five-years-and-it-could-spell-trouble-for-google-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NN7SsqvjHUdZZ3gbo4x5FQ</guid>
      <description>From new colors to Alexa+, these are all the new features in the next Fire TV redesign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble's founder might be just the right person to make an AI ring</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/pebbles-founder-might-be-just-the-right-person-to-make-an-ai-ring-170104222.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a033f94-d17e-44e2-b7cd-ca6a98c5400c</guid>
      <description>Eric Migicovsky has been thinking a lot about friction. Specifically, he&#8217;s been thinking about how too much friction in the way of using a device can put people off wearing it altogether. The founder of Pebble is here at CES 2026 with a few new devices from the company he recently started to bring back the beloved smartwatch brand, including the Pebble Round 2 and the Index 01. That second one is a simple ring with a button on it that you push down to talk to Pebble&#8217;s AI whenever you want it to help you remember something. In the sea of AI gadgets that clutter the showfloors of CES (and the cu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock launches its first robot lawn mower in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851696/roborock-launches-its-first-robot-lawnmower-in-the-us</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851696</guid>
      <description>Roborock is finally bringing its bots to yards in the US, several months after expanding into robot lawn mowers last year. The Roborock RockMow X1 LiDAR, announced today at CES, will be launching later this year, featuring autonomous navigation, all-wheel drive, and 360-degree 3D scanning using a combination of LiDAR and Visual Simultaneous Localization and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock&#8217;s new Saros 20 robot vacuum cleaners got a climbing upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852702/roborock-saros-20-sonic-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852702</guid>
      <description>Roborock's latest robovacs don't need help getting out of tricky situations. At least, that's one of the perks of the improved AdaptiLift Chassis 3.0 on the Roborock Saros 20 and Saros 20 Sonic announced today at CES 2026. The upgraded chassis in Roborock's new flagship robot vacuum cleaners allows the bots to climb over thresholds [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock&#8217;s Next Stair-Climbing Robot Vacuum Has Actual Legs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/roborocks-next-stair-climbing-robot-vacuum-has-actual-legs-2000704705</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704705</guid>
      <description>Whether this stair-climbing&#8212;and cleaning!&#8212;robot is the first true whole-home robot vacuum remains to be seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugh Jackman&#8217;s New &#8216;Robin Hood&#8217; Movie Channels Old Man Logan</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hugh-jackman-robin-hood-trailer-logan-xmen-2000705859</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705859</guid>
      <description>'The Death of Robin Hood,' co-starring Jodie Comer and Bill Skarsg&#229;rd, opens later this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock&#8217;s Rover walks, jumps, and vacuums your stairs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852121/roborock-saros-rover-stair-climbing-robot-vacuum-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852121</guid>
      <description>I've been reviewing robot vacuums for almost a decade, and one question I hear repeatedly is "When will it clean my stairs?" Well, we finally have an answer. Sort of. At CES 2026 this week, Roborock launched the Saros Rover, a robot vacuum with articulating legs on wheels that let it climb a full staircase [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You might mistake Satechi&amp;#8217;s new Thunderbolt 5 hub for Apple&amp;#8217;s Mac Mini</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853378/satechi-thunderbolt-5-dock-mac-mini-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853378</guid>
      <description>Satechi is launching a new dock that supports Intel's Thunderbolt 5 technology - and it looks a lot like an Apple Mac Mini. The Thunderbolt 5 CubeDock fits an NVMe SSD enclosure and several ports inside a relatively compact form factor, measuring 5 inches wide and 2 inches tall. And at $399.99, the device is [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now use Abbott&#8217;s OTC glucose monitors with Withings</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853413/abbott-lingo-withings-cgm-wearable-health-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853413</guid>
      <description>Withings isn't done with CES 2026 announcements just yet. The French health tech company just announced a new partnership with Abbott. In the first quarter of the year, Abbott Lingo users will be able to view their glucose data within the Withings app. Lingo is Abbott's over-the-counter continuous glucose monitor (CGM) for nondiabetic people. Withings [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InkPoster launches a premium, 41-inch e-paper display for your home</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/inkposter-launches-a-premium-41-inch-e-paper-display-for-your-home-170000292.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbba0380-e9d6-47b6-a85f-4ffd670ada06</guid>
      <description>Last year, PocketBook rocked up at CES with a series of large e-paper displays to display art on the walls of your home. This year, the company has turned up with a far larger, A1-sized model called the Duna, which it says mimics the &#8220;texture, depth and tonal richness of printed paper.&#8221; It&#8217;s intended to act as an upmarket alternative to those big screen TVs which display art when they&#8217;re not being used for their intended purpose.&#160;Unsurprisingly, such a fancy product also needs some fancy accessories, so it&#8217;s recruited Italian design house Pininfarina to help. It claims the credit for the Duna&#8217;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lovense launches an AI 'companion doll' at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/lovense-launches-an-ai-companion-doll-at-ces-170000490.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dadac9b-1aab-418d-9b23-230618a4f4de</guid>
      <description>The following article discusses themes of an adult nature.Lovense has turned up to CES with a &#8220;companion doll,&#8221; a life-size sex doll that&#8217;s designed to be more than just a life size sex doll. The company has equipped it with its proprietary AI engine and promises &#8220;human-like cognition, emotional awareness and expressive behavior.&#8221; The doll, which in the marketing video is called Emily, is Lovense&#8217;s answer to the global loneliness crisis. It says, over time, a user&#8217;s relationship with the system will grow deeper as it learns to adapt to their needs. And that the doll is the natural evolution of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble seeks to remedy the wearable industry's original sin</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/pebble-seeks-to-remedy-the-wearable-industrys-original-sin-170000834.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40e564e-6899-4b40-8ce6-db28ab06ed90</guid>
      <description>As soon as I held the Pebble Round 2 in my hand, I suddenly realized what I&#8217;d been missing for the better part of a decade. I&#8217;ve always felt smartwatches should supplement, rather than supplant, your phone, but that&#8217;s an attitude that feels almost quaint these days. After all, Apple and Samsung believe everyone wants a watch that can do almost everything your phone can do. But that wasn&#8217;t the prevailing opinion at the dawn of the smartwatch era, either philosophically or from limitations in the technology. Back then, companies like Pebble, Vector, Basis and others all built devices that added ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satechi is embracing Thunderbolt 5 at CES with a new dock and cable</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/satechi-is-embracing-thunderbolt-5-at-ces-with-a-new-dock-and-cable-170000137.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df27212c-4c81-4a0f-b726-b25250b46d0f</guid>
      <description>Multiple of Satechi's Thunderbolt 4 docks are on Engadget's list of the best docking stations, so when the company announces a new accessory, it's usually worth a look. At CES 2026, Satechi is finally making the jump to Thunderbolt 5 with a new docking station and cable. The Thunderbolt 5 CubeDock with SSD Enclosure and Thunderbolt 5 Pro Cable leverage the faster speeds of Intel's cable tech, and in the case of the dock, also include extra benefits like space for SSD storage.
The CubeDock is made from a block of solid aluminum and is clearly supposed to evoke Apple's desktop Macs, like the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok users can&#8217;t stop dunking on cheesy HR training videos</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469453/tiktok-users-cant-stop-dunking-on-cheesy-hr-training-videos</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469453/tiktok-users-cant-stop-dunking-on-cheesy-hr-training-videos</guid>
      <description>Should you A: report them to your manager, or B: stealthily watch the clips on your phone?
Workplace training invites are dropping in many employees&#8217; inboxes now that the new year is underway. Most employers require staff to complete multiple HR modules annually: training on harassment, workplace relationships, or conflicts of interest, for example, followed by a quick quiz....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock dropped 3 new robot vacuums at CES 2026. Of course they set a new suction power record.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-roborock-robot-vacuums-announced</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Jg9q3FqPcBD3AkwZg0gVj</guid>
      <description>Of Roborock's CES 2026 drops, the Saros 20 Sonic is already a contender for best robot vacuum of the year. A stairs-climbing robovac is also on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Ivory Coast vs. Burkina Faso online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ivory-coast-burkina-faso-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02s7xBM1vIGRUVkzZ8Jyy88</guid>
      <description>How to watch AFCON for free. Live stream Ivory Coast vs. Burkina Faso in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roborock a craqu&#233; : un aspirateur avec des jambes pour tuer et on devine tr&#232;s bien &#224; quoi &#231;a sert</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/roborock/2926461_roborock-a-craque-un-aspirateur-avec-des-jambes-pour-tuer-et-on-devine-tres-bien-a-quoi-ca-sert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/roborock/2926461_roborock-a-craque-un-aspirateur-avec-des-jambes-pour-tuer-et-on-devine-tres-bien-a-quoi-ca-sert</guid>
      <description>
C'est le boss final des aspirateurs robots : l'escalier. Jusqu'ici, aucun constructeur n'avait de solution cr&#233;dible, malgr&#233; pas mal de prototypes &#224; l'IFA 2025. Roborock vient peut-&#234;tre de changer la donne au CES 2026. Pas avec une nouvelle brosse ou plus d'IA, mais avec un concept de ch&#226;ssis &#224; jambes articul&#233;es capable de mim&#233;tiser la marche humaine.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspiration puissante, lavage des serpilli&#232;res &#224; 100 &#186;C, petites pattes pour franchir les seuils : voici les nouveaux Roborock Saros 20</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/roborock/2926861_aspiration-puissante-lavage-des-serpillieres-a-100-oc-petites-pattes-pour-franchir-les-seuils-voici-les-nouveaux-roborock-saros-20</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/roborock/2926861_aspiration-puissante-lavage-des-serpillieres-a-100-oc-petites-pattes-pour-franchir-les-seuils-voici-les-nouveaux-roborock-saros-20</guid>
      <description>
Comme &#224; son habitude, Roborock profite du CES pour pr&#233;senter ses derniers aspirateurs porte-&#233;tendards. Au programme, deux mod&#232;les qui se diff&#233;rencient principalement par leurs serpilli&#232;res.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer is making a version of its best controller specifically for LG Smart TVs &#8212; and you can check it out at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/razer-is-making-a-version-of-its-best-controller-specifically-for-lg-smart-tvs-and-you-can-check-it-out-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Dq3DuCBwA8F52Hrtq8CziD</guid>
      <description>Razer just announced an LG Smart TV controller based on its excellent Wolverine V3 Pro at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finish your DIY projects with the DeWalt Mechanics Tool Set for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-dewalt-mechanics-tool-set-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01kjkeZgyj3sJ1BlJK0x9Nc</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 6, get the DeWalt Mechanics Tool Set for its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google TV&#160;: Gemini va prendre la main sur les r&#233;glages de la t&#233;l&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/google-tv-gemini-va-prendre-la-main-sur-les-reglages-de-la-tele.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318460</guid>
      <description>Gemini continue de se faire une petite place dans Google TV. Le g&#233;ant du web a annonc&#233; plusieurs nouveaut&#233;s IA, plus ou moins utiles il faut le reconnaitre, pour faciliter la vie des t&#233;l&#233;spectateurs devant leur t&#233;l&#233; connect&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested this Lenovo Legion gaming laptop and its design is sumptuous &#8212; but there are better performers at this price point</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/lenovo-legion-7i-gen-10-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BXZA5euVb2xX37nSB4QN8X</guid>
      <description>The Lenovo Legion 7i Gen 10 certainly has the looks, but does it have the grunt?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Is Pushing the Number of Fake Frames for Games to Ludicrous Levels</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nvidia-is-pushing-the-number-of-fake-frames-for-games-to-ludicrous-levels-2000706195</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706195</guid>
      <description>DLSS isn&#8217;t done evolving, even if it means more and more AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Pass en janvier 2026 : on commence l&#8217;ann&#233;e avec du lourd dans cette premi&#232;re s&#233;lection de 2026 !</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2931685_game-pass-en-janvier-2026-on-commence-lannee-avec-du-lourd-dans-cette-premiere-selection-de-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2931685_game-pass-en-janvier-2026-on-commence-lannee-avec-du-lourd-dans-cette-premiere-selection-de-2026</guid>
      <description>
Microsoft vient de d&#233;voiler la premi&#232;re s&#233;lection de 2026 pour son Game Pass. Plus d'une dizaine de jeux sont &#224; l'honneur entre les titres AAA et quelques jeux ind&#233;s. Voici ce qui vous occupera les prochaines semaines.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betelgeuse&#8217;s Hidden Companion May Finally Be Revealing Itself</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/betelgeuses-hidden-companion-may-finally-be-revealing-itself-2000706185</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706185</guid>
      <description>With this new evidence, the existence of &#8220;Betelbuddy&#8221; is closer than ever to being confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon phase today: What the Moon will look like on January 6</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/moon-phase-today-jan-6</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03LMEbxOjdXl6SWbRE3Db6E</guid>
      <description>See the Moon phase expected for January 6, 2025 as well as when the next Full Moon is expected.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
