<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:05:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta has discontinued its metaverse for work, too</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/863209/meta-has-discontinued-its-metaverse-for-work-too</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T21:01:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863209</guid>
      <description>Two months before it changed its name to "Meta," Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg personally introduced us to his metaverse for work: Horizon Workrooms, envisioned as a virtual space for workers to collaborate. Today, the company announced it's shutting that space down: "Meta has made the decision to discontinue Workrooms as a standalone app, effective February [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pitt season 2 episode 2&#8217;s new trauma is more disastrous than any medical emergency &#8212; and it&#8217;s all thanks to AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/the-pitt-season-2-episode-2s-new-trauma-is-more-disastrous-than-any-medical-emergency-and-its-all-thanks-to-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8aaKbU8gSbw2E3ukAYjpxc</guid>
      <description>Not even a doctor can fix the mess The Pitt season 2 episode 2 has got itself into &#8212; but maybe Sam Altman at OpenAI could.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Sonos speakers to buy in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/652171/best-sonos-speakers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:33:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=652171</guid>
      <description>After the self-induced tumult Sonos went through last year, I can understand why some people are reluctant to spend money on the company&#8217;s products. But newly appointed CEO Tom Conrad has shown that he&#8217;s determined to get back on track and revitalize Sonos as the leading whole-home audio brand. The contentious mobile app is in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I found 5 Dyson Supersonic dupes that are almost as good as the real thing</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/roundup/best-dyson-supersonic-dupes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02OKGrglPovghQ58Lr1xXZT</guid>
      <description>Our beauty tech expert chose the top Dyson Supersonic alternatives from L'Oreal, Shark, and more. Here's what worth shopping during 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI journalism startup Symbolic.ai signs deal with Rupert Murdoch&#8217;s News Corp</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/ai-journalism-startup-symbolic-ai-signs-deal-with-rupert-murdochs-news-corp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083269</guid>
      <description>The startup claims its AI platform can help optimize editorial processes and research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kathleen Kennedy steps down as Lucasfilm president, marking a new era for the Star Wars franchise</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/kathleen-kennedy-steps-down-as-lucasfilm-president-marking-a-new-era-for-the-star-wars-franchise-003407687.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e3bbfc8-71ce-4d8c-ae6d-7d93bf3e5a1a</guid>
      <description>Kathleen Kennedy is stepping down as president of Lucasfilm. Although she will continue as a producer for several Star Wars projects, including upcoming movie The Mandalorian and Grogu, the company will now be helmed by a duo in Dave Filoni and Lynwen Brennan. It's a big changing of the guard for Star Wars fans, and marks the start of a fresh chapter for the sci-fi universe.&#160;Before taking over at Lucasfilm, Kennedy had seen great success as a producer with a couple little films you may have heard of: E.T. and Jurassic Park. She became Lucasfilm's president in 2012 when the company was acquired...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the best Apple Watch deals available right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21289209/best-apple-watch-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T19:17:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21289209/best-apple-watch-deals</guid>
      <description>In September, Apple launched its latest fleet of smartwatches, including the Apple Watch Series 11, the SE 3, and the Ultra 3. Each wearable offers something a little different (their prices indicate their breadth of features), and we&#8217;re already starting to see big price drops. Additionally, we&#8217;re still recommending some recent predecessors in Apple&#8217;s portfolio, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
