<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta's metaverse is going mobile-first</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/metas-metaverse-is-going-mobile-first-233030532.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9f078dd-ba8c-4530-ae08-b1af61348a8a</guid>
      <description>Meta is formally sectioning off Horizon Worlds, the closest thing it has to a metaverse, from its Quest VR platform, according to a new blog post from Samantha Ryan, Meta's VP of Content, Reality Labs. While the decision runs counter to Meta's original plan to own an immersive virtual world that could serve as the future home for all online interaction, it fits with the recent cuts it made to its costly Reality Labs division, and Mark Zuckerberg's public commitment to focus the company on AI hardware like smart glasses going forward.&#160;"We&#8217;re explicitly separating our Quest VR platform from our ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The executive that helped build Meta&#8217;s ad machine is trying to expose it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/881706/meta-executive-brian-boland-testimony-social-media-addiction-trial</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T18:22:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881706</guid>
      <description>Brian Boland spent more than a decade figuring out how to build a system that would make Meta money. On Thursday, he told a California jury it incentivized drawing more and more users, including teens, onto Facebook and Instagram - despite the risks. Boland's testimony came a day after Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg took the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An FBI &#8216;Asset&#8217; Helped Run a Dark Web Site That Sold Fentanyl-Laced Drugs for Years</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/an-fbi-asset-helped-run-a-dark-web-site-that-sold-fentanyl-laced-drugs-for-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6994d157b9a628d3ca165c7a</guid>
      <description>A staffer of the Incognito dark web market was secretly controlled by the FBI&#8212;and still allegedly approved the sale of fentanyl-tainted pills, including those from a dealer linked to a confirmed death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pitt has a sharp take on AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/881016/hbo-the-pitt-generative-ai-charting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T18:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881016</guid>
      <description>Each episode of HBO's The Pitt features some degree of medical trauma that almost makes the hospital drama feel like a horror series. Some patients are dealing with gnarly lacerations while others are fighting off vicious blood infections that could rob them of their limbs, and the chaos of working in an emergency room often [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Phil Lord and Chris Miller Get Shaken About for &#8216;Project Hail Mary&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/watch-phil-lord-and-chris-miller-get-shaken-about-for-project-hail-mary-2000724193</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724193</guid>
      <description>The directors break down all 12 formats the new Ryan Gosling sci-fi movie will be released in, including 4DX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL&#8217;s clever &#8216;SQD mini-LED&#8217; TV tech has arrived in its first set, and we&#8217;ve measured it &#8212; here&#8217;s how it compares to RGB TVs and OLED</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/tcls-clever-sqd-mini-led-tv-tech-has-arrived-in-its-first-set-and-weve-measured-it-heres-how-it-compares-to-rgb-tvs-and-oled</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xiJEbMJwmHEiUiGbTf8QcR</guid>
      <description>This is impressive TV tech, but it still might be a middle-ground upgrade that&#8217;s destined to be lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget the Samsung Galaxy Watch Ultra 2 &#8212; the Amazfit T-Rex Ultra 2 might be the surprise outdoor smartwatch to beat this year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/forget-the-samsung-galaxy-watch-ultra-2-the-amazfit-t-rex-ultra-2-might-be-the-surprise-outdoor-smartwatch-to-beat-this-year</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KNdF3KkFjbkRmKyibC5ubb</guid>
      <description>If Amazfit can deliver a five-star watch for under $100 / &#163;100, what can it do for five times the price? Introducing the 'expedition-focused' Amazfit T-Rex Ultra 2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens had &#8216;an addicts' narrative about their Instagram use&#8217; &#8212; Mark Zuckerberg takes stand in trail which could reshape not just social media, but his AI and Ray-Ban XR dreams</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/mark-zuckerberg-takes-stand-in-trail-which-could-reshape-not-just-social-media-but-his-ai-and-ray-ban-xr-dreams</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">B3Q5rsj5cdbesMVZhaCYmS</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg defends Meta in social media addiction trial, which could have major ramifications for online platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Apple set to turn to China for its next memory partner? Mac maker reportedly searching for new partners as negotiations get tricky</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/is-apple-set-to-turn-to-china-for-its-next-memory-partner-mac-maker-reportedly-searching-for-new-friends-as-negotiations-get-tricky</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wFYYx8HoxXSirgXTmqKXpM</guid>
      <description>Apple explores partnerships with Chinese memory manufacturers YMTC and CXMT to diversify DRAM and NAND supply amid price volatility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $10K+ bounty is waiting for anyone who can unplug Ring doorbells from Amazon&amp;#8217;s cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881678/ring-doorbell-bounty-amazon-servers-fulu</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T17:32:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881678</guid>
      <description>With Ring facing fierce backlash over its Search Party feature, a new program is challenging developers to move Ring doorbell footage off of Amazon's cloud - and into users' own devices. The Fulu Foundation, the consumer advocacy group cofounded by YouTuber Louis Rossmann, is offering an initial bounty of $10,000 to anyone who can integrate [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI says ATM &#8216;jackpotting&#8217; attacks are on the rise, and netting hackers millions in stolen cash</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/fbi-says-atm-jackpotting-attacks-are-on-the-rise-and-netting-hackers-millions-in-stolen-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094673</guid>
      <description>The FBI says hacks that trick ATMs into spitting out cash on demand are rising, with hundreds of attacks in the past year alone netting hackers millions in stolen bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At a critical moment, Snap loses a top Specs exec</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/at-a-critical-moment-snap-loses-a-top-specs-exec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094590</guid>
      <description>As Snap readies the public release of its long-awaited VR glasses, one of the key executives on the project has left the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second and last chance for innovators to win scaling perks: Belden extends nomination window</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/second-and-last-chance-for-innovators-to-win-scaling-perks-belden-extends-nomination-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094631</guid>
      <description>Last day to nominate for the 2026 Joseph C. Belden Innovation Award has been extended through February 27. Don't miss your chance to win scaling perks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult performer Siri Dahl doxxed by Grok: Go f*ck yourself you nazi clanker</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/siri-dahl-doxxed-by-grok</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06nZvnsuebgHDAUbBVfd5Fu</guid>
      <description>Adult performer Siri Dahl had her legal name and birthdate exposed by Elon Musk's AI bot Grok. She didn't hold back in punching back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NASA Chief Blames Prior Leadership for Botched Starliner Mission</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-nasa-chief-blames-prior-leadership-for-botched-starliner-mission-2000724290</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724290</guid>
      <description>Jared Isaacman said the goal of maintaining multiple means of ISS access influenced decision-making when mission and crew safety should have been the top priority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I looted 36 Cyberpunk home office upgrades for jacking into work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/i-looted-36-cyberpunk-home-office-upgrades-for-jacking-into-work</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MMKHMqs6jmQiBfJiBXmaqM</guid>
      <description>From Tier 1 components to Tier 5++ gear for your home office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Claims Obama Leaked Classified Intel When He Said Aliens Are Real</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-are-aliens-real-obama-classified-intel-2000724273</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724273</guid>
      <description>Lara Trump recently claimed the president already has a speech prepared on UFOs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellebrite cut off Serbia citing abuse of its phone unlocking tools. Why not others?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/cellebrite-cut-off-serbia-citing-abuse-of-its-phone-unlocking-tools-why-not-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094602</guid>
      <description>Cellebrite, which makes phone unlocking and hacking tools, stopped sales to countries that allegedly abused its tools. But after new allegations in Jordan and Kenya, the company has changed its approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Green Arrow Is a Horror-Fueled Billionaire Killer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dc-comics-absolute-green-arrow-release-date-details-2000724195</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724195</guid>
      <description>DC's Absolute Universe expands with series following Green Arrow and Catwoman, plus the first-ever Absolute Universe event miniseries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It seems Microsoft just started work on Windows 11 27H2 &#8212; and this could be the update that saves the OS... or dooms it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/it-seems-microsoft-just-started-work-on-windows-11-27h2-and-this-could-be-the-update-that-saves-the-os-or-dooms-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pyGnYdYDnkTiEuXpaa7oF4</guid>
      <description>I just hope Microsoft delivers on the promises of greater stability and faster performance for the OS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A massive new EV study just dispelled the biggest myth about electric car batteries</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/a-massive-new-ev-survey-just-dispelled-the-biggest-myth-about-electric-car-batteries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EcvDfLbE2qw73aCnQqT9a9</guid>
      <description>The UK's largest EV Battery Performance Index proves that used car customers have little to fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Era of the $20,000 New Car Is Over</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-era-of-the-20000-new-car-is-over-2000724260</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724260</guid>
      <description>This is the first year no automaker is selling a new car for under $20,000 in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wired cover on techs gay mafia ignites controversy</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wired-cover-gay-mafia-reactions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02875s2fYArhQLMTaHeGsJF</guid>
      <description>'Wired' magazine writes about a Silicon Valley 'gay mafia' with some unusual imagery. The internet does its thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government shutdown wont affect your 2026 tax return</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/2026-government-shutdown-irs-taxes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01EsXATF2nhoz3KWed4AU9E</guid>
      <description>Things are business as usual at the IRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeywell CCTV cameras vulnerable to hijacking which allows hackers to crack passwords easily</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/honeywell-cctv-cameras-vulnerable-to-hijacking-which-allows-hackers-to-crack-passwords-easily</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CdaAoCaxxhcHGsHu5wXQwH</guid>
      <description>CISA tells Honeywell CCTV users to patch now - or risk hackers hijacking their devices.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
