<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the Irony: Microsoft&#8217;s Push for Copilot+ PCs Could Stall Laptop Sales</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsofts-push-for-copilot-plus-pcs-could-stall-laptop-sales-2000701505</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701505</guid>
      <description>Windows users can't go back to 8GB of RAM, but laptop makers may not have a choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam&#8217;s annual winter sale is here &#8212; these are the best games to get</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/846242/best-steam-winter-sale-game-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T17:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846242</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re lucky enough to have a bit of time off around the holidays, we have great news: Steam&#8217;s annual winter sale kicked off today, and will run through Monday, January 5th at 1PM ET. Now&#8217;s a great time to stock up on some of the best games of 2025 at a solid discount, or [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new &#8216;smallest&#8217; subwoofer packs deep bass into a 10-inch cube &#8211; 1 driver, 2 radiators, 25Hz, 200W of power</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/this-new-smallest-subwoofer-packs-deep-bass-into-a-10-inch-cube-1-driver-2-radiators-25hz-200w-of-power</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">p9g3GAteH4aLohpL6isaGX</guid>
      <description>IK Multimedia's small iLoud Sub promises big booms, but with accuracy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI and Anthropic will start predicting when users are underage</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847780/openai-anthropic-teen-safety-chatgpt-claude</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T16:55:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847780</guid>
      <description>OpenAI and Anthropic are making tweaks to their chatbots that they say will make them safer for teens. As OpenAI has updated its guidelines on how ChatGPT should interact with users between the ages of 13 and 17, Anthropic is working on a new way to identify if someone might be underage. On Thursday, OpenAI [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG will let you delete the previously unremovable Microsoft Copilot shortcut on its smart TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/lg-will-let-you-delete-the-previously-unremovable-microsoft-copilot-shortcut-on-its-smart-tvs-215352944.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c09589-49ec-43d9-b897-fb88b2ee50dc</guid>
      <description>Several LG smart TV owners, including some Engadget staff, were surprised to find what looked like an unremovable Microsoft Copilot app suddenly installed on their devices earlier this week. After all the raised eyebrows, a representative from LG has reached out to say that the company "will take steps to allow users to delete the shortcut icon if they wish."
According to the spokesperson, the Copilot icon is a shortcut for launching the AI chatbot in the TV's web browser rather than an application embedded in the appliance. We've asked for more specifics about when people will be able to get ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Has a New Chief. Here&#8217;s What He Could Do in His First 20 Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-has-a-new-chief-heres-what-he-could-do-in-his-first-20-days-2000701547</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701547</guid>
      <description>Newly minted NASA administrator Jared Isaacman has expressed a desire to shake things up at NASA. It appears he&#8217;ll hit the ground running.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Is Going Into the New Year With Some Real Loser Energy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-is-going-into-the-new-year-with-some-real-loser-energy-2000701439</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701439</guid>
      <description>The slop machine giveth, and the slop machine taketh away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's not just RAM getting more expensive - the tools to make chips are set to explode in cost too, experts warn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/its-not-just-ram-getting-more-expensive-the-tools-to-make-chips-are-set-to-explode-in-cost-too-experts-warn</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vKihdx5Ex3m98G5cmtJziM</guid>
      <description>Chipmakers are spending more as components become more advanced and demand for AI hardware continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugh Jackman&#8217;s New Movie Has a Bunch of Talking Sheep Solve His Murder</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hugh-jackmans-new-movie-has-a-bunch-of-talking-sheep-solve-his-murder-2000701407</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701407</guid>
      <description>What the flock is even happening in 'The Sheep Detectives'?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kia and Hyundia Could Pay Over $500 Million to Settle Viral &#8216;Kia Boys&#8217; Thefts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kia-and-hyundia-could-pay-over-500-million-to-settle-viral-kia-boys-thefts-2000701494</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701494</guid>
      <description>The automakers reached a multistate settlement after a social media trend exposed missing anti-theft protections in some of their cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram wants to limit hashtag spam</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847739/instagram-hashtag-spam-limit</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T16:16:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847739</guid>
      <description>If you're tired of seeing Instagram posts with a seemingly endless list of hashtags, Instagram is making a change to stop that. In a post today, Instagram chief Adam Mosseri said that the platform will now cap hashtags to five per post. "While I know it can be tempting to use more, a few specific [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC price update: Bitcoin, crypto market could plummet again on &#8216;Witching Friday.&#8217; Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463106/bitcoin-btc-price-update-crypto-market-could-plummet-again-on-witching-friday-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T21:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463106/bitcoin-btc-price-update-crypto-market-could-plummet-again-on-witching-friday-heres-why</guid>
      <description>Investors are bracing for December 18, when billions of options are due to expire&#8212;making for what could be a volatile roller-coaster ride for digital assets.
Bitcoin investors are bracing for &#8220;Witching Friday&#8221; tomorrow, December 18, when billions of options are due to expire&#8212;making for what could be a highly volatile, roller-coaster ride at the end of the week for the markets. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart to pay $60M to settle FTC claims it deceived consumers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/instacart-to-pay-60m-to-settle-ftc-claims-it-deceived-consumers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077553</guid>
      <description>The federal agency alleged Instacart misled consumers with unlawful tactics, causing them to pay higher fees while also denying refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best foldable phone you can buy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/635839/best-foldable-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=635839</guid>
      <description>A foldable phone isn&#8217;t for the faint of heart. They&#8217;re generally heavier, pricier, and have less capable cameras than a standard slab-style phone. They&#8217;re also still not as durable as regular smartphones, though they&#8217;re not nearly as fragile as they once were. In fact, thanks to Google, we finally have a foldable phone we can [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new report says Trump&#8217;s  ballroom will ruin the White House, but he can build it anyway</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462429/a-new-report-says-trumps-ballroom-will-ruin-the-white-house-but-he-can-build-it-anyway</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462429/a-new-report-says-trumps-ballroom-will-ruin-the-white-house-but-he-can-build-it-anyway</guid>
      <description>The National Park Service found that Trump&#8217;s planned ballroom would &#8216;adversely alter the design, setting, and feeling of the White House and the grounds over the long-term.&#8217; 
President Donald Trump&#8217;s plans to add a ballroom to the White House would be bad for the design of the White House complex and grounds, according to a National Park Service (NPS) report. The report said the annex would &#8220;disrupt the historical continuity of the White House grounds and alter the architectural integrity of the easts side of the property.&#8221; Still, Trump is clear for now to move ahead with his plans....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eli Lilly&#8217;s Experimental Pill Could Help You Ditch GLP-1 Obesity Shots, Trial Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/eli-lillys-experimental-pill-could-help-you-ditch-glp-1-obesity-shots-trial-finds-2000701348</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701348</guid>
      <description>People who switched from semaglutide or tirzepatide to orforglipron largely maintained their weight loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta AI glasses adds conversation focus feature</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/meta-ai-glasses-conversation-focus</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">014w85HyHywoIIGzCGSO7oT</guid>
      <description>A software update lets glasses wearers amplify the voice of someone they're trying to hear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;Open innovation is the foundation of AI progress&#8221; says Jensen Huang as Nvidia reveals big open source AI push - major acquisition sealed and new models on the way</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/open-innovation-is-the-foundation-of-ai-progress-says-jensen-huang-as-nvidia-reveals-big-open-source-ai-push-major-acquisition-and-new-models-on-the-way</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Bp7Z5U4m25Frzpm6d5L4A</guid>
      <description>Nvidia acquires SchedMD and launches Nemotron 3 open models, providing datasets, AI tools, and libraries for multi-agent workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG forced a Copilot web app onto its TVs but will let you delete it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847685/lg-copilot-web-app-delete</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T15:31:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847685</guid>
      <description>LG says it will let users delete the Microsoft Copilot shortcut it installed on newer TVs after several reports highlighted the unremovable icon. In a statement to The Verge, LG spokesperson Chris De Maria says the company "respects consumer choice and will take steps to allow users to delete the shortcut icon if they wish." [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&amp;#8217;s Gemini app can check videos to see if they were made with Google AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847680/google-gemini-verification-ai-generated-videos</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T15:31:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847680</guid>
      <description>Google expanded Gemini's AI verification feature to videos made or edited with the company's own AI models. Users can now ask Gemini to determine if an uploaded video is AI-generated by asking, "Was this generated using Google AI?" Gemini will scan the video's visuals and audio for Google's proprietary watermark called SynthID. The response will [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Was a Turning Point for &#8216;Star Trek&#8217;, Whether It Knew It or Not</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-2025-retrospective-section-31-strange-new-worlds-skydance-2000701013</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701013</guid>
      <description>With the 60th anniversary and the launch of a new show, 2026 is shaping up to be a vital year for 'Star Trek'&#8212;but 2025 was where the steps towards that big year really started.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
