<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:25:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>'We are helping innovate at the frontiers of what is possible, to evolve the sport and make it next generation': Lenovo tells us how it is working with FIFA to make the 2026 World Cup the smartest yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/we-are-helping-innovate-at-the-frontiers-of-what-is-possible-to-evolve-the-sport-and-make-it-next-generation-lenovo-tells-us-how-it-is-working-with-fifa-to-make-the-2026-world-cup-the-smartest-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aZsgqxE4Q3KWU38iQnFQmi</guid>
      <description>Lenovo and FIFA team up to make the 2026 World Cup the smartest and most engaging yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fight for Warner Bros. Is Paramount&#8217;s Most Embarrassing Moment Yet</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paramount-netflix-warner-bros-david-ellison-2000710809</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710809</guid>
      <description>No one should be fighting for Warner Bros., but here we are, forced to pretend Paramount's justified in pursuing an acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple really went backwards when it ditched titanium on iPhones</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/apple-really-went-backwards-when-it-ditched-titanium-on-iphones</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2YYNGiEcqjF9RvMjrQUyqC</guid>
      <description>I've already battered and bruised my iPhone 17 from the hard knocks my titanium-sporting iPhone 16 Pro Max would shrug off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nanometer-thick magnet produced at room temperature using lasers could one day produce better HDDs, faster non-silicon processors</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/nanometer-thick-magnet-produced-at-room-temperature-using-lasers-could-one-day-produce-better-hdds-faster-non-silicon-processors</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVTgWxmw4yhV9PCZmqYkrQ</guid>
      <description>Researchers show brief laser pulses can reversibly tune magnetic behavior in ultrathin materials operating at room temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TV not looking as good as you hoped? Here are 3 settings I always change to get better picture quality</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/new-tv-not-looking-as-good-as-you-hoped-here-are-3-settings-i-always-change-to-get-better-picture-quality</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6hUTo934RVKbxMC2WozjWJ</guid>
      <description>While it's easier to leave your TV in its out-of-the-box settings, you'll be rewarded with a better picture if you take a trip to the menus. Here's my top 3 to get you started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar Grit X2 review: the Grit X2 Pro in a smaller, cheaper package</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/polar-grit-x2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sok74R7Mux8HnEBXp42555</guid>
      <description>A feature-packed fitness watch let down by limited smartwatch functionality and a clunky companion app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new Netflix series starring Ed Westwick and John Hannah is a throwback to classic pirate movies &#8211; here are 3 of the cast&#8217;s guilty pleasures</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/this-new-netflix-series-starring-ed-westwick-and-john-hannah-is-a-throwback-to-classic-pirate-movies-here-are-3-of-the-casts-guilty-pleasures</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hhz77nrRVE6h9VgEAScqeP</guid>
      <description>John Hannah, Ed Westwick and Alanah Bloor reveal the pirate movies they unapologetically love &#8211; and why their new Netflix series is a &#8216;classic adventure love story for the modern day&#8217;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Nikon pulling a Canon? What the Viltrox lawsuit rumors mean for the future of Z-mount lenses</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-lenses/is-nikon-pulling-a-canon-what-the-viltrox-lawsuit-rumors-mean-for-the-future-of-z-mount-lenses</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9z2xPtQLBhbm2jexKpnCEZ</guid>
      <description>Rumors suggest that Nikon has started legal action against the Chinese lens maker Viltrox, over alleged Z-mount patent infringements. Here's what that could mean moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google restores much-missed JPEG XL format to Chromium code base - better image compression and better bandwidth are on the way</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/google-restores-much-missed-jpeg-xl-format-to-chromium-code-base-better-image-compression-and-better-bandwidth-are-on-the-way</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bzPDiJ47br8RmcrVqS3dRM</guid>
      <description>Google restored JPEG XL support in Chromium, enabling native decoding after years of industry pressure and growing adoption elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS will not release any new smartphones this year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/asus-will-not-release-any-new-smartphones-this-year-213043832.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fb175fd-b13e-4be4-985b-8280e9d884ad</guid>
      <description>ASUS appears to be shifting its business operations away from smartphones. According to translations of recent quotes from Chairman Jonney Shih, the company does not plan to release new phone models in the future. The chairman did not confirm whether smartphones would be completely phased out, but he did acknowledge that possibility. Whatever direction ASUS takes, its existing phones will continue to receive software updates and warranty assistance. Shih suggested that its future plans may include a shift into AI-related projects such as robotics or smartglasses.Previous reports hinted that AS...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I love this hidden feature on my Sony headphones, but you may not know it even exists</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/i-love-this-hidden-feature-on-my-sony-headphones-but-you-may-not-even-know-it-even-exists</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xTrxpJfrMp9XiimytVT2x3</guid>
      <description>I love this nifty feature on my Sony headphones, but a lot of users may not even know it&#8217;s there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
