<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:37:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 devs dropped a big update after sweeping The Game Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/clair-obscur-expedition-33-devs-dropped-a-big-update-after-sweeping-the-game-awards-183628313.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b93d5a9-bdea-476a-8fc8-9849a55a04d8</guid>
      <description>Sandfall Interactive, the developer of Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, knows how to ride the wave. Right after the visually stunning RPG finished dominating The Game Awards, the team dropped a free "Thank You" content update for fans.This is no minor patch. It adds a playable environment and new boss battles for late-game players. The "Thank You" update also adds new music tracks, a Photo Mode and new text and UI localizations. On top of that, you'll find quality-of-life tweaks, including improved performance on handheld PCs.Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 won a record-breaking nine categories at The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh Great, Smart Glasses That Record Everything You Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oh-great-smart-glasses-that-record-everything-you-say-2000699011</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699011</guid>
      <description>It's just audio for now, but the Mira set an icky precedent for always-on recording in smart glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The all-new Apple Watch 11 would make a great Christmas gift &#8212; and it's on sale for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/the-all-new-apple-watch-11-would-make-a-great-christmas-gift-and-its-on-sale-for-its-lowest-price-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CezhoGSXS8CUBPXqzMCP3A</guid>
      <description>The all-new Apple Watch 11 is now on sale at its lowest price ever on Walmart, making it a great gift idea and arriving before Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 34 best gifts that your teen will actually use</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/785418/best-teen-gift-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:24:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=785418</guid>
      <description>Between keeping up with TikTok trends and whatever new gadget just dropped, it's tough to know exactly what teens are into these days. Luckily, we can help. We may be older than teenagers, but many of us here at The Verge are kids at heart. Plus, we've also got a few staffers with older kids. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel, AMD accused of 'willful ignorance' in allowing chips to get to Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/intel-amd-accused-of-willful-ignorance-in-allowing-chips-to-get-to-russia</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vAQtfwH44Tc27Dm96YQmFK</guid>
      <description>The Ukrainians are suing US tech firms over Russian bombs allegedly carrying their tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Zootopia 2&#8217; Has Reached $1 Billion in Record-Breaking Time</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/zootopia-2-box-office-records-disney-2000699178</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699178</guid>
      <description>The animated Disney sequel hit the box-office milestone after just 17 days in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Translate brings real-time speech translations to any headphones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843483/google-translate-live-speech-translations-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:11:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843483</guid>
      <description>Google Translate's latest update brings live speech translations, originally available only on the Pixel Buds, to any headphones you want, with support for over 70 languages. It's rolling out today in beta and just requires a compatible Android phone with the Translate app (unlike Apple's similar feature, which requires AirPods). It's one of a few [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best stocking stuffers you can get for $50 or less</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-best-stocking-stuffers-you-can-get-for-50-or-less-130049325.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32df60b9-ebc7-4bd2-a9e6-0777477036d5</guid>
      <description>While it&#8217;s probably tempting to go all-out and give a loved one their most desired gadget this year, doing so could put a big dent in your budget. And it would be wrong to assume that you have to spend hundreds to get a good tech gift that anyone will appreciate. There are plenty of gadgets and accessories out there that don&#8217;t cost an arm and a leg and that will also make good additions to their kits. Here are some of our favorite tech gift ideas that come in at $50 or less.
Best stocking stuffers for $50 or less


























Check out the rest of our gift ideas here. This article...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman&#8217;s Eyeball-Scanning Startup Launches &#8216;Super App&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altmans-eyeball-scanning-startup-launches-super-app-2000699091</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699091</guid>
      <description>Want to chat with your friends? Please look into this orb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Rare Video of Orcas Teaming Up With Dolphins to Hunt Giant Salmon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/watch-rare-video-of-orcas-teaming-up-with-dolphins-to-hunt-giant-salmon-2000699100</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699100</guid>
      <description>The two top predators seem to be working together to track, kill, and feast on salmon, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hisenses 65-inch The Frame dupe is down to a record-low $699 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-hisense-canvas-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02t2Kqh31Gaab4FQWO6Iazu</guid>
      <description>The Hisense 65-inch Canvas TV is down to just $699.99 at Amazon, a new best price ever. That beats its Black Friday price by nearly $200.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 best gift ideas for mom this holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/802964/best-mom-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T12:45:20-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=802964</guid>
      <description>Your mom deserves the best, and we're going to help you get them something special. The right gift can make family or friend time more valuable, after all, or it can greatly enrich time spent alone. If your mom says that she has all that she needs, don't take her word for it and show [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Batch of Epstein Photos Include Bill Gates, Richard Branson, and Segway Inventor</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-batch-of-epstein-photos-include-bill-gates-richard-branson-and-segway-inventor-2000699130</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699130</guid>
      <description>President Trump is in there too, but you could probably guess that by now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hisense&#8217;s CanvasTV is a great Samsung Frame TV alternative at nearly half off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/843667/hisense-s7n-canvas-tv-tomtoc-fancycase-g05-slim-case-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T12:36:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843667</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s Frame TV is one of the coolest-looking TVs you can buy, doubling as wall art when you&#8217;re not watching &#8212;&#160; but it&#8217;s pricey. If you like the idea of a TV that displays art when not in use but is far more affordable, Hisense&#8217;s S7N CanvasTV delivers a similar vibe for a lot less, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data breach at credit check giant 700Credit affects at least 5.6 million</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/data-breach-at-credit-check-giant-700credit-affects-at-least-5-6-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075630</guid>
      <description>700Credit, a company that runs credit checks and identity verification services for auto dealerships across the U.S., had a data breach that allowed a hacker to steal names, addresses, dates of birth, and Social Security numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Translate is now better at translating slang terms and idioms using AI</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/google-translate-is-now-better-at-translating-slang-terms-and-idioms-using-ai-173428316.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45a8c511-994c-4cec-b1b4-42c2732ee35a</guid>
      <description>Google is rolling out new Gemini-assisted functionality to Search and its Translate app. It says its AI can now provide more natural and accurate text translations for phrases that have more "nuanced meanings."&#160; Translate will now take slang terms and colloquial expressions into consideration rather than provide sometimes unhelpful direct translations.
The latest update to its text translation feature is rolling out first in the US and India, translating between English and just under 20 other languages, including German, Spanish, Chinese and Arabic. It works in the Translate app for iOS and A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple loses contempt ruling appeal, but could revisit iPhone app fees</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459732/apple-loses-appeal-contempt-epic-iphone-app-fees</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T17:34:09</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459732/apple-loses-appeal-contempt-epic-iphone-app-fees</guid>
      <description>Apple continued to fight the alternative payment option in appeals before being&#160;rebuffed by the U.S. Supreme Court in January 2024.
A federal appeals court on Thursday backed a ruling that held Apple in civil contempt for brazenly defying an order designed to open its iPhone app store to other payment systems besides its own, but the decision also reopened a door for the company to collect commission from the rival options....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New MacOS malware exploits trusted AI and search tools</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/new-macos-malware-exploits-trusted-ai-and-search-tools</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42yeGSUGsXbmjuLMAGVhkH</guid>
      <description>Mac users are being targeted with AMOS again, this time through a dubious combination of malvertising and AI results poisoning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Kindles are back on sale at Amazon for holiday shoppers &#8212; prices start at $89</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-amazon-kindle-paperwhite-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03mxxDPlFlksdmjQcA5TNfd</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 12, get the Amazon Kindle Paperwhite for just $134.99. That saves you $25 off its list price. The savings aren't quite as abundant as they were on Black Friday, but it's a great last minute deal to close out the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant-Based Diets Can Work for Kids, but New Study Outlines Concerning Risks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/plant-based-diets-can-work-for-kids-but-new-study-outlines-concerning-risks-2000699057</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699057</guid>
      <description>There are several nutrients that vegan and vegetarian kids can miss out on without careful planning, a review of the evidence finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce says per-user pricing will be new AI norm</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/salesforce-says-per-user-pricing-will-be-new-ai-norm</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8SLMNvtTpt4uQpVijcm6e8</guid>
      <description>Marc Benioff expects to increase AI monetization while delivering more value for customers on their preferred pricing model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le flash de votre smartphone est nul : voici pourquoi &#231;a pourrait enfin changer avec le retour du x&#233;non</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2909257_le-flash-de-votre-smartphone-est-nul-voici-pourquoi-ca-pourrait-enfin-changer-avec-le-retour-du-xenon</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2909257_le-flash-de-votre-smartphone-est-nul-voici-pourquoi-ca-pourrait-enfin-changer-avec-le-retour-du-xenon</guid>
      <description>
Le flash LED de votre smartphone sert surtout de lampe torche pour trouver vos cl&#233;s. Pour la photo ? C'est une catastrophe. Mais Samsung travaille sur une technologie, le Global Shutter, qui pourrait ressusciter le l&#233;gendaire flash au x&#233;non. Et l&#224;, on parle de vraie photographie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ford is fighting off F-150 thieves with amped up tech</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459722/how-ford-fighting-off-f-150-thieves-amped-up-tech</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T17:22:27</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459722/how-ford-fighting-off-f-150-thieves-amped-up-tech</guid>
      <description>In 2024, Ford&#8217;s F-150 pickup truck was in the top 10 of most stolen models.
Ford Motor Co. has stepped up technology in its popular F-150 pickup to combat the ever-evolving techniques car thieves have at their disposal.It is the latest cat-and-mouse move that the automaker hopes will help customers avoid the costly and frustrating process that occurs when vehicles are swiped and includes a feature that won&#8217;t allow an engine to start even if a key fob is in the pickup.Motor vehicle thefts recently have been on the decline in the U.S. after several years of increases. Still, the National Highway...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following Rockstar Games laying off 31 GTA 6 developers, even the UK Prime Minister Sir Kier Starmer is interested now and says that Parliament will investigate the matter &#8212; 'It's a deeply concerning case'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/following-rockstar-games-laying-off-31-gta-6-developers-even-the-uk-prime-minister-sir-kier-starmer-is-interested-now-and-says-that-parliament-will-investigate-the-matter-its-a-deeply-concerning-case</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oxSJhyC5vNn7AJ4NUA94BH</guid>
      <description>UK Prime Minister Sir Kier Starmer has said that the UK Parliament will investigate union-busting allegations against Rockstar Games after the studio fired 31 Grand Theft Auto 6 developers in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not&#233; 9/10, le r&#233;cent bracelet Xiaomi Smart Band 10 est d&#233;j&#224; &#224; -25 % sur Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2842425_note-9-10-le-recent-bracelet-xiaomi-smart-band-10-est-deja-a-moins-25-pourcents-sur-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2842425_note-9-10-le-recent-bracelet-xiaomi-smart-band-10-est-deja-a-moins-25-pourcents-sur-amazon</guid>
      <description>
Accessible, pr&#233;cis dans ses mesures et &#233;l&#233;gant, le r&#233;cent Xiaomi Smart Band 10 occupe actuellement la premi&#232;re place dans notre classement des meilleurs bracelets connect&#233;s du moment. Et avec un prix qui passe de 49,99 euros &#224; 37,99 euros sur Amazon, on peut dire qu'il m&#233;rite encore plus son statut de num&#233;ro 1.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DJI Power 1000 is $350 off right now</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-dji-power-1000-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03r2hyTCdloBJWpMK7EjiVo</guid>
      <description>Right now, you can grab the DJI Power 1000 Portable Power Station for $349 at Amazon. That's a 50% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Un b&#233;n&#233;vole en Afrique &#187; : nous avons test&#233; 5 IA, le r&#233;sultat est g&#234;nant</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2909119_un-benevole-en-afrique-nous-avons-teste-5-ia-le-resultat-est-genant</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/2909119_un-benevole-en-afrique-nous-avons-teste-5-ia-le-resultat-est-genant</guid>
      <description>
Accus&#233; de pr&#233;f&#233;rence de couleur, Nano Banana Pro est-il le seule g&#233;n&#233;rateur d'images &#224; favoriser des personnes blanches ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hannibal creator Bryan Fuller wanted his first film to be horror for everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/843561/bryan-fuller-interview-dust-bunny</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T12:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843561</guid>
      <description>When Bryan Fuller set out to make his first feature film, his goal was to make the kind of family-friendly scares that he loved as a kid. Think Gremlins or Ghostbusters. The creator of Hannibal and Pushing Daisies ended up crafting a story called Dust Bunny, about a young girl named Aurora who hires a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect your business data! Get LastPass for up to 50% off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/protect-your-business-data-get-lastpass-for-up-to-50-percent-off</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VFWFszbXpKorcdFgKXUSJU</guid>
      <description>TechRadar US readers can now get up to 50% off LastPass plans - ideal for small and medium-sized businesses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need a last-minute gift? Walmart has a massive sale with deals from Apple, Ninja, Shark, Lego, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/need-a-last-minute-gift-walmart-has-a-massive-sale-with-deals-from-apple-ninja-shark-lego-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4iFdWNzPQpuTuJKfUa9jvK</guid>
      <description>Walmart has a massive weekend holiday sale on best-selling gifts, and I'm rounding up the 25 best, including AirPods, coffee makers, Lego, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring home a Roborock Qrevo S5V robot vacuum and mop for its lowest price ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-roborock-qrevo-s5v-robot-vacuum-mop-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">051bkCZYX05BFbz9BIVzJqY</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 12, get the Roborock Qrevo S5V robot vacuum and mop for its lowest price ever at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s AI executive order promises &#8216;one rulebook&#8217; &#8212; startups may get legal limbo instead</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/trumps-ai-executive-order-promises-one-rulebook-startups-may-get-legal-limbo-instead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075611</guid>
      <description>Trump signed an AI executive order targeting state laws and promising one national rulebook. Critics warn it could trigger court battles and prolong uncertainty for startups while Congress debates federal rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Max&amp;#8217;s new channels keep&#160;Friends and Game of Thrones playing 24/7</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843631/hbo-max-curated-channels-friends-harry-potter-big-bang-theory</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T12:07:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843631</guid>
      <description>HBO Max is launching curated channels, a new feature that will allow you to quickly jump into a continuous feed of a popular series or tune into a specific genre. When you select a channel on HBO Max, the streaming service will start you at the beginning of whatever's playing, while giving you the ability [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI will play an even bigger role in our love lives in 2026, experts say</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dating-trends-2026-ai-lovehoney</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03N4y5DOTxpoWy6fBdbHJz8</guid>
      <description>Lovehoney's predictions for dating and sex in 2026 include an increasing reliance on AI for advice for love and sex, and a move away from dating apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test de la ROG Xbox Ally : le Steam Deck &#224; la sauce Gamepass</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2905391_test-de-la-rog-xbox-ally-le-steam-deck-a-la-sauce-gamepass</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2905391_test-de-la-rog-xbox-ally-le-steam-deck-a-la-sauce-gamepass</guid>
      <description>
Derri&#232;re la ROG Xbox Ally X se cache la ROG Xbox Ally toute blanche, plus accessible mais aussi moins puissante. Une machine qui ne manque pas d'int&#233;r&#234;t, bien qu'elle soit focalis&#233;e sur un profil type de joueurs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Group Pays Bounties to Repair Broken Devices&#8212;Even If the Fix Breaks the Law</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/fulu-repair-bounties-nest-molekule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693c369f1106a0d083b8d942</guid>
      <description>Fulu sets repair bounties on consumer products that employ sneaky features that limit user control. Just this week, it awarded more than $10,000 to the person who hacked the Molekule air purifier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Top 42 Moments From Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and Horror TV in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-top-42-moments-from-sci-fi-fantasy-and-horror-tv-in-2025-2000698107</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698107</guid>
      <description>io9 watched a ton of TV this year&#8212;and standout scenes, shocking reveals, and sometimes entire episodes from 'Andor,' 'Dan Da Dan,' 'Pluribus,' 'Severance,' and beyond are lingering in our minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Translate now lets you hear real-time translations in your headphones</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/google-translate-now-lets-you-hear-real-time-translations-in-your-headphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075551</guid>
      <description>The real-time headphone translations experience keeps each speaker&#8217;s tone, emphasis, and cadence intact, so it&#8217;s easier to follow the conversation and tell who&#8217;s saying what.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le meilleur drone de l&#8217;ann&#233;e &#8211; Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2903177_voici-quel-est-le-meilleur-drone-de-2025-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2903177_voici-quel-est-le-meilleur-drone-de-2025-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
Le prix du meilleur drone de l'ann&#233;e 2025 est pour le DJI Neo 2. Celui-ci re&#231;oit notre Frandroid Awards de 2025 avec toutes les explications sur ce choix.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Climate Migrants Arrive in Australia, Leaving Their Sinking Island Home Behind</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hundreds-of-climate-migrants-arrive-in-australia-leaving-their-sinking-island-home-behind-2000699085</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699085</guid>
      <description>This year, thousands of Tuvaluans applied for Australia&#8217;s climate-migration visas to escape the impacts of rising sea levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola might announce a book-style foldable phone at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/motorola-book-style-foldable-teased-ces-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02SFU8yg6RhbZBliBqB51j2</guid>
      <description>Motorola might expand its foldable portfolio with a book-style smartphone in January, which would compete with Samsung and an expected foldable iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro, a photo-sharing app for friends, lets you &#8216;time-travel&#8217; through your camera roll</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/retro-a-photo-sharing-app-for-friends-lets-you-time-travel-through-your-camera-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075566</guid>
      <description>Retro's new feature, Rewind, lets you look back at your photo memories and scroll through them with a dial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 just won Game of the Year and its now 20% off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-clair-obscur-expedition-33-game-of-the-year-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00qRruWUzkxjnBX6Fzwxvf7</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 12, get 'Clair Obscur: Expedition 33' for just $39.99 at Amazon. Save $10 for 20% off on this acclaimed fantasy RPG game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doom studio id Software forms 'wall-to-wall' union, with a majority of employees voting in favor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/doom-studio-id-software-forms-wall-to-wall-union-with-a-majority-of-employees-voting-in-favor-164808829.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a359a59a-913c-474d-bb80-7ed15d3b63dc</guid>
      <description>Id Software, the company behind Doom, has voted in favor of forming a "wall-to-wall" union. The term "wall-to-wall" refers to a union that includes every employee, regardless of duties. The vote wasn't unanimous, though a majority did vote in favor of the union.
The union will work in conjunction with the Communications Workers of America (CWA), which is the same organization involved with parent company ZeniMax's recent unionization efforts. Microsoft, who owns ZeniMax, has already recognized this new effort, according to a statement by the CWA. It agreed to a labor neutrality agreement with ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quel est le meilleur aspirateur robot &#224; acheter en 2025 ? Notre guide d&#8217;achat complet</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guide-objets-connectes/616642_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-robots-aspirateurs-pour-dire-adieu-aux-corvees</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guide-objets-connectes/616642_quels-sont-les-meilleurs-robots-aspirateurs-pour-dire-adieu-aux-corvees</guid>
      <description>
Vous &#234;tes &#224; la recherche d'un bon aspirateur robot pour vous simplifier la vie? Voici notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs robots aspirateurs, tous test&#233;s et approuv&#233;s.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The TCL QM9K is an excellent flagship TV, but I&#8217;m not sure who it&#8217;s for</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/843074/tcl-qm9k-mini-led-tv-review</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843074</guid>
      <description>TCL has been a solid competitor in the midrange TV market for years, going head-to-head with Hisense. Not only are TVs from both manufacturers competitive on features, they even use similar nomenclature to categorize their TV lines - the TCL QM8 and Hisense U8, QM7 and U7, and QM6 and U6. But with TCL's new [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit sues Australia over under-16 social media ban</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/reddit-lawsuit-australia-social-media-ban</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03l3Rwb7VA7acaKWLgdxkBk</guid>
      <description>Reddit is suing Australia over its social media ban for young people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot exposed access to internal systems for a year, says researcher</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/home-depot-exposed-access-to-internal-systems-for-a-year-says-researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075593</guid>
      <description>A security researcher tried to alert Home Depot to the security lapse exposing its back-end GitHub source code repos and other internal cloud systems, but was ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile's epic iPhone 17 deal from Black Friday is still available - get four devices for free without a trade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/t-mobiles-epic-iphone-17-deal-from-black-friday-is-still-available-get-four-devices-for-free-without-a-trade</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eWCywU6QkxnpvFDVRnMPd4</guid>
      <description>Don't miss your chance to score four whole iPhone 17s for free at T-Mobile this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nakamura E-Summit 940 LTD : le VTT &#233;lectrique des randonneurs perd 600 &#8364; pour les f&#234;tes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2882753_nakamura-e-summit-940-ltd-le-vtt-electrique-des-randonneurs-perd-600-euros-pour-les-fetes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2882753_nakamura-e-summit-940-ltd-le-vtt-electrique-des-randonneurs-perd-600-euros-pour-les-fetes</guid>
      <description>
Ce sont les adeptes d'excursions en for&#234;t, ou simplement celles et ceux qui recherchent un v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique performant pour aller au travail, qui seront servis. Intersport propose en effet le puissant et endurant VTTAE Nakamura E-Summit 940 LTD &#224; 1 299,99 euros au lieu de 1 899,99 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon is giving away free Nintendo Switch consoles &#8212; heres how to qualify for the deal</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-verizon-nintendo-switch-free-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04EdttOcHfXZZySrR2S3S41</guid>
      <description>Get a free Nintendo Switch, Samsung TV, or Samsung tablet by signing up for a new Verizon home internet plan this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why AI errors are inevitable and what that means for healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458967/ai-errors-health-care-prescriptions</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T16:38:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458967/ai-errors-health-care-prescriptions</guid>
      <description>Healthcare datasets have significant overlaps that would prevent AI from being error-free.
In the past decade, AI&#8217;s success has led to uncurbed enthusiasm and bold claims&#8212;even though users frequently experience errors that AI makes. An AI-powered digital assistant can misunderstand someone&#8217;s speech in embarrassing ways, a chatbot could hallucinate facts, or, as I experienced, an AI-based navigation tool might even guide drivers through a corn field&#8212;all without registering the errors....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
