<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 22:22:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I bought a Kia EV6, my first electric car - here are 9 things I wish I'd known before buying an EV</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/i-bought-a-kia-ev6-my-first-electric-car-here-are-9-things-i-wish-id-known-before-buying-an-ev</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">txhhWHRcb7X6JPCYGLgNhN</guid>
      <description>I bought a used Kia EV6 even though I don't have charging at home. Here are the things I wish I'd known to inform my buying decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good news, I found the cheapest large-capacity PCIe Gen4 SSD per TB - bad news, it will cost you more than $58,300</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/good-news-i-found-the-cheapest-large-capacity-pcie-gen4-ssd-per-tb-bad-news-it-will-cost-you-more-than-usd58-300</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QnXjCmCLzpToFqTmby8wke</guid>
      <description>Want the cheapest large capacity PCIe Gen4 SSD per TB? You&#8217;ll need to buy ten of Solidigm&#8217;s D5-P5336 61.44TB SSD monsters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIP, &#8216;Dead Space&#8217;&#8230;.Again (2008-2023)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rip-dead-space-again-2000696495</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696495</guid>
      <description>Unless EA decides to sell off the 'Dead Space' IP to someone else, the sci-fi horror series has died a second death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X cuts off the European Commission&#8217;s ad account after being fined &#8364;120 million</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839742/x-cuts-off-the-european-commissions-ad-account</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T15:52:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839742</guid>
      <description>Friday, the EU slapped X with a &#8364;120 million fine (about $140 million) for violating the Digital Services Act (DSA). It was the first time that a company had been hit with a penalty for running afoul of the law. Elon Musk responded with his trademark tact and professionalism by posting &#8220;Bullshit&#8221; on X in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix co-CEO reportedly discussed Warner Bros. deal with Trump</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/07/netflix-co-ceo-reportedly-discussed-warner-bros-deal-with-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 20:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073671</guid>
      <description>Will Netflix&#8217;s $82.7 billion deal to acquire Warner Bros. get approval from federal regulators? While Paramount was assumed to be the frontrunner to acquire the storied movie studio thanks to CEO David Ellison&#8217;s connections to the Trump administration, new reporting in Bloomberg and The Hollywood Reporter suggests that Netflix co-CEO Ted Sarandos met with President [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lord of the Rings trilogy returns to theaters in January for 25th anniversary</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/the-lord-of-the-rings-trilogy-returns-to-theaters-in-january-for-25th-anniversary-202433217.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 20:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fff69622-0f6d-4cd9-ab62-a56888b0f7c5</guid>
      <description>One does not simply spend more than 11 hours watching The Lord of the Rings trilogy  in a single weekend at home when the opportunity to do so in theaters arises. As The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring turns 25, Fathom Entertainment and Warner Bros. announced theatrical screenings of the Peter Jackson trilogy in their extended editions, according to an exclusive report from Variety.
The re-releases will be available in DBOX presentations from January 16 to 19, complete with movements and vibrations to make you feel like you're making the journey to Mordor with Frodo and his entou...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
