<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:26:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced and all the winners at The Game Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/everything-announced-and-all-the-winners-at-the-game-awards-2025-044101761.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 04:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e683d1f8-50c7-4b51-8e47-e037f7be62d6</guid>
      <description>This year at The Game Awards, if your game wasn&#8217;t melodramatic, mechanically innovative, beautifully presented and aggressively French, it didn&#8217;t stand a chance. The Game Awards 2025 wrapped up on the evening of Thursday, December 11 with a record-breaking showing by Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 from Sandfall Interactive. The game received the most nominations and wins in the show&#8217;s 12-year history.But, we know that&#8217;s not really why you&#8217;re here. Between the award presentations and musical numbers, there were heaps of new game trailers, announcements and updates, and we&#8217;ve collected them all for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housemarque's Saros is delayed to April 30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/housemarques-saros-is-delayed-to-april-30-041813989.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 04:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d818b36d-4792-404d-90b0-9f1b845b1efb</guid>
      <description>
PlayStation had said on X that it would have news about Saros at The Game Awards, and unfortunately, fans excited for the new Housemarque project will need to wait a little longer to get their hands on it. The game has been delayed from its planned March release. But there's only a short time until the new date of April 30, and pre-orders are open now. Star Rahul Kohli appeared at The Game Awards to introduce the newest trailer for the game.&#160;
I'm glad we won't be waiting too much longer, because Saros looks very cool. Housemarque made its name on titles like Resogun and Returnal, and Saros se...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4:LOOP is a co-op shooter from the creator of Left 4 Dead and JJ Abrams' Bad Robot</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/4loop-is-a-co-op-shooter-from-the-creator-of-left-4-dead-and-jj-abrams-bad-robot-035835461.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef9c1461-5839-4a91-9ccc-1bbb8d823dc9</guid>
      <description>The next game from Left 4 Dead designer Mike Booth is putting a sci-fi spin on his last game's co-op action, based on a trailer Booth and producer JJ Abrams shared at The Game Awards 2025. The new game is called 4:LOOP, and it's the first project entirely developed by Bad Robot Games, film production company Bad Robot's game studio.
4:LOOP combines the four-player co-op action of Left 4 Dead, with roguelike elements enabled by what seems like a time loop mechanic. Based on the trailer, players fight a mixture of aliens and robots in each mission, all in the hopes of eventually drawing the atte...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: Galactic Racer is a podracing game set for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/star-wars-galactic-racer-is-a-podracing-game-set-for-2026-035508891.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d80f191-b91a-4169-9c64-2f0e193dfd28</guid>
      <description>
Why have one Star Wars game announcement at an edition of The Game Awards when you can have two? Star Wars: Galactic Racer is a podracing (and speeder racing) game from Fuse Games, a studio established in 2023 by former Burnout and Need for Speed developers. It's scheduled to hit PS5, Xbox Series X/S and PC in 2026.
The action here is set after the fall of the Empire. With the galaxy in rebuild mode after dealing with that whole mess, an unsanctioned, underground racing circuit called the Galactic League comes into being in the Outer Rim. Here, according to the game's Steam page, "syndicates ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Star Wars: Galactic Racer&#8217; Is Speeding Into Our Hearts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-galactic-racer-announcement-trailer-game-awards-2026-2000698847</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698847</guid>
      <description>Now this is podracing, among other things.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
