<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:30:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra n&#8217;est pas encore l&#224;, mais les coques de protection sont d&#233;j&#224; pr&#234;tes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2936111_le-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-nest-pas-encore-la-mais-les-coques-de-protection-sont-deja-pretes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2936111_le-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-nest-pas-encore-la-mais-les-coques-de-protection-sont-deja-pretes</guid>
      <description>
Le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra n'est pas encore officialis&#233;, mais on a d&#233;j&#224; vu des coques de protection pr&#234;tes pour le smartphone, au CES 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Grok and X Still Available in App Stores?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/x-grok-app-store-nudify-csam-apple-google-content-moderation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695e909fd435a2f4643b6d47</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s chatbot has been used to generate thousands of sexualized images of adults and apparent minors. Apple and Google have removed other &#8220;nudify&#8221; apps&#8212;but continue to host X and Grok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The weirdest tech we've seen at CES 2026 so far</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-weirdest-tech-weve-seen-at-ces-2026-so-far-134056504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a400df8-3389-4aee-8595-d1a0f59b424f</guid>
      <description>The usual suspects always show up at CES &#8212; new TVs, laptops, chips, robots and the like. But CES is also a place where companies feel free to ask some very strange questions about how technology could further infiltrate our lives. For example, should your toilet analyze your poop? Should your nails change color on command?  From experimental laptops to health tech that probably didn&#8217;t need a camera, these are the weirdest gadgets we spotted at CES 2026. Also, be sure to check out our list of the best CES tech we saw this year at the show.Throne toilet computerThe Throne device perched on the s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The coolest laptops we saw at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858897/ces-2026-best-laptops-asus-dell-acer-msi-hp-lenovo-concepts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T15:20:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858897</guid>
      <description>CES is always jam-packed with new laptop announcements, acting as a barometer for the year's upcoming releases. The proofs of concept at the show display what could potentially come further in the future. 2026 will soon bring us new chip options from Intel, AMD, and Qualcomm. While I'm excited to see how the latest horse [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Is Already Rewriting the ICE Shooting in Minneapolis</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/maga-trump-rewriting-ice-shooting-minneapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695fbfb833fe679ee74ae7ec</guid>
      <description>The sanctioned government narrative of the Minneapolis shooting diverts wildly from video footage of the incident shared online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerson Smart brings offline voice control to lamps and fans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/emerson-smart-brings-offline-voice-control-to-lamps-and-fans-201500078.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">545e2238-777a-4daa-a5bf-b36d441b2d33</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you like the idea of controlling your home appliances with your voice, but aren&#8217;t super keen on a data center processing recordings of you. Fair enough. The trade-off for most smart home conveniences is relinquishing at least some of your privacy. Today at CES, I saw a line of voice-controlled home appliances from Emerson Smart that adjust power and setting via voice commands. But commands are recognized on the devices themselves, not carried through Wi-Fi and processed elsewhere. 
The huge array of smart plugs, fans, heaters and even air fryers require no app for setup and don&#8217;t need ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Will Stand Alone Outside the World&#8217;s Climate Treaty</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-us-will-stand-alone-outside-the-worlds-climate-treaty-2000707741</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707741</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday, President Trump announced he was withdrawing the U.S. from the principal treaty for international cooperation on climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget's best of CES 2026: All the new tech that caught our eye in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/engadgets-best-of-ces-2026-all-the-new-tech-that-caught-our-eye-in-las-vegas-200057123.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">289bf078-4351-4457-b4ba-74ba94fb78b6</guid>
      <description>This year, over 4,000 exhibitors descended on Las Vegas, Nevada to showcase their wares at CES, and the Engadget team was out in full force. The week started with press conferences from the biggest companies at the show, which were often a flurry of AI buzzwords, vague promises and very little in the way of hard news.&#160;More than one company even decided to forgo announcing things during their conferences to make way for more AI chatter, only to publish press releases later quietly admitting that, yes, actually, they did make some consumer technology. It's appropriate, I guess, that as we're beg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Jujustu Kaisen&#8217; Opening Is an Art History Fever Dream</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jujutsu-kaisen-jjk-culling-game-season-3-classic-art-reference-opening-theme-2000707576</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707576</guid>
      <description>Sukuna pinkies up, everyone. We're looking at all the art references sprinkled in season 3's opening sequence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US withdraws from dozens of international bodies, including climate-focused organizations</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-us-withdraws-from-dozens-of-international-bodies-including-climate-focused-organizations-195259578.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf3a3fcf-2159-49d1-9f59-4e6e17b36cba</guid>
      <description>In a new executive order, President Donald Trump has declared that the United States will withdraw from 66 international organizations and bodies, including several focused on tackling climate change. Trump made his disregard for climate change clear when he withdrew the US from the Paris climate agreement for a second time in early 2025, but these new withdrawals further confirm the second Trump administration is against global collaboration in general.Among the organizations targeted, the US will no longer participate in the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change, the Intergovernmental Pa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone 4 is the classic camera phone that retro lovers can't get enough of &#8212; but don't skip these essential security tips</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/the-iphone-4-is-the-classic-camera-phone-that-retro-lovers-cant-get-enough-of-but-dont-skip-these-essential-security-tips</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2yvsFVo2mwS7k64nREZE5</guid>
      <description>Demand for the iPhone 4 is up almost 1,000%, but using such an old handset comes with a few cyber security caveats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoLTE, 3G, itin&#233;rance Orange, satellite, 5G sur l&#8217;Apple Watch, 5G SA : le directeur c&#339;ur de r&#233;seau de Free r&#233;pond &#224; toutes nos questions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2935865_volte-3g-itinerance-orange-satellite-5g-sur-lapple-watch-5g-sa-le-directeur-reseau-de-free-repond-a-toutes-nos-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/free/2935865_volte-3g-itinerance-orange-satellite-5g-sur-lapple-watch-5g-sa-le-directeur-reseau-de-free-repond-a-toutes-nos-questions</guid>
      <description>
C'est une mise au point n&#233;cessaire. Alors que certains abonn&#233;s &#233;voquent des probl&#232;mes d'appels chez Free Mobile, nous avons interrog&#233; Pascal Mayeux, directeur du c&#339;ur de r&#233;seau. On en a profit&#233; pour poser plein d'autres questions.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing NBC on Fubo? Here's how to watch Sunday Night Football, figure skating, and more this week</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/missing-nbc-on-fubo-heres-how-to-watch-sunday-night-football-figure-skating-and-more-this-week-014052346.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7c5b935-7bd3-4149-94ef-aa50624bc67b</guid>
      <description>


  Amber Glenn is competing in the 2026 United States Figure Skating Championships this week.(Jamie Squire/Getty Images)
 

  Jamie Squire via Getty Images
 

It's been almost two months since Fubo has stopped carrying NBCUniversal-owned channels, and there's still no sign of them coming back to the streaming service. Customers have had to find alternate methods of watching Sunday Night Football, all the latest episodes of the Real Housewives franchise, and so much more because of Fubo and NBCUniversal's contract dispute, so channels like NBC, USA Network, Telemundo, and Bravo have been unav...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vantrue unveils world&#8217;s first dash cam with thermal imaging for Predator-style night vision on the move</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/vantrue-unveils-worlds-first-dash-cam-with-thermal-imaging-for-predator-style-night-vision-on-the-move</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2LMbKJk2f85yPQPkDdDLMf</guid>
      <description>Vantrue's Pilot 2 claims to be the world's first system with integrated thermal imaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Forced Copilot Into Your Life. Now It Can Accidentally Drain Your Bank Account</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsoft-forced-copilot-into-your-life-now-it-can-accidentally-drain-your-bank-account-2000707721</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707721</guid>
      <description>The agent has your wallet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three months of Audible is only $3 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/three-months-of-audible-is-only-3-right-now-193859847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>Have a hankering for some audiobooks? Audible is holding one heck of a sale right now, giving users three months of access for $3. That's a dollar per month. This is something of a winter tradition for the Amazon-owned platform and the promotion ends on January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated titles. Think of it like N...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional staff emails hacked as part of Salt Typhoon campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/congressional-staff-emails-hacked-as-part-of-salt-typhoon-campaign</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">F45DkKB4eTYDtGYUczU2im</guid>
      <description>Emails used by staff members of &#8220;powerful committees in the US House of Representatives were allegedly breached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Bird Feeders With Cameras, Tested and Reviewed (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-smart-bird-feeders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6671f1ec865e53584d1a830b</guid>
      <description>These bird feeders come with cameras and connected apps to let you see and learn about the birds in your neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTMfund&#160;has rewritten the distribution&#160;playbook for the AI era</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/gtmfund-has-rewritten-the-distribution-playbook-for-the-ai-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081272</guid>
      <description>Building software products has never been easier, so why are so many well-funded startups&#160;failing to take&#160;off no matter how good their product is? In this season finale episode of Build Mode, our guest has an answer: Startups have focused too much on product development and not enough on distribution excellence. Paul Irving is partner and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Longbow Motors shows off its Speedster EV with Donut Lab's in-wheel motors</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/ces-2026-longbow-motors-shows-off-its-speedster-ev-with-donut-labs-in-wheel-motors-192329111.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68ef9415-866e-4001-86ab-471103ee8137</guid>
      <description>As an unabashed fan of electric vehicles, even I have to admit that most of them are pretty boring. Their smooth, quiet and calm demeanors don't offer much in the way of intrinsic personality, which has led to many brands slapping on outr&#233; designs and fake engine sounds to try and dial up the excitement.To that end, a pair of offerings coming soon from UK-based EV startup Longbow Motors looks to deliver exactly that. The Speedster and Roadster are high-performance electric machines built using advanced in-wheel motors from Donut Labs. Those motors and a bespoke design enable an astonishing cur...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will now let you filter Shorts out of search results</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/858867/youtube-shorts-search-results-filter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T14:22:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858867</guid>
      <description>As part of a few changes to its search filters, YouTube is going to allow you to search specifically for Shorts or longform videos. Right now, a filter-less search shows a mix of longform and short form videos, which can be annoying if you just want to see videos in one format or the other. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok will broadcast some unknown portion of the 2026 World Cup live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/tiktok-will-broadcast-some-unknown-portion-of-the-2026-world-cup-live-192035507.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f53d1360-f0ba-45ac-9f16-b0f1a7ca3b0a</guid>
      <description>TikTok and FIFA are teaming up for World Cup matches. On Thursday, FIFA said its media partners will be able to broadcast &#8220;parts of matches&#8221; on the social platform. The &#8220;preferred platform&#8221; partnership will run through the end of 2026.How long the live clips will be is anyone&#8217;s guess because &#8220;parts of matches&#8221; is as specific as the announcement got. We emailed TikTok for clarification and will update this story if we learn more.FIFA said the collaboration is designed to bring fans "closer to the action.&#8221; Getting more to the point, TikTok's global head of content said live sports on the platfor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Using AI to Unmask the ICE Agent Who Killed Renee Good</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stop-using-ai-to-unmask-the-ice-agent-who-killed-renee-good-2000707575</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707575</guid>
      <description>One X user had Grok put a bikini on an image of her dead body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics pan spyware maker NSO&#8217;s transparency claims amid its push to enter US market</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/critics-pan-spyware-maker-nsos-transparency-claims-amid-its-push-to-enter-us-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080919</guid>
      <description>The infamous spyware maker released a new transparency report claiming to be a responsible spyware maker, without providing insight into how the company dealt with problematic customers in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 ways Trump&#8217;s proposed institutional single-family homebuying ban could affect the housing market</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471458/housing-market-institutional-homebuying-ban-trump-single-family-homes-sfr</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T19:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471458/housing-market-institutional-homebuying-ban-trump-single-family-homes-sfr</guid>
      <description>On a national level, &#8220;large investors&#8221;&#8212;those owning at least 100 single-family homes&#8212;own only about 1% of the total U.S. single-family housing stock. That said, this share varies widely across the country.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it even worth mentioning that Elon Musk blew past his own Full Self-Driving goals again?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/858782/elon-musk-tesla-fsd-unsupervised-missed-goals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T14:13:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858782</guid>
      <description>Last year, Tesla defied its critics by boldly launching a robotaxi service that, by the end of the year, required no human supervision and was available to over 50 percent of the US population. At least that's what Tesla CEO Elon Musk told us would happen by the end of 2025. The reality, of course, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Brown University students documented a campus shooting online in real time</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471460/brown-university-students-campus-shooting-sidechat-real-time</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T19:10:23</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471460/brown-university-students-campus-shooting-sidechat-real-time</guid>
      <description>An Associated Press analysis of nearly 8,000 posts from the 36 hours after the shooting shows how social media has become central to&#160;how students navigate campus emergencies.
When a gunman began&#160;firing inside an academic building&#160;on the Brown University campus, students didn&#8217;t wait for official alerts warning of trouble. They got information almost instantly, in bits and bursts &#8212; through phones vibrating in pockets, messages from strangers, rumors that felt urgent because they might keep someone alive....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD will launch its first PC in 2026, and it will compete with a very familiar brand &#8212; Ryzen AI Halo will go head-to-head against Nvidia's DGX Spark mini PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amd-will-launch-its-first-pc-in-2026-and-it-will-compete-with-a-very-familiar-brand-ryzen-ai-halo-will-go-head-to-head-against-nvidias-dgx-spark-mini-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4wGw6HatMqSZzzg3VBZLzm</guid>
      <description>AMD&#8217;s Ryzen AI Halo PC launches in 2026 to compete directly with Nvidia DGX Spark mini PC for local AI workloads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EverNitro is simplifying the process of crafting silky nitro coffee at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/evernitro-is-simplifying-the-process-of-crafting-silky-nitro-coffee-at-ces-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081291</guid>
      <description>EverNitro is positioning itself against competitors such as NitroBrew as a long-term more affordable all-in-one solution. &#8220;We offer the quality of a commercial tap with the footprint of a coffee maker. While others sell you gas, we give you technology to harvest it for free,&#8221; founder and CEO Terry Tan said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few pairs of budget earbuds deliver like Nothing&#8217;s Ear (a), which are down to $59</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/858740/nothing-ear-a-wireless-earbuds-cmf-headphone-pro-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T14:05:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858740</guid>
      <description>The new year has brought a wave of deals on wireless earbuds and headphones, from the fitness-focused Beats Powerbeats Fit to the open-ear Shokz OpenRun Pro. Now, Nothing has joined in with a sale of its own, offering the Nothing Headphone (1), CMF Headphone Pro, and Nothing Ear (3) earbuds at their lowest prices to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched LG&#8217;s new home robot CLOid do laundry but I have questions</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/i-watched-lgs-new-home-robot-cloid-do-laundry-but-i-have-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080689</guid>
      <description>CES is always chock-full of robots, and this year electronics giant LG announced a new bot, dubbed CLOid, that it claims will revolutionize household chores (as in, you won't have to do them anymore).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Dogs Can Learn New Words by Snooping in Our Conversations, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/some-dogs-can-learn-new-words-by-snooping-in-our-conversations-study-finds-2000707107</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707107</guid>
      <description>Gifted word learner dogs seem capable of eavesdropping about as well as 18-month-old toddlers, the study researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Bose Noise-Canceling Earbuds Are $50 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-earbuds-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695feb1668e04b04f2497df3</guid>
      <description>With top-quality noise reduction and advanced spatial audio support, these earbuds might come for your AirPods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Ahead in Superheroes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-year-ahead-in-superheroes-2000705170</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705170</guid>
      <description>The superpowered (and those who love and/or hate them) are poised to have a blockbuster 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Devices Are Coming. Will Your Favorite Apps Be Along for the Ride?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-amazon-operating-system-ai-apps-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695c1d17b8d433ee584443c1</guid>
      <description>Tech companies are calling AI the next platform. But some developers are reluctant to let AI agents stand between them and their users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce que vous voyez briller si fort en ce moment n&#8217;est pas une &#233;toile, et il ne faut pas rater &#231;a</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-ce-vous-voyez-briller-si-fort-ce-moment-nest-pas-etoile-il-ne-faut-pas-rater-ca-129876/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:57:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-ce-vous-voyez-briller-si-fort-ce-moment-nest-pas-etoile-il-ne-faut-pas-rater-ca-129876/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le 10 janvier, la plan&#232;te Jupiter sera &#224; l'opposition, ce qui signifie qu'elle sera align&#233;e avec la Terre, &#224; l'oppos&#233;&#160;du Soleil, et donc beaucoup plus facilement rep&#233;rable dans le ciel nocturne. L'occasion de voir au mieux la g&#233;ante gazeuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best deals on 4K TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22371561/best-4k-tv-deals-sale-lg-samsung-sony-tcl</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T13:50:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22371561/best-4k-tv-deals-sale-lg-samsung-sony-tcl</guid>
      <description>Things are looking bright for those who want to nab a great TV in 2026 at a substantial discount. Even though the year&#8217;s biggest, brightest, and priciest TVs were announced at CES 2026, there&#8217;s usually a great deal happening on a mid- or high-end TV from LG, Sony, Hisense, or Samsung. With the Super Bowl [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best soundbars of CES 2026: Dolby Atmos FlexConnect, Audio by Bang &amp; Olufsen, and Icelandic volcanoes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/the-best-soundbars-of-ces-2026-dolby-atmos-flexconnect-audio-by-bang-and-olufsen-and-icelandic-volcanoes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hh9krXnzaS2T9YhxapYaMK</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 showcased a handful of interesting soundbars, including the LG H7, the first model with Dolby Atmos FlexConnect support</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet collapses in Iran amid protests over economic crisis</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/internet-collapses-in-iran-amid-protests-over-economic-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081251</guid>
      <description>Internet monitoring firms and experts say Iran&#8217;s internet has almost completely shut down, as protests spread through major cities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
