<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:22:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet to buy Intersect Power to bypass energy grid bottlenecks</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/alphabet-to-buy-intersect-power-to-bypass-energy-grid-bottlenecks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078399</guid>
      <description>Alphabet is set to pay $4.75 billion in cash, plus debt, for the data center and clean energy developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT &#8216;Wrapped&#8217; Is a Good Reminder to Check Your Privacy Settings</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openais-chatgpt-wrapped-is-a-good-reminder-to-check-your-settings-2000702643</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702643</guid>
      <description>A chatbot never forgets (unless you opt out of memories).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out, Nvidia - Qualcomm acquires Alphawave Semi in latest addition to its AI data center push</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/watch-out-nvidia-qualcomm-acquires-alphawave-semi-in-latest-addition-to-its-ai-data-center-push</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aXVJRwm9TcEU4VisxyPmn3</guid>
      <description>Qualcomm completes Alphawave Semi acquisition early, strengthening connectivity capabilities while advancing its strategy for scalable AI data center platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Weather Map Predicts Record-Breaking Heat Across the US</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/christmas-weather-map-predicts-record-breaking-heat-across-the-us-2000702663</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702663</guid>
      <description>In some areas, the weather could feel more like May than late December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The Mighty Nein&#8217; Wants You to Know Everyone&#8217;s Big Secrets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-mighty-nein-wants-you-to-know-everyones-big-secrets-2000702352</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702352</guid>
      <description>The creators of the Prime Video series explain why character-specific changes and reveals diverge from the source material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TechRadar Gaming's favorite gaming devices of 2025: personal picks from all the year's gear</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/techradar-gamings-favorite-gaming-devices-of-2025-personal-picks-from-all-the-years-gear</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NFoaeaAHEtWxXvrQ5PKco7</guid>
      <description>Read all about TechRadar Gaming's hardware products of the year right here, including everything from consoles to headsets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty, Titanfall developer Vince Zampella has died at age 55</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849297/vince-zampella-dies-call-of-duty-titanfall-respawn-battlefield</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T15:57:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849297</guid>
      <description>Vince Zampella, who had a major hand in developing franchises like Medal of Honor, Call of Duty, and Battlefield, died in a car crash on Sunday, NBC Los Angeles reports. He was 55. NBC Los Angeles and CBS Los Angeles report California Highway Patrol responded to a single-car crash at around 12:45PM local time on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin halts 6 GW of offshore wind leases again</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/trump-admin-halts-6-gw-of-offshore-wind-leases-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078391</guid>
      <description>The move is the latest attempt by the Trump administration to delay the construction of 6 gigawatts of offshore wind near a hotspot of data center development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase buys The Clearing Company, doubling down on prediction markets</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465133/coinbase-clearing-company-prediction-markets</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T20:47:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465133/coinbase-clearing-company-prediction-markets</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, Coinbase launched its prediction markets platform.
Coinbase said on Monday it will buy prediction markets startup The Clearing Company, its tenth acquisition this year, as the crypto exchange looks to expand beyond its core digital assets business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty co-creator Vince Zampella killed in a car crash</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/call-of-duty-co-creator-vince-zampella-killed-in-a-car-crash-204046354.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d15b9ff-7ec9-4fc2-b968-425b5f8477e6</guid>
      <description>Game developer Vince Zampella, known for his work on many popular first-person shooter franchises, has died. According to Los Angeles news channel NBC4, Zampella was killed in a single-vehicle car crash on Sunday along with one other unnamed person. He was 55.Zampella has helmed several well-known first-person shooter titles. He was a founder of Infinity Ward, where he was a creator of the Call of Duty series. Zampella remained at the company for the launch of the hugely popular franchise's first few installments. In 2010, he co-founded Respawn Entertainment, the studio behind Titanfall, Titan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Magnetic Cloak Could Make Sensitive Tech Practically Invisible</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/proposed-magnetic-cloak-could-make-sensitive-tech-practically-invisible-2000702571</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702571</guid>
      <description>The cloak can shield objects of any shape from unwanted noise, the researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart Says It Is Pulling the Plug on Its AI-Powered Price Tests</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/instacart-says-it-is-pulling-the-plug-on-its-ai-powered-price-tests-2000702649</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702649</guid>
      <description>After an investigation found some customers were charged nearly 25% more for identical items, Instacart says it&#8217;s ending its controversial price-testing program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco power outage brings Waymo robotaxis to a standstill</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91464879/san-francisco-power-outage-brings-waymo-robotaxis-to-a-standstill</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T20:09:21</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91464879/san-francisco-power-outage-brings-waymo-robotaxis-to-a-standstill</guid>
      <description>A substation fire knocked out traffic lights across the city, leaving autonomous cars frozen at intersections and clogging streets.
When a major power outage left tens of thousands of San Francisco residents in the dark weekend, the city&#8217;s fleet of high tech self-driving vehicles went offline too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite the &#8216;M3GAN&#8217; Sequel&#8217;s Big Bust, Blumhouse Notched a Billion-Dollar Year for Horror</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/despite-the-m3gan-sequels-big-bust-blumhouse-notched-a-billion-dollar-year-for-horror-2000702585</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702585</guid>
      <description>Even with a so-so showing for 'M3GAN 2.0,' the Blumhouse-Atomic Monster alliance ended up having a fantastic 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration suspends 5 offshore wind projects, citing national security risks</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465120/trump-administration-suspends-5-offshore-wind-projects-east-coast</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465120/trump-administration-suspends-5-offshore-wind-projects-east-coast</guid>
      <description>Wind supporters called the administration&#8217;s actions illegal.
The Trump administration on Monday suspended leases for five large-scale offshore wind projects under construction along the East Coast due to what it said were national security risks identified by the Pentagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount renews bid for Warner Bros, ensuring $40B Larry Ellison backing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/paramount-renews-bid-for-warner-bros-ensuring-40-billion-larry-ellison-backing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078323</guid>
      <description>It's the latest attempt by one major Hollywood superpower to acquire another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ fans express disappointment in Nicki Minaj after she appears with Erika Kirk at Turning Point USA event</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91464983/nicki-minaj-erika-kirk-turning-point-usa-queer-fans-express-disappointment</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T19:47:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91464983/nicki-minaj-erika-kirk-turning-point-usa-queer-fans-express-disappointment</guid>
      <description>The star, who once positioned herself as a queer ally, is generating quite an intense reaction from fans who feel betrayed. Here&#8217;s why.
Over the weekend, rapper Nicki Minaj made a surprise appearance at Turning Point USA&#8217;s AmericaFest convention, where she praised President Donald Trump and Vice President J.D. Vance, mocked California Governor Gavin Newsom, and instructed listeners, &#8220;If you are born a boy, be a boy.&#8221; ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin does cultural diplomacy in a dive bar</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/849133/pubkey-dc-opening-bitcoin-bar</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T14:43:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849133</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin culture, by nature, is anarchical and chaotic. It has to be, given the nature of Bitcoin itself and the people who adopted it: free-market libertarians who've gone all in on turning computer code into a form of money divorced from central banks, government intervention, and traceability. In short, it's the exact opposite culture of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Justice Department Released More Epstein Files&#8212;but Not the Ones Survivors Want</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-justice-department-just-released-more-epstein-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">694594efd2ae1c7afe304d3d</guid>
      <description>The DOJ says it still has &#8220;hundreds of thousands&#8221; of pages to review, as the latest Epstein files release spurred more pushback from Democratic lawmakers and other critics of the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banksy unveils a new mural in London</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465110/banksy-new-murals-art-london-stargazing</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T19:42:25</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465110/banksy-new-murals-art-london-stargazing</guid>
      <description>While his work is often critical of government policy on migration and war, the latest artwork did not seem to carry an overt political message.
Elusive street artist&#160;Banksy&#160;appeared to confirm Monday that a new mural in London, depicting two children lying down and pointing up at the sky, is his latest work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large External SSDs are now cheaper than internal ones as 4TB SATA SSD face extinction due to negligible price difference</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/large-external-ssds-are-now-cheaper-than-internal-ones-as-4tb-sata-ssd-face-extinction-due-to-negligible-price-difference</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sRnrPeszvppmPJSTesuFdS</guid>
      <description>External 4TB SSDs costing less than internal SATA models shows shifting NAND priorities and increasing market pressures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate library rips 86 million of the most popular songs on Spotify</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849141/spotify-scrape-attack-breach-annas-archive-music-300tb-download</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T14:23:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849141</guid>
      <description>Spotify says it has launched new protections against "anti-copyright attacks" after the open-source library / pirate activist group Anna's Archive announced it's ripped 86 million songs from the platform that it plans to make available in torrents, as reported earlier by Billboard. According to the group, "We have archived around 86 million songs from Spotify, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
