<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:23:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 1977 cut of Star Wars will return to theaters in 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/the-1977-cut-of-star-wars-will-return-to-theaters-in-2027-221113091.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b1caa18-52fb-4fd0-818b-67439ba88ca6</guid>
      <description>Here's some good news for the "Han shot first" crowd. The original cut of Star Wars (1977), the film known today as A New Hope, is coming back to theaters. We first learned in August that some version of the film would be screened again in 2027 for its 50th anniversary. But we know now this will indeed be the version everyone saw before George Lucas made those questionable, CGI-heavy changes in the 1997 Special Editions. The re-release arrives in theaters on February 19, 2027.In a short update posted Friday on the official Star Wars website, Lucasfilm all but clarified that this will be the or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the big leagues, Netflix</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/839480/netflix-warner-bros-acquisition-hbo-theatrical-releases-layoffs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T17:02:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839480</guid>
      <description>Warner Bros. has an infamous history of being bought by other companies and then quickly ending up back on the market after its new owners realize how difficult it is to capitalize on a legacy production studio's assets. Those challenges are part of what doomed WB's mergers with AOL and AT&amp;T, who bought the studio [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Studios Is Trying to Move to Other Theme Parks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dc-studios-universal-theme-park-negotations-2000696312</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696312</guid>
      <description>DC-themed rides are now currently in Six Flags parks, but that may change. Could Universal scoop them up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS needs you to believe in AI agents</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/aws-needs-you-to-believe-in-ai-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3073407</guid>
      <description>AWS announced a wave of new AI agent tools at re:Invent 2025, but can Amazon actually catch up to the AI leaders? While the cloud giant is betting big on enterprise AI with its third-gen chip and database discounts that got developers cheering, it&#8217;s still fighting to prove it can compete beyond infrastructure.&#160; This week [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds find more complaints of Tesla&#8217;s FSD running red lights and crossing lanes</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/feds-find-more-complaints-of-teslas-fsd-running-red-lights-and-crossing-lanes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073463</guid>
      <description>The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration has identified at least 80 incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia Has Its Own Version of &#8216;Wrapped&#8217; Now, But There&#8217;s One Little Problem</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wikipedia-has-its-own-version-of-wrapped-now-but-theres-one-little-problem-2000696361</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696361</guid>
      <description>The online encyclopedia is offering personalized stats on users' reading habits, along with a list of the year&#8217;s most-read articles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science says these Christmas songs tank productivity at work</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455739/science-says-these-christmas-songs-tank-productivity-at-work</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455739/science-says-these-christmas-songs-tank-productivity-at-work</guid>
      <description>Do you hear what I hear, indeed.
It&#8217;s the first week in December. If you don&#8217;t already have the Christmas tunes blasting in the office, what are you waiting for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC panel overturns 1991 newborn vaccine policy, triggering warnings of a public health backslide</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455886/cdc-panel-overturns-1991-newborn-vaccine-policy-triggering-warnings-of-a-public-health-backslide</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455886/cdc-panel-overturns-1991-newborn-vaccine-policy-triggering-warnings-of-a-public-health-backslide</guid>
      <description>Members appointed under RFK Jr. argued universal guidance was too broad, while medical groups said the change jeopardizes decades of near-eradication.
A powerful advisory group within the CDC voted Friday to overturn a longstanding precaution designed to protect newborn babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta's latest acquisition suggests hardware plans beyond glasses and headsets</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/metas-latest-acquisition-suggests-hardware-plans-beyond-glasses-and-headsets-212930339.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fdc07f4-40aa-4b0e-8f22-de045ef52f74</guid>
      <description>Meta has acquired Limitless, the maker of an AI-powered "Pendant," to work on building consumer hardware for the company, the startup announced via a YouTube video and blog post. So far, Meta has focused on selling VR headsets and AI smart glasses. Now the company seems interested in branching out."Meta recently announced a new vision to bring personal superintelligence to everyone and a key part of that vision is building incredible AI-enabled wearables. We share this vision and we'll be joining Meta to help bring our shared vision to life," Limitless CEO Dan Siroker said in the post announci...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brace Yourself: Laptops Prices Are About to Skyrocket</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/laptops-prices-are-about-to-skyrocket-2000696366</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696366</guid>
      <description>Dell says it will take 'targeted pricing action, when necessary.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This startup built a Fitbit for your brain to combat chronic stress</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/this-startup-built-a-fitbit-for-your-brain-to-combat-chronic-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073409</guid>
      <description>Forenza collaborated with data scientists and biomedical engineers to develop Awear, a small device worn behind the ear for continuous brainwave monitoring. The device transmits results to an app, which provides information about the wearer&#8217;s mood and offers AI-powered coaching advice for managing stress and improving emotional resilience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX reportedly in talks for secondary sale at $800B valuation, which would make it America&#8217;s most valuable private company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/spacex-reportedly-in-talks-for-secondary-sale-at-800b-valuation-which-would-make-it-americas-most-valuable-private-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073436</guid>
      <description>The eye-popping figure reflects how routine mega-valuations have become in private markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta acquires AI device startup Limitless</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/meta-acquires-ai-device-startup-limitless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073443</guid>
      <description>Limitless said it shares Meta's vision of bringing personal superintelligence to everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Telescope&#8217;s Final Data Release Just Killed 30 Cosmological Theories</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-telescopes-final-data-release-just-killed-30-cosmological-theories-2000696247</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696247</guid>
      <description>The Atacama Cosmology Telescope in Chile not only confirmed one of the greatest mysteries in the universe&#8212;it also ruled out dozens of models that attempted to solve it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Renegades&#8217; Is Good &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; and Pretty Okay &#8216;Destiny 2&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/destiny-2-renegades-impressions-star-wars-bungie-2000696304</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696304</guid>
      <description>Bungie and Lucasfilm's intriguing new collaboration nails the 'Star Wars' vibe, but if you're looking to hop in from one galaxy far, far away to another closer to home... it's still 'Destiny 2', warts and all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chamberlain blocks smart home integrations with its garage door openers &#8212; again</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/839294/chamberlain-myq-garage-door-opener-update-blocks-aftermarket-controllers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839294</guid>
      <description>Garage door opener manufacturer The Chamberlain Group has launched a new version of the communication platform that powers its connected garage door openers - and it's bad news for smart home users. The new Security+ 3.0 platform, launching alongside Chamberlain's latest openers, shuts down the workarounds that third-party accessory makers such as Tailwind, Meross, and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Est-ce que l&#8217;algorithme de LinkedIn est sexiste&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-05/est-ce-que-l-algorithme-de-linkedin-est-sexiste.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">964ac59b61323cf186e5755e39ecf304</guid>
      <description>Des femmes ont tent&#233; l&#8217;exp&#233;rience d&#8217;apporter des modifications bien pr&#233;cises &#224; leur compte LinkedIn&#160;: elles ont ajout&#233; une moustache &#224; leur photo de profil et elles ont d&#233;coch&#233; le genre f&#233;minin pour choisir le f&#233;minin. R&#233;sultat&#160;: le r&#233;seau social les aurait soudainement valoris&#233;es. Son algorithme est-il sexiste&#160;?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horses, the Most Controversial Game of the Year, Doesn&#8217;t Live Up to the Hype</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/horses-the-most-controversial-game-of-the-year-doesnt-live-up-to-the-hype/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693339bf552b8eac14afb2b2</guid>
      <description>First it was banned. Then its sales blew up. But Horses fails to meet the lofty goals of its own ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Gehry, world-renowned architect, dies at 96</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455963/frank-gehry-dies-guggenheim-disney</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455963/frank-gehry-dies-guggenheim-disney</guid>
      <description>The Canadian American was awarded every major prize architecture has to offer, including the field&#8217;s top honor, the&#160;Pritzker Prize.
Frank Gehry, who designed some of the most imaginative buildings ever constructed and achieved a level of worldwide acclaim seldom afforded any architect, has died. He was 96.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars&#8217; original theatrical cut returns to theaters in 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839434/disney-star-wars-original-theatrical-cut-theaters-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T15:44:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839434</guid>
      <description>Disney is bringing a &#8220;newly restored version&#8221; of the original, 1977 theatrical cut of Star Wars back to theaters on February 19th, 2027. It will only be available in theaters for &#8220;a limited time,&#8221; Disney says, and it&#8217;s being released as part of &#8220;Lucasfilm&#8217;s yearlong 50th anniversary celebration&#8221; for the franchise. Tickets aren&#8217;t on sale [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying Warner Bros. Gives Netflix What It&#8217;s Always Needed: An Identity</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/netflix-warner-bros-acquisition-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693315620ff840aee08aa423</guid>
      <description>The $83 billion deal gives the streamer a century&#8217;s worth of prestige television and movies, from Batman movies to Game of Thrones. It also ends the streaming wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel owners: You can now use your phone as a Switch 2 webcam</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/pixel-owners-you-can-now-use-your-phone-as-a-switch-2-webcam-203407555.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5622f3c-34e7-4d53-8b3f-cbc837ee2175</guid>
      <description>The Switch 2's lack of a built-in camera means you need an external one for GameChat video calls. But now, if your phone is a Google Pixel, you don't even need one of those. Android Authority reported on Friday that the two now work nicely together (without needing third-party apps), and our tests confirm that.Google has technically supported the use of Android devices as external webcams for two years: The company added it in a quarterly update for Android 14. (Specifically, it added the ability for devices to use USB Video Class mode, or UVC.) But that functionality didn't work with the Swit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s Chatbot Will Provide AI-Powered Live News via CNN, Fox News</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/metas-chatbot-will-provide-ai-powered-live-news-via-cnn-fox-news-2000696248</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696248</guid>
      <description>Meet your new news anchor, Meta AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban&#160;mining is a smarter path to mineral independence</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455037/urban-mining-is-a-smarter-path-to-mineral-independence</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455037/urban-mining-is-a-smarter-path-to-mineral-independence</guid>
      <description>The next gold rush for rare earth elements is in our homes and in landfills. 
In&#160;South&#160;Korea&#160;several&#160;weeks ago, the U.S. and China came to a&#160;temporary agreement, in which&#160;they&#8217;ll&#160;kick a rare-earth can down the road.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Swords' debut title is a $25 'noir action game' coming next year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/liquid-swords-debut-title-is-a-25-noir-action-game-coming-next-year-215544328.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f447bf60-40dd-46ba-b48d-b318d12eb2a8</guid>
      <description>The debut game from Liquid Swords will arrive in early 2026, it was announced at today's PC Gaming Show. Samson: A Tyndalston Story is billed as "a consequence-heavy noir action game" by its developer, and focuses on the eponymous Samson McCray, a man who's got himself into serious debt in a city that doesn&#8217;t seem particularly forgiving.&#160;
The debut trailer doesn&#8217;t give too much away in terms of story, but I&#8217;m getting gritty Max Payne-y vibes. Combat looks crunchy and visceral, and it sounds like Liquid Swords is going for an oppressive atmosphere. "Samson is built on a simple, brutal truth: ev...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
