<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:26:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Videos of ICE Agents Eating Shit in the Brutal Minneapolis Winter</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-best-video-supercuts-ice-agents-falling-in-minneapolis-winter-2000711134</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711134</guid>
      <description>Watch out for that ice, you fascist clowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok quietly launches a micro drama app called &#8216;PineDrama&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/tiktok-quietly-launches-a-micro-drama-app-called-pinedrama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083493</guid>
      <description>Think TikTok, but every single video you come across is a short episode of a fictional story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Favorite Compact Power Station Is on Sale for 33% Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/jackery-explorer-300-plus-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696a7befb12ced811baf1873</guid>
      <description>This little power station can keep your stuff topped up, plus you can save some cash on solar panels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These cheap JBL earbuds offer all-day battery life and cost less than $30</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/these-jbl-vibe-beam-earbuds-offer-all-day-battery-life-and-cost-less-than-usd30</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gtvFaGk44DLpYnB2TQYiTE</guid>
      <description>The JBL Vibe Beam are a super-cheap pair of earbuds that offer excellent battery life &#8212; and they're now down to a great low price on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Mid-Atlantic governors want tech companies to pay for new power plants</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863620/data-centers-ai-power-auction-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T15:51:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863620</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration and a bipartisan group of governors are pressuring the PJM Interconnection, the biggest electricity market in the US, to hold a power auction meant to spur a massive buildout of new power plants. Together, they're "urging" PJM to hold an "emergency" auction for companies to procure electricity over 15-year contracts. The unusually [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA rules that xAI&#8217;s natural gas generators were illegally used</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/epa-rules-that-xais-natural-gas-generators-were-illegally-used/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083507</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's AI company had installed and operated 35 natural gas turbines without permits, something the EPA now says was illegal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Love That Holly Hunter Can&#8217;t Sit in a Chair Normally on &#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-holly-hunter-chairs-2000710852</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710852</guid>
      <description>Hunter's new 'Star Trek' captain is taking the Riker maneuver to a whole new level of chair-clambering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Is Really Mad That Ryanair&#8217;s CEO Doesn&#8217;t Want Starlink on His Planes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-is-really-mad-that-ryanairs-ceo-doesnt-want-starlink-on-his-planes-2000711149</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711149</guid>
      <description>&#8220;I would pay no attention whatsoever to Elon Musk. He's an idiot. Very wealthy, but he's still an idiot.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavlink WL-UTD58 review: this sleek Thunderbolt 5 dock upgraded my studio setup, but there&#8217;s one thing missing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/wavlink-wl-utd58-thunderbolt-5-dock-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jZuFk82AJNQBLqNxFe5XXn</guid>
      <description>The Wavlink WL-UTD58 is a premium Thunderbolt 5 docking station and an ideal solution for anyone working in the creative sector. The dock features a good selection of ultrafast Thunderbolt 5 ports, offering fast data delivery and 140W PD, making this a great choice for both laptop and desktop use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft, Meta, and Amazon are paying up for &#8216;enterprise&#8217; access to Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-meta-and-amazon-are-paying-up-for-enterprise-access-to-wikipedia</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EDWPgWYUvbPNM4rSySmNa5</guid>
      <description>Wikipedia reminds us how important it is for AI training, which is why many tech firms pay for enterprise subscriptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite blocks creators from selling prize wheel spins</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863597/fortnite-creators-steal-the-brainrot-prize-wheel-spins-block</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T15:20:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863597</guid>
      <description>Epic Games is making a big change to the rules for Fortnite creators just days after allowing them to publish experiences with in-game transactions. Beginning January 20th, experiences - which Epic Games calls "islands" - will not be able to offer in-island transactions as "a 'spin' or 'increased luck' for a prize wheel," according to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From OpenAI&#8217;s offices to a deal with Eli Lilly &#8212; how Chai Discovery became one of the flashiest names in AI drug development</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/from-openais-offices-to-a-deal-with-eli-lilly-how-chai-discovery-became-one-of-the-flashiest-names-in-ai-drug-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076938</guid>
      <description>The startup has partnered with Eli Lilly and enjoys the backing of some of Silicon Valley's most influential VCs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada cuts tariff on Chinese EVs in exchange for lower tariffs on Canadian farm products</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476330/canada-cuts-tariff-on-chinese-evs-in-exchange-for-lower-tariffs-on-canadian-farm-products</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T20:09:23</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476330/canada-cuts-tariff-on-chinese-evs-in-exchange-for-lower-tariffs-on-canadian-farm-products</guid>
      <description>Xi told Carney in a meeting at the Great Hall of the People that he is willing to continue working to improve ties.
Breaking with the United States, Canada has agreed to cut its 100% tariff on Chinese electric cars in return for lower tariffs on Canadian farm products, Prime Minister Mark Carney said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the chief resource officer</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476709/meet-the-chief-resource-officer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T20:08:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476709/meet-the-chief-resource-officer</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s the next big job change driven by AI
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get up to 78 percent off ExpressVPN two-year plans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-up-to-78-percent-off-expressvpn-two-year-plans-180602525.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $101 for two years, plus four additional free months. That works out to $3.59 per month during the promotional period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hacker posted stolen government data on Instagram</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/supreme-court-hacker-posted-stolen-government-data-on-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083477</guid>
      <description>Nicholas Moore pleaded guilty to stealing victims&#8217; information from the Supreme Court and other federal government agencies, and then posting it on his Instagram @ihackthegovernment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Glasses Are Trying to Break Up With Your Phone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/smart-glasses-are-trying-to-break-up-with-your-phone-2000711064</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711064</guid>
      <description>It's not you, it's LTE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-end SSDs have gotten so pricey they're worth more than their weight in gold</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/storage-backup/top-end-ssds-have-gotten-so-pricey-theyre-worth-more-than-their-weight-in-gold</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TV3rJY9gavQYm7CRgovvwj</guid>
      <description>Is a high-end SSD worth more than its weight in gold? Yes, in some cases, as storage prices follow in the footsteps of RAM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberGhost VPN review: Despite its flaws, the value is hard to beat</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/cyberghost-vpn-review-despite-its-flaws-the-value-is-hard-to-beat-200000250.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39c4e470-0d47-4f79-ba84-4c4c09a987e7</guid>
      <description>CyberGhost is the middle child of the Kape Technologies VPN portfolio, but in quality, it's much closer to ExpressVPN than Private Internet Access. I mainly put it on my best VPN list because it's so cheap, but I wouldn't have done that if it didn't earn its place in other ways &#8212; affordable crap is still crap, after all.
My universal impression of CyberGhost is a VPN that's not perfect but is always genuinely working to make itself better. It makes decisions based on what will help its users, not to set itself apart in a crowded market. This makes it similar to a lot of other VPNs, but that's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT users are about to get hit with targeted ads</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/chatgpt-users-are-about-to-get-hit-with-targeted-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083430</guid>
      <description>OpenAI says that users impacted by the ads will have some control over what they see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucasfilm Tried to Make an Animated &#8216;Indiana Jones&#8217; Show</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lucasfilm-tried-to-make-an-animated-indiana-jones-show-2000711185</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711185</guid>
      <description>A new report says that Lucasfilm scrapped both an animated show and a live-action spinoff too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Go&#160;: l&#8217;abonnement &#224; 8&#160;&#8364; d&#8217;OpenAI arrive en France&#8230; avec de la publicit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/chatgpt-go-labonnement-a-8-e-dopenai-arrive-en-france-avec-de-la-publicite.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320801</guid>
      <description>OpenAI lance une version moins ch&#232;re de ChatGPT en France et partout ailleurs dans le monde. Il s'agit de ChatGPT Go, une formule &#224; 8&#160;&#8364;&#160;par mois avec des avantages int&#233;ressants &#224; la cl&#233;. Un tarif abordable mais attention, qui sera financ&#233;e en partie par&#8230; la publicit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic opens up its Claude Cowork feature to anyone with a $20 subscription</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-opens-up-its-claude-cowork-feature-to-anyone-with-a-20-subscription-194000021.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75a1d7f4-4292-40c8-8897-118f80914963</guid>
      <description>Claude Cowork, Anthropic's AI assistant for taking care of simple tasks on your computer, is now available for anyone with a $20 per month Pro subscription to try. Anthropic launched Cowork as an exclusive feature for its Max subscribers, who pay a minimum of $100 per month for more uses of Claude's expensive reasoning models and early access to experimental features. Now Claude Cowork is available at a cheaper price, though Anthropic notes "Pro users may hit their usage limits earlier" than Max users do.Like other AI agents, the novelty of Claude Cowork is its ability to work on its own. If y...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration wants tech companies to buy $15B of power plants they may not use</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/trump-administration-wants-tech-companies-to-buy-15b-of-power-plants-they-may-not-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083434</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to alleviate rising electricity prices, the White House wants grid operator PJM to hold an auction for new generating capacity, and it wants tech companies to bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google brings its AI videomaker to Workspace users</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863570/google-flow-ai-video-generator-workspace</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T14:37:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863570</guid>
      <description>Google is expanding access to its AI videomaking tool. Launched last May, Flow was initially only available to Google AI Pro and AI Ultra subscribers, but now, those with Business, Enterprise, and Education Workspace plans can access it, too. Flow uses Google's AI video generation model Veo 3.1 to generate eight-second clips based on a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The era of AI hype is over - firms now want to see real returns</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-era-of-ai-hype-is-over-firms-now-want-to-see-real-returns</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sZ3WUncyMrmPg69naudCB7</guid>
      <description>Many businesses have already operationalized generative AI, and are looking at the future of agentic AI within their workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best n8n hosting</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/best-n8n-hosting</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HSrDbVFmbu2nbiseTibQMB</guid>
      <description>Want to self-host your AI-powered workflows on a VPS server to avoid n8n&#8217;s high per-usage costs? Here are the best services to pick from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic launches Claude Cowork, a version of its coding AI for regular people</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-launches-claude-cowork-a-version-of-its-coding-ai-for-regular-people-193000849.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e96f209-4988-475c-9ec3-ef79a87a6915</guid>
      <description>If you follow Anthropic, you're probably familiar with Claude Code. Since the fall of 2024, the company has been training its AI models to use and navigate computers like a human would, and the coding agent has been the most practical expression of that work, giving developers a way to automate rote programming tasks. Starting today, Anthropic is giving regular people a way to take advantage of those capabilities, with the release of a new preview feature called Claude Cowork.The company is billing Cowork as "a simpler way for anyone &#8212; not just developers &#8212; to work with Claude." After you give...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM CEO Mary Barra says people aren&#8217;t plugging in their plug-in hybrids. That defeats their whole purpose</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476440/gm-ceo-mary-barra-says-people-arent-plugging-in-their-plug-in-hybrids-that-defeats-their-whole-purpose</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T19:29:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476440/gm-ceo-mary-barra-says-people-arent-plugging-in-their-plug-in-hybrids-that-defeats-their-whole-purpose</guid>
      <description>Plug-in hybrid vehicles might be even less fuel efficient than gas-only cars when owners don&#8217;t plug them in, and most owners apparently don&#8217;t.
If drivers want to switch away from a completely gas-powered car to something electric, they have a few options. Namely: battery electric vehicles, hybrids, or plug-in hybrids (PHEVs).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is bringing ads to ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-is-bringing-ads-to-chatgpt-192831449.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23288a39-c283-481a-a672-fd726808266e</guid>
      <description>OpenAI plans to start testing ads inside of ChatGPT "in the coming weeks." In a blog post published Friday, the company said adult users in the US of its free and Go tiers (more on the latter in a moment) would start seeing sponsored products and services appear below their conversations with its chatbot. "Ads will be clearly labeled and separated from the organic answer," OpenAI said, adding any sponsored spots would not influence the answers ChatGPT generates. "Answers are optimized based on what's most helpful to you."&#160;OpenAI says people won't see ads appear when they're talking to ChatGPT ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
