<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:36:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to stream the 2026 Super Bowl for free tonight: Patriots vs. Seahawks time, where to watch Super Bowl LX, start time, halftime show and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-stream-the-2026-super-bowl-for-free-tonight-patriots-vs-seahawks-time-where-to-watch-super-bowl-lx-start-time-halftime-show-and-more-124512549.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b2b14-4380-47f2-9cb8-bd2dfe744915</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Super Bowl between the New England Patriots and the Seattle Seahawks will air on NBC today, Feb. 8, at 6:30PM ET/3:30PM PT. The Big Game will also stream live on Peacock. If you no longer subscribe to cable, don't have access to NBC over the air and aren't currently signed up for Peacock, there are still ways to watch Super Bowl LX &#8212; and Bad Bunny's history-making Super Bowl halftime show &#8212; for free. Here's how to tune in.&#160;
How to watch Super Bowl LX free:




Date: Sunday, Feb. 8
Time: 6:30 p.m. ET
Location: Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.
TV channel: NBC, Telemundo
Streaming: ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl on NBC: Patriots vs. Seahawks kickoff time, where to stream, TV channel and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-on-nbc-patriots-vs-seahawks-kickoff-time-where-to-stream-tv-channel-and-more-175759659.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is just one day away. This Sunday, the Big Game will be played at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA. The 2026 NFL Championship Game kicks off at 6:30PM ET. Pre-game coverage starts at 12PM ET. Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the Super Bowl will be broadcast on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. Here's everything you need to know to tune in to Super Bowl LX on Feb. 8, including the game channel, where to stream, and all about the Halftime Show.
How to watch Super Bowl LX



...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for out of this world selfies - NASA says astronauts can now take their own phones with them to space</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/get-ready-for-out-of-this-world-selfies-nasa-says-astronauts-can-now-take-their-own-phones-with-them-to-space</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wcxeaYamqE4Rw4CMHum3RK</guid>
      <description>NASA will allow astronauts to use personal smartphones, reshaping how missions are documented and shared publicly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Svedka to Anthropic, brands make bold plays with AI in Super Bowl ads</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/08/super-bowl-60-ai-ads-svedka-anthropic-brands-commercials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090483</guid>
      <description>From the first AI-generated Big Game ad courtesy of Svedka to Anthropic's beef with OpenAI, here are the biggest ads from Super Bowl LX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Budget Gaming PC in 2026 Is a Pain in the Ass</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/building-a-budget-gaming-pc-in-2026-is-a-pain-in-the-ass-2000719095</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719095</guid>
      <description>Come with me on my adventure to craft a PC when memory prices are worse than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer won&#8217;t make the gaming chair of my dreams a reality &#8212; but the DXRacer Martian Pro proves it should</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-accessories/razer-wont-make-the-gaming-chair-of-my-dreams-a-reality-but-the-dx-racer-martian-pro-proves-it-should</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BrrufuFoEa4tH7ueWDYvKF</guid>
      <description>Razer hasn't made Project Arielle real, but the DX Racer Martian Pro proves it should.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Music Helped Inspire the Not-Musical Stars of &#8216;The Bride!&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-music-helped-inspire-the-not-musical-stars-of-the-bride-2000719174</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719174</guid>
      <description>Like Frankenstein himself, crafting 'The Bride!' required a hodgepodge of songs from musicians of the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone 17e could launch soon with MagSafe and an A19 chip</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/875454/iphone-17e-launching-soon-magsafe-a19</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T10:26:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875454</guid>
      <description>Almost exactly one year after launching the iPhone 16e, Apple is preparing to launch the 17e, according to Mark Gurman. The iPhone 17e will feature an upgraded A19 chip from the iPhone 17 lineup, plus MagSafe charging, and move Apple's in-house cellular chips. Just as importantly, the company apparently plans to keep the price at [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conduite molle, &#233;crans complexes : le vrai probl&#232;me des voitures chinoises vendues en Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2961613_conduite-molle-ecrans-complexes-le-vrai-probleme-des-voitures-chinoises-vendues-en-europe</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2961613_conduite-molle-ecrans-complexes-le-vrai-probleme-des-voitures-chinoises-vendues-en-europe</guid>
      <description>
Longtemps craint, le raz de mar&#233;e des voitures &#233;lectriques chinoises n'a pas (encore) atteint l'Europe. Et si l'offre n'&#233;tait pas si adapt&#233;e aux go&#251;ts europ&#233;ens ? Faisons un tour d'horizon des points de divergence, et pourquoi cela pourrait bient&#244;t &#234;tre de l'histoire pass&#233;e.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony&#8217;s Hawk-Eye Cameras Still Aren&#8217;t Giving Football Fans the One Thing They Want</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sonys-hawk-eye-cameras-still-arent-giving-football-fans-the-one-thing-they-want-2000717879</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717879</guid>
      <description>Sony's Hawk-Eye tech is an impressive feat of camera technology that changed the NFL this year, but there's still one thing fans and football commentators are begging for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Built the Star Trek control panel of my dreams</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/862070/lcars-homes-assistant-star-trek</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862070</guid>
      <description>One of my pandemic hobbies that stuck was home automation. I discovered Home Assistant - the popular open source, extremely customizable home automation platform - and all the intricate things you can do with it to make your home work better. I have ADHD and have found Home Assistant to be a valuable tool for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuliKit&#8217;s tiny USB dongle lets you connect your PS5 controller to your Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874842/gulikit-hyperlink-gen2-usb-adapter-wireless-switch-2-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874842</guid>
      <description>Dongles have a well-earned reputation for being a nuisance. They're often costly and annoying to deal with, but for gamers, there's one that I love to recommend that's neither. 8BitDo's $20 USB Adapter 2 lets you wirelessly link controllers to the Switch 2 that would otherwise be unsupported, like the Sony DualSense (complete with rumble [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunsetting the print server: why 2026 is the year to finally go serverless</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sunsetting-the-print-server-why-2026-is-the-year-to-finally-go-serverless</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">evbmGSeTpqg44v9qb3wqHJ</guid>
      <description>Legacy print servers have always carried costs; why you should eradicate them in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Moflin had a really warm and fuzzy moment' &#8211; a week with the robot pet that wriggled and squeaked its way into my heart</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/moflin-had-a-really-warm-and-fuzzy-moment-a-week-with-the-robot-pet-that-wriggled-and-squeaked-its-way-into-my-heart</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ckdDe3vNPvk2TiGB8fXnMG</guid>
      <description>How I learned to stop worrying and love Casio's affectionate AI guinea pig.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Monday, February 9 (game #1477)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-9-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cHfHct8dWwN6fa9HrUPqMG</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Monday, February 9 (game #974)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-9-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KTBByZhckN2tcCLbh2wKa9</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Monday, February 9 (game #708)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-9-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cJcURFm3abu5fpHyD29iPC</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon brade ce g&#233;ant TV Samsung Mini LED et 144 Hz de 65 pouces : le moment parfait pour changer de TV ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2968831_amazon-brade-ce-geant-tv-samsung-mini-led-et-144-hz-de-65-pouces-le-moment-parfait-pour-changer-de-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2968831_amazon-brade-ce-geant-tv-samsung-mini-led-et-144-hz-de-65-pouces-le-moment-parfait-pour-changer-de-tv</guid>
      <description>
Si vous cherchez un t&#233;l&#233;viseur polyvalent, performant en gaming et riche en fonctionnalit&#233;s connect&#233;es, le Samsung 65QN80F est fait pour vous. D'ailleurs, il est m&#234;me moins cher en ce moment sur Amazon et passe de 990 euros &#224; 871 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
