<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:24:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>All You Need Is Kill is a dazzling movie with the soul of a video game</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/862881/all-you-need-is-kill-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862881</guid>
      <description>While Hollywood has repeatedly tried adapting stories from Japanese manga, vanishingly few of them have been as good as Edge of Tomorrow - Warner Bros.' 2014 live-action film based on Hiroshi Sakurazaka's sci-fi light novel All You Need Is Kill. Edge of Tomorrow wasn't a one-to-one translation of All You Need Is Kill's original story [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolby Atmos Flex Connect : la r&#233;volution du home cin&#233;ma sans fil expliqu&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/audio/2942377_dolby-atmos-flex-connect-la-revolution-du-home-cinema-sans-fil-expliquee</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/audio/2942377_dolby-atmos-flex-connect-la-revolution-du-home-cinema-sans-fil-expliquee</guid>
      <description>
Fini les c&#226;bles qui serpentent &#224; travers le salon. Termin&#233;e la torture de l'installation millim&#233;trique. Dolby promet de d&#233;mocratiser le son surround avec sa technologie Flex Connect. Mais derri&#232;re le discours marketing, que vaut vraiment cette innovation ? On d&#233;cortique tout.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Atari Hotel in Las Vegas Isn&#8217;t Happening Anymore</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-atari-hotel-in-las-vegas-isnt-happening-anymore-2000711372</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711372</guid>
      <description>The company says the plans for Phoenix are still in play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deux nouveaux milieux de gamme sold&#233;s &#224; moins de 250 &#8364; : faut&#8209;il craquer pour le Xiaomi Redmi Note 15 5G ou le Nothing Phone (3a) Lite ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944429_deux-nouveaux-milieux-de-gamme-soldes-a-moins-de-250-e-faut%e2%80%91il-craquer-pour-le-xiaomi-redmi-note-15-5g-ou-le-nothing-phone-3a-lite</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944429_deux-nouveaux-milieux-de-gamme-soldes-a-moins-de-250-e-faut%e2%80%91il-craquer-pour-le-xiaomi-redmi-note-15-5g-ou-le-nothing-phone-3a-lite</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver sont souvent le moment id&#233;al pour s&#8217;offrir un nouveau smartphone sans faire exploser son budget. Il y a deux mod&#232;les r&#233;cents sous la barre des 300 euros qui attirent particuli&#232;rement l&#8217;attention : le Xiaomi Redmi Note 15 5G et le Nothing Phone (3a) Lite. On les oppose pour vous aider &#224; choisir celui qui offre le meilleur rapport qualit&#233;-prix.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cute frog game that remixes Nintendo&amp;#8217;s best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/860917/big-hops-review-pc-nintendo-switch-ps5</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860917</guid>
      <description>While playing Big Hops, a new 3D platformer starring an adorable frog, I kept feeling like I was breaking the game - and, like with The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom, breaking it is kind of the point. In Big Hops, you play as a frog named Hop. Early on, Hop is taken [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota wants to win a war of attrition</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/863632/minnesota-walz-trump-sousveillance-ice</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863632</guid>
      <description>As masked and armed men in combat armor swarmed throughout the Twin Cities, Gov. Tim Walz took to primetime television to ask Minnesotans to film ICE. The videos, he said, would "create a database of the atrocities against Minnesotans - not just to establish a record for posterity, but to bank evidence for future prosecution." [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of chips: how gate-all-around design is powering the AI era and the next node</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-future-of-chips-how-gate-all-around-design-is-powering-the-ai-era-and-the-next-node</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6NoZS44vZA3LT9oU2dTTEk</guid>
      <description>Materials innovation drives next-gen AI chips, enabling performance, efficiency and scalability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California AG sends cease and desist to xAI over Grok's explicit deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/california-ag-sends-cease-and-desist-to-xai-over-groks-explicit-deepfakes-140000574.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e11287aa-db96-48c2-aa5d-e3590a0bfe86</guid>
      <description>California Attorney General Rob Bonta has sent a cease and desist letter to xAI, days after his office launched an official investigation into the company over reports that Grok was generating nonconsensual  If you&#8217;ll recall, xAI and Grok have been under fire for taking images of real individuals and putting them in revealing clothing like bikinis upon random users&#8217; requests. Bonta&#8217;s office demands that xAI immediately cease and desist from creating &#8220;digitized sexually explicit material&#8221; when the depicted individual didn&#8217;t consent to it or if the individual is a minor. It also demanded that xA...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to pair AirPods with any device</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/how-to-pair-airpods-with-any-device-140000234.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dd726c0-ef43-4ed4-8d23-6962bf83a1ae</guid>
      <description>AirPods work most smoothly with Apple hardware, but they also connect reliably to Android phones, Windows laptops and other Bluetooth devices. The pairing process depends on the platform in use although the basics remain the same. Once the AirPods are placed in pairing mode, most devices detect them quickly and handle the remaining steps in the background. The guide below explains how to pair AirPods with Apple products, how the process differs on newer iPhones that support H2 features and how to connect them to non-Apple devices.How to pair AirPods with Apple devicesApple builds AirPods to pa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New year, new upgrades &#8211; here are 5 improvements I want Spotify to make in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/spotify/new-year-new-upgrades-here-are-5-improvements-i-want-spotify-to-make-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">spdbSADMy5xAcg3YGReLA7</guid>
      <description>2025 was great, but 2026 could be even better. These are the upgrades I need to see from Spotify this year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
