<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:46:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic vs. The Pentagon: what enterprises should do</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/anthropic-vs-the-pentagon-what-enterprises-should-do</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5pHPvMEnCZ3UYStw22o5j0</guid>
      <description>The relationship between one of Silicon Valley's most lucrative and powerful AI model makers, Anthropic, and the U.S. government reached a breaking point on Friday, February 27, 2026.President Donald J. Trump and the White House posted on social media ordering all federal agencies to immediately cease using technology from Anthropic, the maker of the powerful Claude family of AI models, after reportedly months of renegotiating a less than two-year-old contract. Following the President&#8217;s lead, Secretary of War Pete Hegseth said he was directing the Department of War to designate Anthropic a "Su...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette petite cam&#233;ra de surveillance connect&#233;e filme en HD, peut fonctionner avec Alexa et ne co&#251;te pas plus de 15 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2991743_cette-petite-camera-de-surveillance-connectee-filme-en-hd-peut-fonctionner-avec-alexa-et-ne-coute-pas-plus-de-15-e</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2991743_cette-petite-camera-de-surveillance-connectee-filme-en-hd-peut-fonctionner-avec-alexa-et-ne-coute-pas-plus-de-15-e</guid>
      <description>
Compacte et discr&#232;te, la Blink Mini d'Amazon propose toutes les fonctionnalit&#233;s que l'on est en droit d'attendre d'une cam&#233;ra de surveillance connect&#233;e. Elle est en plus l'une des moins ch&#232;res du moment : elle est affich&#233;e &#224; 14,99 euros au lieu de 34,99 euros sur le site du g&#233;ant am&#233;ricain.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Model 3 code suggests it could get an upgrade soon &#8212; but were the Model S and Model X axed too soon?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/tesla-model-3-code-suggests-it-could-get-an-upgrade-soon-but-were-the-model-s-and-model-x-axed-too-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R8qfRhFFxikup3omq6Ghv9</guid>
      <description>The Tesla Model 3 could get two big upgrades soon, according to code hints &#8212; meanwhile, used Model S and X prices are on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI strikes a deal with the Defense Department to deploy its AI models</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-strikes-a-deal-with-the-defense-department-to-deploy-its-ai-models-054441785.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85cc2c5f-22a9-48df-8b44-00d676cb8e54</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has reached an agreement with the Defense Department to deploy its models in the agency&#8217;s network, company chief Sam Altman has revealed on X.  In his post, he said two of OpenAI&#8217;s most important safety principles are &#8220;prohibitions on domestic mass surveillance and human responsibility for the use of force, including for autonomous weapon systems.&#8221; Altman claimed the company put those principles in its agreement with the agency, which he called by the government&#8217;s preferred name of Department of War (DoW), and that it had agreed to honor them. The agency has closed the deal with OpenAI,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurdle hints and answers for February 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/hurdle-hints-answers-february-28-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03NYUfQ0mk0sDE2Gf9p8RZI</guid>
      <description>Hints and answers to today's Hurdle all in one place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon phase today: What the Moon will look like on February 28</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/moon-phase-today-feb-28</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01pYRvEenRIO41wqxe9h2bx</guid>
      <description>See the Moon phase expected for February 28, 2026 as well as when the next Full Moon is expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to unblock XNXX for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/how-to-unblock-xnxx-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">014kKS9Yt59NwMAN3W2ddrm</guid>
      <description>How to unblock porn for free. Unblock and watch XNXX from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
