<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:18:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nouveau Tesla Model Y, un crash-tests 2025 100 % &#233;lectrique et un moteur qui d&#233;fie Bosch et DJI &#8211; R&#233;cap&#8217; Survolt&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2945497_recap-survoltes-202603</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2945497_recap-survoltes-202603</guid>
      <description>
Cette semaine sur Survolt&#233;s, les actualit&#233;s ont &#233;t&#233; nombreuses et vari&#233;es : le FSD de Tesla passe en mode abonnement, Ananda a d&#233;gain&#233; un nouveau moteur pour v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique, les crash-tests automobiles de 2025 sont tomb&#233;s, et Canyon d&#233;voile de grandes ambitions financi&#232;res.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why reinforcement learning plateaus without representation depth (and other key takeaways from NeurIPS 2025)</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/why-reinforcement-learning-plateaus-without-representation-depth-and-other</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Zcu5wNTYJnUcuXqTdyYaE</guid>
      <description>Every year, NeurIPS produces hundreds of impressive papers, and a handful that subtly reset how practitioners think about scaling, evaluation and system design. In 2025, the most consequential works weren't about a single breakthrough model. Instead, they challenged fundamental assumptions that academicians and corporations have quietly relied on: Bigger models mean better reasoning, RL creates new capabilities, attention is &#8220;solved&#8221; and generative models inevitably memorize.This year&#8217;s top papers collectively point to a deeper shift: AI progress is now constrained less by raw model capacity a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok's latest spinoff app feels a lot like Quibi, but with shorter and cornier content</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/tiktoks-latest-spinoff-app-feels-a-lot-like-quibi-but-with-shorter-and-cornier-content-185702010.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b30f46c8-bad5-4968-adb7-2253f252284e</guid>
      <description>In another attempt to reduce our attention spans to mush, TikTok has released the PineDrama app, which offers serialized drama series that are roughly a minute per episode. As first spotted by Business Insider, the app is designed exactly like TikTok, but instead of trendy dance videos, you can scroll through and watch "micro dramas."
For those new to the category, micro dramas are bite-sized TV shows shot in vertical video and available in minute-long episodes. Don't expect any nominations for Best Original Screenplay with series like The Officer Fell For Me or Married to my past life's nemes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney deleted a Thread because people kept quoting its movies at it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863980/disney-deleted-anti-fascist-thread</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T13:38:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863980</guid>
      <description>"Share a Disney quote that sums up how you're feeling right now!" That's what Disney posted on Threads the other day, and people immediately replied with lines from Star Wars, The Hunchback of Notre Dame, and even Mary Poppins. The throughline between all the quotes: they were pretty pointedly anti-fascist and clearly aimed at the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills vs Broncos Free Streams: TV Channels &amp; Preview for NFL 2026 Divisional Round Game</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/buffalo-bills-vs-denver-broncos-nfl-2026-divisional-round-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ijVzkEdbVBJw53UoSxqq8h</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Bills vs Broncos live streams for FREE, in the Divisional Round of the 2025/26 NFL playoffs at Empower Field at Mile High in Denver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes PS5, Nintendo Switch et Xbox : les jeux vid&#233;o pas chers pour se faire plaisir &#224; petit prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2945513_soldes-ps5-nintendo-switch-et-xbox-les-jeux-video-pas-chers-pour-se-faire-plaisir-a-petit-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2945513_soldes-ps5-nintendo-switch-et-xbox-les-jeux-video-pas-chers-pour-se-faire-plaisir-a-petit-prix</guid>
      <description>
Les Soldes sont toujours le bon moment pour ajouter des jeux &#224; sa collection et faire monter son backlog de fa&#231;on &#233;hont&#233;e. Que ce soit un titre que vous aviez &#224; l'&#339;il depuis longtemps ou une nouveaut&#233; que vous &#234;tes curieux de tester, cette s&#233;lection vous pr&#233;sente les offres les plus int&#233;ressantes sur PlayStation 5, Switch/Switch 2 et Xbox Series.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wacky Musk-OpenAI Legal War Now Involves a Fittingly Insane Amount of Money</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-wacky-musk-openai-legal-war-now-involves-a-fittingly-insane-amount-of-money-2000709452</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709452</guid>
      <description>$134 billion, with more to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's the last day to get up to $90 off reMarkable E Ink tablet bundles</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/tablets/its-the-last-day-to-get-up-to-90-off-remarkable-e-ink-tablet-bundles-150242090.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37b6fead-a9b3-44fd-8244-00ae1ade3bb9</guid>
      <description>E Ink tablet maker reMarkable is running a bundle deal right now that can save you between $80 and $90 when buying a reMarkable 2 along with a Marker stylus and a folio case. The savings vary depending on the bundle you configure, but this can bring your out-the-door cost down to $449 from $529 for the tablet, Marker stylus and polymer weave book folio. The offer runs through January 17.
The company also sells a newer stylus called Marker Plus that lets you erase by flipping it around just like a real pencil, but that will cost you an extra $50. If you&#8217;ve been eyeing a dedicated writing tablet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures souris gamer &#224; choisir en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/713273_guide-meilleures-souris-gamer</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/713273_guide-meilleures-souris-gamer</guid>
      <description>
La souris gaming est l'accessoire indispensable de toute personne souhaitant jouer sur PC. Souris premium, sans fil, RGB, ou encore abordables... on a tout test&#233;, on vous dit quelles sont nos pr&#233;f&#233;r&#233;es !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sony A7 V just dethroned Nikon &#8211; it&#8217;s rocketed to number one in Japan&#8217;s best-selling lists and tops our our camera buying guides too</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/mirrorless-cameras/the-sony-a7-v-just-dethroned-nikon-its-rocketed-to-number-one-in-japans-best-selling-lists-and-tops-our-our-camera-buying-guides-too</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hxwC7qJEbChwuxtPsJSizc</guid>
      <description>Sony's latest full-frame mirrorless is selling like hotcakes around the world, and has become TechRadar's own top pick in two major buying guide categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Apple MacBook Air with an M4 chip is $200 off right now</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-17-macbook-air-m4-chip-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01PJW4w3TpCe1y14KI1eFNj</guid>
      <description>This Apple MacBook Air with an M4 chip is $200 off right now and it&#8217;s sky blue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Setapp Mobile iOS store is shutting down on February 16th</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863978/setapp-mobile-ios-store-shutdown</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T12:36:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863978</guid>
      <description>Setapp Mobile seemed like one of the many alternative app markets with promise that launched in the wake of the EU's Digital Markets Act (DMA). While the law may have forced Apple to allow third-party app stores on its devices, it couldn't make users actually embrace them. MacPaw, the Ukrainian developer behind the subscription-based Setapp, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get NBA League Pass for up to 55 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-nba-league-pass-for-up-to-55-percent-off-right-now-163421800.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a364f8fe-4cef-4bc2-89cf-730e7b34af39</guid>
      <description>NBA League Pass, the streaming service that lets you catch hundreds of out-of-market NBA games, is on sale right now for up to 55 percent off. The League Pass Premium subscription is on sale for $75, down from $160, while League Pass Standard is marked down to $50 from $110. We're almost halfway through the season at this point, so it makes sense for a service like League Pass to start offering some discounts.
The Standard plan includes commercials and support for only one device at a time, while the Premium tier offers no commercials, in-arena streams during breaks in the game, offline viewin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration&#8217;s legal setbacks are good news for offshore wind &#8212; and the grid</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/17/trump-administrations-legal-setbacks-are-good-news-for-offshore-wind-and-the-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083476</guid>
      <description>Three offshore wind projects under construction on the U.S. East Coast are back to building after judges rebuked the Department of the Interior's actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's OLED, touchscreen MacBook Pro upgrade could be arriving sooner than we expected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/macbooks/apples-oled-touchscreen-macbook-pro-upgrade-could-be-arriving-sooner-than-we-expected</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22ocFLWMSBWnFcXCi95hXA</guid>
      <description>An OLED upgrade has been tipped for late 2026 before &#8211; but the schedule may have moved forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Finally Know Real Things About the Next J.J. Abrams Movie</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/we-finally-know-real-things-about-the-next-j-j-abrams-movie-2000711329</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711329</guid>
      <description>J.J. Abrams is making his return to the big screen this fall with Glen Powell and Jenna Ortega in 'The Great Beyond.'</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
