<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:35:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>As Gambling Apps Grow, Bettors are Slated to Owe More in Taxes This Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/as-gambling-apps-grow-bettors-are-slated-to-owe-more-in-taxes-this-year-2000703073</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703073</guid>
      <description>Hope that 20-leg parlay was worth it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today's the last day to get $100 off the PS5 and PS5 Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/todays-the-last-day-to-get-100-off-the-ps5-and-ps5-pro-181454333.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6eba115-9a6b-4ac9-bf33-623b739bc112</guid>
      <description>Back in November, Sony started selling PS5 consoles at a $100 discount as part of a Black Friday/Cyber Monday promotion. The deal officially sunsets at 3AM ET, so now is a good time to bite the bullet on a gaming console given that prices aren't likely to go down anytime soon.
You can pick up a regular disc-based PS5 for $450 and a digital model for $400. The beefy PS5 Pro is available for $650. All of these deals are active on Amazon, but also directly from Sony. 
If the costs here still sound a bit high, that's because Sony raised console prices by $50 back in August. In other words, these $...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s beefy Laptop Power Bank has returned to its Black Friday low</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/849637/anker-laptop-power-bank-xbox-series-x-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849637</guid>
      <description>As you might expect, things have been relatively quiet on the deals front since Black Friday, particularly when it comes to discounts on charging accessories. Thankfully, Anker&#8217;s aptly titled Laptop Power Bank is once again on sale at Amazon and Walmart for $87.99 ($47 off), which matches the record-low price we last saw at the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The European startup market&#8217;s data doesn&#8217;t match its energy &#8212; yet</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/24/the-european-startup-markets-data-doesnt-match-its-energy-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077586</guid>
      <description>Europe's startup market hasn't produced meaningful numbers but there is reason to believe the data will start to change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give yourself the gift of digital privacy this Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/give-yourself-the-gift-of-digital-privacy-this-christmas</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gqB9H2sbByhWvAcNykDZLW</guid>
      <description>A VPN is the gift that keeps giving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Disney+, Hulu and ESPN bundle deal is the perfect last-minute Christmas gift for families</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hulu/this-disney-hulu-and-espn-bundle-deal-is-the-perfect-last-minute-christmas-gift-for-families</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Dud27ikTPozevFu5WJquuL</guid>
      <description>Unexpected family guests this Christmas? Entertain everyone for less with this Disney+, Hulu and ESPN bundle deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France&#8217;s postal service was hit by a major cyberattck right before Christmas. Here are the hackers who did it</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91466742/frances-postal-service-hit-major-cyberattck-right-before-christmas-hackers-who-did-it</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T17:53:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91466742/frances-postal-service-hit-major-cyberattck-right-before-christmas-hackers-who-did-it</guid>
      <description>The Russian hacking group known as Noname057 claimed responsibility for the holiday attack on France&#8217;s national postal service.
A pro-Russian hacking group claimed responsibility for a major cyberattack that halted package deliveries by France&#8217;s national postal service just days before Christmas, prosecutors said Wednesday.After the claim by the cybercrime group known as Noname057, French intelligence agency DGSI took over the investigation into the hacking attack, the Paris prosecutor&#8217;s office said in a statement to The Associated Press.The group has been accused of other cyberattacks in Euro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-created ransomware and NFC attacks lead the surge in new cyberattacks - here's how you can stay safe this holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/ai-created-ransomware-and-nfc-attacks-lead-the-surge-in-new-cyberattacks-heres-how-you-can-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eKKbZb26o5t7ogU33XpEc7</guid>
      <description>AI is no longer being used just to craft convincing phishing emails - it's being used to build ransomware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why TikTok&#8217;s &#8216;For You&#8217; page is so valuable and what&#8217;s to change for U.S. users</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463828/tiktok-for-you-page-value-sale-deal-whats-next</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463828/tiktok-for-you-page-value-sale-deal-whats-next</guid>
      <description>The value of TikTok&#8217;s algorithm&#8217;s lies in its uncanny capacity to anticipate users&#8217; content preferences.
Chinese tech giant ByteDance has signed an agreement to sell a majority stake in its video platform TikTok to a group of U.S. investors. President Donald Trump announced a preliminary agreement for the sale on Sept. 19, 2025, following his negotiation with Chinese leader Xi Jinping....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key workforce trends to watch in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91466644/key-workforce-trends-to-watch-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T17:29:43</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91466644/key-workforce-trends-to-watch-in-2026</guid>
      <description>These three trends will redefine collaboration and hiring.
As 2026 begins, the workplace is rapidly changing due to technological advances, shifting labor dynamics, and evolving employee expectations. Organizations that anticipate and adjust to these changes are more likely to attract top talent, boost productivity, and stay competitive. From embracing artificial intelligence in the workplace to a continued focus on skill-based hiring, the future of work is being shaped by trends that could redefine how we collaborate, learn, and thrive. Here are three top workforce trends to watch in 2026....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brands: Stay true to your core to win</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91466634/brands-stay-true-to-your-core-to-win</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T17:27:57</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91466634/brands-stay-true-to-your-core-to-win</guid>
      <description>Four lessons on building a company that instills loyalty in staff and customers
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le SSD externe Samsung T7 et ses 2 Go de stockage perdent 15 % sur le site de la marque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2920813_le-ssd-externe-samsung-t7-et-ses-2-go-de-stockage-perdent-15-sur-le-site-de-la-marque</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2920813_le-ssd-externe-samsung-t7-et-ses-2-go-de-stockage-perdent-15-sur-le-site-de-la-marque</guid>
      <description>
Sorti depuis presque six ans, le Samsung T7 reste encore une valeur s&#251;re et il perd 15 % de son prix chez Samsung. Ce SSD est actuellement vendu &#224; 127,50 euros gr&#226;ce au code STORAGE15.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to stop punching the clock at work and have more work-life balance</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462949/stop-punching-the-clock-work-life-balance</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T17:20:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462949/stop-punching-the-clock-work-life-balance</guid>
      <description>If you have a choice in the matter of when and how much you work, should you choose differently?
About 1 in 3 Americans make at least one New Year&#8217;s resolution, according to Pew Research. While most of these vows focus on weight loss, fitness, and other health-related goals, many fall into a distinct category: work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald&#8217;s just made a very big announcement, and these 13 words mattered most</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91466654/mcdonalds-just-made-very-big-announcement-13-words-mattered-most</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-24T17:05:25</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91466654/mcdonalds-just-made-very-big-announcement-13-words-mattered-most</guid>
      <description>&#8216;Adversity can strengthen you if you have the will to grind it out.&#8217;
I&#8217;ve read a lot of business memoirs. One I keep coming back to is&#160;Grinding It Out&#160;by&#160;Ray Kroc&#8212;the man who built&#160;McDonald&#8217;s&#160;into the global giant it is today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini, ChatGPT&#8230; comment l&#8217;IA s&#8217;invite (enfin) intelligemment dans vos parties de jeux de soci&#233;t&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/gemini-chatgpt-comment-lia-sinvite-enfin-intelligemment-dans-vos-parties-de-jeux-de-societe.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317230</guid>
      <description>Fini les retours &#224; la r&#232;gle en pleine partie et les d&#233;bats interminables sur un point de d&#233;tail. En 2025, ChatGPT, Gemini et Perplexity s'imposent comme des assistants pratiques pour fluidifier vos soir&#233;es jeux sans tuer la convivialit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best live TV streaming services to cut cable in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/best-live-tv-streaming-service-133000410.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50eb34db-c0fc-4bfb-ab41-1cbe97faffd8</guid>
      <description>Price hikes, media consolidation and contract disputes that turn channels dark have made live TV streaming services feel a lot more like cable. But, for most people it&#8217;s still a better deal to cut the cord. For sports fans and news junkies, there&#8217;s still no better option than one of the best live TV streaming services. We tried all the major players and currently recommend YouTube TV for most people. But we also spelled out just what you get from other providers (along with what we think about them) so you can decide for yourself.Editor&#8217;s note: YouTube TV will start offering genre-specific pla...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>It's the night before Christmas, and holiday VPN deals are going strong. It's a great time to grab a last-minute subscription for yourself or a loved one. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart  online trackers. It might be cute that Santa sees you when you're sleeping and knows when you're awake, but Russian hacker collectives and the Amazon marketing department don't really share St. Nick's charm.
Although we strongly recommend using a VPN, jumping on the first deal that come...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Streaming Shows and Movies You May Have Missed This Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/best-streaming-tv-movies-2025-2000702962</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702962</guid>
      <description>If your watchlist is looking a little vacant, the io9 crew has some gems for your consideration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cameroon vs Gabon Free Streams: How to watch AFCON 2025 Group F opener, TV channels, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/cameroon-vs-gabon-afcon-2025-group-f-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Xt5hKbBYqhteq82Lhpg9YG</guid>
      <description>We'll show you all the ways you can watch Cameroon vs Gabon in the 2025 AFCON from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Christmas VPN deals to keep your present hauls safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/3-christmas-vpn-deals-to-keep-your-present-hauls-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85bMXcoySNZymsvvihezLK</guid>
      <description>Don't take a chance with your shiny new gadgets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FrandroidOffreMoi un setup gaming Erazer (PC fixe + &#233;cran)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/medion/2915719_frandroidoffremoi-un-setup-gaming-erazer-pc-fixe-ecran</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/medion/2915719_frandroidoffremoi-un-setup-gaming-erazer-pc-fixe-ecran</guid>
      <description>
C'est le tout dernier jour du calendrier de l'Avent et on boucle notre concours #FrandroidOffreMoi en beaut&#233; avec une tour gaming et un moniteur parfait pour vos jeux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo explains why its robotaxis got stuck during the SF blackout</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/24/waymo-explains-why-its-robotaxis-got-stuck-during-the-sf-blackout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078810</guid>
      <description>The company also said its robotaxis navigated more than 7,000 dark stoplights successfully on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $130 on this compact Sonos soundbar and upgrade your TV speakers for less</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/save-usd130-on-this-compact-sonos-soundbar-and-upgrade-your-tv-speakers-for-less</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HFgxnDk7CKU2t2Uq8ysLc</guid>
      <description>An excellent four-star soundbar for small spaces</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
