<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:49:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Giant, 10 Skulls, and Rope-Bound Corpses: This Viking-Era &#8216;Execution Pit&#8217; Has Stories to Tell</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-giant-10-skulls-and-rope-bound-corpses-this-viking-era-execution-pit-has-stories-to-tell-2000718224</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718224</guid>
      <description>Archaeologists and students in England have uncovered a mass grave, which includes the remains of an exceptionally tall man with a hole in his skull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette importante promotion sur le drone DJI Neo Fly et tous ses accessoires donne le vertige</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967663_cette-promotion-de-37-sur-le-drone-dji-neo-fly-et-tous-ses-accessoires-donne-le-vertige</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967663_cette-promotion-de-37-sur-le-drone-dji-neo-fly-et-tous-ses-accessoires-donne-le-vertige</guid>
      <description>
Joybuy fait une offre incontournable sur le drone DJI Neo dans sa version Fly More Combo puisque le site la propose &#224; 219 euros au lieu de 349 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElevenLabs CEO: Voice is the next interface for AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/elevenlabs-ceo-voice-is-the-next-interface-for-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089899</guid>
      <description>ElevenLabs CEO argued at Web Summit Qatar that voice is the next interface for AI, as OpenAI, Google, and Apple push conversational systems into wearables, new hardware, and everyday interactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deux services d&#8217;Apple &#233;chappent aux r&#232;gles europ&#233;ennes du DMA</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/deux-services-dapple-echappent-aux-regles-europeennes-du-dma.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324345</guid>
      <description>Voil&#224; une &#233;pine en moins dans le pied d'Apple, et m&#234;me deux. La Commission europ&#233;enne a en effet &#233;tabli que ni Apple Plans, ni Apple Ads ne seront soumis aux dispositions contraignantes du r&#232;glement sur les march&#233;s num&#233;riques (DMA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A potential Starlink competitor just got FCC clearance to launch 4,000 satellites</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/a-potential-starlink-competitor-just-got-fcc-clearance-to-launch-4000-satellites-143905076.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">773636c0-46ed-49e1-af6d-a639a996c44d</guid>
      <description>Aspiring Starlink competitor Logos Space Services has secured FCC clearance to launch more than  4,000 broadband satellites into low Earth orbit by 2035, as reported by Space News. Under FCC regulations, the company must deploy half of the approved amount within the next seven years.
The company is headed by its founder, Milo Medin, a former project manager at NASA as well as a former vice president of wireless services at Google. The company has been raising money since it opened its doors in 2023 and reportedly hopes to deploy its first satellite by 2027. Logos&#8217; planned low Earth orbit const...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une sonde de la Nasa remet en question la taille de Jupiter apr&#232;s 50 ans de certitudes</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-sonde-nasa-remet-question-taille-jupiter-apres-50-ans-certitudes-130935/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:39:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-sonde-nasa-remet-question-taille-jupiter-apres-50-ans-certitudes-130935/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Jupiter serait finalement beaucoup plus petite et plate que ce que nous pensions. De nouvelles donn&#233;es r&#233;colt&#233;es par la sonde Juno d&#233;voilent un nouveau visage de la g&#233;ante gazeuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Opening Ceremony at the 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympics</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-opening-ceremony-at-the-2026-milan-cortina-winter-olympics-143529451.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c67003b7-b33a-46d4-8e16-afd2150a7a2a</guid>
      <description>


  The 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympic Games kick off with the Opening Ceremony this Friday. Here's how to watch. (REUTERS/Claudia Greco)
 

  REUTERS / Reuters
 

The 2026 Milan Cortina Winter Olympics begin this week, and this year's Opening Ceremony promises to be one for the ages. The three-hour event will feature performances from Mariah Carey and Andrea Bocelli, 3,000 athletes participating in the Parade of Nations, and not one but two Olympic cauldrons being lit. (One at Milan's Arco della Pace, since Milan will serve as the main hub for this year's Games, and the other in the Alpin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici les prix des trottinettes Xiaomi Electric Scooter 6, avec une belle surprise en prime</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2967615_voici-les-prix-des-trottinettes-xiaomi-electric-scooter-6-avec-une-belle-surprise-en-prime</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2967615_voici-les-prix-des-trottinettes-xiaomi-electric-scooter-6-avec-une-belle-surprise-en-prime</guid>
      <description>
Xiaomi avait d&#233;voil&#233; sa nouvelle gamme de trottinettes &#233;lectriques il y a quelques semaines, mais sans parler des prix. Les voici en avance, plus celui d'un mod&#232;le Ultra pas encore annonc&#233; officiellement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A seriously powerful all-in-one PC has been revealed, packing an AMD Ryzen AI Max+ 395 CPU under the hood</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/desktop-pcs/a-seriously-powerful-all-in-one-pc-has-been-revealed-packing-an-amd-ryzen-ai-max-395-cpu-under-the-hood</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZcmWqwRqC99tTMGQ3fmk8U</guid>
      <description>Another Apple iMac alternative has arrived, and it's built around AMD's most powerful APU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I test budget earbuds for a living, and I'd buy these 5 buds right now &#8212; including a new lowest price for my absolute favorites</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/i-test-budget-earbuds-for-a-living-and-id-buy-these-5-buds-right-now-including-a-new-lowest-price-for-my-absolute-favorites</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PDC7hd73QEqzusyFx5pWcR</guid>
      <description>It seems like every pair of earbuds I've enjoyed is discounted right now; here are five you should check out, all at reduced prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Memory Shortage Has Come for Valve&#8217;s Steam Machine</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-memory-shortage-has-come-for-valves-steam-machine-2000718415</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718415</guid>
      <description>You really, really shouldn&#8217;t expect a cheap Steam Machine or Steam Frame headset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous new malware exploits WinRAR flaw - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/dangerous-new-malware-exploits-winrar-flaw-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aonNBmzRxSSKVxQwn8N5HA</guid>
      <description>A Chinese state-sponsored actor was seen exploiting a WinRAR bug, soon after the Russians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk change d&#8217;avis et pr&#233;pare un rival pour l&#8217;iPhone chez SpaceX</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/spacex/2967701_elon-musk-change-davis-et-prepare-un-rival-pour-liphone-chez-spacex</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/spacex/2967701_elon-musk-change-davis-et-prepare-un-rival-pour-liphone-chez-spacex</guid>
      <description>
Le feuilleton du t&#233;l&#233;phone &#171;&#160;made in Musk&#160;&#187; prend un nouveau tournant. Alors que SpaceX s'appr&#234;te &#224; entrer en Bourse et que Starlink cartonne, les rumeurs autour d'un appareil mobile propri&#233;taire reviennent en force. Et cette fois, la r&#233;ponse du patron a subtilement chang&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 series could launch any week now &#8212; and I think these are the most likely discounts at launch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-s26-series-could-launch-any-week-now-and-i-think-these-are-the-most-likely-discounts-at-launch</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Qq32EN7fgxKZNtjZ2onF7W</guid>
      <description>A new generation of Samsung Galaxy devices could be imminent - here's what to expect if you're thinking about upgrading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sony WH-1000XM6 headphones drop to a record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-sony-wh-1000xm6-headphones-drop-to-a-record-low-price-175038542.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4519507c-493c-4bae-a537-e3800e375935</guid>
      <description>Now's a great time to consider upgrading your wireless headphones since you can get our favorites at their best price yet. The Sony WH-1000XM6 headphones are down to $398, which is $62 off and the best discount we've seen since their debut. The sale applies to all three colorways.
These easily topped our list of the best wireless headphones. They are, in a word, fantastic. The headphones are packed with premium features, like advanced ANC. There are a whopping 12 ANC microphones throughout and a brand-new chip to power the feature. The end result? It successfully blocks background noise at med...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN launches new-look plans with 4 huge new features &#8212; here's what it means for your VPN subscription</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/expressvpn-launches-new-look-plans-with-4-huge-new-features-heres-what-it-means-for-your-vpn-subscription</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9yqjUCyC7RKZ6esBiCjnuE</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN has launched four new features that'll be included in its VPN plans. We've broken down everything you need to know about what's changing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throwing a Super Bowl party? Here are 18 last-minute deals at Amazon that I'd buy for the big game</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/throwing-a-super-bowl-party-here-are-18-last-minute-deals-at-amazon-that-id-buy-for-the-big-game</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fN35CPrBWAzgoK8es5YWbc</guid>
      <description>Throwing a Super Bowl party? I've rounded up 18 last-minute deals at Amazon, including TVs, soundbars, air fryers, party supplies, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une Xiaomi SU7 prend feu en pleine rue et &#231;a n&#8217;a rien avoir avec la batterie</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2967387_une-xiaomi-su7-prend-feu-en-pleine-rue-et-ca-na-rien-avoir-avec-la-batterie</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2967387_une-xiaomi-su7-prend-feu-en-pleine-rue-et-ca-na-rien-avoir-avec-la-batterie</guid>
      <description>
Un incendie impliquant une Xiaomi SU7 dans la province du Liaoning, en Chine, a aliment&#233; les d&#233;bats sur la s&#233;curit&#233; des v&#233;hicules &#233;lectriques chinois. Pourtant, selon le constructeur, la batterie n'est pas en cause. Mais ce fait divers vient une nouvelle fois alimenter de vieux d&#233;mons autour de la voiture &#233;lectrique et des incendies.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake thinks AI coding agents are solving the wrong problem</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487016/snowflake-thinks-ai-coding-agents-are-solving-the-wrong-problem</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T14:02:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487016/snowflake-thinks-ai-coding-agents-are-solving-the-wrong-problem</guid>
      <description>As coding agents stumble in production, the battle for enterprise AI is shifting to the governed data layer.
AI coding agents are suddenly everywhere, the latest thing Silicon Valley cannot stop talking about. From venture-backed startups to splashy big tech keynotes, the promise sounds the same: just describe what you want, and the AI will build it for you. It is a seductive idea, especially in a world where software projects are notorious for moving slowly. But inside large companies, that vision is already starting to unravel....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#8217;s New Era Could Bring Back &#8216;Pirates of the Caribbean&#8217; in a Major Way</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-reboot-disney-josh-damaro-margot-robbie-2000718094</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718094</guid>
      <description>Plus, Mark Ruffalo addresses his Marvel future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I offer you a tiny Bluetooth speaker in these trying times?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874009/bluetooth-speaker-gadget-ikea-vappeby</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874009</guid>
      <description>I knew as soon as I laid eyes on Vappeby that I had to have it. Sure, it would be right at home on my desk, given that everything in and around my workstation is from Ikea, from the Skadis on the wall right down to the Sp&#228;nd desk legs. But there was something else [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators ask Meta why it waited so long to make teen accounts private by default</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/874158/senators-meta-teen-accounts-private-default</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874158</guid>
      <description>A group of senators has written a letter to Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg asking why his company delayed launching key protections for users under 18. The letter, signed by Brian Schatz (D-HI), Katie Britt (R-AL), Amy Klobuchar (D-MN), James Lankford (R-OK), and Christopher Coons (D-DE), cites court documents unsealed late last year that revealed claims [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Frontier is a single platform to control your AI agents</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/874258/openai-frontier-ai-agent-platform-management</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874258</guid>
      <description>Managing humans is hard. Managing AI agents is&#8230; also hard. That's why OpenAI is launching a new platform called OpenAI Frontier, which it says will help businesses "build, deploy, and manage" AI agents, even those not made by OpenAI itself. OpenAI's description of Frontier sounds something like HR for AI. "Frontier gives agents the same [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your email is about to get an AI-powered security boost - ExpressVPN launches new email protection and privacy tool for the new world of AI attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/your-email-is-about-to-get-an-ai-powered-security-boost-expressvpn-launches-new-email-protection-and-privacy-tool-for-the-new-world-of-ai-attacks</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dotknQ2jHZFwEow47xgYQ</guid>
      <description>ExpressMailGuard allows unlimited email aliases, automated filtering, and cross-device management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The best way to protect user data is not to collect it in the first place' - top VPN maker reveals ExpressAI, possibly the most secure and safe AI platform around right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/the-best-way-to-protect-user-data-is-not-to-collect-it-in-the-first-place-top-vpn-maker-reveals-expressai-possibly-the-most-secure-and-safe-ai-platform-around-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vM6h2U6pqcpbbqKbAyQodh</guid>
      <description>ExpressAI brings privacy-first AI by applying VPN-level encryption, secure enclaves, and zero data collection, allowing safe AI interactions globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN unveils new standalone password manager &#8211; ExpressKeys is now available for iOS and Android</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/expressvpn-unveils-new-standalone-password-manager-expresskeys-is-now-available-for-ios-and-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XGiQQyzDqJGBLBKQpsuGjF</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN has introduced a dedicated password manager app, ExpressKeys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN launches four new standalone apps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/expressvpn-launches-four-new-standalone-apps-140000686.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac952e6a-804c-4bfa-9336-695b9e60d2f3</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is launching a new cybersecurity suite consisting of four standalone products: a password manager called ExpressKeys, a masked email relay called ExpressMailGuard, an encrypted AI platform called ExpressAI and an app called Identity Defender that monitors public information for any threats to your identity. All four apps are being rolled into ExpressVPN's existing multi-tiered pricing structure.ExpressKeys and ExpressMailGuard have officially launched and are now available to subscribers. Identity Defender launches for U.S. customers only on February 26. ExpressAI was originally pla...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the hell is Moltbook, the social network for AI agents?</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/what-the-hell-is-moltbook-the-social-network-for-ai-agents-140000787.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61095e60-971a-48cc-aad8-4ee2d5144bd6</guid>
      <description>Last week, a new social network was created and it's already gone very, very viral even though it's not meant for human users. I'm talking, of course, about Moltbook, a Reddit-like platform that's populated entirely by AI agents.&#160;The platform has gained a lot of attention since it was created last week, thanks to a lot of wild posts from AI agents that have gone extremely viral among AI enthusiasts on X. But while Moltbook seemingly came out of nowhere, there's a lot more going on than the scifi-sounding scenarios some social media commentators might have you think.&#160;&#160;What is Moltbook and where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Germany fined $70 million for 'influencing' third-party Marketplace pricing</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/amazon-germany-fined-70-million-for-influencing-third-party-marketplace-pricing-140000588.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3707e08e-f109-4e3c-bdef-e3edf4fb8b79</guid>
      <description>The Bundeskartellamt, or the Federal Cartel Office of Germany, has prohibited Amazon from continuing its practice of using mechanisms to control the prices charged by sellers on its platform in the country. Germany&#8217;s competition regulator explained that the company uses &#8220;various price control mechanisms&#8221; to review prices set by third-party Markerplace sellers. If the website deems a specific listing&#8217;s pricing as too high, it allegedly removes the listing altogether or prevents it from being prominently displayed in the Buy Box section that lets you quickly purchase items. If those listings are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla hit with another wrongful death suit over its electronic door handles</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/874283/tesla-door-handle-wrongful-death-tremblett</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T08:59:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874283</guid>
      <description>The mother of 20-year-old man who died after becoming trapped in his burning Tesla Model Y is suing the company over its electronic door handles. It's the latest wrongful death case centering on Tesla's door handles, which have triggered numerous customer complaints over the years and is now under investigation by the federal safety regulators. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony says Ghost of Yotei made a 'significant contribution' to the 8 million PS5 units that were sold in late 2025, a feat that surpassed the Nintendo Switch 2 by 1 million units</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/sony-says-ghost-of-yotei-made-a-significant-contribution-to-the-8-million-ps5-units-that-were-sold-in-late-2025-a-feat-that-surpassed-the-nintendo-switch-2-by-1-million-units</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MSZXsfMKZueCbCj5EjdZj3</guid>
      <description>The PS5 managed to outsell the Nintendo Switch 2 in the latter half of 2025 by 1 million units. The console sold 8 million units between October and December, which Sony partly attributes to Ghost of Yotei and other live service games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce VTC &#233;lectrique polyvalent, parfait en ville comme hors bitume, vient de perdre 1 400 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967271_ce-vtc-electrique-polyvalent-parfait-en-ville-comme-hors-bitume-vient-de-perdre-1-400-e</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967271_ce-vtc-electrique-polyvalent-parfait-en-ville-comme-hors-bitume-vient-de-perdre-1-400-e</guid>
      <description>
Aussi bien &#224; l&#8217;aise hors bitume qu&#8217;en ville, le Scott Axis 20 Wave est un VTC &#233;lectrique polyvalent qui ne manque pas d&#8217;atouts, et dont le prix devient nettement plus abordable en passant de 4 199 euros &#224; 2 799 euros.&#160;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le mode Isolement d&#8217;Apple emp&#234;che le FBI d&#8217;acc&#233;der &#224; l&#8217;iPhone d&#8217;une journaliste</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-mode-isolement-dapple-empeche-le-fbi-dacceder-a-liphone-dune-journaliste.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324328</guid>
      <description>Le FBI est tomb&#233; sur un os lorsque les enqu&#234;teurs ont voulu acc&#233;der &#224; l&#8217;iPhone d&#8217;une journaliste du Washington Post. Le mode Isolement &#233;tait en effet actif, emp&#234;chant les outils d&#8217;extraction num&#233;rique utilis&#233;s par les forces de l&#8217;ordre de contourner les protections de l&#8217;appareil, malgr&#233; sa saisie dans le cadre d&#8217;une enqu&#234;te f&#233;d&#233;rale sensible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Bunny&#8217;s interview on Apple Music could reveal more details about the Super Bowl halftime show</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487505/bad-bunnys-interview-on-apple-music-could-reveal-more-details-about-the-super-bowl-halftime-show</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:34:42</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487505/bad-bunnys-interview-on-apple-music-could-reveal-more-details-about-the-super-bowl-halftime-show</guid>
      <description>Sunday&#8217;s performance is expected to be entirely in Spanish. 
What can viewers expect from Bad Bunny&#8217;s highly anticipated Super Bowl halftime performance? So far, all we know is that he&#8217;s expected to perform solely in Spanish, bringing Latin identity at the center of America&#8217;s most-watched television event.But Bad Bunny could reveal more details Thursday in San Francisco when the Grammy winner speaks ahead of Sunday&#8217;s game.Apple Music&#8217;s Zane Lowe and Ebro Darden will interview Bad Bunny and pregame performers beginning at 10 a.m. Pacific time on Thursday. The Puerto Rican superstar has become o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I bought this cheap air duster and now I no longer worry about dust clogging my gaming PC ever again</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/i-bought-this-cheap-air-duster-and-now-i-no-longer-worry-about-dust-clogging-my-gaming-pc-ever-again</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Me3H8WqwPFNYwoeJJ8np4C</guid>
      <description>And I'm done with buying compressed air cans, too</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TurboTax Deluxe is on sale for only $45 ahead of tax season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/turbotax-deluxe-is-on-sale-for-only-45-ahead-of-tax-season-204848111.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d4b28c6-34f1-44bb-800a-eec732a96ded</guid>
      <description>With the spring approaching, it's time to start thinking about how you'll file your taxes. Unfortunately, with the recent demise of Direct File, there isn't a free, government-provided alternative to TurboTax in 2026, and you'll need to look to other federal programs, including IRS Free File, to file your paperwork. If you don't qualify for Free File, chances are you'll need to dish out cash for Intuit's software. And while we hate to suggest you give money to a company that has spent decades lobbying to ensure America's tax system remains a nightmare, we can at least save you some money if Tu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valve pushes back Steam Machine launch due to storage and memory shortage</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/valve-pushes-back-steam-machine-launch-due-to-storage-and-memory-shortage-133000103.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b47b063f-4ca5-4fe5-9efc-0217d2534780</guid>
      <description>You will have to wait a bit longer before you can buy a Steam Machine &#8212; and you may have to pay more for one, too. Valve had intended to release the console-style SteamOS-powered device in early 2026, and AMD CEO Lisa Su just claimed that the company was on track to start shipping it soon. But in a new post detailing the latest updates for its upcoming Steam products, Valve has revealed that while it&#8217;s still aiming to start selling the console in the first half of the year, it has yet to decide on concrete pricing and a launch date for it. The release of Valve&#8217;s upcoming Steam Frame VR headset...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP price keeps tumbling as Trump-era crypto gains get wiped out. How low can it go in 2026?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487509/xrp-price-usd-today-why-down-how-low-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:29:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487509/xrp-price-usd-today-why-down-how-low-2026</guid>
      <description>Popular cryptocurrencies, including the closely watched XRP token, continue to see their value decline. These factors are driving the downfall.
It&#8217;s a hard time to be an XRP investor. The token, the fifth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, has been on a downward trajectory for nearly half a year. And this week, things have gotten much worse. Here&#8217;s what you need to know about XRP and the beating the coin is taking....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal data stolen during Harvard and UPenn data breaches leaked online - over a million details, including emails, home addresses and more, all published</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/personal-data-stolen-during-harvard-and-upenn-data-breaches-leaked-online-emails-home-addresses-and-more-all-published</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ugemGy4maJe4QhgeWRTNLL</guid>
      <description>Negotiations were unsuccessful, so ShinyHunters decided to leak everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan SCAM Act would require online platforms to crack down on fraudulent ads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/bipartisan-scam-act-would-require-online-platforms-to-crack-down-on-fraudulent-ads-210316594.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a6fc10-dcf2-4949-8e6e-2bb33526fe98</guid>
      <description>Without meaningful deterrents, Big Tech companies will do what's profitable, regardless of the cost to consumers. But a new bipartisan bill could add a check that would make them think twice, at least in one area. On Wednesday, Senators Ruben Gallego (D-AZ) and Bernie Moreno (R-OH) introduced legislation that would require social platforms to crack down on scam ads.The Safeguarding Consumers from Advertising Misconduct (SCAM) Act would require platforms to take reasonable steps to prevent fraudulent or deceptive ads that they profit from. If they don't, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sur Steam aussi, les processeurs Intel reprennent des couleurs</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/intel/2967285_sur-steam-aussi-les-processeurs-intel-reprennent-des-couleurs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/intel/2967285_sur-steam-aussi-les-processeurs-intel-reprennent-des-couleurs</guid>
      <description>
La derni&#232;re enqu&#234;te de mat&#233;riel Steam Survey fait &#233;tat d'une quantit&#233; de machines &#233;quip&#233;es de processeurs Intel l&#233;g&#232;rement plus importante qu'un mois auparavant. Une nouvelle toujours bonne &#224; prendre pour l'&#233;quipe bleue apr&#232;s une longue p&#233;riode de d&#233;clin en la mati&#232;re.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 10 Automatic Cat Feeders Were the Best We Tested (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-automatic-cat-feeders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f57d01d391c274aa7a23f8</guid>
      <description>We tested some of the most popular automatic dry- and wet-food pet feeders to see which ones are worth the money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get one month of the Disney+ and Hulu bundle for only $10</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-one-month-of-the-disney-and-hulu-bundle-for-only-10-192814218.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b6e8a2-981f-4fc9-b476-d49dcaeed4ba</guid>
      <description>You have the best chance to save on streaming services during the holiday shopping season, but throughout the year, the occasional deal pops up that's worth considering. Case in point: this new Disney+ deal. New and eligible returning subscribers can sign up for the Disney+ Hulu bundle (with ads) for $10 for one month of access. That's $3 off the usual price of the bundle for one month, and more than 58 percent off if you consider the cost of each service individually (Disney+ at $12 per month and, separately, Hulu also at $12 per month).
We'd be remiss if we didn't mention that this isn't qui...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Eragon&#8217; Dragon Fantasy Series Is Still Alive at Disney+</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/eragon-disney-plus-tv-update-2000718189</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718189</guid>
      <description>After Brandon Sanderson's 'Cosmere' pickup at Apple TV, series based on hit fantasy books are having a big moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony's holiday PS5  sales dropped 16 percent compared to last year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/sonys-holiday-ps5-sales-dropped-16-percent-compared-to-last-year-130000476.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b70f6a6a-1e53-4b77-88b4-5df26d5a2e5b</guid>
      <description>Sony has now shipped 92.2 million PlayStation 5 consoles in total around the world, but sales were down sharply over the holiday season compared to last year. In its latest earnings report, the company said it shipped eight million PS5s during its key third quarter, 1.5 million (16 percent) lower than in the same period last year. The gaming division still made more profit, though, thanks to a boost in software sales and a low yen.Sony&#8217;s first two quarters this fiscal year saw an increase in PS5s sold, so the holiday decline is a bit surprising. That said, sales during the same period the prev...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sur cette exoplan&#232;te, des tsunamis de vagues de lave g&#233;antes d&#233;fient tout ce que l&#8217;on croyait possible</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cette-exoplanete-tsunamis-vagues-lave-geantes-defient-tout-ce-on-croyait-possible-130923/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 13:57:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cette-exoplanete-tsunamis-vagues-lave-geantes-defient-tout-ce-on-croyait-possible-130923/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le cosmos ne cesse de nous surprendre et la diversit&#233; que l'on a constat&#233;e avec les plan&#232;tes et les lunes du Syst&#232;me solaire semble bel et bien se prolonger au fur et &#224; mesure que l'on explore le monde des exoplan&#232;tes. Celui de la super-Terre 55 Cancri e est peut-&#234;tre encore plus dantesque qu'on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Lockdown Mode on iPhone and how do you enable it?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/lockdown-mode-iphone</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">053e7jTYlPYQZ1SnVNLFSnN</guid>
      <description>The iPhone feature is getting press after foiling the FBI. But just know it's "extreme protection."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
