<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:37:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>'SDUC cards in multi-terabyte capacities are already shipping': but where are these removable memory cards with 4TB or 8TB capacities that Sandisk launched almost two years ago?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sduc-cards-in-multi-terabyte-capacities-are-already-shipping-but-where-are-these-removable-memory-cards-with-4tb-or-8tb-capacities-that-sandisk-launched-almost-two-years-ago</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vGq5ssUdbD7VV77ZxZZsPf</guid>
      <description>The SD Association outlines a future of SD Express speeds and SDUC capacities up to 128TB, although where are the 4TB and 8TB cards announced years ago?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America&#8217;s Largest Particle Collider Just Shut Down. Here&#8217;s What Happens Next</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/americas-largest-particle-collider-just-shut-down-heres-what-happens-next-2000720696</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720696</guid>
      <description>Don't worry, it's all good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Is Crashing the US Court System in Minnesota</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-crashing-us-court-system-minnesota/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69860bd949f2bbe1c3c08afb</guid>
      <description>Petitions demanding people get the chance to be released from ICE custody have overwhelmed courts throughout the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The great RAMaggedon of 2026 might have just claimed the Steam Deck</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/the-great-ramaggedon-of-2026-might-have-just-claimed-the-steam-deck-211958306.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1378371-af26-48d8-9bc6-239d4f87e293</guid>
      <description>Less than a week after Valve admitted that the current shortage (and growing prices) of RAM were affecting its hardware plans, the Steam Deck is completely sold out. The Steam Deck has gone in and out of stock in the past, but as Kotaku notes, the timing does raise the question whether Valve's RAM issues could also be impacting its Linux handheld. The 256GB Steam Deck LCD, and both the 512GB and 1TB models of the Steam Deck OLED, are completely sold out on Steam. Valve announced that it was discontinuing the LCD versions of its handheld and selling through its remaining inventory in December 2...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s Siri revamp reportedly delayed&#8230; again</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/apples-siri-revamp-reportedly-delayed-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092232</guid>
      <description>Apple has been promising a new-and-improved, cutting-edge, AI-powered Siri since it first unveiled Apple Intelligence in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aurora says it will &#8216;triple&#8217; its driverless truck network</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/877191/aurora-driverless-truck-triple-routes-texas</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T16:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877191</guid>
      <description>Aurora, the driverless truck firm founded by former members of Google's pioneering self-driving car team, is branching out. In advance of its quarterly earnings report today, the company announced that a new software update would enable it to triple its driverless network to a total of 10 routes across the Southern US. Currently, Aurora has [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple keeps hitting bumps with its overhauled Siri</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/877494/apple-siri-ai-overhaul-ios-personalized</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T16:08:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877494</guid>
      <description>Apple had been reportedly pushing to introduce some big changes to Siri with iOS 26.4, but now the company is planning to introduce them in later versions of iOS, including iOS 26.5 and iOS 27, Bloomberg reports. Nearly a year ago, Apple delayed planned features for Siri that would let it understand your personal context [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber Eats launches AI assistant to help with grocery cart creation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/uber-eats-launches-ai-assistant-to-help-with-grocery-cart-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092207</guid>
      <description>Uber Eats launched a new AI feature, &#8220;Cart Assistant,&#8221; that can automatically add items to your cart based on text or image prompts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Could Lose Track of Time Appreciating These Immaculate &#8216;Jujutsu Kaisen&#8217; Color Scripts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jujutsu-kaisen-jjk-anime-mappa-crunchyroll-culling-game-color-scripts-2000720652</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720652</guid>
      <description>Mappa continues to elevate Gege Akutami's megapopular manga with kinetic key animation and, more importantly, its painterly scripts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple aurait encore pris du retard pour le nouveau Siri</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/apple-aurait-encore-pris-du-retard-pour-le-nouveau-siri.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325517</guid>
      <description>La version de Siri carburant &#224; l'IA a &#233;t&#233; pr&#233;sent&#233;e par Apple en juin 2024, et elle n'est toujours pas disponible. Avec l'apport des mod&#232;les de Google, l'espoir &#233;tait qu'au moins une partie des fonctions promises par le constructeur soit pr&#233;sente dans iOS 26.4, mais il faut craindre un nouveau retard&#8230; encore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who will own your company&#8217;s AI layer? Glean&#8217;s CEO explains</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/who-will-own-your-companys-ai-layer-gleans-ceo-explains/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3092215</guid>
      <description>Enterprise AI is shifting fast from chatbots that answer questions to systems that actually do the work across an organization. But who will own the AI layer that powers all of it?&#160; Glean, which started as an enterprise search product, has evolved into what it calls an &#8220;AI work assistant,&#8221; aiming to&#160;sit underneath other AI [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk suggests spate of xAI exits have been push, not pull</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/senior-engineers-including-co-founders-exit-xai-amid-controversy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091919</guid>
      <description>At least nine engineers, including two co-founders, have announced their exits from xAI in the past week, fueling online speculation and raising questions about stability at Musk&#8217;s AI company amid mounting controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft says hackers are exploiting critical zero-day bugs to target Windows and Office users</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/microsoft-says-hackers-are-exploiting-critical-zero-day-bugs-to-target-windows-and-office-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092145</guid>
      <description>Critical security flaws targeting Windows and Office users allow hackers to take complete control of a victim's computer by clicking a malicious link or opening a file. Patch now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HDD brand that brought you the 1.8-inch, 2.5-inch, and 3.5-inch hard drives is now back with a $19 pocket-sized personal cloud for your smartphones - just make sure you don't lose it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hdd-brand-that-brought-you-the-1-8-inch-2-5-inch-and-3-5-inch-hard-drives-is-now-back-with-a-usd19-pocket-sized-personal-cloud-for-your-smartphones-just-make-sure-you-dont-lose-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BsWyJa3Eb4Sw7j57DP3DmN</guid>
      <description>Conner introduces Pocket Cloud, a tiny device enabling phone backups, fast charging, 4K recording, expandable microSD storage, and multi-device compatibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get up to 81 percent off ExpressVPN two-year plans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-up-to-81-percent-off-expressvpn-two-year-plans-180602916.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $88 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.14 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Satisfying and great-tasting results' &#8212; this five-star De'Longhi coffee maker is a spectacular value, and it's $200 off at Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/satisfying-and-great-tasting-results-this-five-star-delonghi-coffee-maker-is-a-spectacular-value-and-its-usd200-off-at-best-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uDRJXmY64Zd9Qbd3RShsyV</guid>
      <description>The De'Longhi La Specialista Arte Evo earned full marks in our 2024 review, and it's still an exceptional buy for beginner baristas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s Claude Cowork finally lands on Windows &#8212; and it wants to automate your workday</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/anthropics-claude-cowork-finally-lands-on-windows-and-it-wants-to-automate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6tu9Xga3uy0jV8acrnGjAY</guid>
      <description>Anthropic released its Claude Cowork AI agent software for Windows on Monday, bringing the file management and task automation tool to roughly 70 percent of the desktop computing market and intensifying a remarkable corporate realignment that has seen Microsoft embrace a direct competitor to its longtime AI partner, OpenAI.The Windows launch arrives with what Anthropic calls "full feature parity" with the macOS version: file access, multi-step task execution, plugins, and Model Context Protocol (MCP) connectors for integrating external services. Users can now also set global and folder-specifi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google reporte l&#8217;arriv&#233;e de la premi&#232;re b&#234;ta d&#8217;Android 17</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/android-17-google-confirme-larrivee-dune-beta-mais-previent-dun-piege-pour-vos-donnees.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325357</guid>
      <description>Google acc&#233;l&#232;re la cadence. La firme de Mountain View vient d'officialiser le lancement tr&#232;s prochain de la premi&#232;re b&#234;ta d'Android 17. Une excellente nouvelle qui cache toutefois une petite subtilit&#233; technique pour les testeurs actuels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Success of &#8216;Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is Boosting Its Comic Adaptations</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-success-of-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-is-boosting-its-comic-adaptations-2000720651</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720651</guid>
      <description>Graphic novel versions of the 'Dunk and Egg' stories have risen up in the ranks thanks to HBO's latest 'Game of Thrones' spin-off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway Navimow CEO on why it won't be 'simply piling on features' in its robot lawn mowers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/segway-navimow-ceo-on-why-it-wont-be-simply-piling-on-features-in-its-robot-lawn-mowers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AkUyVRXqJw9M76BhCqttrY</guid>
      <description>Exclusive: 'I have always hoped that technology can truly be applied to people's daily needs.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA just released the smart sensor range I've been waiting for &#8211; simple, helpful gadgets from as little as $6</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/ikea-just-released-the-smart-sensor-range-ive-been-waiting-for-simple-helpful-gadgets-from-as-little-as-usd6</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UkQggqtoVmc5X68yEKv6rK</guid>
      <description>Take a look at my favorite picks from IKEA's new Matter-compatible smart sensor lineup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out, Tesla &#8211; the early Rivian R2 verdicts suggest it's going to be a serious Model Y rival</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/watch-out-tesla-the-early-rivian-r2-verdicts-suggest-its-going-to-be-a-serious-model-y-rival</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YQP7MGTctLPtB8rCJh6WDf</guid>
      <description>World's top media get an early drive with Rivian's R2 and early reports suggest the company is on to a winner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to cancel Mullvad VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-cancel-mullvad-vpn-200000516.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">623efe4e-af14-47df-9cbe-af2899ff83e3</guid>
      <description>This is going to be one of the shortest articles in my series on how to cancel your subscriptions to the best VPNs. Unlike most providers, Mullvad VPN does not automatically renew an expired subscription unless you tell it to. Thanks to its unique pricing approach, cancelling Mullvad is the default option.When you sign up for Mullvad, you pay for as many months upfront as you want at the constant rate of 5 Euro per month (varying with exchange rates). Each month, Mullvad takes 5 Euro out of your account until there's nothing left. If you're no longer satisfied with Mullvad, all you have to do ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT's new fine-tuning method lets LLMs learn new skills without losing old ones</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/mits-new-fine-tuning-method-lets-llms-learn-new-skills-without-losing-old</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7j3Ps59eCY7PWgFnuZ0zhT</guid>
      <description>When enterprises fine-tune LLMs for new tasks, they risk breaking everything the models already know. This forces companies to maintain separate models for every skill.Researchers at MIT, the Improbable AI Lab and ETH Zurich have developed a new technique that enables large language models to learn new skills and knowledge without forgetting their past capabilities.Their technique, called self-distillation fine-tuning (SDFT), allows models to learn directly from demonstrations and their own experiments by leveraging the inherent in-context learning abilities of modern LLMs. Experiments show th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get into a16z&#8217;s super-competitive Speedrun startup accelerator program</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/how-to-get-into-a16zs-super-competitive-speedrun-startup-accelerator-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091907</guid>
      <description>TechCrunch spoke to a16z partner Joshua Lu for some tips on standing out for the Speedrun program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une base sur la Lune avant Mars ? Ce que r&#233;v&#232;le le nouveau virage strat&#233;gique de Musk</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/elon-musk-base-lune-avant-mars-ce-revele-nouveau-virage-strategique-musk-131175/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:57:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/elon-musk-base-lune-avant-mars-ce-revele-nouveau-virage-strategique-musk-131175/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Mais pourquoi n&#8217;y a-t-il pas pens&#233; plus t&#244;t&#160;? Au lieu de partir vers Mars, Elon Musk parle beaucoup d'implanter une base permanente sur la Lune. Futura s&#8217;est mis dans la t&#234;te de Musk pour comprendre les motivations de son projet lunaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash App adds payment links so you can get paid in a DM</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/11/cash-app-adds-payment-links-so-you-can-get-paid-in-a-dm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3092022</guid>
      <description>The new feature allows users to share payment requests in a variety of digital settings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Bunny streams jumped 175% in the U.S. after the Super Bowl</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91491304/bad-bunny-super-bowl</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-11T19:41:40</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91491304/bad-bunny-super-bowl</guid>
      <description>Apple Music found that Bad Bunny&#8217;s show playlist&#160;became its most-played set list shortly after the performance. 
The legacy of Bad Bunny&#8217;s&#160;Super Bowl halftime show&#160;continues. Streams of his catalog jumped 175% in the U.S. on Monday, the day after the Super Bowl, when compared to the previous Monday, Feb. 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic beefs up Claude's free tier as OpenAI prepares to stuff ads into ChatGPT's</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-beefs-up-claudes-free-tier-as-openai-prepares-to-stuff-ads-into-chatgpts-194100939.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b59bf80f-7990-40bd-a200-fe0fc30cae84</guid>
      <description>Anthropic is upgrading Claude's free tier, apparently to capitalize on OpenAI's planned integration of ads into ChatGPT. On Wednesday, Anthropic said free Claude users can now create files, connect to external services, use skills and more.Anthropic added the ability for paid users to create files in September. Starting today, free users of the chatbot can also create and edit Excel spreadsheets, PowerPoint presentations, Word docs and PDFs. Claude's file creation abilities are powered by Sonnet 4.5.Free users can now create and edit Excel spreadsheets, PowerPoint presentations, Word docs, and...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
