<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:36:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>India&#8217;s AI boom pushes firms to trade near-term revenue for users</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/india-ai-boom-pushes-firms-to-trade-near-term-revenue-for-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095753</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT and rivals are testing whether India's massive AI user boom can translate into paying customers as free offers wind down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth&#8217;s Pentagon AI bro squad includes a former Uber executive and a private equity billionaire</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/884165/pentagon-anthropic-emil-michael-steve-feinberg</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T20:59:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884165</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers covering the broligarchs, the influencers, and the (potentially conscious) artificial intelligence models scrambling for power in Washington. If you're not a subscriber yet, assert your humanity against the will of the machines by signing up here. Very important news: Do you want to tell me [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Touchscreen MacBook Pro Will Have a Very iPhone-Like Screen, Report Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-touchscreen-macbook-pro-will-have-a-very-iphone-like-screen-report-says-2000726201</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726201</guid>
      <description>It'll reportedly have an OLED screen featuring a Dynamic Island. But users can still reportedly de-emphasize touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia challenger AI chip startup MatX raised $500M</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/nvidia-challenger-ai-chip-startup-matx-raised-500m/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096626</guid>
      <description>The startup was founded by former Google TPU engineers in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&amp;#8217;s new age verification tools block underage app downloads where required by law</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/884136/apple-age-verification-assurance-underage-app-downloads</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T19:45:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884136</guid>
      <description>Apple, like many others, has had to launch age verification features in response to new requirements for age checks in many regions, and on Tuesday, the company announced new details about its tools that developers can use to "meet their age assurance obligations under upcoming U.S. and regional laws, including in Brazil, Australia, Singapore, Utah, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic says Claude Code transformed programming. Now Claude Cowork is coming for the rest of the enterprise.</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/anthropic-says-claude-code-transformed-programming-now-claude-cowork-is</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">605uYzglHYY2My97pa5Wqg</guid>
      <description>Anthropic opened its virtual "Briefing: Enterprise Agents" event on Tuesday with a provocation. Kate Jensen, the company's head of Americas, told viewers that the hype around enterprise AI agents in 2025 "turned out to be mostly premature," with many pilots failing to reach production. "It wasn't a failure of effort, it was a failure of approach, and it's something we heard directly from our customers," Jensen said.The implicit promise: Anthropic has figured out the right approach, and it starts with the playbook that made Claude Code one of the most consequential developer tools of the past y...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-driving tech startup Wayve raises $1.2B from Nvidia, Uber, and three automakers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/self-driving-tech-startup-wayve-raises-1-2b-from-nvidia-uber-and-three-automakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096448</guid>
      <description>Major automakers, tech giants, AI companies, and chipmakers are all trying to get a piece of Wayve.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
