<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:42:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FTC declines to enforce a kids privacy law for data collected to verify users&#8217; ages</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/885592/ftc-age-verification-childrens-online-privacy-enforcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:42:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885592</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission is encouraging companies to adopt age verification technologies by announcing it will not enforce a children's online privacy law against certain websites that collect and use minors' personal data in order to verify their ages. "Age verification technologies are some of the most child-protective technologies to emerge in decades," Christopher Mufarrige, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis Lost $26.3 Billion Last Year, Says It&#8217;s Pivoting Back to Combustion Engines</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stellantis-lost-26-3-billion-last-year-says-its-pivoting-back-to-combustion-engines-2000727243</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727243</guid>
      <description>Jeep's parent company is struggling as the U.S. swerves away from EVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm won&amp;#8217;t be announcing Windows gaming handhelds at GDC after all</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/885314/qualcomm-wont-be-announcing-windows-gaming-handhelds-at-gdc-after-all</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:25:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885314</guid>
      <description>In January, Qualcomm hinted to The Verge that it might finally bring its powerful Arm-based Snapdragon processors to Windows gaming handhelds at the 2026 Game Developers Conference in San Francisco - just in time to challenge Nvidia's own first Arm gaming CPU and Intel's first dedicated handheld gaming chips. But plans have shifted, Qualcomm now [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opera has turned 30&#8212;and is celebrating with a compelling tribute to web nostalgia</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/opera-has-turned-30-and-is-celebrating-with-a-compelling-tribute-to-web-nostalgia-2000725245</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725245</guid>
      <description>It certainly wasn't like this in the old days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, we&#8217;re getting Prada Meta AI glasses, right?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/so-were-getting-prada-meta-ai-glasses-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097528</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg was at Prada's fashion week event in Milan, leaving everyone to wonder if we're getting Meta AI glasses under the Prada brand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO approves the iPhone and iPad for classified use</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/nato-approves-the-iphone-and-ipad-for-classified-use-200857276.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d60a12-647a-4d50-bc41-47df7dd9a4c8</guid>
      <description>Apple's mobile devices are secure enough for NATO. Following extensive testing by the German government, the iPhone and iPad are now considered secure enough for the NATO-restricted classified level.Germany's Federal Office for Information Security (Bundesamt f&#252;r Sicherheit in der Informationstechnik, or BSI) tested the devices. BSI first approved the iPhone and iPad for governmental use by German authorities in 2022. To take the additional step of NATO approval, Apple says BSI conducted exhaustive technical assessments, comprehensive testing and deep security analysis.Unless you work for NATO...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Chinese AI Chatbots Censor Themselves</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-how-chinese-ai-chatbots-censor-themselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a08892157af8f83feddbc8</guid>
      <description>Researchers from Stanford and Princeton found that Chinese AI models are more likely than their Western counterparts to dodge political questions or deliver inaccurate answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuite massive de donn&#233;es m&#233;dicales&#160;: jusqu&#8217;&#224; 15 millions de Fran&#231;ais touch&#233;s, dont des personnalit&#233;s publiques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fuite-massive-de-donnees-medicales-jusqua-15-millions-de-francais-touches-dont-des-personnalites-publiques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1328501</guid>
      <description>&#192; chaque jour suffit sa fuite des donn&#233;es. Aujourd'hui, c'est une base de donn&#233;es m&#233;dicales qui serait en acc&#232;s libre sur le dark web. Les informations de sant&#233; de millions de Fran&#231;ais sont en danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney World&#8217;s Villains Land Is Pivoting Itself Away From Scaring Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-worlds-villains-land-is-pivoting-itself-away-from-scaring-kids-2000727140</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727140</guid>
      <description>Inspired by the rival Epic Universe, Disney's Villains Land is reportedly becoming a little less evil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s Eddy Cue calls F1 &#8216;unscripted drama at its best&#8217; &#8212; here&#8217;s our first look at the Apple TV race-day experience and a rare Netflix collaboration for Drive to Survive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/apples-eddy-cue-calls-f1-unscripted-drama-at-its-best-heres-our-first-look-at-the-apple-tv-race-day-experience-and-a-rare-netflix-collaboration-for-drive-to-survive</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cxnp44AAEHseoMjMWmF8Ah</guid>
      <description>With the Australian Grand Prix around the corner, Apple TV is readying its formal launch of broadcasting Formula 1 in the US, with multi-camera angles, and Eddy Cue teasing "this will be the highest quality."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditching Discord? Make sure you take this one important step before deleting your account</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/ditching-discord-make-sure-you-take-this-one-important-step-before-deleting-your-account</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EXvKbqcpET6KPTE2Y7ikSX</guid>
      <description>Discord isn't pulling out of its age verification plans, so here's how to delete your account and messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We want to create a new Android OS&#8217;: Samsung says it&#8217;s going to beat Apple with its bold new Google-powered 'AI OS'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/we-want-to-create-a-new-android-os-samsung-says-its-going-to-beat-apple-with-its-bold-new-google-powered-ai-os</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MV4XmTB8RJnjeXZxsBV966</guid>
      <description>Samsung has spoken about its vision for an AI OS that can help you out without even being asked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI-generated Resident Evil Requiem review briefly made it on Metacritic</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/an-ai-generated-resident-evil-requiem-review-briefly-made-it-on-metacritic-194414929.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a6afb98-195e-496a-9169-b0f47fa77c16</guid>
      <description>Review aggregator Metacritic has removed a review of Resident Evil Requiem because it was AI-generated, Kotaku reports. The review was published by UK gaming site VideoGamer, but appears to be "written" by a fake AI journalist rather than a real person.While it's unfortunately difficult to confirm with 100 percent accuracy whether a piece of text is AI-generated, you don't have to read VideoGamer's review for long to notice all the ways it feels off. The biggest giveaway, beyond heavy use of contrived metaphors, is a striking lack of detail beyond what you could glean from a trailer for the ga...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Space raises $10M seed to demo novel space computers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/sophia-space-raises-10m-seed-to-demo-novel-space-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096833</guid>
      <description>The company's modular computer tiles offer a new vision for space data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS reportedly detained a Columbia University student and content creator</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/885525/columbia-university-student-detained-dhs-influencer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:49:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885525</guid>
      <description>Department of Homeland Security agents "made misrepresentations" to gain access to a Columbia University residential building and detained a student early Thursday morning, according to a statement issued by the school. "Our understanding at this time is that the federal agents made misrepresentations to gain entry to the building to search for a 'missing person,'" [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Cybercab Program Manager Exits, Brags About Pushing the Boundaries of Safety</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-cybercab-program-manager-exits-brags-about-pushing-the-boundaries-of-safety-2000727134</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727134</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's xAI has also seen a number of departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory shortage could cause the biggest dip in smartphone shipments in over a decade</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/memory-shortage-could-cause-the-biggest-smartphone-shipments-dip-in-over-a-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097542</guid>
      <description>IDC says phone makers will ship only 1.12 billion smartphones as compared to 1.26 billion last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla sues Calif. DMV after agency called its autopilot deceptive marketing</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tesla-sues-california-dmv-autopilot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">046Y09xVIXfAOkNtWOldUvZ</guid>
      <description>Tesla is fighting back against a California decision that blocked using "autopilot" to advertise vehicles, even after the company complied with demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&amp;#8217;s F1 series Drive to Survive will stream on Apple TV, too</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/885538/netflix-f1-drive-to-survive-apple-tv-streaming</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:40:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885538</guid>
      <description>Netflix's sports docuseries obsession started a few years ago with F1: Drive to Survive, but when the eighth season premieres after midnight tonight, it will also be available on Apple TV. Now that Apple TV has a five-year deal to be the US streaming home for F1 races, subscribers in the US will be able [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsair is halting Drop sales after March 25th</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/884824/corsair-ending-drop-shopping-site</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:34:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884824</guid>
      <description>The Drop store, which was acquired by gaming gear giant Corsair in 2023, was a haven for mechanical keyboard enthusiasts and audiophiles to discover and buy hard-to-find gear - sometimes at surprisingly good prices. The company will cease sales after March 25th at 11:59PM PT, which is also the cut off to redeem Drop Rewards. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new $25 action game from the creator of Just Cause arrives on April 8</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/the-new-25-action-game-from-the-creator-of-just-cause-arrives-on-april-8-193058294.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a63981a4-05f8-4b38-abc3-1bd44d27344d</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re still waiting for releases dates for Remedy&#8217;s in-development Max Payne remakes, but if you&#8217;re in need of a noir fix sooner than that, keep an eye on Liquid Swords&#8217; Samson: A Tyndalston Story, which just got a release date of April 8.
The debut game from a new studio formed by Just Cause creator Christofer Sundberg, Samson looks like a tighter, more narrative-led experience than Avalanche&#8217;s proudly ridiculous open-world series, but no less packed with over-the-top action. You play as the eponymous Samson McRay, a man down on his luck and seriously in debt in the punishing city of Tyndalst...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The reason behind Walmart&#8217;s cottage cheese recall isn&#8217;t what most shoppers expect</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499156/the-reason-behind-walmarts-cottage-cheese-recall-isnt-what-most-shoppers-expect</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499156/the-reason-behind-walmarts-cottage-cheese-recall-isnt-what-most-shoppers-expect</guid>
      <description>The recall affects multiple Great Value cottage cheese varieties sold between Feb. 17 and Feb. 20, according to the FDA.
If you&#8217;ve been caught up in the cottage cheese craze, take heed: The U.S. Food and Drug Administration recommends that you toss tubs of cottage cheese purchased from Walmart stores in 24 states because of concerns the ingredients weren&#8217;t fully pasteurized....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple and Netflix are teaming up to share Formula 1 programming</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/apple-and-netflix-are-teaming-up-to-share-formula-1-programming-192829498.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5015a81-21b4-47ba-9443-43fa1411a455</guid>
      <description>Apple and Netflix have entered into a rather surprising partnership. The dynamic streaming duo will share Formula 1 programming, according to The Hollywood Reporter. The deal allows Netflix to stream the F1 Canadian Grand Prix in May, along with Apple TV. On the flipside, Apple TV and Netflix will both air season eight of the docuseries Drive to Survive.
The Netflix-created series spotlights various F1 drivers and their teams. The season premieres at midnight on both platforms. Eddy Cue, Apple&#8217;s senior VP of services, said that Netflix "has played a pivotal role in growing F1 since the launch ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Comeback Season 3 trailer: Valerie Cherish is back, baby!</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/the-comeback-season-3-trailer-lisa-kudrow</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02M6UZojOLAyRqwLOCK7JzG</guid>
      <description>Lisa Kudrow and Michael Patrick King's cult classic "The Comeback" returns for a third and final season March 22 on HBO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prices of AMD's popular Ryzen 5 series doubled since February 1st to $400 &#8212; nobody knows why, but here's what may have happened</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/prices-of-amds-popular-ryzen-5-series-doubled-since-february-1st-to-usd400-nobody-knows-why-but-heres-what-may-have-happened</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Tt29QDT3A6LDXntdR39odM</guid>
      <description>AMD Ryzen 5 prices doubled to $400 in February 2026 amid memory shortages, wafer constraints, and thinning retail inventory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral AI inks a deal with global consulting giant Accenture</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/mistral-ai-inks-a-deal-with-global-consulting-giant-accenture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097539</guid>
      <description>Mistral AI lands a partnership with Accenture, the consultant that has also recently announced partnerships with rivals OpenAI and Anthropic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eBay will lay off 800 workers, or 6 percent of its staff</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ebay-will-lay-off-800-workers-or-6-percent-of-its-staff-191500844.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c814602-aeaf-40c5-b434-6c35f816cfba</guid>
      <description>eBay announced that it is cutting about 800 jobs from its global staff. "We are taking steps to reinvest across our business and align our structure with our strategic priorities, which will affect certain roles across our workforce," the retailer said in a statement as reported by Bloomberg. This move will see about 6 percent of eBay's current full-time workers laid off. Bloomberg noted that eBay would continue hiring in "key areas" but did not specify what those fields are.The downsizing follows a week of business updates for eBay. On the same day it shared its latest financial results, the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO says iPhones are secure enough to handle classified data</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885516/nato-iphones-ipads-restricted-classified-information</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:08:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885516</guid>
      <description>The iPhone and iPad have been approved to hold NATO-restricted information, according to an announcement on Thursday. That means off-the-shelf devices running iOS 26 and iPadOS 26 can handle classified information "without requiring special software or settings," Apple says. The NATO-restricted designation is the lowest level of classified information, and it applies to information that [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le t&#233;lescope James-Webb r&#233;v&#232;le un &#171; cr&#226;ne &#187; cosmique dont on devine le cerveau !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-telescope-james-webb-revele-crane-cosmique-on-devine-cerveau-131713/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-telescope-james-webb-revele-crane-cosmique-on-devine-cerveau-131713/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>L'astre ressemblant &#224; un cerveau appel&#233; PMR 1 a &#233;t&#233; surnomm&#233; la n&#233;buleuse du &#171; Cr&#226;ne expos&#233; &#187; par les scientifiques de la d&#233;funte mission Spitzer, avec un t&#233;lescope spatial observant dans l'infrarouge. Cette n&#233;buleuse plan&#233;taire, situ&#233;e &#224; environ 5 000 ann&#233;es-lumi&#232;re dans la constellation des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo expands test drives to Chicago and Charlotte</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/waymo-testing-phase-chicago-charlotte</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00I9ZIa0xpnAeefGXDe3lmX</guid>
      <description>Waymo is testing an expansion into Chicago and Charlotte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about streaming F1 on Apple TV</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/everything-you-need-to-know-about-streaming-f1-on-apple-tv-190600771.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d802e22-feb0-438c-84ed-01e8df49578a</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;ve known Apple would follow up its blockbuster film F1: The Movie with live coverage of F1 races in 2026. Now that we&#8217;re approaching the first grand prix weekend of the year, the company has provided details on what fans can expect to see inside the Apple TV app and beyond. There&#8217;s already a dedicated F1 channel in the Apple TV app, which is where you&#8217;ll stream races live when the time comes. You can also watch practice sessions, sprint races and both pre- and post-race coverage. Apple offers a number of additional F1 videos there (I&#8217;d recommend watching the one on the new rules) and you&#8217;ll...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On &#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217;, the Theater Kids Are All Right</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-recap-episode-8-tilly-2000726815</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726815</guid>
      <description>And also returning 'Discovery' star Sylvia Tilly. But mostly the theater kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neanderthal Men and Human Women Were Most Likely to Hook Up, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/neanderthal-men-and-human-women-were-most-likely-to-hook-up-study-finds-2000726658</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726658</guid>
      <description>Geneticists have found an interesting pattern in how early humans and Neanderthals interbred&#8212;and it wasn't balanced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You &#8216;Agentic&#8217; Enough for the AI Era?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/silicon-valley-agentic-individuals-future-of-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699ca89387b4ddbea4d1c6a0</guid>
      <description>Silicon Valley built AI coding agents that can handle most of the grunt work. Now, the most valuable skill in tech is deciding what they should do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 prompts for Gemini 3.1 that really show off what it can do</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/gemini/5-prompts-for-gemini-3-1-that-really-show-off-what-it-can-do</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cMMGJkovvWQ74KcDKFSxD</guid>
      <description>Showcasing Gemini 3.1 Pro's most impressive features</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta sues advertisers in Brazil and China over 'celeb bait' scams</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-sues-advertisers-in-brazil-and-china-over-celeb-bait-scams-190000268.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88ee3eff-08ff-4e55-9039-e876ca0e4132</guid>
      <description>Meta has sued the people and groups behind three scam operations that used images and deepfakes of celebrities to lure users to scam websites. According to the company, the three entities were based in China and Brazil and targeted people in the US, Japan and other countries. The ads promoted fraudulent investment schemes and fake health products.Meta said that it had filed lawsuits against several people in Brazil who promoted fake or unapproved healthcare products and online courses promoting them. The company also sued a China-based entity it says used ads featuring celebrities "as part of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big banks retreated from mortgages after the 2008 housing market crash&#8212;now this Fed governor wants them back</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499267/housing-market-independent-mortgage-banks-retreated-after-2008-crash-fed-governor-wants-them-back</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499267/housing-market-independent-mortgage-banks-retreated-after-2008-crash-fed-governor-wants-them-back</guid>
      <description>After more than a decade of &#8216;significant migration&#8217; toward nonbanks, the Federal Reserve&#8217;s vice chair for supervision, Michelle Bowman, says it&#8217;s time to consider adjusting policy.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's still in our portfolio. We're not end of life [on] the product': Samsung exec on why the Galaxy S25 Edge is so important and here to stay</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/its-still-in-our-portfolio-were-not-end-of-life-the-product-samsung-exec-on-why-the-galaxy-s25-edge-is-so-important-and-here-to-stay</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aU2Cags5TnnuY8SPQ5cNBS</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S26 Edge was a no-show at Galaxy Unpacked, but there are a few very good reasons, and reasons for hope about an edgy future.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
