<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:28:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Siri is a Gemini</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/863340/siri-is-a-gemini</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T09:21:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863340</guid>
      <description>We know how the next-generation Siri is supposed to work. Apple showed it off in 2024, made commercials about it, and generally promised that AI would change the way we used our gadgets forever. And then, well, none of that came to pass. So Apple made a deal: It tapped Google's Gemini technology to help [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Man Gets 5 Years in Prison for Setting Fire to Cybertruck</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/arizona-man-gets-5-years-in-prison-for-setting-fire-to-cybertruck-2000710896</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710896</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk remains at large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French court backs LFP and orders top VPNs to block illegal football streams</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/french-court-backs-lfp-and-orders-top-vpns-to-block-illegal-football-streams</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nydPwwmn3Czp3hHmy92TkA</guid>
      <description>A court in France has served its third blocking order against NordVPN, Surfshark, Proton VPN, ExpressVPN, and CyberGhost since May 2025, as the fight against online piracy heats up. Here's what at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes TV et vid&#233;oprojecteurs : la deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque s&#8217;attaque &#224; encore plus de mod&#232;les avec des r&#233;ductions &#224; plus de 1 000 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933417_soldes-tv-et-videoprojecteurs-la-deuxieme-demarque-sattaque-a-encore-plus-de-modeles-avec-des-reductions-a-plus-de-1-000</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2933417_soldes-tv-et-videoprojecteurs-la-deuxieme-demarque-sattaque-a-encore-plus-de-modeles-avec-des-reductions-a-plus-de-1-000</guid>
      <description>
Nous sommes dans le deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque des soldes d'hiver avec encore plus d'offres sur les TV 4K et les vid&#233;oprojecteurs foisonnent chez les e-commer&#231;ants. Si l'heure est venue de changer d'&#233;cran, voici notre s&#233;lection des meilleures offres sur les TV 4K et les vid&#233;oprojecteurs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our favorite 3-in-1 wireless charger is on sale for 32 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/our-favorite-3-in-1-wireless-charger-is-on-sale-for-32-percent-off-214707127.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc4c398-0e79-409e-bf43-095a0740d354</guid>
      <description>Now that the winter holidays are well and truly past, now's the perfect time to take stock of your tech setup. If you were gifted (or gifted yourself) some new gear in December, make sure that you've got the proper accessories to keep that gear performing at its best. If a new way to power all those batteries would be a benefit, Amazon's currently running a discount on an excellent wireless charging pad. The UGREEN MagFlow Qi2 3-in-1 Charger Station 25W is on sale for $95. That's only a little bit above the lowest price we've ever seen for the product (which was $90), and it's still a 32 perce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of &#8216;micro&#8217; apps: non-developers are writing apps instead of buying them</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/the-rise-of-micro-apps-non-developers-are-writing-apps-instead-of-buying-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082739</guid>
      <description>A new era of app creation is here. It's fun, it's fast, and it's fleeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony, Anker, and other headphones have a serious Google Fast Pair security vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/863338/google-fast-pair-whisperpair-security-vulnerability-bluetooth-headphones-speakers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T09:13:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863338</guid>
      <description>Several Bluetooth audio devices from companies like Sony, Anker, and Nothing are susceptible to a new flaw that can allow attackers to listen in on conversations or track devices that use Google's Find Hub network, as reported by Wired. Researchers from KU Leuven University's Computer Security and Industrial Cryptography group in Belgium discovered several vulnerabilities [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix will give WBD movies 45-day theater exclusivity if deal goes through</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/netflix-will-give-wbd-movies-45-day-theater-exclusivity-if-deal-goes-through-141223786.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edff5e5c-58a3-46cc-ae59-ade329f56281</guid>
      <description>The fate of Warner Bros. Discovery remains the biggest story in Hollywood, with Paramount Skydance refusing to back down from its rival bid to the proposed Netflix acquisition of the company. If the Netflix deal does go through, the company&#8217;s co-chief executive, Ted Sarandos, has attempted to ease concerns around what that could mean for theaters.
In an interview with The New York Times, Sarandos responded to a question about his company&#8217;s commitment to the theatrical business by insisting that he has no interest in bringing a swift end to it. "We will run that business largely like it is toda...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The maker of our favorite affordable wired audiophile headphones has a new mid-range model &#8212; but mid-range is relative, isn't it&#8230;</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/headphones/the-maker-of-our-favorite-affordable-wired-audiophile-headphones-has-a-new-mid-range-model-but-mid-range-is-relative-isnt-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcnGniwVch7eFN4iJHb9Ck</guid>
      <description>Austrian Audio fills the gap between its affordable and audiophile models</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung built a stunning micro-LED TV where the bezel is also a screen &#8212; and I saw it in action</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/samsung-built-a-stunning-micro-led-tv-where-the-bezel-is-also-a-screen-and-i-saw-it-in-action</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">binLds6Y8cpy2kNDpu2cKk</guid>
      <description>Samsung's 140-inch next-gen TV shows how micro-LED can create very cool new design opportunities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grubhub says hackers stole company data in recent breach - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/grubhub-says-hackers-stole-company-data-in-recent-breach-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Aqm6GNMJsVbX2GvwqhuwYZ</guid>
      <description>Grubhub hack is being linked to ShinyHunters and the August 2025 Salesloft Drift fiasco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver : voici les offres &#224; saisir avant de partir en week-end</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-offres-week-end-2e-demarque</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-offres-week-end-2e-demarque</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver suivent leur chemin et nous arrivons au d&#233;j&#224; au deuxi&#232;me week-end ! Au programme : toujours plus d'offres Tech &#224; prix cass&#233;s, que ce soient les smartphones, les tablettes, les t&#233;l&#233;viseurs 4K, et surtout les ordinateurs portables, gaming ou de bureautique. M&#234;me le gaming s'invite avec la PS5 en promo. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta sacrifie la VR professionnelle</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/meta-sacrifie-la-vr-professionnelle.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320667</guid>
      <description>Que reste-t-il du m&#233;tavers ? Plus grand chose depuis l'annonce cette semaine de la charrette de licenciements au sein des Reality Labs de Meta. Mais dans le d&#233;tail, la purge est pire que pr&#233;vue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen Labs raises $69M after viral billboard hiring stunt to scale AI customer interviews</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/listen-labs-raises-usd69m-after-viral-billboard-hiring-stunt-to-scale-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wOG0z6nm91FOeUqhpizqI</guid>
      <description>Alfred Wahlforss was running out of options. His startup, Listen Labs, needed to hire over 100 engineers, but competing against Mark Zuckerberg's $100 million offers seemed impossible. So he spent $5,000 &#8212; a fifth of his marketing budget &#8212; on a billboard in San Francisco displaying what looked like gibberish: five strings of random numbers.The numbers were actually AI tokens. Decoded, they led to a coding challenge: build an algorithm to act as a digital bouncer at Berghain, the Berlin nightclub famous for rejecting nearly everyone at the door. Within days, thousands attempted the puzzle. 430 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Everyone Is Suddenly in a &#8216;Very Chinese Time&#8217; in Their Lives</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-chinese-time-of-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69652f49d61f8a53819e4204</guid>
      <description>The viral meme isn&#8217;t really about China or actual Chinese people. It's a symbol of what Americans believe their own country has lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visions of Four Heroes is Dynasty Warriors Origins at its best, but issues I had with the base game remain</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/visions-of-four-heroes-is-dynasty-warriors-origins-at-its-best-but-issues-i-had-with-the-base-game-remain</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">U2jHNNpSEjWer3CnQJBmUg</guid>
      <description>Dynasty Warriors Origins&#8217; Visions of Four Heroes expansion trims the fat to deliver a near uncompromised musou experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms episode 1 on HBO Max?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/hbo-max/what-is-the-release-date-for-a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-episode-1-on-hbo-max</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hkV32NiwjGjsFSGTiDzzCg</guid>
      <description>HBO's new Game of Thrones TV adaptation comes out soon &#8211; here's when and where you can watch it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink Floyd: Live at Pompeii MCMLXXII is getting the 4K Blu-ray and Dolby Atmos treatment at long last</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/pink-floyd-live-at-pompeii-mcmlxxii-is-getting-the-4k-blu-ray-and-dolby-atmos-treatment-at-long-last</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e988m2LJ2y4WvnhkqQtve3</guid>
      <description>Pink Floyd's classic concert is coming to 4K Blu-ray for the first time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is closing down its VR meeting rooms as part of its wider cull</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/meta-is-closing-down-its-vr-meeting-rooms-as-part-of-its-wider-cull-140000422.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b688365f-2f22-4cf6-9ce1-bc4dbbd6d64e</guid>
      <description>Meta is killing the standalone Workrooms app on February 16, 2026. The company presented Workrooms as a virtual reality space where teams can meet and collaborate in an immersive environment when it launched the product. Now Meta says its Horizon platform has evolved enough to support &#8220;a wide range of productivity apps and tools,&#8221; so it &#8220;made the decision to discontinue Workrooms as a standalone app.&#8221;The company recently slashed its spending on the metaverse and started the process to lay off more than 1,000 employees from its Reality Labs division. Due to those layoffs and organizational chan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilo launches AI-powered Slack bot that ships code from a chat message</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/kilo-launches-ai-powered-slack-bot-that-ships-code-from-a-chat-message</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4n1PCTjNdJeZfBO5xcGJ6q</guid>
      <description>Kilo Code, the open-source AI coding startup backed by GitLab cofounder Sid Sijbrandij, is launching a Slack integration that allows software engineering teams to execute code changes, debug issues, and push pull requests directly from their team chat &#8212; without opening an IDE or switching applications.The product, called Kilo for Slack, arrives as the AI-assisted coding market heats up with multibillion-dollar acquisitions and funding rounds. But rather than building another siloed coding assistant, Kilo is making a calculated bet: that the future of AI development tools lies not in locking en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested ChatGPT Translate against Google Translate &#8212; here's which one wins</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/i-tested-chatgpt-translate-against-google-translate-heres-which-one-wins</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xKQ2PFhryBWgbnnACDotr8</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT Translate challenges Google Translate in a head-to-head test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian regulators are investigating Activision Blizzard's monetization practices</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/italian-regulators-are-investigating-activision-blizzards-monetization-practices-135057481.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22d4c6b1-a620-4031-92d5-6e08fef57131</guid>
      <description>The Italian Competition Authority (AGCM) has opened two investigations into Microsoft-owned game studio Activision Blizzard, centered around the mobile games Diablo Immortal and Call of Duty: Mobile. The AGCM alleges the free-to-play games use "misleading and aggressive practices" to encourage in-game purchases.
Regulators say the games rely on a "deceptive user interface design" meant to encourage longer and more frequent play sessions while bombarding players with reminders and opportunities to spend real money in-game. Players might be reminded to buy a limited-time item before it's gone or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's latest MagSafe charger is on sale for $30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-latest-magsafe-charger-is-on-sale-for-30-141707636.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ce1496f-1e48-428a-bb64-aefda025bc79</guid>
      <description>One way you can reduce the number of cables you have to deal with on the regular is by investing in a few wireless chargers. Those with iPhones should consider Apple's own MagSafe charger not only because of its sleek and effective design, but also because it's on sale right now at Amazon. The Qi2.2-rated MagSafe charger is down to $30 for the one-meter version, or $40 for the two-meter version.


If you have an iPhone 16, iPhone 17 or iPhone Air, this cable can charge your device at 25W as long as it's connected to a 30W power adapter on the other end. While you'll need a more recent iPhone t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame has expanded its remit to 'literally anything' and I'm not sure it's good news for one of my favorite vacuum brands</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/dreame-has-expanded-its-remit-to-literally-anything-and-im-not-sure-its-good-news-for-one-of-my-favorite-vacuum-brands</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rR2KdwspXogy2CX6xUc85K</guid>
      <description>From action cameras to TVs to coffee machines to smart rings, Dreame has it covered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dans l&#8217;espace, le feu devient une sph&#232;re&#8230; et c&#8217;est un cauchemar pour les astronautes</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/espace-espace-feu-devient-sphere-cest-cauchemar-astronautes-130245/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:49:03 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/espace-espace-feu-devient-sphere-cest-cauchemar-astronautes-130245/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Dans l&#8217;espace, le feu ne se comporte&#160;pas comme sur Terre. En apesanteur, la flamme se pr&#233;sente en effet sous une forme fascinante&#8230; mais dangereuse. Face &#224; ce comportement atypique et au risque accru d&#8217;incendie, la Nasa et des chercheurs, comme ceux du projet Firespace, cherchent &#224; comprendre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baisse de prix pour le Xpeng G6 en France, la voiture &#233;lectrique rivale du Tesla Model Y qui se recharge en 12 minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xpeng/2945477_baisse-de-prix-pour-le-xpeng-g6-en-france-la-voiture-electrique-rivale-du-tesla-model-y-qui-se-recharge-en-12-minutes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xpeng/2945477_baisse-de-prix-pour-le-xpeng-g6-en-france-la-voiture-electrique-rivale-du-tesla-model-y-qui-se-recharge-en-12-minutes</guid>
      <description>
Au royaume des SUV &#233;lectriques, le Tesla Model Y est toujours le roi, mais son h&#233;g&#233;monie est mise &#224; mal par une concurrence de plus en plus f&#233;roce. &#192; commencer par le Xpeng G6, qui se dote d'une nouvelle version plus abordable mais qui se recharge toujours en 12 minutes.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Id&#233;al pour les familles, le v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique Nakamura E-Cross City s&#8217;all&#232;ge de 200 &#8364; lors des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2560353_ideal-pour-les-familles-le-velo-electrique-nakamura-e-cross-city-sallege-de-200-euros-lors-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2560353_ideal-pour-les-familles-le-velo-electrique-nakamura-e-cross-city-sallege-de-200-euros-lors-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Le Nakamura E-Cross City, un v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique que l'on pourrait qualifier de midtail, est un mod&#232;le taill&#233; pour les familles, gr&#226;ce notamment &#224; son porte-bagages pouvant supporter jusqu'&#224; 60 kg de charge ; parfait pour transporter un enfant, par exemple. Actuellement, on trouve ce VAE affich&#233; &#224; 1 099,99 euros au lieu de 1 299,99 euros pendant les soldes chez Intersport.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Watch : cette nouvelle fonctionnalit&#233; d&#8217;alerte pourrait bien sauver votre journ&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2945499_pixel-watch-cette-nouvelle-fonctionnalite-dalerte-pourrait-bien-sauver-votre-journee</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2945499_pixel-watch-cette-nouvelle-fonctionnalite-dalerte-pourrait-bien-sauver-votre-journee</guid>
      <description>
Google travaillerait &#224; une nouvelle fonction d'alerte sur ses montres Pixel Watch. Elle permettrait de pr&#233;venir l'utilisateur lorsqu'il s'&#233;loigne trop de son smartphone et risque de l'oublier. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XREAL files lawsuit against rival smart glass maker Viture</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/xreal-files-lawsuit-against-rival-smart-glass-maker-viture-133018692.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e519e04-ca2b-46bc-8145-ca18295fa581</guid>
      <description>San Francisco-founded Smart glasses maker Viture has been sued in a US court by rival XREAL over claims it infringed on its patents, XREAL announced in a press release. The complaint, lodged in a federal Texas court, accuses Viture of illegally incorporating XREAL's patented tech into its products including the Luma Pro, Luma Ultra and Beast models.&#160;
"The lawsuit is not merely about enforcing a single patent," the company wrote. "It is about stopping a pattern of intellectual property infringement that undermines the integrity of innovation and endangers continued technological development in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dos Equis brings back the Most Interesting Man&#8212;and bets nostalgia still sells beer</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475751/dos-equis-brings-back-the-most-interesting-man-and-bets-nostalgia-still-sells-beer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475751/dos-equis-brings-back-the-most-interesting-man-and-bets-nostalgia-still-sells-beer</guid>
      <description>Dos Equis is reviving its most iconic campaign, bringing back Jonathan Goldsmith and a familiar catchphrase.
The Most Interesting Man is set to make a return to television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix and Sony just struck a global streaming megadeal &#8211; here are 5 confirmed movies to look forward to</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/netflix-and-sony-just-struck-a-global-streaming-megadeal-here-are-5-confirmed-movies-to-look-forward-to</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UWJXy6GUvUSgL8oVN6owP</guid>
      <description>Sony films will be available on Netflix first after their theatrical run, all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ and Hulu deal: Get the bundle for only $10 for one month</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/disney-and-hulu-deal-get-the-bundle-for-only-10-for-one-month-192814913.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b6e8a2-981f-4fc9-b476-d49dcaeed4ba</guid>
      <description>You have the best chance to save on streaming services during the holiday shopping season, but throughout the year, the occasional deal pops up that's worth considering. Case in point: this new Disney+ deal. New and eligible returning subscribers can sign up for the Disney+ Hulu bundle (with ads) for $10 for one month of access. That's $3 off the usual price of the bundle for one month, and more than 58 percent off if you consider the cost of each service individually (Disney+ at $12 per month and, separately, Hulu also at $12 per month).
We'd be remiss if we didn't mention that this isn't qui...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Sideshow&#8217; concerns and billionaire dreams: What I learned from Elon Musk&#8217;s lawsuit against OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/863319/highlights-musk-v-altman-openai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T08:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863319</guid>
      <description>This is an excerpt of Sources by Alex Heath, a newsletter about AI and the tech industry, syndicated just for The Verge subscribers once a week. Elon Musk first sued OpenAI in February 2024. Despite OpenAI's repeated attempts to throw it out, the case is now headed to a jury trial on April 27th in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of our favorite budgeting apps is only $50 for the year for new users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/one-of-our-favorite-budgeting-apps-is-only-50-for-the-year-for-new-users-204507183.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764214b-3509-4628-8631-8692fa12e904</guid>
      <description>The start of the new year is a great time to get your finances in order, and a good budgeting app can help with that. Instead of laboring over a spreadsheet, you can try one of our favorite budgeting apps for less than usual. Monarch Money is running a sale that gives new users 50 percent off one year of the service, bringing the final cost down to just $50. Just use the code NEWYEAR2026 at checkout to get the discount.
Monarch Money makes for a capable and detailed budgeting companion. You can use the service via apps for iOS, Android, iPadOS or the web, and Monarch also offers a Chrome exten...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung : quand les promotions des soldes cassent les prix des Galaxy S, Galaxy Book, Galaxy Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2939747_samsung-quand-les-promotions-des-soldes-cassent-les-prix-des-galaxy-s-galaxy-book-galaxy-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2939747_samsung-quand-les-promotions-des-soldes-cassent-les-prix-des-galaxy-s-galaxy-book-galaxy-watch</guid>
      <description>
La deuxi&#232;me d&#233;marque des soldes apporte son lot de nouvelles offres Samsung&#8239;! Et &#224; l&#8217;approche du week-end, c&#8217;est le moment id&#233;al pour saisir les meilleurs deals du g&#233;ant sud-cor&#233;en. Entre TV QLED &#233;l&#233;gants, smartphones &#224; clapet et &#233;crans Ultra Wide OLED, il y en a pour tous les go&#251;ts &#8212; avec, en vedette, un vid&#233;oprojecteur affichant plus de 60&#8239;% de remise&#8239;!
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS changes mind, will continue selling the RTX 5070 Ti after all</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/asus-changes-mind-will-continue-selling-the-rtx-5070-ti-after-all-130934271.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1752fbb-9aad-4ef9-9be1-00875b1788e6</guid>
      <description>After telling the YouTube channel Hardware Unboxed that it was putting its RTX 5060 Ti 16GB and 5070 Ti into "end-of-life status," ASUS has backtracked on those comments and now says the GPUs will remain on sale.&#160;
"Certain media may have received incomplete information from an ASUS PR representative regarding these products," the company said in a dedicated press release." The GeForce RTX 5070 Ti and GeForce RTX 5060 Ti 16 GB have not been discontinued or designated as end-of-life (EOL). ASUS has no plans to stop selling these models."
ASUS further clarified that supply fluctuations, primarily...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des s&#233;nateurs exigent des comptes sur le Trump T1, le smartphone aux 59 millions de dollars de pr&#233;commandes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2945409_des-senateurs-exigent-des-comptes-sur-le-trump-t1-le-smartphone-aux-59-millions-de-dollars-de-precommandes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2945409_des-senateurs-exigent-des-comptes-sur-le-trump-t1-le-smartphone-aux-59-millions-de-dollars-de-precommandes</guid>
      <description>
L&#8217;absence du smartphone Trump sur le march&#233; commence &#224; interroger des s&#233;nateurs qui souhaitent saisir la FTC, l&#8217;autorit&#233; du commerce aux &#201;tats-Unis, pour obtenir des explications.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 common myths about AI tools, debunked</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/5-common-myths-about-ai-tools-debunked</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FhErFhoKSNXH5FVJ8pT2Z9</guid>
      <description>Debunking widespread myths about AI tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried Fujifilm's wacky new 3-in-1 Instax cinema hybrid &#8211; there's no other retro camera like it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/instant-cameras/i-tried-fujifilms-wacky-new-3-in-1-instax-cinema-hybrid-theres-no-other-retro-camera-like-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jdH9X7mzYe6sbRQLjVhFqM</guid>
      <description>The Fujifilm Instax Mini Evo Cinema is an instant camera / super-8-style video camera mash up, with over 100 looks inspired from the last 100 years of image making. It really is something</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail could fix your biggest regret soon &#8211; evidence grows that you&#8217;ll be able to change your embarrassing email handle</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gmail-could-fix-your-biggest-regret-soon-evidence-grows-that-youll-be-able-to-change-your-embarrassing-email-handle</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ttj5Z2NazXnaEs6jr82Uwg</guid>
      <description>Google is even closer to letting you change your old Gmail address, and this is my chance to put my embarrassing handle behind me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google may bring a new 'forgotten device' feature to its Pixel Watch ecosystem in its quiet quest to catch up with Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/google-may-bring-a-new-forgotten-device-feature-to-its-pixel-watch-ecosystem-in-its-quiet-quest-to-catch-up-with-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YidUNk3NzcB2GhKsUMM7k</guid>
      <description>Pixel Watches might soon alert you if you've left your phone behind, and vice versa, incorporating a feature Apple Watches have had for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Reminds Us We Need Ordinary Heroes More Than Ever</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-reminds-us-we-need-ordinary-heroes-more-than-ever-2000710818</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710818</guid>
      <description>Bertie Carvel, who plays the sympathetic Baelor Targaryen in the new HBO series, breaks it down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Best Wi-Fi Routers of 2026 for Working, Gaming, and Streaming</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-wifi-routers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6246df08ceb527a328de3864</guid>
      <description>Don&#8217;t suffer the buffer. These WIRED-tested home routers will deliver reliable internet across your home, whatever your needs or budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok tightens age verification across Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/tiktok-tightens-age-verification-across-europe-130000847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36f79865-fe4b-44c4-8881-3fceb8abe7d2</guid>
      <description>TikTok is bolstering its age-verification measures across Europe. In the coming weeks, the platform will roll out upgraded age-detection tech in the European Economic Area, as well as in the UK and Switzerland. The systems will assess the likely age of a user based on their profile information and activity. When the tech flags an account that may belong to a user aged under 13 (the minimum age to use TikTok), a specialist moderator will assess whether it should be banned. TikTok will send users in Europe a notification to tell them about these measures and offer them a chance to learn more.Als...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your headphones may be tracking you &#8211; how a Google Fast Pair exploit lets hackers spy in seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cyber-security/your-headphones-may-be-tracking-you-how-a-google-fast-pair-exploit-lets-hackers-spy-in-seconds</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2LRkvPdyDj4ms4ZDdiNRuR</guid>
      <description>Researchers have discovered that hackers can access millions of speakers and headphones in just a few seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Leon &#8212; here are eight fan-favorite characters I think could show up in Resident Evil Requiem</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/forget-leon-here-are-eight-fan-favorite-characters-i-think-could-show-up-in-resident-evil-requiem</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ncPvPdi7qojm3Wr3pj45mP</guid>
      <description>Leon is returning in Resident Evil Requiem, but is he bringing any classic series comrades with him?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This hidden vacuum feature could change the way you clean your home</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/this-hidden-vacuum-feature-could-change-the-way-you-clean-your-home</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">x9zoCLuA57Qu3ZrZAqhuqQ</guid>
      <description>As a vacuum tester, this is the feature I always look for &#8211; and your vacuum probably already has it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Dirty Talk: When Daytime Talk Shows Ruled TV online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/dirty-talk-when-daytime-talk-shows-ruled-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aAMvxfLj5mFAVatoetbVfX</guid>
      <description>Want to watch Dirty Talk: When Daytime Talk Shows Ruled TV from anywhere? Stream every wild reveal as daytime TV&#8217;s most chaotic era gets exposed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew McConaughey trademarking himself saying 'alright, alright, alright' is a preview of Hollywood&#8217;s coming AI identity crisis</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/matthew-mcconaughey-trademarking-himself-saying-alright-alright-alright-is-a-preview-of-hollywoods-coming-ai-identity-crisis</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i6dcXKq3PQYz4BVwsgQu2S</guid>
      <description>Matthew McConaughey&#8217;s trademark filings on his own performance are a smart but incomplete defense against the rise of AI-generated celebrity clones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is shutting down its Horizons VR for businesses - I doubt it will be missed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/meta-is-shutting-down-its-horizons-vr-for-businesses</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4yq7eJPJdWsJgSPz9NMFST</guid>
      <description>Meta is pulling Horizon Workrooms as it backs out of the commercial VR business to focus on consumer products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The massive Currys New Year sale ends soon &#8212; here are the 14 best tech deals I'd buy before they're gone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/the-massive-currys-new-year-sale-ends-soon-here-are-the-14-best-tech-deals-id-buy-before-theyre-gone</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Y5S9keaaX9ejhY6WrDJsr</guid>
      <description>The Currys New Year sale is set to end very soon, so I've looked through the offers one final time to pick out the 14 best tech deals you don't want to miss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch What Drives You with John Cena season 2 &#8212; it's *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/what-drives-you-with-john-cena-season-2-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EAzGwge4TEEzCSjLTbrouB</guid>
      <description>Want to watch Cena blend fast cars with candid, motivational celebrity chats? Here's how to watch What Drives You with John Cena season 2 for FREE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNK faces backlash over heavy-handed generative AI usage in Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves Season 2 trailer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/snk-faces-backlash-over-heavy-handed-generative-ai-usage-in-fatal-fury-city-of-the-wolves-season-2-trailer</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pkyFvVhW3wiN6a3gRRzHx</guid>
      <description>Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves' Season 2 trailer makes liberal use of generative AI &#8212; and fans are rightfully incensed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Plug Guide (2026): When You Should and Shouldn&#8217;t Use One</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/do-you-need-a-smart-plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6966c65c4cce920695222367</guid>
      <description>Smart plugs can add controls to any outlet, but they aren&#8217;t perfect for everything. Here&#8217;s our guide to using one and which ones to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is shutting down New World next year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/amazon-is-shutting-down-new-world-next-year</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pVAQbFv7eqE9yKABMdutH3</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced that its MMO game New World will be shut down come the end of January 2027.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The bill for tech&#8217;s Trump 2.0 appeasement may be coming due</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474672/tech-ceos-trump-minneapolis-ice</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T12:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474672/tech-ceos-trump-minneapolis-ice</guid>
      <description>A year into Trump&#8217;s second term, Big Tech has made nice when tenable and otherwise kept its mouth shut. But its &#8216;This is fine&#8217; strategy may be slipping.
Hello again, and thanks for reading Fast Company&#8217;s Plugged In.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
