<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:26:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s When Elon Musk Will Finally Have to Reckon With His Nonconsensual Porn Generator</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/heres-when-elon-musk-will-finally-have-to-reckon-with-his-nonconsensual-porn-generator-2000707799</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707799</guid>
      <description>It would be deeply embarrassing if the law has to go into effect before X acts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governments grapple with the flood of non-consensual nudity on X</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/08/governments-grapple-with-the-flood-of-non-consensual-nudity-on-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081355</guid>
      <description>For the past two weeks, X has been flooded with AI manipulated nude images, created by the Grok AI chatbot &#8212; and governments around the world are promising to take action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#8217;t Sleep on &#8216;MAD,&#8217; One of the Wildest Sci-Fi Manga Out Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dont-sleep-on-mad-one-of-the-wildest-sci-fi-manga-out-now-2000707695</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707695</guid>
      <description>'MAD' is basically what would happen if 'Alien: Earth' was a manga and its battles were on par with 'Chainsaw Man' and 'Jujutsu Kaisen.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best earbuds we&#8217;ve tested for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T17:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s hard to buy a bad pair of wireless earbuds these days, and with constant discounts and deals wherever you look, now is as good a time as any to splurge on the pair you&#8217;ve been eyeing. The market has come a long way since the early era of true wireless earbuds, when we had [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch A Thousand Blows &#8212; stream Stephen Graham boxing drama online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/a-thousand-blows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Kk94XDHvSz8t2ajcg4FMpJ</guid>
      <description>Want to watch A Thousand Blows from anywhere? Stream every brutal showdown as Hezekiah navigates the fight to survive London&#8217;s bare-knuckle underworld.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG propose aussi des TV g&#233;ants jusqu&#8217;&#224; 115 pouces</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2936153_lg-propose-aussi-des-tv-geants-jusqua-115-pouces</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2936153_lg-propose-aussi-des-tv-geants-jusqua-115-pouces</guid>
      <description>
Lors du CES 2026 LG a pr&#233;sent&#233; deux nouvelles s&#233;ries de t&#233;l&#233;viseurs LCD utilisant un syst&#232;me de r&#233;tro&#233;clairage Mini LED, les QNED85 et QNED90 qui monte jusqu&#8217;&#224; 115 pouces et dont voici tous les d&#233;tails.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handwriting is my new favorite way to text with the Meta Ray-Ban Display glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/handwriting-is-my-new-favorite-way-to-text-with-the-meta-ray-ban-display-glasses-213744708.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82355909-2fe4-4eae-b967-7199d226403b</guid>
      <description>When Meta first announced its display-enabled smart glasses last year, it teased a handwriting feature that allows users to send messages by tracing letters with their hands. Now, the company is starting to roll it out, with people enrolled in its early access program getting it first,I got a chance to try the feature at CES and it made me want to start wearing my Meta Ray-Ban Display glasses more often. When I reviewed the glasses last year, I wrote about how one of&#160; my favorite tings about the neural band is that it reduced my reliance on voice commands. I've always felt a bit self conscious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ Adding TikTok-Style Vertical Videos to Attract the Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-adding-tiktok-style-vertical-videos-to-attract-the-kids-2000707794</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707794</guid>
      <description>Those movies and stuff are too wide and long to be real content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell unveils 52-inch pseudo-6K monitor that's bound to give you a neck torticollis &#8212; but if you want a true 6K experience, don't buy it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dell-unveils-52-inch-pseudo-6k-monitor-thats-bound-to-give-you-a-neck-torticollis-but-if-you-want-a-true-6k-experience-just-dont-buy-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uW6T8rLmf99j7B7Za7sNXg</guid>
      <description>Dell&#8217;s 52-inch UltraSharp monitor offers four virtual desktops, a wide IPS Black panel, extensive ports, and ergonomic adjustments, but lacks true 6K resolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IXI&#8217;s autofocusing lenses are almost ready to replace multifocal glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/ixis-autofocusing-lenses-multifocal-glasses-ces-2026-212608427.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79bc9e2d-ff4b-4c8c-9b18-476bb6b041a4</guid>
      <description>While wave upon wave of smartglasses and face-based wearables crash on the shores of CES, traditional glasses really haven&#8217;t changed much over the hundreds of years we&#8217;ve been using them. The last innovation, arguably, was progressive multifocals that blended near and farsighted lenses &#8212; and that was back in the 1950s. It makes sense that autofocusing glasses maker IXI thinks it&#8217;s time to modernize glasses.
After recently announcing a 22-gram (0.7-ounce) prototype frame, the startup is here in Las Vegas to show off working prototypes of its lenses, a key component of its autofocus glasses, whi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Chinese Robot Vacuum Company Spun Off Not One but 2 EV Brands</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-what-chinese-companies-showed-off-at-ces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695eb8f8bbd4755fc7697654</guid>
      <description>The pivot doesn&#8217;t look out of place at CES, where Chinese electronics companies are increasingly applying their manufacturing prowess to new industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 could well be the year of the $500 32GB DDR5 memory module &#8212; experts predict DDR will go up by 60% in Q1 2026 alone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/2026-could-well-be-the-year-of-the-usd500-32gb-ddr5-memory-module-experts-predict-ddr-will-go-up-by-60-percent-in-q1-2026-alone</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AMaNVjgtEKxAptVrnbQyJk</guid>
      <description>2026 could see 32GB DDR5 memory costing $500 as analysts warn of steep DRAM price rises driven by server demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Coin Zcash Drops 20% as Core Dev Team Departs Electric Coin Company</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/privacy-coin-zcash-drops-20-as-core-dev-team-departs-electric-coin-company-2000707755</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707755</guid>
      <description>The fears of centralizing forces in crypto are creating a lot of skittishness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics unveils production-ready version of Atlas robot at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/boston-dynamics-unveils-production-ready-version-of-atlas-robot-at-ces-2026-234047882.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">207c5a82-d64f-4628-b6d7-ef00999cd1c5</guid>
      <description>After years of testing its humanoid robot (and forcing it to dance), Boston Dynamics' Atlas is entering production. The robotics company said at CES 2026 that the final product version of the robot is being built now, and the first companies that will receive deployments are Hyundai, Boston Dynamics' majority shareholder, and Google DeepMind, the firm's newly minted AI partner.This final enterprise version of Atlas "can perform a wide array of industrial tasks," according to Boston Dynamics, and is specifically designed with consistency and reliability in mind. Atlas can work autonomously, via...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Emmys Create a New &#8216;Legacy Award&#8217; to Honor Old Favorites</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/emmys-legacy-award-franchises-2000707772</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707772</guid>
      <description>The nostalgia-fueled prize is designed to honor shows that have made 'a profound and lasting impact' on culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS will accept 2025 tax returns starting Jan. 26</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471589/irs-2025-tax-returns-jan-26</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-08T20:56:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471589/irs-2025-tax-returns-jan-26</guid>
      <description>Tax experts have warned that this year&#8217;s filing season could be hampered by federal layoffs and buyouts.
Jan. 26 marks the official start date of the 2026 tax filing season, when the IRS will begin accepting and processing 2025 tax returns. April 15 is the filing deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer put a waifu in a bottle at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/razer-put-a-waifu-in-a-bottle-at-ces-2026-205315908.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b82353d-fa02-44f4-a29f-03c921796cd4</guid>
      <description>Last year Razer showed off Project Ava as a digital assistant that lived inside your computer to help adjust settings or provide gaming tips. But now at CES 2026, the company&#8217;s AI companion platform has gotten a major glow-up while moving into some new digs.&#160;Now, in lieu of being constrained entirely to your PC&#8217;s screen, Razer has given Project Ava a real home in the form of a small tube that can display a 5.5-inch animated hologram of the AI&#8217;s avatar. You&#8217;ll still need to connect it to your computer via USB-C to provide Ava with the power and data it needs. However, all of your companion&#8217;s ot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal data on over 700,000 exposed by Illinois government agency</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/personal-data-on-over-700-000-exposed-by-illinois-government-agency</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5v58FY9nBdnyZqTihJfidL</guid>
      <description>A human mistake resulted in a major data leak in late September 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truly phoneless AI glasses to the first specs with HDR10 &#8212; here are the best smart glasses from CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/truly-phoneless-ai-glasses-to-the-first-specs-with-hdr10-here-are-the-best-smart-glasses-from-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">W7AMzeHYh3QscoEnsmg77f</guid>
      <description>We got 20-26 vision at CES this year thanks to the five best smart glasses announced at the show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to Demolish Iconic Towers Used to Test Saturn V, Space Shuttle</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-to-demolish-iconic-towers-used-to-test-saturn-v-space-shuttle-2000707670</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707670</guid>
      <description>One of the test stands was last used as a drop tower for microgravity testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will let you exclude Shorts from search results</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/youtube/youtube-will-let-you-exclude-shorts-from-search-results-204500097.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ad1c89f-f184-4edc-8abe-d92077cb182d</guid>
      <description>YouTube introduced some new filters to its advanced search tools today. Possibly the most exciting change is that Shorts are now listed as a content type, so the three-minute-or-less videos can be excluded as results in your searches. This is a welcome update for any of us who have been on the hunt for a long-form explainer only to wade through dozens of ten-second clips before finding anything close to our goal. Especially with the addition of even more AI slop last year thanks to the Google Veo 3 engine, an option to exclude Shorts may look even more appealing.The other updates include a pai...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands-on with Fender Audio's headphones and speakers at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/hands-on-with-fender-audios-headphones-and-speakers-at-ces-2026-203104561.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17e8d8d5-ed2c-4cd6-b88b-119c4d9244e4</guid>
      <description>Fender Audio may have announced its new headphones and speakers right before CES, but Las Vegas afforded us the first opportunity to see the brand&#8217;s new lineup in person. Fender Audio is a Fender-owned brand from Riffsound that&#8217;s designing and making new devices after licensing the name. It&#8217;s been a while since the guitar and amplifier company made any general-use speakers of its own, and this new arrangement is similar to what Zound was doing with Marshall for a spell. Logistics out of the way, let&#8217;s get down to what the Mix and Ellie are like in the flesh. First, the Mix headphones offer a m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 CES gadgets you can buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/19-ces-gadgets-you-can-buy-right-now-164325541.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">486c0883-fd9d-4677-b8fe-ca2db36c7354</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is nearly over and it&#8217;s been a fruitful one with a lot of new, weird and impressive tech. But you don&#8217;t have to wait until later this year to get your hands on some of the things announced this week in Las Vegas. A surprising number of gadgets are up for pre-order, if not outright available to buy already, from chargers and docks to projectors, keyboards and smart home gear. CES remains a place for companies to showcase concepts and big ideas, but these are the gadgets that have real prices and real order buttons as of today. Check out all of the CES 2026 gadgets you can buy right now...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra n&#8217;est pas encore l&#224;, mais les coques de protection sont d&#233;j&#224; pr&#234;tes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2936111_le-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-nest-pas-encore-la-mais-les-coques-de-protection-sont-deja-pretes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2936111_le-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-nest-pas-encore-la-mais-les-coques-de-protection-sont-deja-pretes</guid>
      <description>
Le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra n'est pas encore officialis&#233;, mais on a d&#233;j&#224; vu des coques de protection pr&#234;tes pour le smartphone, au CES 2026.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
