<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:54:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta hits pause on Ray-Ban Display expansion plans</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856216/meta-ray-ban-display-smart-glasses-international-expansion-paused</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T07:46:32-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856216</guid>
      <description>International customers who had their sights set on Meta's Ray-Ban Display smart glasses will have to wait a little longer. Meta announced that it's pausing plans to launch the glasses in France, Italy, Canada, and the UK by early 2026, due to "unprecedented demand and limited inventory." "Since launching last fall, we've seen an overwhelming [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch ASB Classic 2026 in Auckland: live stream WTA tennis online, start time, what TV channel?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tennis/asb-classic-2026-auckland-wta-tennis</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rhmAU86PhM6BojXGGDi7KU</guid>
      <description>Watch free trial tennis streams today in the season's first WTA event from Auckland, New Zeland &#8211; 2026 ASB Classic TV channels, broadcasters and streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Performance defines the PC experience&#8217; &#8212; Samsung aims to take down Apple with its new Galaxy Book6 laptops and Intel&#8217;s latest tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/performance-defines-the-pc-experience-samsung-aims-to-take-down-apple-with-its-new-galaxy-book6-laptops-and-intels-latest-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27LeeQiXgPmu4gsiZ4yKK8</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s new Galaxy Book6 laptops "combine unparalleled speed and power with dependable AI" &#8211; could these be the MacBook-killers PC users have been waiting for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ways to walk for fitness, from rucking to the viral 'Japanese walking' trend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/7-ways-to-walk-for-fitness-from-rucking-to-the-viral-japanese-walking-trend</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UFnHx6Kx3PvVp9ZD3UEok9</guid>
      <description>7 walking workouts you need to know about, from beginner-friendly, low-impact routines to tougher sweat sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Suunto 9 Peak Pro &#224; -60 % : une montre id&#233;ale pour les sportifs au budget serr&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930427_la-suunto-9-peak-pro-a-60-une-montre-ideale-pour-les-sportifs-au-budget-serre</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930427_la-suunto-9-peak-pro-a-60-une-montre-ideale-pour-les-sportifs-au-budget-serre</guid>
      <description>
Propos&#233;e &#224; seulement&#160;199 euros&#160;au lieu de 499 euros, la Suunto 9 Peak Pro devient une vraie bonne affaire et se trouve &#234;tre un choix malin pour les runners et traileurs au budget serr&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free fait le m&#233;nage&#160;: pourquoi vous pouvez d&#233;sinstaller Freebox Connect d&#232;s aujourd&#8217;hui</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/free-fait-le-menage-pourquoi-vous-pouvez-desinstaller-freebox-connect-des-aujourdhui.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318382</guid>
      <description>C'&#233;tait dans l'air, c'est d&#233;sormais officiel : Free fusionne Freebox Connect avec son application principale. Gestion du Wi-Fi, factures et contr&#244;le parental sont enfin r&#233;unis dans une interface unique et simplifi&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three new JBL gaming headsets are on the way and one of them is crammed with high-end features</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/three-new-jbl-gaming-headsets-are-on-the-way-and-one-of-them-is-crammed-with-high-end-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i5MEBtJrh4AmtzfFNxVz5V</guid>
      <description>JBL has revealed three new gaming headsets coming to the US this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birdbuddy's new smart bird feeder can ID birds by their songs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/birdbuddys-new-smart-bird-feeder-can-id-birds-by-their-songs-122000692.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5b28b23-f82e-4bdb-881b-cbece313aa42</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m seeing a ton of smart bird feeders again this year at CES &#8212; and I&#8217;m inexplicably drawn to them. Perhaps because the idea of birds nibbling on seeds and flying away represents a natural purity and freedom that doesn&#8217;t exist within the halls of CES. Birdbuddy was one of the first smart bird feeder brands, with a wildly successful Kickstarter back in 2020. And this year, they&#8217;ve added birdsong to their species identification capabilities. Two new feeders, the Birdbuddy 2 and the Birdbuddy 2 Mini both have the new feature, but the latter is a more affordable, starter version. The Bird Buddy 2 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose is giving away free Ultra Open earbuds &#8212; heres how to get a pair</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-bose-ultra-open-earbuds-free-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02cot66VEjbDluZwWSpsvHO</guid>
      <description>Bose is giving away free refurbished Ultra Open earbuds when you buy the QuietComfort Ultra 2 earbuds. Here's how to get the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pok&#233;mon TCG: Mega Evolutions Phantasmal Flames Booster Display Box is down to market value at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-pokemon-tcg-mega-evolutions-phantasmal-flames-booster-box-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03GCmSdqXrJTP00L8mxeTzH</guid>
      <description>The Pok&#233;mon TCG: Mega Evolutions Phantasmal Flames Booster Display Box is on sale for $254.67 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Bird Feeding Tips for the Peak of Bird Watching Season (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/our-best-tips-for-winter-bird-feeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69307bd10c11887cee72a781</guid>
      <description>Winter is often the best time for bird-watching at bird feeders&#8212;here&#8217;s what ornithologists recommend to get the most out of the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla met &#224; jour le Model Y : &#233;cran 16 pouces et int&#233;rieur noir pour tous, enfin presque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2930995_tesla-met-a-jour-le-model-y-ecran-16-pouces-et-interieur-noir-pour-tous-enfin-presque</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2930995_tesla-met-a-jour-le-model-y-ecran-16-pouces-et-interieur-noir-pour-tous-enfin-presque</guid>
      <description>
Vous en avez marre de voir la Chine servir de laboratoire pour Tesla ? Moi aussi. Le constructeur vient de mettre &#224; jour silencieusement tous ses Model Y produits &#224; Shanghai. Au menu : la disparition tant attendue du ciel de toit gris et un &#233;cran 16 pouces bien plus s&#233;rieux. Et nous ? On regarde les photos.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta has delayed the international rollout of its display glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-has-delayed-the-international-rollout-of-its-display-glasses-120056833.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3132a727-43db-414f-8c5e-b8a6c0276dc2</guid>
      <description>Meta is pausing release of its Ray-Ban Display smart glasses to the UK, France, Italy and Canada due to "unprecedented demand and limited inventory," the company said on Monday at CES 2026. There's no new date for the expansion that was originally set for early 2026. "We'll continue to focus on fulfilling orders in the US while we re-evaluate our approach to international availability," Meta wrote on its blog.
Since Meta's display glasses first went on sale, acquiring them has been a challenge. They're not available online and can only be found in a limited number of retail outlets including s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timekettle Reveals a Major Upgrade to Its Real-Time, In-Ear AI Translation Technology at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/timekettles-real-time-in-ear-ai-translation-tech-just-got-a-massive-upgrade-2000705424</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705424</guid>
      <description>The Babel fish real-time translator is becoming a reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clarke, the Comet in &#8216;Greenland,&#8217; Wasn&#8217;t Actually Named After the Sci-Fi Legend</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/clarke-the-comet-in-greenland-wasnt-actually-named-after-the-sci-fi-legend-2000705684</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705684</guid>
      <description>Sorry, '2001: A Space Odyssey' fans, but the cosmic menace in the Gerard Butler disaster series has a more ordinary inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta's EMG wristband is moving beyond its AR glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/metas-emg-wristband-is-moving-beyond-its-ar-glasses-120000503.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">917ebb29-267e-4f45-824a-1ae21cbc52a1</guid>
      <description>Meta has been experimenting with EMG technology for years. In 2025, the company commercialized it for the first time in its Meta Ray-Ban Display glasses, which users control via a dedicated neural band that is able to interpret subtle muscle movements in the wrist.Now, at CES 2026, the company is offering its first look at how its neural band could be used to control devices outside of its smart glasses lineup. Meta has teamed up with Garmin, as well as a handful of research partners, to explore some intriguing use cases for its wrist-based controller.The social media company has previously wo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum computing momentum grows: D-Wave announces first major breakthrough of 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469364/d-wave-quantum-computing-first-major-breakthrough-of-2026-scalable-technology</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469364/d-wave-quantum-computing-first-major-breakthrough-of-2026-scalable-technology</guid>
      <description>D-Wave, one of the industry&#8217;s rising stars, is continuing to make progress toward scalable quantum technology.
A new year, a new quantum computing breakthrough: D-Wave, one of the quantum industry&#8217;s rising stars, announced &#8220;an industry-first breakthrough&#8221; on Tuesday as it works to make quantum computing commercially viable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI says 40 million people use ChatGPT for healthcare every day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/openai/openai-says-40-million-people-use-chatgpt-for-healthcare-every-day</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zsw9vNjeVXbWi8yyqqBGcY</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's latest report states that 40 million people use ChatGPT for health-related questions every day. Should we be worried?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Kimmel gives a 13-minute recap of everything Trump did over the holidays</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/jimmy-kimmel-trump-holiday-recap</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07DVGWXIYtAu8sOibgLVR5e</guid>
      <description>Jimmy Kimmel has recapped everything Donald Trump did over the holidays, including the U.S. attack on Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit your fitness goals with the Fitbit Sense 2, now $60 off at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-fitbit-sense-2-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04PVC4OmusiwPvAQlc3apKQ</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 6, the Fitbit Sense 2 is on sale at Amazon for $189.95. This limited-time deal saves you 24% off its list price of $249.95.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung just revealed the first creaseless foldable screen &#8211; and it could be a serious hint towards the iPhone Fold</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/samsung-just-revealed-the-first-creaseless-foldable-screen-and-it-could-be-a-serious-hint-towards-the-iphone-fold</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NZidFuT49QwvHKW8LUZnye</guid>
      <description>Samsung has shown off a foldable screen that appears to have no crease at all, and it's likely to be used by the foldable iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valerion just unveiled two elite ultra-short throw projectors made for massive 4K visuals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/projectors/valerion-just-unveiled-two-elite-ultra-short-throw-projectors-made-for-massive-4k-visuals</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4R2bk6n6Xw3MuWnrqbMzeb</guid>
      <description>AWOL's ultra-short throw projector is made for massive images</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG's and Samsung's 2026 mid-range OLED TVs both look great, but I know which one I'm more excited for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lgs-and-samsungs-2026-mid-range-oled-tvs-both-look-great-but-i-know-which-one-im-more-excited-for</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i63CN4ySzGLZ2Bfgbt8da9</guid>
      <description>LG and Samsung's mid-range OLEDs, the LG C6 and Samsung S90H, have both been revealed at CES 2026, and I've picked my most anticipated of the two.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, Lego, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philips 65OLED959 : le TV Ambilight des gamers et des cin&#233;philes est &#224; moiti&#233; prix pour le d&#233;but de l&#8217;ann&#233;e 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2854359_philips-65oled959-le-tv-ambilight-des-gamers-et-des-cinephiles-est-a-moitie-prix-pour-le-debut-de-lannee-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2854359_philips-65oled959-le-tv-ambilight-des-gamers-et-des-cinephiles-est-a-moitie-prix-pour-le-debut-de-lannee-2026</guid>
      <description>
Lanc&#233; l'an dernier, le TV Philips 65OLED959 a de s&#233;rieux atouts : dalle OLED plus lumineuse, technologie Ambilight bien immersive, syst&#232;me audio 3D complet... Son autre avantage, c'est son prix qui passe de 3 990 euros &#224; 1 929 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why more companies are hiring &#8216;Culture Coaches&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91454723/why-more-companies-are-hiring-culture-coaches-company-culture-coaches</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T11:32:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91454723/why-more-companies-are-hiring-culture-coaches-company-culture-coaches</guid>
      <description>Experts share thoughts on the burgeoning trend.
Organizations are increasingly turning to &#8220;Culture Coaches&#8221; to address workplace challenges that traditional management approaches can&#8217;t solve. These specialized professionals bring outside perspective and emotional intelligence strategies to help teams build stronger communication patterns, employee engagement, and alignment. In this article, experts share insights on how culture coaching is reshaping the way companies approach employee growth, leadership development, and organizational success....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Margaret Atwood on Doomscrolling: &#8216;I Want to Keep Up With the Latest Doom&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-big-interview-podcast-margaret-atwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">694199f7617cecf5a1334a47</guid>
      <description>On this week&#8217;s episode of The Big Interview, the author of The Handmaid&#8217;s Tale talks about Elon Musk, political resistance, and why she still has hope for America&#8217;s future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Newest Health Trend Is Tracking Your Pee</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/smart-pee-trackers-trend-vivoo-kohler-withings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69580d38ca6d32756ace7a42</guid>
      <description>Ready, aim, fire&#8212;the latest health trackers use sensors to check your urine for proper hydration, ketone levels, and possible kidney stones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>660 &#8364; pour des clignotants : les propri&#233;taires de Tesla Model 3 se ruent sur cet accessoire d&#233;j&#224; en rupture de stock</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2930745_660-e-pour-des-clignotants-les-proprietaires-de-tesla-model-3-se-ruent-sur-cet-accessoire-deja-en-rupture-de-stock</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2930745_660-e-pour-des-clignotants-les-proprietaires-de-tesla-model-3-se-ruent-sur-cet-accessoire-deja-en-rupture-de-stock</guid>
      <description>
Point d&#233;cri&#233; de sa nouvelle Model 3, Tesla propose d&#233;sormais une commande physique de clignotants &#224; installer sur ses voitures d&#233;j&#224; vendues. Une d&#233;cision manifestement attendue des clients : le commodo est en rupture de stock.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini les tapis mouill&#233;s avec le nouvel Ecovacs Deebot X12 OmniCyclone</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fini-tapis-mouilles-avec-nouvel-ecovacs-deebot-x12-omnicyclone.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318334</guid>
      <description>Ecovacs d&#233;voile son Deebot X12 OmniCyclone, un robot aspirateur haut de gamme qui int&#232;gre une protection pour les tapis et un syst&#232;me de pr&#233;traitement pour mieux nettoyer les t&#226;ches tenaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD Projekt Red is reportedly working on a new expansion for The Witcher 3 ahead of The Witcher 4's release &#8212; and I'll be there day one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/cd-projekt-red-is-reportedly-working-on-a-new-expansion-for-the-witcher-3-ahead-of-the-witcher-4s-release-and-ill-be-there-day-one</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oehLWizRUeEgEaWrKykRD6</guid>
      <description>CD Projekt Red has hinted that "new content" for an unnamed game will be released this year ahead of The Witcher 4, and an industry insider has claimed that it's the long-rumored The Witcher 3: The Wild Hunt expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non, ce n&#8217;est pas la fin de Microsoft Office</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/non-ce-nest-pas-la-fin-de-microsoft-office.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318351</guid>
      <description>Plusieurs publications sur les r&#233;seaux sociaux s&#8217;affolent au sujet d&#8217;un pr&#233;tendu rebranding de la suite Office de Microsoft en Microsoft 365 Copilot. C&#8217;est faux, et c&#8217;est en r&#233;alit&#233; un peu plus complexe que &#231;a.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Core Ultra Series 3 vs Qualcomm Snapdragon X2 : voici le duel des processeurs de PC portables de 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/intel/2930721_intel-core-ultra-series-3-vs-qualcomm-snapdragon-x2-voici-le-duel-des-processeurs-de-pc-portables-de-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/intel/2930721_intel-core-ultra-series-3-vs-qualcomm-snapdragon-x2-voici-le-duel-des-processeurs-de-pc-portables-de-2026</guid>
      <description>
D'un c&#244;t&#233;, Intel joue sa survie technique avec son proc&#233;d&#233; 18A et promet des performances graphiques d&#233;lirantes. De l'autre, Qualcomm d&#233;mocratise ses puces ARM avec le Snapdragon X2 Plus et Elite. Vous cherchez un nouveau PC portable cette ann&#233;e ? Voici le match sanglant qui se pr&#233;pare.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra might have just been caught on camera</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-might-have-just-been-caught-on-camera</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4i2Mj2YLTPDTcMmKLnfji</guid>
      <description>This leaked video seemingly shows both the Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra and its retail box, but there's some doubt about its authenticity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the best preorder price for the Magic: The Gathering Lorwyn Eclipsed Play Booster Box on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-magic-the-gathering-lorwyn-eclipsed-pre-order</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00jwdMKoBO0GuipHjkjNigY</guid>
      <description>The Magic: The Gathering Lorwyn Eclipsed Play Booster Box is available to pre-order on Amazon. Get the best price guaranteed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs smartphones pliables ? Samsung Galaxy Z, Honor Magic V, Motorola Razr&#8230; notre comparatif</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1617799_meilleur-smartphone-pliant-quel-telephone-pliable-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1617799_meilleur-smartphone-pliant-quel-telephone-pliable-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Les smartphones pliants ont une belle place sur le march&#233;. Tr&#232;s compacts une fois referm&#233;s, ils d&#233;ploient de grands &#233;crans pour une exp&#233;rience visuelle plus agr&#233;able. D&#233;couvrez ici notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs mod&#232;les pliables, test&#233;s et approuv&#233;s par nos soins.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin, Coros, Apple&#8230; voici les marques de montres les plus populaires chez les coureurs en France</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2930651_garmin-coros-apple-voici-les-marques-de-montres-les-plus-populaires-chez-les-coureurs-en-france</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2930651_garmin-coros-apple-voici-les-marques-de-montres-les-plus-populaires-chez-les-coureurs-en-france</guid>
      <description>
Le m&#233;dia fran&#231;ais Run'ix, d&#233;di&#233; &#224; la course &#224; pied, a publi&#233; le classement des marques de montres les plus utilis&#233;es par sa communaut&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Best Tablets (2026), Tested and Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/the-best-tablets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5af4622ff2b84f222a2e5fc8</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;ve tested all the top slates, from Apple&#8217;s iPads to Android and Windows devices, and rounded up our favorites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyclef Jean reveals his creative super power&#8212;and how you can tap into it too</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461354/wyclef-jean-reveals-his-creative-super-power-and-how-you-can-tap-into-it-too</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T11:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461354/wyclef-jean-reveals-his-creative-super-power-and-how-you-can-tap-into-it-too</guid>
      <description>The music producer and founding member of the Fugees tells us how he taps into inspiration, why his environment is key to creating, and how he reboots his brain to find new ideas.
As a child growing up with his grandmother in Haiti, the artist Wyclef Jean developed an early appreciation for the idea that any worthy pursuit requires a blend of agency and preparation. On the day I spoke to him, Jean recalled a time when a missionary visited his village. &#8220;At five years old, a car pulls up and a man gets out and this was like my first time seeing a white person ever. I looked at my grandma and I s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harder than Harvard: How to get a job at the most in-demand tech companies</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463956/harder-than-harvard-how-to-get-a-job-at-the-most-in-demand-tech-companies</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T11:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463956/harder-than-harvard-how-to-get-a-job-at-the-most-in-demand-tech-companies</guid>
      <description>Companies like Coinbase, ElevenLabs, and Ramp receive so many job applicants, their hiring rate makes Harvard look like a safety school. Hiring pros dish on how to beat the bots, survive the hiring gauntlet, and stand out from the massive crowd. 
On December 1, podcaster and venture capitalist Harry Stebbings posted on LinkedIn that candidates were 200 times more likely to get into Harvard University than they were to get a job at the $6.6 billion valuation AI startup ElevenLabs. According to his statistic, out of 180,000 applicants in the first half of the year, only 0.018% were hired by the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It turns out that Kia&#8217;s new logo wasn&#8217;t brand suicide after all</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469156/kia-new-logo-not-brand-suicide-after-all</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T11:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469156/kia-new-logo-not-brand-suicide-after-all</guid>
      <description>After a dramatic rebrand 5 years ago, the South Korean automaker is selling more cars than ever in the U.S. 
Five years ago this month, Kia took what seemed at the time to be a sledgehammer to its brand in the form of an inscrutable new logo. Today, its U.S. sales have never been higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We recommend the Victrix Pro BFG for its excellent back-paddles and modular design, and you can now pick it up for cheap as part of some excellent New Year&#8217;s deals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/we-recommend-the-victrix-pro-bfg-for-its-excellent-back-paddles-and-modular-design-and-you-can-now-pick-it-up-for-cheap-as-part-of-some-excellent-new-years-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RDV28FmyiKnBUZWCQ3juKg</guid>
      <description>One of the best premium game controllers is still heavily discounted for the New Year. Get excellent savings on one of our favorite PS5 and Xbox gamepads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In not remotely shocking news, Xbox has reportedly suffered its 'worst year on record' for console sales</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/in-not-remotely-shocking-news-xbox-has-reportedly-suffered-its-worst-year-on-record-for-console-sales</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dkX2inK7HJL5CpNpaXQuRV</guid>
      <description>Xbox reportedly had its 'worst year on record' in 2025 in news that should surprise no one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Technica just updated one of its best ever turntables at CES 2026, and I want it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/audio-technica-just-updated-one-of-its-best-ever-turntables-at-ces-2026-and-i-want-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SdRQBSv3nJjiyngVfotcMd</guid>
      <description>The new AT-LP7X updates an already talented turntable &#8211;and just look at it!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 heures d&#8217;autonomie : Samsung sort l&#8217;artillerie lourde avec le Galaxy Book6 Ultra</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2930691_30-heures-dautonomie-samsung-sort-lartillerie-lourde-avec-le-galaxy-book6-ultra</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2930691_30-heures-dautonomie-samsung-sort-lartillerie-lourde-avec-le-galaxy-book6-ultra</guid>
      <description>
Samsung profite de l'ouverture du CES 2026 pour annoncer sa nouvelle gamme de PC portables. Avec la nouvelle s&#233;rie Galaxy Book6, le constructeur cor&#233;en en profite pour affiner son design et annoncer une autonomie toujours plus folle.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foldy Bird : ce jeu insolite va d&#233;truire l&#8217;&#233;cran de votre smartphone pliant en 5 minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/2930731_foldy-bird-ce-jeu-insolite-va-detruire-lecran-de-votre-smartphone-pliant-en-5-minutes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/2930731_foldy-bird-ce-jeu-insolite-va-detruire-lecran-de-votre-smartphone-pliant-en-5-minutes</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que Flappy Bird &#233;tait frustrant ? Attendez de tester cette version pour smartphones pliants. Pour faire voler votre oiseau, il ne faut plus tapoter l'&#233;cran, mais plier et d&#233;plier votre t&#233;l&#233;phone. C&#8217;est brillant, mais c'est surtout le meilleur moyen d'achever votre charni&#232;re.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
