<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:24:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify&amp;#8217;s Prompted Playlists use AI to control your algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842053/spotify-ai-prompted-playlists</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T17:11:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842053</guid>
      <description>A new beta feature on Spotify takes the idea behind the Discover Weekly playlist and puts the control in users' hands through AI prompts. Prompted Playlists, which are initially launching in New Zealand on Thursday, let users type out exactly what they want to listen to, with as much or little detail as they like. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NES game Jaws is getting a retro physical re-release on Switch and PS5</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-nes-game-jaws-is-getting-a-retro-physical-re-release-on-switch-and-ps5-221052996.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de931d2-037d-48f0-b595-ecc32a925c93</guid>
      <description>The year is 1987. Beverly Hills Cop II is the highest-grossing movie. "Walk Like an Egyptian" is the hottest song. The Iran-Contra scandal dominates American political headlines, while Konami&#8217;s Contra sucks up coins in arcades. But towering above them all is the watershed moment of Jaws arriving on the NES. ("This time there's no escape!", warned the box art.) Now, 38 years later, the 8-bit game is returning as a Limited Run Games physical re-release.The retro release coincides with the Spielberg movie's 50th anniversary. From December 19 to January 18, you can pre-order a physical copy for Sw...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV and Apple Music were down for some users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/apple-tv-and-apple-music-were-down-for-some-users-214425802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26f8cfe4-c1e9-4ebf-97ba-995a63248b54</guid>
      <description>Apple Music and Apple TV were briefly down during outage, according to Apple&#8217;s System Status page. The outage was logged on Apple&#8217;s own system at around 2:53PM ET and affected both of the company&#8217;s streaming services, along with Apple TV&#8217;s Channels feature, until the company resolved the issue around 4:31PM ET. On DownDetector, reports of issues with Apple TV and Apple Music first appeared right around 2:33PM ET, a little before Apple officially confirmed the outage on its own site. Only &#8220;some&#8221; users were affected by the outage, according to Apple, and anecdotally, multiple members of Engadget...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia is&#160;reportedly testing&#160;tracking software as chip smuggling&#160;rumors swirl</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/nvidia-is-reportedly-testing-tracking-software-as-chip-smuggling-rumors-swirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074807</guid>
      <description>A new software option could make it possible to see the approximate location of some of Nvidia's AI chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of the Cuts of the Original &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/every-change-to-star-wars-a-new-hope-ever-made-2000697419</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697419</guid>
      <description>The original theatrical cut of 'Star Wars: A New Hope' is returning to theaters for its 50th anniversary. But what does 'original' actually mean?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan On Alert for &#8216;Megaquake&#8217; After Magnitude 7.6 Shakes the Nation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/japan-on-alert-for-megaquake-after-magnitude-7-6-shakes-the-nation-2000698091</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698091</guid>
      <description>"Please stay prepared to evacuate immediately if you feel any shaking, while continuing your socioeconomic activities.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald&#8217;s pulls AI-generated Christmas ad after backlash over 'soulless' visuals and holiday chaos</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/mcdonalds-pulls-ai-generated-christmas-ad-after-backlash-over-soulless-visuals-and-holiday-chaos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5XmNRvMEiNDyQZfRq2B3N5</guid>
      <description>McDonald&#8217;s removed an AI-made Christmas commercial after intense public backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is reportedly working on a new AI model called 'Avocado' and it might not be open source</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/meta-is-reportedly-working-on-a-new-ai-model-called-avocado-and-it-might-not-be-open-source-215426778.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1069db79-3fad-434a-99de-f83d17d34bb3</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg has for months publicly hinted that he is backing away from open-source AI models. Now, Meta's latest AI pivot is starting to come into focus. The company is reportedly working on a new model, known inside of Meta as "Avocado," which could mark a major shift away from its previous open-source approach to AI development.&#160;Both CNBC and Bloomberg have reported on Meta's plans surrounding "Avocado," with both outlets saying the model "could" be proprietary rather than open-source. Avocado, which is due out sometime in 2026, is being worked on inside of "TBD," a smaller group within...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now share live video with emergency services on Android</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/you-can-now-share-live-video-with-emergency-services-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074909</guid>
      <description>This feature could help give emergency dispatchers context in circumstances like car accidents, fires, or medical crises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Bluebird wants to reclaim Twitter&#8217;s &#8216;abandoned&#8217; trademarks for a new social network</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/841994/operation-bluebird-twitter-trademarks-petition</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T16:31:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841994</guid>
      <description>A startup called Operation Bluebird is trying to reclaim Twitter's branding, as reported earlier by Ars Technica and Reuters. Last week, Operation Bluebird filed a petition that asks the US Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) to cancel X Corp.'s ownership of the "Twitter" and "Tweet" trademarks, claiming they've been "abandoned" by the Elon Musk-owned company. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best budget robot vacuums</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23846479/best-budget-robot-vacuum-robot-mop</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T16:31:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23846479/best-budget-robot-vacuum-robot-mop</guid>
      <description>Today&#8217;s robot vacuums are becoming a bit like cars: with all the features, upgrades, and fancy trimmings available these days, it&#8217;s easy to forget that they can just be simple machines that get us from point A to point B. Yes, some bots blow hot air on their bums (mop pads), deftly navigate dog poop, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Classic Tees Deals for the 2025 Holidays: 25 Percent Off Crew Necks</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/true-classic-tees-flash-deals-december-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939c7358d85d77833f7b8a9</guid>
      <description>True Classic Tees is running holiday &#8220;flash deals&#8221; with some of the best prices we've seen in months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New study: Women are more likely to be penalized for working remotely than men</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458285/new-study-women-are-more-likely-to-be-penalized-for-working-remotely-than-men</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T21:15:27</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458285/new-study-women-are-more-likely-to-be-penalized-for-working-remotely-than-men</guid>
      <description>A new McKinsey and Lean In report shows companies are backsliding on gender equity&#8212;and punishing women for working remotely even as men skate by.
The consulting firm McKinsey and women&#8217;s nonprofit Lean In just released their annual Women in the Workplace report, which examines how gender disparities are impacting womens&#8217; career prospects. Unfortunately, this year&#8217;s results show that companies are backsliding on their commitment to workplace equity&#8212;and one way that&#8217;s harming women is by making it more difficult for them to work remotely....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of South Korean retail giant Coupang resigns after massive data breach</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/ceo-of-south-korean-retail-giant-coupang-resigns-after-massive-data-breach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074924</guid>
      <description>The massive data breach at the South Korean retail giant Coupang affects more than half of the country's population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Week&#8217;s &#8216;Mighty Nein&#8217; Inherits the Beef Between Its 2 Best Characters</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-weeks-mighty-nein-inherits-the-beef-between-its-2-best-characters-2000694310</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694310</guid>
      <description>The Mighty Nein will become a great, well-oiled party someday, but first, they've got some kinks to work out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s favorite holiday gifts under $100</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/800440/best-gifts-under-100-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800440</guid>
      <description>Between all the new phones, smartwatches, and laptops we see throughout the year, it often feels like we're constantly being nudged toward shinier, more expensive gadgets. And I get it. As a self-professed gadget nerd, few things are more exciting than unboxing and setting up a new device. But the truth is, you can still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eufy&#8217;s Best Robot Vacuum Is $405 Off (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-best-robot-vacuum-deal-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939c384ac300a7f1db48d19</guid>
      <description>Eufy&#8217;s last-season robot vacuum-mop has a crazy price cut. Grab it before it&#8217;s gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify's new playlist feature gives users more control over their recommendation algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/spotifys-new-playlist-feature-gives-users-more-control-over-their-recommendation-algorithm-203237903.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d363f959-a9d1-4f31-9725-f863e4fe7a59</guid>
      <description>Spotify is attempting to give users more control over the music the streaming service recommends with a new playlist feature called "Prompted Playlist." The beta feature is rolling out in New Zealand starting on December 11, and will let users write a custom prompt that Spotify can use &#8212; alongside their listening history &#8212; to create a playlist of new music.By tapping on Prompted Playlist, Spotify subscribers participating in the beta will be presented with a prompt field where they can type exactly what they want to hear and how they want Spotify's algorithm to respond. And while past AI featu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finally! Another external USB4 SSD hit the market &#8212; and this one is likely to be far more affordable than rivals</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/finally-another-external-usb4-ssd-hit-the-market-and-this-one-is-likely-to-be-far-more-affordable-than-rivals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QRXjtqQi2wYnPe7Ugt34ta</guid>
      <description>TeamGroup PD40 is a lightweight, travel-ready USB4 SSD offering strong performance, broad compatibility, and appealing value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best smart rings for tracking sleep and health</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/647901/best-smart-rings</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T15:29:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=647901</guid>
      <description>So, you&#8217;re thinking of buying a smart ring. Well, some good news. Picking the best of the lot is incredibly easy right now. The &#8220;bad&#8221; news is that, as far as trustworthiness and reliability, your choices are somewhat limited, as this is still a niche and emerging gadget category. Smart rings are in the middle [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
