<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:36:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Apple might let you use ChatGPT from CarPlay</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/875199/apple-carplay-third-party-chatbots-rumor</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T16:32:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875199</guid>
      <description>CarPlay users could soon be able to use their chatbot of choice instead of Siri. As Bloomberg reports, Apple is working to add support for CarPlay voice control apps from OpenAI, Anthropic, Google, and others. Previously, users who wanted to access third-party chatbots in the car would need to go through their iPhone, but soon [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the Trump Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/875190/trump-phone-t1-first-look-design-interview-eric-thomas-don-hendrickson</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T16:32:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875190</guid>
      <description>Where's the Trump phone? We're going to keep talking about it every week. We've reached out, as usual, to ask about the Trump phone's whereabouts. This time, surprisingly, we received a response - and an interview. The Trump phone is real - maybe, sort of, soon? - and I've seen it. Not in the flesh, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean Crypto Exchange Accidentally Gave Away $43 Billion Worth of Paper Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/south-korean-crypto-exchange-accidentally-gave-away-43-billion-worth-of-paper-bitcoin-2000719158</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719158</guid>
      <description>Now that is a promotion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew advisor pitched Jeffrey Epstein on investing in EV startups like Lucid Motors</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/prince-andrew-advisor-pitched-jeffrey-epstein-on-investing-in-ev-startups-like-lucid-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090515</guid>
      <description>The mysterious businessman pitched Jeffrey Epstein on numerous mobility startups in an era when the sector was white hot, according to TechCrunch's review of hundreds of documents released by the Department of Justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What will Nvidia think? Intel CEO confirms GPU building will continue as it looks to stake a claim in the most lucrative industry around right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-will-nvidia-think-intel-ceo-confirms-gpu-building-will-continue-as-it-looks-to-stake-a-claim-in-the-most-lucrative-industry-around-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9qzQBgdQx5HYUfDL2RpmaV</guid>
      <description>Intel confirms internal GPU development, hires key engineers, and aims to challenge Nvidia in high-performance AI and gaming markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Has Packed an Autism Panel With Cranks and Conspiracy Theorists</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/rfk-jr-s-picks-for-a-key-autism-panel-include-advocates-for-bizarre-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698205ea600484f7c8d439be</guid>
      <description>Among those Robert F. Kennedy Jr. recently named to a federal autism committee are people who tout dangerous treatments and say vaccine manufacturers are &#8220;poisoning children.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Eulogized What Mattered Most About Captain Sisko</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-captain-sisko-deep-space-nine-2000719039</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719039</guid>
      <description>This week's stellar episode of the new 'Star Trek' series looked back at the legacy left behind by the captain of 'Deep Space Nine' and found the best perspective it could.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worried about winter EV range loss? Brutal test reveals the 10 hardiest models you can buy &#8211;and Tesla only just made the list</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/worried-about-winter-ev-range-loss-brutal-test-reveals-the-10-hardiest-models-you-can-buy-and-tesla-only-just-made-the-list</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jqvUpoRdBanaSN8vEoBGmf</guid>
      <description>The Norwegian Automotive Federation tested some of the top-selling EVs to see how they performed in extreme weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HR exec from the Coldplay kiss cam incident is headlining a crisis PR conference</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487933/the-hr-exec-from-the-coldplay-kiss-cam-incident-is-headlining-a-crisis-pr-conference</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487933/the-hr-exec-from-the-coldplay-kiss-cam-incident-is-headlining-a-crisis-pr-conference</guid>
      <description>Individual tickets start at $875 a person.
Kristin Cabot, the HR exec at the center of last year&#8217;s Coldplay kiss cam scandal, is headlining a crisis communications conference happening later this year.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivian Tu on how to spot good financial advice in an uncertain economy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488732/vivian-tu-on-how-to-spot-good-financial-advice-in-an-uncertain-economy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488732/vivian-tu-on-how-to-spot-good-financial-advice-in-an-uncertain-economy</guid>
      <description>The financial educator and creator behind Your Rich BFF shares what to watch for online, and why volatility distorts decision-making.
Why does uncertainty make us less rational with money? And who should we trust for financial advice online? Vivian Tu, financial educator and CEO of Your Rich BFF, breaks down today&#8217;s personal finance risks and opportunities, from &#8220;lifestyle inflation&#8221; and the most common money mistakes smart people make to how Gen Z is navigating 2026 volatility and a shifting job market....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why People Think Jeffrey Epstein Is Alive and Playing Fortnite</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-people-think-jeffrey-epstein-is-alive-and-playing-fortnite-2000718952</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718952</guid>
      <description>There's no evidence that Epstein is alive and hiding in Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something Mysteriously Powerful Slammed Into Earth in 2023. Scientists Now Have a Theory</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/something-unimaginably-powerful-slammed-into-earth-in-2023-scientists-now-have-a-theory-2000719040</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719040</guid>
      <description>The science here gets really dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ loses access to Dolby Vision in some European countries</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/disney-loses-access-to-dolby-vision-in-some-european-countries-193930702.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c91c8c4-5448-4bca-accb-c31c1671c8d2</guid>
      <description>Disney+ subscribers in some European countries have lost access to advanced HDR features like Dolby Vision, TechRadar and FlatpanelsHD report. The issue was first spotted by German Disney+ subscribers on Reddit, but currently also impacts subscribers in Portugal, Poland, France and the Netherlands, according to FlatpanelsHD."Dolby Vision support for content on Disney+ is currently unavailable in several European countries due to technical challenges," Disney said in a statement. "We are actively working to restore access to Dolby Vision and will provide an update as soon as possible. 4K UHD an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finally, I&#8217;ve Found the Perfect Switch 2 Controller</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/finally-ive-found-the-perfect-switch-2-controller-2000718700</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718700</guid>
      <description>Gulikit's TT Pro and TT Max have many more stick and button options than a Switch 2 Pro controller, and they have one feature no other gamepad does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google- and Microsoft-backed Terradot acquires carbon-removal competitor</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/google-and-microsoft-backed-terradot-acquires-carbon-removal-competitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090493</guid>
      <description>The acquisition could mark the beginning of consolidation in the carbon-removal market since removal costs remain higher than buyers would like to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe AI agents can be lawyers after all</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/maybe-ai-agents-can-be-lawyers-after-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090494</guid>
      <description>This week's release of Opus 4.6 shook up the agentic AI leaderboards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI strategies are kind of destined to fail</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488929/ai-strategies-are-kind-of-destined-to-fail</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T20:11:42</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488929/ai-strategies-are-kind-of-destined-to-fail</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s why a company &#8220;posture&#8221; is better.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turns Out Congestion Pricing Has Been Good for Drivers in the Suburbs, Too</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/turns-out-congestion-pricing-has-been-good-for-drivers-in-the-suburbs-too-2000718956</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718956</guid>
      <description>Traffic has improved inside and out of Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Knight Insisted Skeletor Had His Skull Face for &#8216;Masters of the Universe&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/travis-knight-insisted-skeletor-had-his-skull-face-for-masters-of-the-universe-2000719056</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719056</guid>
      <description>The director was not going to make the film without the Skeletor we know and love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worried you can&#8217;t wow your loved one with a Valentine&#8217;s day latte? I&#8217;ve found the perfect automatic coffee machines for you &#8211; even if your milk-frothing game is as mid as mine</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/worried-you-cant-wow-your-loved-one-with-a-valentines-day-latte-ive-found-the-perfect-automatic-coffee-machines-for-you-even-if-your-milk-frothing-game-is-as-mid-as-mine</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SLFCyMBojHPsdthArX4mk5</guid>
      <description>Tired of collapsing foam and milk spatter? I&#8217;ve assembled all of my favorite automatic coffee machines for reducing the fuss when frothing coffee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s how much Amazon, Microsoft, Meta, and Google will spend to develop more AI&#160;in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488664/how-much-amazon-microsoft-meta-google-alphabet-are-spending-on-ai-investment-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488664/how-much-amazon-microsoft-meta-google-alphabet-are-spending-on-ai-investment-2026</guid>
      <description>Big Tech is set for a big spend, with the number reaching into the hundreds of billions, according to earnings reports this week.
Big Tech is on a spending spree, forecast to drop a staggering $650 billion on artificial intelligence (AI) in 2026 alone&#8212;and that&#8217;s just for Alphabet, Meta, Microsoft, and Amazon. The companies are ramping up their investment&#160;in an increasingly competitive, high-stakes arms race, pouring hundreds of billions into massive data centers and semiconductors, in hopes of establishing a long-term strategic advantage in their quest to dominate the future of technology....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite TV to Watch the Winter Olympics Is on Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-s90f-qd-oled-tv-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69862655115bb05a5bf45c23</guid>
      <description>Forget the Super Bowl, Samsung&#8217;s Fantastic S90F QD-OLED TV is on a sweet sale just in time for the Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Outbreak in South Carolina Linked to Brain Swelling in Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/measles-outbreak-in-south-carolina-linked-to-brain-swelling-in-kids-2000718913</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718913</guid>
      <description>Several children have come down with serious complications like encephalitis and pneumonia, state health officials reported this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s GPT-5.3-Codex thinks deeper and wider about coding work</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488584/openai-gpt-5-3-codex-release</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T19:38:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488584/openai-gpt-5-3-codex-release</guid>
      <description>The company says its latest model&#8217;s agentic skills also apply to a broader set of knowledge work such as presentations and spreadsheets.
On Thursday, OpenAI released GPT-5.3-Codex, a new model that extends its Codex coding agent beyond writing and reviewing code to performing a much wider range of work tasks. The release comes as competition continues to heat up among AI companies vying for market share in the AI-powered coding tools space....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl on NBC: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, where to stream, start time, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-on-nbc-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-where-to-stream-start-time-and-more-175759402.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is nearly here. This weekend, the Big Game will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA. The NFL Championship Game kicks off at 6:30PM ET this Sunday, Feb. 8. Pre-game coverage starts at 12PM ET. Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the Super Bowl will be broadcast on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. Here's everything you need ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
