<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:31:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers are teaming up with organized crime gangs to steal cargo right from supply chains</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-team-up-with-organized-crime-gangs-to-steal-cargo-right-from-supply-chains</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Fv6FhjtLzinhpsNhtGMUf</guid>
      <description>Sophisticated attacks bring the physical and digital worlds together to put freights at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive Steelcase discount: get 28% off four of our favourite ergonomic office chairs ahead of Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/steelcase-black-friday-deals-australia</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nKRXSvmoAcxjUKgVLrJEPU</guid>
      <description>Steelcase makes some of the best office chairs available, and the brand's getting the Black Friday sale season started early with an exclusive coupon for TechRadar Australia readers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon sends legal threats to Perplexity over agentic browsing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/04/amazon-sends-legal-threats-to-perplexity-over-agentic-browsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3065094</guid>
      <description>Amazon won't allow agents on its site that don't identify themselves as such. Perplexity is not pleased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valve will finally turn off the Steam Deck&amp;#8217;s screen while it&amp;#8217;s downloading games</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813864/valve-steam-deck-screen-download-games-low-power-screen-off</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T18:02:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813864</guid>
      <description>Valve is testing a low-power way to complete downloads on your Steam Deck without having to leave the handheld running with the screen on. As part of an update that&#8217;s currently on the Steam Deck&#8217;s Beta and Preview channels, the handheld can &#8220;complete all active downloads in a new display-off low-power mode before going to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 new Hulu shows that every true crime fan needs to watch this November 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/3-new-hulu-shows-that-every-true-crime-fan-needs-to-watch-this-november-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">t3fnXzVEmJELZrCKeagWBa</guid>
      <description>Hulu can be true crime all the time &#8211;and these newly streaming seasons are well worth checking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Podcasts is generating automatic links and chapters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813817/apple-podcasts-automatic-links-and-chapters</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T17:34:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813817</guid>
      <description>Apple Podcasts will soon include automatically-generated chapters for shows in English and allow creators to add links at specific timestamps in their episodes. Timed links may also be added to episodes automatically whenever creators mention another podcast.&#160; Creators can opt-out of both features, and chapters will only be generated when creators don&#8217;t add their own. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Inc forges AI licensing deal with Microsoft as Google traffic drops</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/04/people-inc-forges-ai-licensing-deal-with-microsoft-as-google-traffic-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3065066</guid>
      <description>People Inc. signs an AI licensing deal with Microsoft, which will use its media content in Copilot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ever Lego &#8216;Ideas&#8217; Project That Is Currently in the Works</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/every-lego-ideas-project-in-development-2025-2000681461</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681461</guid>
      <description>After a streak of high-profile crossover announcements, from 'X-Files' to 'Power Rangers', here's everything that's currently in development for Lego's crowd-supported line of sets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beta Technologies ends first day on NYSE in the green and $1B raised</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/04/beta-technologies-ends-first-day-on-nyse-in-the-green-and-1b-raised/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3065077</guid>
      <description>The electric aviation company Beta Technologies made an impressive showing in its debut on the New York Stock Exchange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Stream Deck&#8217;s &#8216;device not supported&#8217; error should fix itself if you log in</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/813814/your-stream-decks-device-not-supported-error-should-fix-itself-if-you-log-in</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T17:17:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813814</guid>
      <description>Did your Stream Deck sprout a red &#8220;Device Not Supported&#8221; badge where a button used to be? If so, you were probably using BarRaider&#8217;s popular plug-ins, which apparently check to see if StreamDeck.exe is digitally signed &#8212; and it just so happens that Elgato&#8217;s digital signature expired yesterday (see image below). But as of 5PM [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer reveals its fanciest Chromebook yet - but will it be enough to convince your IT team to upgrade you?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/acer-reveals-its-fanciest-chromebook-yet-but-will-it-be-enough-to-convince-your-it-team-to-upgrade-you</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98snqP4CQgm9mmiVSjPfSm</guid>
      <description>Acer Chromebook Plus Enterprise 714 and 514 blend AI tools, long battery life, and rugged builds for serious business use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's no better PC under $350 than this Ryzen 7 powerhouse with a CPU that's faster than a 10-core Apple M5 CPU, and that's no mistake</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/theres-no-better-pc-under-usd350-than-this-ryzen-7-powerhouse-with-a-cpu-thats-faster-than-a-10-core-apple-m5-cpu-and-thats-no-mistake</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dNWSCqgq9BcnNFKSxgD4B</guid>
      <description>$349 Machenike AI Mini PC is one of the best sub-$400 desktops available, powered by an AMD Ryzen 7 8745HS and delivering performance that rivals more expensive systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best deals on 4K TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22371561/best-4k-tv-deals-sale-lg-samsung-sony-tcl</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T17:05:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22371561/best-4k-tv-deals-sale-lg-samsung-sony-tcl</guid>
      <description>Things are looking bright for those who want to nab a great TV in 2025 at a substantial discount. There&#8217;s usually a great deal happening on a mid- or high-end TV from LG, Sony, Roku, Hisense, or Samsung &#8212; even if the biggest discounts remain reserved for Black Friday, Amazon Prime Day, and the lead-up [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian blames ChatGPT for low law class test scores &#8211; even as OpenAI dismisses a rumored ban of legal and medical advice from ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/kim-kardashian-blames-chatgpt-for-low-law-class-test-scores-even-as-openai-dismisses-a-rumored-ban-of-legal-and-medical-advice-from-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">akBY22JWWnmHLeRB9soob7</guid>
      <description>Kim Kardashian&#8217;s confession that ChatGPT led to flunking law tests arrives amid confusion over AI&#8217;s legal and medical advice policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Immigration Enforcement Apparently Provides Facial Scanning Tech to Local Cops</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/u-s-immigration-enforcement-apparently-provides-facial-scanning-tech-to-local-cops-2000681475</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681475</guid>
      <description>It's part of a program that essentially deputizes police into the federal mass deportation effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDA email warns stores: discounts for SNAP users could violate federal law</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435252/usda-email-warns-stores-discounts-for-snap-users-could-violate-federal-law</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:48:32</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435252/usda-email-warns-stores-discounts-for-snap-users-could-violate-federal-law</guid>
      <description>The agency says offering discounts exclusively to food-aid recipients violates program rules, sparking backlash during the shutdown.
Restaurants, food banks, nonprofits, and other organizations have stepped up to offer assistance to the 41 million Americans who have been thrust into limbo this month regarding SNAP benefits that have been halved. But retailers are prohibited from offering discounts on groceries....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AI&amp;#8217;s first in-house image generator MAI-Image-1 is now available</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813789/microsoft-in-house-ai-image-generator-mai-image-1</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:48:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813789</guid>
      <description>Microsoft&#8217;s first in-house AI image generator, MAI-Image-1, is now available in two products, Bing Image Creator and Copilot Audio Expressions. The company announced the model in October. Microsoft AI chief Mustafa Suleyman wrote in a post on X that the text-to-image model will be &#8220;coming soon&#8221; to the EU.&#160; Suleyman added that the model &#8220;really [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrysler recalls 320,000 Jeep plug-in hybrids over battery fire risk</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435238/chrysler-recalls-jeep-plug-in-hybrids-battery-fire</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435238/chrysler-recalls-jeep-plug-in-hybrids-battery-fire</guid>
      <description>Chrysler is aware of 19 reports and 1 injury potentially related to the issue.
Chrysler is recalling more than 320,000 Jeep plug-in hybrid vehicles due to a faulty battery that can fail and lead to a fire, U.S. traffic safety regulators said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nomad&#8217;s magnetic charging stands now support faster 25W rates</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813769/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max-wireless-charging-25w-magsafe-pixelsnap</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:42:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813769</guid>
      <description>Nomad has announced updated versions of its Stand One and Stand One Max hubs that now support the Qi2.2 standard for faster wireless charging rates of up to 25W when used with compatible smartphones like the Pixel 10 Pro XL and the iPhone 16 and 17 series. As with previous versions, the new Stand One [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon and Perplexity have kicked off the great AI web browser fight</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813755/amazon-perplexity-ai-shopping-agent-block</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:36:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813755</guid>
      <description>Amazon doesn&#8217;t want to be a part of Perplexity&#8217;s AI-powered shopping experience. In a post on Tuesday, the ecommerce giant says it has &#8220;repeatedly requested&#8221; that Perplexity stop allowing its Comet AI browser to buy products for customers, which Perplexity has responded to by accusing Amazon of &#8220;bullying.&#8221; Perplexity&#8217;s AI browser, Comet, currently offers an [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Trump hijacked the .gov domain</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/813499/viral-politics-trump-mamdani-cuomo</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:33:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/813499/what-the-trump-family-stands-to-gain-from-changpeng-zhaos-pardon</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator. Happy New York City mayoral election day to everyone who's voting, watching from afar, or just here for the memes. And happy 35th day of the federal government shutdown, which, as of today, is tied for the longest shutdown in history. But let's step back for a second, because there's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI and AWS team up in potentially one of the biggest tech partnerships ever seen - so what will it mean for you?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/openai-and-aws-team-up-in-potentially-one-of-the-biggest-tech-partnerships-ever-seen-so-what-will-it-mean-for-you</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RFoTvXxyUu9KMFFEqxDSXe</guid>
      <description>OpenAI&#8217;s $38 billion partnership with AWS will expand massive AI workloads, deepening cloud hosting dependence and raising sustainability concerns.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
