<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:23:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s war on offshore wind faces another lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850461/offshore-wind-trump-lawsuit-dominion-energy-ai-data-center</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T17:14:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850461</guid>
      <description>Dominion Energy, an offshore wind developer and utility serving Virginia's "data center alley," filed suit against the Trump administration this week over its decision to pause federal leases for large offshore wind projects. The move puts a sudden stop to five wind farms already under construction, including Dominion's Coastal Virginia Offshore Wind project. The complaint [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uh Oh: Male Mosquitoes Can Feed on Our Blood, Too</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/uh-oh-male-mosquitoes-can-feed-on-our-blood-too-study-finds-2000703485</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703485</guid>
      <description>The findings might overturn a widely held belief that only females pose a disease risk to people, though more research is needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cameron Will Tell Us the Future of &#8216;Avatar,&#8217; No Matter What</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/james-cameron-avatar-4-5-press-conference-2000703566</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703566</guid>
      <description>Cameron teased he'll reveal the plots of 'Avatar 4' and '5' in a press conference if the movies don't get made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes Leveled up in 2025&#8212;Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Coming&#160;Next</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/deepfakes-leveled-up-in-2025-heres-whats-coming-next-2000703649</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703649</guid>
      <description>Fake images, videos, and audio files crossed the &#8220;indistinguishable threshold" this year. Where do we go from here?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York State will require warning labels on social media platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/new-york-state-will-require-warning-labels-on-social-media-platforms-210306716.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">800eb432-6e82-4126-a6ad-b50b196bae7b</guid>
      <description>The State of New York will now require social media platforms to display warning labels similar to those found on cigarettes. The bill was passed by the New York Legislature in June and signed into law by Gov. Kathy Hochul on Friday. It will apply to any platforms that feature infinite scrolling, auto-play, like counts or algorithmic feeds. The labels will caution those on the platform about potential harm to young users' mental health.
Social media companies will be required to display these warning labels when a user first interacts with any of the features the state considers predatory. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've been a Windows user for over 15 years &#8212; these are the 7 key things to check on a new gaming PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/ive-been-a-windows-user-for-over-15-years-these-are-the-7-key-things-to-check-on-a-new-gaming-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WF4Yuma9VL6VAkuiw2pENR</guid>
      <description>If you just landed a new gaming PC, these are the most important things to do before you game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Times Square NYE ball drop will be patriotic for America&#8217;s 250th birthday</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467336/times-square-nye-ball-drop-patriotic-america-250</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467336/times-square-nye-ball-drop-patriotic-america-250</guid>
      <description>Organizers are also planning a second ball drop event on July 3.
After the crystal ball drops on New Year&#8217;s Eve in New York City, it will rise again, sparkling in red, white, and blue to usher in 2026 and kick off&#160;months of celebrations&#160;for the nation&#8217;s&#160;upcoming 250th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Star Jamie Campbell Bower on Playing Vecna&#8217;s Variations</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-star-jamie-campbell-bower-on-playing-vecnas-variations-2000703553</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703553</guid>
      <description>The actor behind Vecna, Henry, and Mr. Whatsit breaks down his complex role in season five.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
