<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:23:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google releases emergency fix for yet another zero-day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/google-releases-emergency-fix-for-yet-another-zero-day</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Xedd2SEPwPfuHNobVAKHfZ</guid>
      <description>Details are being withheld until the patch is deployed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Holiday Coffee Subscription Deals (2025): Atlas, Trade</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-holiday-coffee-subscription-deals-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692dd481979b5ac28c18bfda</guid>
      <description>Coffee subscriptions offer their steepest discounts in December&#8212;including on WIRED's two favorite coffee subscriptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Official &#8216;Fallout&#8217; Season 1 Recap Is AI Garbage Filled With Mistakes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-ai-recap-prime-video-amazon-2000698573</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698573</guid>
      <description>Prime Video's latest needle-poke into generative AI's bubble comes on the heels of its anime dubbing debacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Xbox controller to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23025443/best-xbox-controllers-one-series-x-s</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23025443/best-xbox-controllers-one-series-x-s</guid>
      <description>We live in a golden age of controllers. The gamepads on the market now are of higher quality, more versatile, and more customizable than anything from even one console generation ago. If you play games on an Xbox Series X or Series S (or a Windows PC), you have the unenviable task of choosing between [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s $100,000 fee on H-1B visas is backfiring&#8212;and shutting out foreign workers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458236/trumps-100000-fee-on-h-1b-visas-is-backfiring-and-shutting-out-foreign-workers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458236/trumps-100000-fee-on-h-1b-visas-is-backfiring-and-shutting-out-foreign-workers</guid>
      <description>The decades-old program may need to be reformed, but experts say the exorbitant new fee won&#8217;t deter companies from abusing it.
This fall, President Trump took aim at the H-1B visa, in a move that has been telegraphed for years amid criticism that the program diverts jobs away from American workers. In September, Trump announced that new applications for the work visa would now be subject to a $100,000 fee&#8212;a bold attempt to curtail excessive use of the H-1B program.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doxers Posing as Cops Are Tricking Big Tech Firms Into Sharing People's Private Data</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/doxers-posing-as-cops-are-tricking-big-tech-firms-into-sharing-peoples-private-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">692ddce5259b04d366e07261</guid>
      <description>A spoofed email address and an easily faked document is all it takes for major tech companies to hand over your most personal information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney hits Google with cease-and-desist claiming &#8216;massive&#8217; copyright infringement</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/disney-hits-google-with-cease-and-desist-claiming-massive-copyright-infringement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075292</guid>
      <description>Disney is accusing the tech giant of unauthorized distribution of its copyrighted characters without permission via Gemini AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5.2 est l&#224; : la r&#233;ponse de ChatGPT &#224; Google Gemini 3</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/openai/2907117_gpt-5-2-est-la-la-reponse-de-chatgpt-a-google-gemini-3</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/openai/2907117_gpt-5-2-est-la-la-reponse-de-chatgpt-a-google-gemini-3</guid>
      <description>
OpenAI a d&#233;voil&#233; GPT-5.2, son nouveau LLM le plus puissant &#224; ce jour. La firme esp&#232;re rattraper l'avance prise par Google avec Gemini 3 Pro.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases GPT-5.2 to take on Google and Anthropic</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-releases-gpt-52-to-take-on-google-and-anthropic-185029007.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30190bed-34ae-4250-a39d-8e5613de573b</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's "code red" response to Google's Gemini 3 Pro has arrived. On the same day the company announced a Sora licensing pact with Disney, it took the wraps off GPT-5.2.&#160;OpenAI is touting the new model as its best yet for real-world, professional use. &#8220;It&#8217;s better at creating spreadsheets, building presentations, writing code, perceiving images, understanding long contexts, using tools, and handling complex, multi-step projects,&#8221; said OpenAI.In a series of 10 benchmarks highlighted by OpenAI, GPT-5.2 Thinking, the most advanced version of the model, outperformed its GPT-5.1  counterpart, some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian airline hack came through third-party tech vendor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/russian-airline-hack-came-through-third-party-tech-vendor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JJThSUaJmyPW2JUe8UZDx6</guid>
      <description>Local journalists are investigating last summer's breach allegedly done by Ukrainian and Belarussian hacktivists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested a bunch of Switch 2 screen protectors, and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/694948/best-switch-2-glass-screen-protector-glossy-matte</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:37:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=694948</guid>
      <description>A glass screen protector is one of a few essential accessories that every Switch 2 owner should buy, along with a select few others. In fact, it should be a priority to stick one onto the console&#8217;s screen as soon as possible to avoid accidental scratches.&#160; To test the candidates below, I installed and removed [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit accuses ChatGPT of reinforcing delusions that led to a woman's death</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/lawsuit-accuses-chatgpt-of-reinforcing-delusions-that-led-to-a-womans-death-183141193.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63236523-f30e-4814-9f21-15cd0e5df80c</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has been hit with a wrongful death lawsuit after a man killed his mother and took his own life back in August, according to a report by The Verge. The suit names CEO Sam Altman and accuses ChatGPT of putting a "target" on the back of victim Suzanne Adams, an 83-year-old woman who was killed in her home.
The victim's estate claims the killer, 56-year-old Stein-Erik Soelberg, engaged in delusion-soaked conversations with ChatGPT in which the bot "validated and magnified" certain "paranoid beliefs." The suit goes on to suggest that the chatbot "eagerly accepted" delusional thoughts leading...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Launches 34,175-Mile AI Network That Acts Like One Massive Supercomputer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/china-launches-34175-mile-ai-network-that-acts-like-one-massive-supercomputer-2000698474</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698474</guid>
      <description>If the system holds out long-term, it could significantly boost AI development in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoto&#8217;s new PixelDrive electric screwdriver is on sale for the first time</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/842687/hoto-pixeldrive-electric-screwdriver-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:18:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842687</guid>
      <description>You may not have heard of Hoto, but as my colleague Sean Hollister pointed out in his recent profile, the company is quickly becoming a household name thanks to its penchant for high-quality design. Hoto&#8217;s new PixelDrive electric screwdriver is a great example of what the company is capable of, and right now it&#8217;s on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disney-OpenAI tie-up has huge implications for intellectual property</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458957/disney-openai-copyright-intellectual-property-slop</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T18:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458957/disney-openai-copyright-intellectual-property-slop</guid>
      <description>The House of Mouse is one of the most aggressive defenders of its IP. OpenAI literally just said it&#8217;d welcome erotica. What&#8217;s going on?
Walt Disney and OpenAI make for very odd bedfellows: The former is one of the most-recognized brands among children under the age of 18. The near-$200 billion company&#8217;s value has been derived from more than a century of aggressive safeguarding of its intellectual property and keeping the magic alive among innocent children....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is building an experimental new browser and a new kind of web app</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/842000/google-disco-browser-ai-experiment</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:10:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842000</guid>
      <description>The Chrome team at Google recently built a new browser. It takes a query or prompt, opens a bunch of related tabs for you, and then builds you a custom app for whatever you're trying to do. Ask it for travel tips and it'll build you a planner app; ask it for study help and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&amp;#8217;s &#8216;adult mode&#8217; is expected to debut in Q1 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842657/openai-chatgpt-adult-mode-debut-q1-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:10:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842657</guid>
      <description>We've seen NSFW offerings from Grok and other chatbots, and OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has been teasing adult content within ChatGPT for a while. Now, we have a timeline. Fidji Simo, OpenAI's CEO of Applications, told reporters during a Thursday briefing about GPT-5.2 that she expects "adult mode" to debut within ChatGPT in the first [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s AI try-on feature for clothes now works with just a selfie</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/googles-ai-try-on-feature-for-clothes-now-works-with-just-a-selfie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075253</guid>
      <description>In the past, users had to upload a full-body picture of themselves to virtually try on a piece of clothing. Now, they can use a selfie and&#160;Nano Banana will generate a full body digital version of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Taiwan Made Cashless Payments Cute</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/icash-taiwan-payments-keychains-how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6936645f9a4c34f57fa814e9</guid>
      <description>Taiwan&#8217;s digital payment infrastructure is tactile, decentralized, and completely distinct from China&#8217;s QR code-dominated model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney will open up its toy chest of 200+ characters for AI creators in a $1 billion deal with OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458841/disney-characters-ai-openai</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T18:03:25</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458841/disney-characters-ai-openai</guid>
      <description>The investment signals Disney&#8217;s willingness to embrace certain AI platforms while fighting others over alleged copyright violations.
Mickey Mouse, welcome to the AI era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI fires back at Google with GPT-5.2 after &#8216;code red&#8217; memo</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/openai-fires-back-at-google-with-gpt-5-2-after-code-red-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075273</guid>
      <description>OpenAI just launched GPT-5.2, a frontier model aimed at developers and professionals, pushing reasoning and coding benchmarks as it races Google&#8217;s Gemini 3 while grappling with compute costs and no generator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hideaki Anno Bids a Final Farewell to Original &#8216;Evangelion&#8217; Studio Gainax</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hideaki-anno-gainax-bankruptcy-neon-genesis-evangelion-studio-khara-2000698488</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698488</guid>
      <description>A year after the animation studio filed for bankruptcy, Gainax has shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Launches GPT-5.2 as It Navigates &#8216;Code Red&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-gpt-launch-gemini-code-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939fab6adb3c84b25e0f697</guid>
      <description>The ChatGPT-maker is releasing its &#8220;best model yet&#8221; as it faces new pressures from Google and other AI competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comcast cable boxes are getting Amazon Luna cloud gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842201/amazon-luna-comcast-xfinity-rogers-cable-boxes</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842201</guid>
      <description>Amazon's Luna cloud gaming service is coming to cable boxes from Comcast and Rogers. The Luna app is already available via web browsers, Fire TV devices, Fire tablets, and many smart TVs from Samsung and LG, and this new expansion will bring the service to "millions" more devices, according to Amazon. Starting Thursday, Luna will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5.2 is OpenAI&amp;#8217;s latest move in the agentic AI battle</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/842529/openai-gpt-5-2-new-model-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842529</guid>
      <description>GPT-5.2 is here, and with it, OpenAI wants "to unlock even more economic value for people," Fidji Simo, the company's CEO of Applications, told reporters in a Thursday briefing. She said it's been in the works for "many, many months." The company calls GPT-5.2 its "best model yet for everyday professional use" in a release, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google debuts &#8216;Disco,&#8217; a Gemini-powered tool for making web apps from browser tabs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/google-debuts-disco-a-gemini-powered-tool-for-making-web-apps-from-browser-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075205</guid>
      <description>Google Labs is testing a product that will work with your browser tabs to make web apps for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission: Impossible &#8211; The Final Reckoning is massive, messy, and a must-see action movie on Paramount+</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/mission-impossible-the-final-reckoning-is-massive-messy-and-a-must-see-action-movie-on-paramount</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fDiZxogPZFVmhsV32DBBXL</guid>
      <description>Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is to watch the eight Mission Impossible film on Paramount's streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Disco is an experimental web browser that builds AI widgets based on your tabs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-disco-is-an-experimental-web-browser-that-builds-ai-widgets-based-on-your-tabs-180000701.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">929ad3ca-1a30-4fd5-83ff-e995c848163d</guid>
      <description>The latest experiment emerging out of Google Labs is Disco, which is the company's AI-driven approach to web browsing. The first feature for Disco is called GenTabs, built on Google's Gemini 3 model.&#160;GenTabs are interactive widgets created from a mix of user prompts, open tabs and chat history. The preview examples demonstrate how GenTabs can create a model to demonstrate entropy as a study aid, or collect trip ideas into one screen for building an itinerary. The GenTab can be further refined with natural language requests, and it will also offer contextual suggestions for additions that may b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is your 2026 resolution about money? Keep this in mind</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458338/is-your-2026-resolution-about-money-keep-this-in-mind</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458338/is-your-2026-resolution-about-money-keep-this-in-mind</guid>
      <description>When it comes to finances, feelings matter. 
If budgeting spreadsheets and lofty financial goals leave you stressed rather than inspired, consider another New Year&#8217;s ritual: an end-of-year money audit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the Netflix-Warner deal mean for talent?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458374/what-does-the-netflix-warner-deal-mean-for-talent</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458374/what-does-the-netflix-warner-deal-mean-for-talent</guid>
      <description>Netflix&#8217;s blockbuster $82.7 billion acquisition of Warner Bros. is raising concerns about fair pay.
Last week, Netflix announced it was buying Warner Bros. in a massive $82.7 billion deal. The streaming giant&#8217;s acquisition will set Netflix, which already leads the streaming wars, even further apart from competitors, as it will also add HBO, a Warner subsidiary. But while the deal will further cement Netflix&#8217;s domination, questions are swirling around how it will impact viewers, as well as the talent platforms rely on.Streaming platforms have recently undergone&#160; consolidation, creating three me...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian&#8217;s AI&#160;assistant&#160;is&#160;coming to its EVs in early 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/rivians-ai-assistant-is-coming-to-its-evs-in-early-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075197</guid>
      <description>And when it does, the AI assistant will roll out to every existing&#160;EV in its lineup, not just the next-generation versions of its R1T truck and R1S SUV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le tout r&#233;cent robot aspirateur de Roborock, not&#233; 9/10 par nos soins, perd d&#233;j&#224; 300 &#8364; de son prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2906817_le-tout-recent-robot-aspirateur-de-roborock-note-9-10-par-nos-soins-perd-deja-300-e-de-son-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2906817_le-tout-recent-robot-aspirateur-de-roborock-note-9-10-par-nos-soins-perd-deja-300-e-de-son-prix</guid>
      <description>
Avec le lavage &#224; 100 &#186;C, le retrait automatique des serpilli&#232;res, ou encore le capteur LiDAR pour se rep&#233;rer,&#160;le Roborock Qrevo Curv 2 ProX est un aspirateur robot qui assure un nettoyage complet. Cet appareil est on&#233;reux, mais Boulanger adoucit son prix avec 300 euros de remise. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Cops Are Now Using AI-Generated &#8216;Mugshots&#8217; to Sketch Crime Suspects</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/arizona-cops-are-now-using-ai-generated-mugshots-to-sketch-crime-suspects-2000698072</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698072</guid>
      <description>A police department in a suburb of Phoenix has used ChatGPT twice this year to generate images of crime suspects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Nothing Phone (4a) pointent le bout de leur nez dans une fuite&#160;: encore un rapport qualit&#233; prix du tonnerre &#224; venir&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/les-nothing-phone-4a-pointent-le-bout-de-leur-nez-dans-une-fuite-encore-un-rapport-qualite-prix-du-tonnerre-a-venir.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315082</guid>
      <description>Nothing poursuit sa mue vers le milieu de gamme. Apr&#232;s le succ&#232;s du Phone (3a), la marque londonienne pr&#233;parerait d&#233;j&#224; les Nothing Phone (4a) et (4a) Pro, misant sur des sp&#233;cifications solides et un tarif contenu autour de 500&#8239;dollars. Une fuite &#233;voque &#233;galement un casque Nothing Headphone (a), version plus accessible du mod&#232;le phare, qui viendrait compl&#233;ter cette nouvelle offensive sur le march&#233;....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The People Behind &#8216;Supergirl&#8217; Are Ready to Share Their Imperfect Hero</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-people-behind-supergirl-are-ready-to-share-their-imperfect-hero-2000698165</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698165</guid>
      <description>Producer James Gunn, director Craig Gillespie, and star Milly Alcock talked about the DC Studios film coming June 26, 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eli Lilly&#8217;s Weight Loss Superdrug Worked So Well During Trials, Some Quit Over Losing Too Much</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/eli-lillys-weight-loss-superdrug-worked-so-well-during-trials-some-quit-over-losing-too-much-2000698424</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698424</guid>
      <description>Step aside, semaglutide&#8212;retatrutide is showing the most impressive weight loss results of any obesity drug to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamoru Hosoda explains why Hamlet is everywhere this year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/842346/mamoru-hosoda-interview-scarlet</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842346</guid>
      <description>Hamlet is having something of a renaissance in 2025. This year's edition of the Toronto International Film Festival featured three different takes on the idea, including Chlo&#233; Zhao's adaptation of the play's inspiration and Aneil Karia's rendition set in modern-day London. But the most out-there version came from Belle director Mamoru Hosoda, who transformed Shakespeare's [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Crypto king&#8217; Do Kwon faces sentencing for misleading Terraform Labs&#8217; investors</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458731/do-kwon-sentenced-terraform-labs-cryptocurrency</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458731/do-kwon-sentenced-terraform-labs-cryptocurrency</guid>
      <description>Investors worldwide lost billions in the downfall of the Singapore crypto firm, which Kwon cofounded in 2018. 
Cryptocurrency mogul Do Kwon is scheduled to be sentenced Thursday for misleading investors who lost billions when his company&#8217;s crypto ecosystem&#160;collapsed in 2022.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
