<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:27:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;My Hero Academia&#8217; Carried the Shonen Anime Torch to a Triumphant Finish</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/my-hero-academia-boku-no-anime-review-series-finale-crunchyroll-kohei-horikoshi-2000701820</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701820</guid>
      <description>'My Hero Academia' earned its flowers as a superhero epic that never lost its way&#8212;and it also elevated the genre to new heights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Cisco customers are vulnerable to new Chinese hacking campaign, researchers say</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/hundreds-of-cisco-customers-are-vulnerable-to-new-chinese-hacking-campaign-researchers-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077895</guid>
      <description>Cisco warned that Chinese government hackers are exploiting a zero-day in some of its products. Researchers now say there are hundreds of vulnerable Cisco customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesses are hiring AI specialists instead of data engineers - and its a big problem</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/businesses-are-hiring-ai-specialists-instead-of-data-engineers-and-its-a-big-problem</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Va6JuvvurdTxocNhDYA2q</guid>
      <description>Yet again, we're being graced with a report stressing the importance of a solid data foundation to get the most out of AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google releases FunctionGemma: a tiny edge model that can control mobile devices with natural language</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/google-releases-functiongemma-a-tiny-edge-model-that-can-control-mobile</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6G3CmuvbnY1z6vqRdfTeEJ</guid>
      <description>While Gemini 3 is still making waves, Google's not taking the foot off the gas in terms of releasing new models.Yesterday, the company released FunctionGemma, a specialized 270-million parameter AI model designed to solve one of the most persistent bottlenecks in modern application development: reliability at the edge. Unlike general-purpose chatbots, FunctionGemma is engineered for a single, critical utility&#8212;translating natural language user commands into structured code that apps and devices can actually execute, all without connecting to the cloud.The release marks a significant strategic p...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get up to 78 percent off ExpressVPN two-year plans for the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-up-to-78-percent-off-expressvpn-two-year-plans-for-the-holidays-194912043.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5a0f70e-8a7d-42de-8d3c-2a4f80959c2d</guid>
      <description>It looks like the holidays aren't a bad time to shop for a VPN subscription. ExpressVPN, Engadget's pick for the best premium provider, currently has a less premium price. This deal gives you two years of the Advanced plan (with a bonus of four free months) for only $101. When it isn't on sale, the same subscription would cost $392.
Engadget's VPN guru, Sam Chapman, praised ExpressVPN's service. He described it as "high-performing" and having "very few flaws." The service received high marks for its speeds, easy-to-use interface and global network availability. The only significant mark agains...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart to Pay $60 Million in Refunds for Allegedly Deceiving Customers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/instacart-to-pay-60-million-in-refunds-for-allegedly-deceiving-customers-2000701915</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701915</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Federal Trade Commission accused Instacart of misleading costumers with promises of free deliveries and full refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up for a year of Crunchyroll Mega Fan and stream your favorite anime for the lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/sign-up-for-a-year-of-crunchyroll-mega-fan-and-stream-your-favorite-anime-for-the-lowest-price-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UvZmpB42eA5FMmsNmsg59c</guid>
      <description>Save $20 / &#163;12 off an annual subscription before the new year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers in China Are Using AI-Generated Images to Get Refunds</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/scammers-in-china-are-using-ai-generated-images-to-get-refunds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69433673a5f88b1c3aabf50b</guid>
      <description>From dead crabs to shredded bed sheets, fraudsters are using fake photos and videos to get their money back from ecommerce sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco email security products actively targeted in zero-day campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/cisco-email-security-products-actively-targeted-in-zero-day-campaign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bNkD8ZL6J7fKP3EZXQEJCJ</guid>
      <description>Two Chinese-nexus groups have been exploiting a newly discovered flaw to establish persistence and launch backdoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't think RAM is expensive enough yet? DDR5 sticks with a triple-fan cooler on top will be shown off at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/dont-think-ram-is-expensive-enough-yet-ddr5-sticks-with-a-triple-fan-cooler-on-top-will-be-shown-off-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xZYKzxquZMnFYGX3wZ3kaa</guid>
      <description>DDR5 memory sticks with a triple-fan cooler on top are going to leave your wallet quaking in fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube creator&#8217;s finance livestream mysteriously appears on White House website</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463929/white-house-website-youtube-creator-finance-livestream</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463929/white-house-website-youtube-creator-finance-livestream</guid>
      <description>The livestream was from Matt Farley, who posts as @RealMattMoney.
The livestream of a YouTube content creator talking about investments mysteriously appeared to take over a White House website, raising questions about whether the site was hacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Starlink Satellite Is Tumbling Toward Earth After a Strange Anomaly in Orbit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-starlink-satellite-is-tumbling-toward-earth-after-a-strange-anomaly-in-orbit-2000701874</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701874</guid>
      <description>The satellite suffered a sudden drop in altitude, suggesting there may have been a small explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yann LeCun confirms his new &#8216;world model&#8217; startup, reportedly seeks $5B+ valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/yann-lecun-confirms-his-new-world-model-startup-reportedly-seeks-5b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077797</guid>
      <description>Renowned AI scientist Yann LeCun confirmed on Thursday the worst-kept secret in the tech world: that he had indeed launched a new startup. Although he did say he will not be running the new company as its CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Darabont Reveals the Real Story Behind Why He Didn&#8217;t Take on &#8216;The Dark Tower&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/frank-darabont-reveals-the-real-story-behind-why-he-didnt-take-on-the-dark-tower-2000701920</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701920</guid>
      <description>The director of 'The Shawshank Redemption,' 'The Green Mile,' and 'The Mist' talks about the Stephen King project that got away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s Stargate Data Center Approved in Michigan as American Anger Starts to Boil</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openais-stargate-data-center-approved-in-michigan-as-american-anger-starts-to-boil-2000701890</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701890</guid>
      <description>The data center backlash has begun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPad deals this week include the iPad mini for $100 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-ipad-deals-this-week-include-the-ipad-mini-for-100-off-150020342.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c2b9c33-9a87-45ff-b978-e41b8f7a90a2</guid>
      <description>The iPad, of course, isn't the only tablet computer out there &#8212; it wasn't even the first &#8212; but Apple's version redefined the category. In our opinion, it's the best tablet you can buy and these slates consistently earn high scores in our reviews. That doesn't mean you should have to pay full price for your next iPad. We are continually on the hunt for good deals on iPads (and other Apple gear while we're at it) and each week, we round them up right there.Current discounts include the iPad mini and the 11-inch iPad Pro, each for $100 off the list price. Beyond iPads, are a few other Apple deals...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Blacklyte Atlas Lite and it's an ultra-cool standing desk for work and play</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/blacklyte-atlas-lite-standing-desk-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36FpKU3HAXP6YissCUgcam</guid>
      <description>The Blacklyte Atlas Lite is a standing desk with hints of the gamer aesthetic and functionality well-suited for business professionals - and it meets those needs with ease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes: The Trump administration is likely to buy more equity in more private companies in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463660/trump-equity-intel-nippon-warren-sanders-chips</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T19:06:44</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463660/trump-equity-intel-nippon-warren-sanders-chips</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new normal for industrial policy.
The government took stakes in a number of private companies during 2025, and is likely to continue making equity investments while Donald Trump remains in office. Whether or not this is a wise long-term strategy is an ongoing debate with strong opinions on both sides.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman&#8217;s New Brain Venture, Merge Labs, Will Spin Out of a Nonprofit</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/sam-altman-brain-computer-interface-merge-labs-spin-out-nonprofit-forest-neurotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69431180bc07478ec08f559c</guid>
      <description>Merge Labs, a brain-computer interface startup that seeks to read brain activity using ultrasound, is being spun out of Forest Neurotech, a Los Angeles nonprofit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Reddit Post Helped Find the Brown University Shooting Suspect</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-a-reddit-post-helped-find-the-brown-university-shooting-suspect-2000701854</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701854</guid>
      <description>"The police need to look into a grey Nissan with Florida plates, possibly a rental."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new music player is like a hi-res iPod nano, but with microSD storage &#8212; and you won&#8217;t believe how cheap it is</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/portable-media-players/this-new-music-player-is-like-a-hi-res-ipod-nano-but-with-microsd-storage-and-you-wont-believe-how-cheap-it-is</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qyBJS7Y7KRKbwiGHsMaMAV</guid>
      <description>A very tempting new option from our favorite budget audiophile brand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States are divided on whether to follow Trump&#8217;s tax breaks on tips, overtime, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463912/states-trump-tax-breaks-tips-overtime-corporate</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463912/states-trump-tax-breaks-tips-overtime-corporate</guid>
      <description>So far, only a few states have taken votes on whether to adopt the tax breaks.
To tax tips or not? That is a question that will confront lawmakers in states across the U.S. as they convene for work next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg's nonprofit cuts ties with the immigration advocacy group he co-founded</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/mark-zuckerbergs-nonprofit-cuts-ties-with-the-immigration-advocacy-group-he-co-founded-183447900.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6527912-d56a-43d8-ab07-30a9ebbe2f23</guid>
      <description>Behold Mark Zuckerberg: man of principle. Witness the Meta CEO's dedication to the most high-minded of causes: "currying favor with whoever's in charge." In 2013, when Barack Obama was president, Zuckerberg co-founded FWD.us, a pro-immigration advocacy group. For years, he vocally supported providing paths to citizenship for "the most talented and hardest-working people, no matter where they were born." Now, in 2025, with Donald Trump back in power and pushing draconian immigration policies, Zuckerberg's philanthropy organization has officially cut ties with the group. Who says Big Tech execut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used an ATM since 2007? Visa and Mastercard may owe you cash</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463788/used-an-atm-since-2007-visa-and-mastercard-may-owe-you-cash</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463788/used-an-atm-since-2007-visa-and-mastercard-may-owe-you-cash</guid>
      <description>The money would go to customers charged unreimbursed fees at non-bank ATMs nationwide.
Visa and Mastercard have agreed to pay $167.5 million to settle a long-running class action lawsuit. The suit, which was first filed&#160;back in October 2011, accused the two major credit card companies of conspiring to keep ATM fees artificially high.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford recalls over 270,000 electric and hybrid cars due to parking function issue</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463906/ford-recall-electric-hybrid-mustang-maverick-parking</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463906/ford-recall-electric-hybrid-mustang-maverick-parking</guid>
      <description>Ford said that it will implement a park module software update for free.
Ford is recalling more than 270,000 electric and hybrid vehicles in the U.S. because of a parking function problem that could lead to them rolling away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;On s&#8217;est fait avoir&#160;&#187; : comment iRobot a perdu la guerre des aspirateurs robots et pourquoi la Chine est son seul salut</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/irobot/2917283_on-sest-fait-avoir-comment-irobot-a-perdu-la-guerre-des-aspirateurs-robots-et-pourquoi-la-chine-est-son-seul-salut</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/irobot/2917283_on-sest-fait-avoir-comment-irobot-a-perdu-la-guerre-des-aspirateurs-robots-et-pourquoi-la-chine-est-son-seul-salut</guid>
      <description>
C'est rare. Tr&#232;s rare. Un CEO qui vous regarde dans les yeux et vous dit : "On s'est plant&#233;s." C'est pourtant ce que vient de faire Gary Cohen. Alors qu'iRobot passe sous pavillon chinois pour &#233;viter la faillite, le patron de la marque embl&#233;matique ne cherche pas d'excuses. Retards technologiques, arrogance, prix d&#233;connect&#233;s... iRobot nous explique tout.
...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
