<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:37:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Uber Is Sinking Over $100 Million Into Charging Stations for Self-Driving Cars</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/uber-is-sinking-over-100-million-into-charging-stations-for-self-driving-cars-2000723652</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723652</guid>
      <description>The move signals the ride-hailing company is preparing for the rise of robotaxis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dream of Home Arcades Isn&#8217;t Dead, and Neither Is Arcade1Up</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-dream-of-home-arcades-isnt-dead-and-neither-is-arcade1up-2000723657</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723657</guid>
      <description>The company behind Lite Brite said it wants to make Arcade1Up feel even more authentic than before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Moon Race Starts This Year&#8212;and This Time It&#8217;s All About the Water</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-new-moon-race-starts-this-year-and-this-time-its-all-about-the-water-2000723719</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723719</guid>
      <description>The U.S. and China are each planning to land in the Moon&#8217;s Shackleton crater this year. Whoever gets there first will secure the best access to its resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is helping hackers make new malware faster and more complex than ever - and things may only get tougher</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/ai-is-helping-hackers-make-new-malware-faster-and-more-complex-than-ever-and-things-may-only-get-tougher</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">riynM2qfo6r7J9Bh3F27Y</guid>
      <description>Social engineering is still the number one attack vector, but ransomware operators are stepping away from encryptors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPad deals you can get right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21280354/best-ipad-deals-apple</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T17:12:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21280354/best-ipad-deals-apple</guid>
      <description>While the best iPad deals usually land during major sale events like Black Friday,&#160;many great iPad deals are available outside of those times. The day-to-day discounts come and go like changing winds, so there&#8217;s often some amount to be saved, particularly on Apple&#8217;s most affordable iPad, the iPad Mini, and the latest iPad Air. Hell, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah Governor Pushes Back on CFTC&#8217;s Prediction Market Power Grab</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/utah-governor-pushes-back-on-cftcs-prediction-market-power-grab-2000723681</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723681</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration is going to bat for a hands-off approach to the explosion of gambling in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking conference Def Con bans three people linked to Epstein</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/18/hacking-conference-def-con-bans-three-people-linked-to-epstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094187</guid>
      <description>The Def Con hacking conference banned hackers Pablos Holman and Vincenzo Iozzo, as well as former MIT Media Lab director Joichi Ito, from attending the annual conference after their reported connections with Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Embo Episodes to Watch Before &#8216;The Mandalorian and Grogu&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mandalorian-and-grogu-embo-clone-wars-all-appearances-2000723409</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723409</guid>
      <description>With the iconic 'Clone Wars' bounty hunter making his live-action debut in the new 'Star Wars' movie, we look back at the must-watch episodes from his clearly very important back catalogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New agent framework matches human-engineered AI systems &#8212; and adds zero inference cost to deploy</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/new-agent-framework-matches-human-engineered-ai-systems-and-adds-zero</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Z1He3r59yIp4so6YFE4Zz</guid>
      <description>Agents built on top of today's models often break with simple changes &#8212; a new library, a workflow modification &#8212; and require a human engineer to fix it. That's one of the most persistent challenges in deploying AI for the enterprise: creating agents that can adapt to dynamic environments without constant hand-holding. While today's models are powerful, they are largely static.To address this, researchers at the University of California, Santa Barbara have developed Group-Evolving Agents (GEA), a new framework that enables groups of AI agents to evolve together, sharing experiences and reusing ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Unbeatable hardware heist&#8217;: Get a free Asus TUF Gaming X870E-Plus AM5 motherboard when you buy 32GB V-Color Manta DDR5 memory for $449.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/unbeatable-hardware-heist-get-a-free-asus-tuf-gaming-x870e-plus-am5-motherboard-when-you-buy-32gb-v-color-manta-ddr5-memory-for-usd449-99</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qLZ5U2dauaTMF3mcZrVg4W</guid>
      <description>Save a staggering 45% off the prices of the two components sold separately, it&#8217;s another bonkers deal!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farewell, old friend &#8212; Linux 7.0 finally ditches the ancient (but iconic) Intel 440BX chipset's EDAC driver, but what's next?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/farewell-old-friend-linux-7-0-finally-ditches-the-ancient-but-iconic-intel-440bx-chipsets-edac-driver-but-whats-next</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AVGwTK3TvpiUGptQup4SF9</guid>
      <description>Linux kernel 7.0 removes the Intel 440BX EDAC driver, ending legacy support while highlighting the shift toward modern memory and CPU architectures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android gaming has to be taken seriously after this &#8212; this liquid-cooled Chinese phone just ran the PC version of Cyberpunk 2077, and I&#8217;m shocked</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/mobile-gaming/android-gaming-has-to-be-taken-seriously-after-this-this-liquid-cooled-chinese-phone-just-ran-the-pc-version-of-cyberpunk-2077-and-im-shocked</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">U84pxbwKvYucMBRCMrr8zN</guid>
      <description>Android phones are so powerful now that they can emulate AAA PC gaming, as Cyberpunk 2077 now runs above 30fps on the RedMagic 11 Pro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media on trial: tech giants face lawsuits over addiction, safety, and mental health</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/880850/social-media-lawsuits-meta-facebook-instagram-tiktok</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T16:27:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=880850</guid>
      <description>A set of bellwether cases alleging that social media platforms harmed teens&#8217; safety and mental health is going to trial this year, putting executives like Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg on the stand to answer questions about what they&#8217;ve done or not done to protect kids. Unlike many earlier legal challenges against social media companies, these [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bose QuietComfort Ultra Gen 2 Headphones Are at Their Lowest Price in Months</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-2-deal-0218/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6995fadfb9f2ba02861d3096</guid>
      <description>Bose's fabulous QuietComfort Ultra Gen 2 noise-canceling headphones are the best travel headphones and are $50 off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is your startup&#8217;s check engine light on? Google Cloud&#8217;s VP explains what to do</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/is-your-startups-check-engine-light-on-google-clouds-vp-explains-what-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3094123</guid>
      <description>Startup founders are being pushed to move faster than ever, using AI while facing tighter funding, rising infrastructure costs, and more pressure to show real traction early. Cloud credits, access to GPUs, and foundation models have made it easier to get started, but those early infrastructure choices can have unforeseen consequences once startups move beyond [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Is Starting to Show an Impact in Early-Career Jobs, Irish Government Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ai-is-starting-to-show-an-impact-in-early-career-jobs-irish-government-says-2000723436</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723436</guid>
      <description>The data from Ireland could be an early warning for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland&#8217;s Freaky Ice Plumes May Be Fueled by Wild, Pasta-Like Churning</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/greenlands-freaky-ice-plumes-may-be-fueled-by-wild-pasta-like-churning-2000723633</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723633</guid>
      <description>The ice sheet may be undergoing thermal convection, resembling a "boiling pot of pasta," according to researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring&amp;#8217;s AI-powered Search Party won&amp;#8217;t stop at finding lost dogs, leaked email shows</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/880906/ring-siminoff-email-leak-search-party-expansion</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T16:01:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880906</guid>
      <description>A leaked internal email obtained by 404 Media shows that Ring has bigger plans for its AI-powered neighborhood search capability than just looking for lost dogs. The outlet reports the email, sent last October by founder Jamie Siminoff to all Ring employees, says that with Search Party, "You can now see a future where we [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Soderbergh Is Still Disappointed That &#8216;The Hunt for Ben Solo&#8217; Didn&#8217;t Happen</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/steven-soderbergh-is-still-disappointed-that-the-hunt-for-ben-solo-didnt-happen-2000723661</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723661</guid>
      <description>The Oscar-winning director of 'Ocean's Eleven' and 'Traffic' truly thought the 'Star Wars' movie was going to happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bigger than the Super Bowl &#8212; futuristic humanoid robots dominate China&#8217;s most-watched TV show and leap ahead of the Tesla Optimus</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/bigger-than-the-super-bowl-futuristic-humanoid-robots-dominate-chinas-most-watched-tv-show-and-leap-ahead-of-the-tesla-optimus</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">buRXTDecx5MRTVeLc4wWXc</guid>
      <description>Humanoid robots were the star of the show at China's Spring Festival Gala performance &#8211;and interest has never been higher, according to retailers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A startup called Germ becomes the first private messenger that launches directly from Bluesky&#8217;s app</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/18/a-startup-called-germ-becomes-the-first-private-messenger-that-launches-directly-from-blueskys-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094069</guid>
      <description>Social network Bluesky now offers private messaging by integrating the startup Germ's E2E encrypted messenger natively in its app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini can now generate a 30-second approximation of what real music sounds like</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/gemini-can-now-generate-a-30-second-approximation-of-what-real-music-sounds-like-204445903.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b1ea506-6d38-4bad-a73b-b9c8fa1f2d13</guid>
      <description>Google has announced that using its newly incorporated Lyria 3 model, Gemini users will be able to generate 30-second music tracks based on a prompt, or remix an existing track to their liking. The new model builds on Gemini's pre-existing ability to generate text, images and video, and will also be available in YouTube's "Dream Track" feature, where it can be used to generate detailed backing tracks for Shorts.Like some other music generation tools, prompting Gemini doesn't require a lot of detail to produce serviceable results. Google's example prompt is "a comical R&amp;B slow jam about a sock ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI, Google, and Perplexity near approval to host AI directly for the U.S. government (exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91494829/openai-google-perplexity-hosting-ai-us-government-exclusive</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-18T20:43:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91494829/openai-google-perplexity-hosting-ai-us-government-exclusive</guid>
      <description>The shift would let them bypass partners like Palantir and Microsoft and work with the federal government directly.
Three AI companies&#8212;OpenAI, Google, and Perplexity&#8212;are on the verge of receiving approval to sell their technology, hosted on their own cloud systems, directly to the government, a person familiar with the matter tells Fast Company. That authorization will be on a &#8220;low impact&#8221; and pilot level, the person said, but constitutes a major step toward independence....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
