<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:21:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>B Capital founding partner Kabir Narang leaves to launch new investment platform</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/b-capital-founding-partner-kabir-narang-leaves-to-launch-new-investment-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074414</guid>
      <description>Kabir Narang is laying the groundwork for a new investment platform slated for 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab HP Instant Ink 'loophole' worth almost &#163;126 but you have to be quick &#8212;  print up to 2,100 colour pages in 90 days for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/grab-hp-instant-ink-loophole-worth-almost-gbp126-but-you-have-to-be-quick-print-up-to-2-100-colour-pages-in-90-days-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HPvqzsVheywe2rW37c36R5</guid>
      <description>HP Instant Ink trick gives you months of free printing, but the window won&#8217;t stay open for long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superman and Spider-Man Collide in the First Looks at DC and Marvel&#8217;s Next Big Crossover</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dc-superman-spider-man-1-covers-2000697425</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697425</guid>
      <description>It's out March 25, 2026, and there are 11 covers in total by the likes of Jim Lee, Jorge Jim&#233;nez, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation just launched its 2025 Wrap-Up &#8212; but good luck getting it to load</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/playstation/playstation-just-launched-its-2025-wrap-up-but-good-luck-getting-it-to-load</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V6e8qRrDdDNck6QhAJr5tC</guid>
      <description>PlayStation just launched its 2025 Wrap-Up to show users their top games, total trophies, and hours spent on the platform, but, as with last year, the experience is slow to load for some users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some of our favorite gifts will cost you less than $25</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780844/best-gifts-under-25-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780844</guid>
      <description>Holiday shopping on a budget can feel constricting, especially if you've been invited to a white elephant or need a last-minute stocking stuffer. The good news is that, with this guide, you can leave that stress behind. Whether you're aiming for something practical or fun, we've found plenty of great gifts for under $25 - [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Cursor&#8217;s CEO believes OpenAI, Anthropic competition won&#8217;t crush his startup</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/why-cursors-ceo-believes-openai-anthropic-competition-wont-crush-his-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074040</guid>
      <description>After reaching $1 billion in annualized revenue, Anysphere CEO Michael Truell explained the features his company is focused on building out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Game Awards 2025 on December 11</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/how-to-watch-the-game-awards-2025-on-december-11-205500124.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">269098e7-2878-4a34-a0a5-a42fb9289d29</guid>
      <description>The Game Awards are this week, with the grand showcase for 2025 coming up on Thursday, December 11 at 8PM ET. There's also a pre-show (in case the multi-hour affair just isn't enough TGA for you) and that kicks off at 7:30PM ET. The ceremony will be a mix of honoring games from the past year and debuting trailers for future releases, so expect a couple interesting announcements to emerge from Thursday night. Engadget will be reporting on any big stories as they happen at The Game Awards, but if you want to watch along with us, the whole shebang is available to watch for free on just about ever...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traeger debuts Woodridge Pro Plus grill with Wi-Fi features and built-in storage cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/traeger-debuts-woodridge-pro-plus-grill-with-wi-fi-features-and-built-in-storage-cabinet-205320548.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d939bc73-8997-4834-8859-f898480b8bc1</guid>
      <description>Traeger debuted its Woodridge line of Wi-Fi-enabled pellet grills back in January. The overall theme across the Woodridge, Woodridge Pro and Woodridge Elite is the company&#8217;s reliable performance and features are available for less than the cost of its most premium models. Just before Christmas, the company is adding to the the Woodridge lineup with the Woodridge Pro Plus. 
For $400 more than the Woodridge Pro, this Plus model adds the enclosed storage cabinet from the Woodridge Elite. Instead of an open shelf, the cabinet offers a better option for keep pellet bins and other accessories close ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Mouth Wash? The Science Says Yes</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/garlic-mouth-wash-the-science-says-yes-2000697393</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697393</guid>
      <description>Researchers reviewed existing evidence on whether mouthwash with garlic extract could be a viable alternative for the current golden standard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK strengthens subsea cables against Russian interference</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/uk-strengthens-subsea-cables-against-russian-interference</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Vd4PqgBDsfCa8w6U7U4ME8</guid>
      <description>Project Atlantic Bastion is kicking off and should help secure UK undersea critical infrastructure from the Russians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wake Up Dead Man digs deep for a darker, more powerful Knives Out</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/840977/wake-up-dead-man-review-netflix-knives-out</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T15:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=840977</guid>
      <description>Over two films, Rian Johnson's Knives Out series has offered something largely absent from the modern movie landscape: intricate murder mysteries full of humor and gasp-worthy moments. The original Knives Out started things off relatively small with a cozy whodunit, which then became a larger and more elaborate puzzle with the sequel Glass Onion. Both [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian is building its own AI assistant</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/rivian-is-building-its-own-ai-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073894</guid>
      <description>The EV maker will likely share more details on its upcoming AI &amp; Autonomy Day scheduled for December 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Beck Is Giving American History the Grokipedia Treatment</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/glenn-beck-is-giving-american-history-the-grokipedia-treatment-2000697382</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697382</guid>
      <description>"This is not ChatGPT. This is not Wikipedia. This is verified, factual, memorized, first source truth."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best subscription box gifts for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-subscription-box-gifts-for-2025-130037236.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85595b0e-b7d8-4f0e-b8cb-bc77d2b4ff1b</guid>
      <description>The best gifts inspire joy long after the initial unwrapping. Subscription boxes are designed to show up again and again, each time offering something new to try, build or taste. They&#8217;re perfect for friends who already have too much gear or relatives who like to discover things without searching for them. From electronics kits and mystery puzzles to Japanese treats and fresh coffee, these boxes make each month feel like a small celebration. You pick the vibe, the plan and the recipient gets a steady stream of good surprises. Below are 13 subscription boxes that hit the sweet spot between fun a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#8217;re Going to Need a Bigger Wallet to Afford These Rare &#8216;Jaws&#8217; Props</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youre-going-to-need-a-bigger-wallet-to-afford-these-rare-jaws-props-2000697409</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697409</guid>
      <description>Two sought-after items that are not in the Academy Museum's huge exhibit paying tribute to the Spielberg classic are going up for auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PepsiCo to cut prices and 20% of products under a new deal</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457330/pepsico-cut-prices-products-under-deal-elliott-investors</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T20:00:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457330/pepsico-cut-prices-products-under-deal-elliott-investors</guid>
      <description>PepsiCo said it also plans to accelerate the introduction of new offerings with simpler and more functional ingredients.
PepsiCo plans to cut prices and eliminate some of its products under a deal with an&#160;activist investor&#160;announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 51 Best Shows on Hulu, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (December 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-tv-shows-hulu-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63d96ba473cac2b11b42eaae</guid>
      <description>To Cook a Bear, The Manipulated, and Chris Hemsworth: A Road Trip to Remember are just a few of the shows you should be watching on Hulu this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three in 10 US teens use AI chatbots every day, but safety concerns are growing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/three-in-ten-u-s-teens-use-ai-chatbots-every-day-but-safety-concerns-are-growing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074018</guid>
      <description>While teenagers may start out using AI chatbots for basic questions, their relationship with chatbot platforms has the potential to turn addictive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Wildlife Awards 2025 winners announced &#8212; here are the hilarious winning photos</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/photography/comedy-wildlife-awards-2025-winners-announced-here-are-the-hilarious-winning-photos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83eRwXsF24tCHmUpqxBpSH</guid>
      <description>The winners of the Nikon Comedy Wildlife Awards 2025 have been unveiled, with 44 shortlisted images selected from over 10,000 entries &#8211; a record high for the contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly one-third of teens use AI chatbots daily</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/nearly-one-third-of-teens-use-ai-chatbots-daily-200000888.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b68508bc-a105-40af-af92-7d9f6fbc7381</guid>
      <description>AI chatbots haven't come close to replacing teens' social media habits, but they are playing a significant role in their online habits. Nearly one-third of US teens report using AI chatbots daily or more, according to a new report from Pew Research.&#160;The report is the first from Pew to specifically examine how often teens are using AI overall, and was published alongside its latest research on teens' social media use. It's based on an online survey of 1,458 US teens who were polled between September 25 to October 9, 2025. According to Pew, the survey was "weighted to be representative of U.S. t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AirPods Pro 3 are back to their lowest price ahead of the holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/841059/apple-airpods-pro-3-silent-hill-f-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T14:59:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841059</guid>
      <description>If you didn&#8217;t catch the Black Friday deal on Apple&#8217;s AirPods Pro 3, the good news is the price has dropped again ahead of the holidays. Right now, the noise-canceling earbuds are matching their all-time low price of $219.99 ($30 off) at Amazon, Walmart, and Best Buy. It&#8217;s a great deal considering the AirPods Pro [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This top-rated budget gaming laptop with an RTX 5050 just dropped to $579 at Walmart</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/this-top-rated-budget-gaming-laptop-with-an-rtx-5050-just-dropped-to-usd579-at-walmart</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tBMUJVEzpoTwY9WGq8dNSC</guid>
      <description>Walmart has slashed the price of this Acer Nitro V with an RTX 5050 to a fantastic low price of $579, making it a great buy for budget gamers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google brings back Black Friday prices for earbuds, phones, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/841072/google-pixel-9a-pixel-watch-4-holiday-gifts-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T14:47:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841072</guid>
      <description>Google just launched its holiday sale, and it&#8217;s basically Black Friday and Cyber Monday revived. From smartphones to smart security devices, plenty of great gifts have returned to their Black Friday prices, with some third-party retailers in some cases offering better deals than Google. Prices for a few of our favorite gadgets are even matching [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allows Nvidia to sell H200 AI chips to China</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457324/trump-greenlights-nvidia-sale-h200-ai-chips-china</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T19:46:22</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457324/trump-greenlights-nvidia-sale-h200-ai-chips-china</guid>
      <description>Nvidia applauded Trump&#8217;s decision, saying the choice would support domestic manufacturing.
President Donald Trump said Monday that he would allow&#160;Nvidia&#160;to sell an advanced type of computer chip used in the development of artificial intelligence to &#8220;approved customers&#8221; in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Webb telescope spots a supernova from 13 billion years ago</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/the-webb-telescope-spots-a-supernova-from-13-billion-years-ago-194327489.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcaa7745-7905-44ee-975e-73cb409cda29</guid>
      <description>The James Webb Space Telescope and other international observatories have spotted a 13-billion-year-old supernova. On Tuesday, the European Space Agency (ESA) announced the sighting of a gamma-ray burst from a star that exploded when the Universe was only 730 million years old. The Webb telescope even detected the supernova's host galaxy. Before this observation, the oldest recorded supernova was from when the Universe was 1.8 billion years old. That's a difference of more than a billion years.You can see the gamma-ray burst in the image below. It's the tiny red smudge at the center of the zoo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slack CEO Denise Dresser to join OpenAI as chief revenue officer</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/slack-ceo-denise-dresser-to-join-openai-as-chief-revenue-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074320</guid>
      <description>OpenAI says that Dresser will be responsible for the company's revenue strategy in enterprise and customer success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiat Will Sell Tiny EV in the U.S. With a 28 MPH Top Speed</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fiat-will-sell-tiny-ev-in-the-u-s-with-a-28-mph-top-speed-2000697415</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697415</guid>
      <description>It's morning in America for cute little cars that Americans have historically rejected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is CoreWeave the AI boom&#8217;s canary in a coal mine?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91457190/coreweave-ai-boom-cloud-nvidia-openai</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-09T19:40:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91457190/coreweave-ai-boom-cloud-nvidia-openai</guid>
      <description>The highly leveraged company&#8217;s stock dropped 8% Monday after announcing plans to raise another $2 billion via convertible debt.&#160;
CoreWeave stock dropped 8% Monday after the AI cloud computing company announced plans to raise another $2 billion, this time through convertible debt, to finance its rapid build-out of new data centers. On Tuesday, the company said it would increase the total offering to $2.25 billion. CoreWeave, which sells access to powerful Nvidia graphics processing units (GPUs) to run AI models, may be a bellwether in an industry placing unprecedented bets on an AI boom they be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Wallet to gain support for digital Porsche keys</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-wallet-to-gain-support-for-digital-porsche-keys-193000085.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7019bcb6-281f-418c-add1-094aa5290e02</guid>
      <description>Owners of the Porsche Macan and upcoming Porsche Cayenne Electric will be able to unlock and start their cars with their Galaxy phones, Samsung has announced. The cars, alongside other Porsche models, are gaining support for Samsung Wallet's Digital Key feature, which lets users wirelessly control their car over a secure UWB or NFC connection.Digital Key support will be available in Europe in December, before rolling out globally, "aligned with the launch timeline of Porsche vehicles," Samsung says. Samsung Wallet is available on Samsung devices as old as the Galaxy S20, Note 20, Galaxy Z Fold...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; le Samsung Galaxy XR : l&#8217;anti Apple Vision Pro est l&#224;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2902831_on-a-teste-le-samsung-galaxy-xr-ne-vous-precipitez-pas-voici-pourquoi</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2902831_on-a-teste-le-samsung-galaxy-xr-ne-vous-precipitez-pas-voici-pourquoi</guid>
      <description>
Voici la r&#233;ponse de Google et Samsung &#224; l'h&#233;g&#233;monie naissante d'Apple dans la r&#233;alit&#233; mixte. De passage &#224; New York, je n'ai pas r&#233;sist&#233;. J'ai ramen&#233; un Galaxy XR dans mes valises pour comprendre ce que &#171; Android XR &#187; a dans le ventre. Le produit est utilisable en fran&#231;ais, le Play Store est l&#224;, et la promesse est belle : transformer votre environnement en un bureau Android g&#233;ant et infini. Voici ce que j'en pense.
...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
