<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 05:28:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>"We are living in times of great change&#8221; - I speak to AWS&#8217; top AI minds to hear how it wants to open up agents (and building) to everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/we-are-living-in-times-of-great-change-i-speak-to-aws-top-ai-minds-to-hear-how-it-wants-to-open-up-agents-and-building-to-everyone</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DHWd4dCDZvSfPPJVxQiigQ</guid>
      <description>AI agents are set to play a big role in your workplace in 2026 if AWS has anything to do with it - I spoke to its AI experts to hear more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Percy Jackson creator Rick Riordan says he admires the 'imagination' of fan theories: 'I love that they feel so passionately about the material'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/percy-jackson-creator-rick-riordan-says-he-admires-the-imagination-of-fan-theories-i-love-that-they-feel-so-passionately-about-the-material</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9PCPBQRy6zQo9nNE8nbLcG</guid>
      <description>Percy Jackson author Rick Riordan appreciates the imagination of fans who read and watch his works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate group Anna's Archive says it has scraped Spotify in its entirety</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/pirate-group-annas-archive-says-it-has-scraped-spotify-in-its-entirety-211914755.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d44519-fbc3-48af-aa57-80d7b6387beb</guid>
      <description>Anna's Archive, the open-source search engine for shadow libraries, says it scraped Spotify's entire library of music. The group acquired metadata for around 256 million tracks, with 86 million actual songs, and is just under 300TB in total size."A while ago, we discovered a way to scrape Spotify at scale. We saw a role for us here to build a music archive primarily aimed at preservation," the group said in a blog post. The pirated treasure trove of music represents over 15 million artists with over 58 million albums.The group intends to make all files available for download for anyone with th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's Boxing Day sale hasn't officially started &#8211; but these 62 deals are a no-nonsense shortlist for (very) last-minute Christmas shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/live/news/amazon-australia-boxing-day-deals-2025-live</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 03:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Mkk5HT58sRrhR6gZkUK2of</guid>
      <description>Boxing Day sales are here for 2025 is here and you can score a great deal on audio, appliances, tablets and more at Amazon</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
