<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 21:20:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Mortal Kombat&#8217;/&#8217;Street Fighter&#8217; Pissing Contest Now Includes Their Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-mortal-kombat-street-fighter-pissing-contest-now-includes-their-movies-2000699407</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 21:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699407</guid>
      <description>Turns out, the 90s never really left us as the beef between 'Street Fighter' and 'Mortal Kombat' has now extended to theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash driver faces felony charges after allegedly spraying customers&#8217; food</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/13/doordash-driver-faces-felony-charges-after-allegedly-spraying-customers-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 21:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075805</guid>
      <description>A woman is facing felony charges in Evansville, Indiana over a DoorDash delivery in which she allegedly sprayed the food with a substance that made the customers vomit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orico just launched the cutest NAS drive I've ever seen &#8212;  and yes, there's even a knob</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/orico-just-launched-the-cutest-nas-drive-ive-ever-seen-and-yes-theres-even-a-knob</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ytwKdoDi8dhMumSkteBn6D</guid>
      <description>Orico&#8217;s PTM dock lineup introduces sliding M.2 trays and varied port layouts, creating a compact system that can behave like a NAS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A AAA game for the Alien franchise is back in the works</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/a-aaa-game-for-the-alien-franchise-is-back-in-the-works-204401214.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 20:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f34d3fa2-02d6-4774-80b7-6670fd496ab3</guid>
      <description>If Alien: Romulus reawakened your appetite for the iconic sci-fi franchise, the good news is that a promising video game could be on the way. According to an Insider Gaming report, a new game for the Alien franchise is back in development. The report's sources mentioned that the single-player game will be set in a "decaying space station" as an arcade survival horror that can be compared to "Shadow of [the] Tomb Raider with Xenomorphs."
It's not the first time we heard about this Alien game, which was first reported on in 2022 under the codename "Marathon." According to Insider Gaming, the gam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: The Death of Charlie Kirk Led to a New Age of Bosses Policing Social Media</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/report-the-death-of-charlie-kirk-led-to-a-new-age-of-bosses-policing-social-media-2000699486</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699486</guid>
      <description>Experts tell the Washington Post that workers' social media behavior is on the minds of employers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitman at 25: Celebrity crossovers, co-op chaos, and the future of Agent 47</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/hitman-at-25-celebrity-crossovers-co-op-chaos-and-the-future-of-agent-47</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">j5tVfPxevcDzzZcAEkiCqK</guid>
      <description>The IO Interactive team behind the longstanding assassination sim talks Eminem and Milla Jovovich collaborations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch John Cena&#8217;s final match: free streams, schedule for Saturday Night's Main Event XLII</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/john-cenas-final-match-wwe-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ECzqrBzMkBsScGAosfdRY6</guid>
      <description>All the ways to stream John Cena&#8217;s final match live online, with Gunther aiming to crash the farewell party at Saturday Night's Main Event XLII in Washington, DC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why most enterprise AI coding pilots underperform (Hint: It's not the model)</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-most-enterprise-ai-coding-pilots-underperform-hint-its-not-the-model</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0jIfIRK7bn2tBn4YUaNt4</guid>
      <description>Gen AI in software engineering has moved well beyond autocomplete. The emerging frontier is agentic coding: AI systems capable of planning changes, executing them across multiple steps and iterating based on feedback. Yet despite the excitement around &#8220;AI agents that code,&#8221; most enterprise deployments underperform. The limiting factor is no longer the model. It&#8217;s context: The structure, history and intent surrounding the code being changed. In other words, enterprises are now facing a systems design problem: They have not yet engineered the environment these agents operate in.The shift from as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animation and Video Games Lost 3 Voice Actors This Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/animation-and-video-games-lost-3-voice-actors-this-week-2000699341</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699341</guid>
      <description>90s and 00s kids likely grew up hearing voice actors Jim Ward, Jeff Garcia, and Julie Mayfield across the cartoons and games of their youth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI data center boom could be bad news for other infrastructure projects</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/13/ai-data-center-boom-could-be-bad-news-for-other-infrastructure-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075803</guid>
      <description>Improvements to roads, bridges, and other infrastructure could take a hit as data center construction accelerates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-Life 3 is rumored to be a Steam Machine launch title and could arrive in spring 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/half-life-3-is-rumored-to-be-a-steam-machine-launch-title-and-could-arrive-in-spring-2026-193029413.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">105dd1af-3007-4f10-905e-c1236a068d4f</guid>
      <description>Half-Life fans are nothing if not patient. For the diehard fans out there, the latest test of patience comes from Insider Gaming Weekly's podcast, which claimed that the third installment in the Half-Life franchise is set to release with the launch of the Steam Machine sometime in spring 2026.
"The window I was specifically told was spring 2026 for the Steam Machine, for the Frame, for the Controller, for Half-Life 3," Mike Straw, one of the hosts of the Insider Gaming Weekly podcast and senior editor at Insider Gaming, said. "At the end of the day, the game is real."
Straw added that all the ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
