<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:30:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hi-Yah! &#8216;The Muppet Show&#8217; Was a Smash Hit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hi-yah-the-muppet-show-was-a-smash-hit-2000722178</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722178</guid>
      <description>Disney's given everyone more Muppets with 'The Muppet Show,' and people love it. But is there more on the horizon?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Elevation Lab AirTag 10-year extended battery case is on sale for only $16 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/this-elevation-lab-airtag-10-year-extended-battery-case-is-on-sale-for-only-16-right-now-151215739.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61f14f8b-e71c-4724-a1bf-0d7992632921</guid>
      <description>If you're an iPhone user who likes to keep tabs on where your stuff is, you can't go far wrong with an AirTag. The second-gen model that Apple just released outpaces the original in every way (aside from the galling lack of a keyring hole, that is). While it's easy enough to replace the battery in both versions of the AirTag, you might not want to have to worry about the device's battery life for a very long time. Enter Elevation Lab's extended battery case for the AirTag, which is currently on sale at Amazon for $16.
The case usually sells for $23, so that's a 30 percent discount. It's not th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pocket Taco is the best way to turn your phone into a Game Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/877491/gamesir-pocket-taco-wireless-bluetooth-controller-clamp-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=877491</guid>
      <description>My ongoing quest to turn my iPhone into one of my favorite consoles of all time has led me to a curiously named controller. GameSir's Pocket Taco is only barely pocketable, and distinctly lacking in taco fillings, but for $35, it's an excellent and easy way to turn your phone into a Game Boy-inspired handheld [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A powerful tool of resistance is already in your hands</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/879273/alex-pretti-ice-cbp-trump-free-speech</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879273</guid>
      <description>In an eyewitness video analyzed frame by frame by The New York Times, Alex Pretti raises one hand and holds a phone in the other. Federal agents tackle him, and one appears to find and remove a gun holstered on his hip. Then, an agent shoots - and a second follows. They appear to fire [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My uncanny AI valentines</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/879327/eva-ai-cafe-dating-ai-companions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879327</guid>
      <description>Hopping over a pile of dirty snow, I arrived on a frigid February evening at a wine bar in midtown, a purple neon sign reading "EVA AI cafe." Inside, several people were seated at tables and booths, staring at phones. Servers milled about, placing mini potato croquettes and nonalcoholic spritzers on each table. Like many [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aston Villa vs Newcastle Free Streams: How to Watch FA Cup 4th Round Tie 2025/26 Online From Anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/aston-villa-vs-newcastle-fa-cup-4th-round-tie-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Ys2AKuyQiM3JZSjqfCkqkc</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Aston Villa vs Newcastle in the FA Cup fourth round, with the Villans looking to extend their good recent run against the Magpies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident Evil Requiem's marketing has left me itching to play the game &#8212; while no demo is frustrating, here's why I think it may pay off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/resident-evil-requiems-marketing-has-left-me-itching-to-play-the-game-while-no-demo-is-frustrating-heres-why-i-think-it-may-pay-off</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LLM2wyNYQbhV9GcnthkFqT</guid>
      <description>Resident Evil Requiem can't come out soon enough, and no demo for the first time hurts, but the new trailer tells me the wait will be worth it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Sunday, February 15 (game #980)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-15-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AeZjGJEW3KsAohk8NFaZ2T</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Sunday, February 15 (game #714)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-15-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VMZ5pdBWT8vDxRUC6ZM5jQ</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Sunday, February 15 (game #1483)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-15-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DMHhEFSQpCewT6MCVKi5LN</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mais pourquoi autant de capteurs ? On a visit&#233; les impressionants labos o&#249; toutes les souris Logitech sont con&#231;ues</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/logitech/2975893_mais-pourquoi-autant-de-capteurs-on-a-visite-les-impressionants-labos-ou-toutes-les-souris-logitech-sont-concues</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/logitech/2975893_mais-pourquoi-autant-de-capteurs-on-a-visite-les-impressionants-labos-ou-toutes-les-souris-logitech-sont-concues</guid>
      <description>
&#192; l&#8217;occasion du lancement &#233;v&#233;nement de sa nouvelle souris haut de gamme pour le jeu, la G Pro X2 Superstrike, Logitech nous a invit&#233; dans son QG de Lausanne en Suisse. L'occasion d'une visite compl&#232;te des impressionnants laboratoires de la marque.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I gave the Amazfit T-Rex 3 Pro a four-star rating &#8211; and here's why I'd buy it for half the price of an Apple Watch Ultra 3</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/i-gave-the-amazfit-t-rex-3-pro-a-four-star-rating-and-heres-why-id-buy-it-for-half-the-price-of-an-apple-watch-ultra-3</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zEWwcq6FhpsyfTnxpwLizc</guid>
      <description>The Amazfit T-Rex 3 Pro is a much more affordable alternative to the Apple Watch Ultra 3 &#8211; here's why I think you should buy it if you want a rugged, budget-conscious wearable for your outdoor adventures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents' Day sales 2026: The best tech deals to shop this weekend from Apple, Sony, Anker and others</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/presidents-day-sales-2026-the-best-tech-deals-to-shop-this-weekend-from-apple-sony-anker-and-others-163000988.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba4f502-86ba-4c79-a2ff-b27b6e52c38b</guid>
      <description>Presidents&#8217; Day is a great time to buy appliances, mattresses and furniture as they are often on sale for the holiday. Tech also gets discounted around this time, but you have to do a bit more digging to find actually good deals. And this year, Presidents&#8217; Day comes right after Valentine&#8217;s Day and Super Bowl 2026, which means there are some overlapping sales to consider. If you don&#8217;t want to sort through the mess of bad deals out there, Engadget has you covered. We&#8217;re curating the best President Day sales on tech we can find right here. We&#8217;ll update this post through the holiday as more deals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Presidents' Day sales: Get the Apple Watch Series 11 for $299, plus more deals to shop this weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apple-presidents-day-sales-get-the-apple-watch-series-11-for-299-plus-more-deals-to-shop-this-weekend-151616206.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78902e66-331a-45a8-8c59-e293650f49bb</guid>
      <description>If you need a little help with your New Year's resolution to be more active, you can save on the latest Apple Watch right now. The Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for $299 for Presidents' Day, which is $100 off and the lowest price we've seen. A number of other Apple devices are on sale for the holiday as well.
We named the Apple Watch Series 11 as our choice for best smartwatch overall. It scored a 90 in our review thanks to its 24 hours-plus of battery life and a thin, light design that's easy to wear. It also offers new health metrics, including Apple's hypertension alerts system and Sleep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested LG G5 OLED TV&#8217;s free Dolby Vision upgrade &#8212; and the brightness boost is very real</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/i-tested-lg-g5-oled-tvs-free-dolby-vision-upgrade-and-the-brightness-boost-is-very-real</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gVMraW7WtnhjaEUKLNRgt4</guid>
      <description>LG's latest firmware update seemingly brightens most of its Dolby Vision picture modes on its OLED TVs, so I decided to test it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skip Samsung&#8217;s 2026 TVs &#8212; these 7 top-rated models are heavily discounted right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/skip-samsungs-2026-tvs-these-7-top-rated-models-are-heavily-discounted-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">enGWsAYX8rPfu2vDfyCTPh</guid>
      <description>Don't buy a new Samsung 2026 TV; shop incredible deals on older models right now, which include top-rated 4K, QLED, and OLED displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi 15T Pro ou OnePlus 15R&#160;: nos coups de c&#339;ur 8/10 sont en promo, mais lequel choisir ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2974235_xiaomi-15t-pro-ou-oneplus-15r-nos-coups-de-coeur-8-10-sont-en-promo-mais-lequel-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2974235_xiaomi-15t-pro-ou-oneplus-15r-nos-coups-de-coeur-8-10-sont-en-promo-mais-lequel-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Le Xiaomi 15T Pro et le OnePlus 15R sont deux smartphones not&#233;s 8/10 par Frandroid et sont actuellement en promotion. Ils offrent d&#8217;excellentes prestations &#224; prix r&#233;duit. Reste une question essentielle : lequel est fait pour vous ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Went on a Dinner Date With an AI Chatbot. Here&#8217;s How It Went.</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/i-went-on-a-date-with-an-ai-chatbot-heres-how-it-went-2000721484</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000721484</guid>
      <description>How's your Valentine's Day going?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returning stolen artifacts becomes a thrilling heist in Relooted</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/878121/relooted-review-xbox-steam</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=878121</guid>
      <description>Colonialism is not merely about occupying nations. It's a project of mass violence, part of which involves total erasure and the widespread theft of some of the most culturally significant artifacts in the world. Even today, colonizing nations proudly display stolen artifacts, acting as peacocking robbers under the guise of tourism. See, for example, the [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s USB-C cable that lets you charge two gadgets at once is 20 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/879003/anker-140w-2-in-1-usb-c-cable-presidents-day-sale-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-14T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=879003</guid>
      <description>Monday, February 16th, is Presidents Day, and there are plenty of good deals happening on tech in the run-up to the holiday. Even if you don&#8217;t snag any huge upgrades, though, you likely already own multiple gadgets that you need to recharge each and every day. It would sure be nice to be able to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTA 6 arrives in the era of podcasting, and I&#8217;m betting it&#8217;ll absolutely parody wellness bros, true crime, and Reddit relationship confessions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gta-6-arrives-in-the-era-of-podcasting-and-im-betting-itll-absolutely-parody-wellness-bros-true-crime-and-reddit-relationship-confessions</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">J2cJbG7UcPXenehrVPTtYn</guid>
      <description>GTA 6 will absolutely have podcasts, at least that's what I'm betting on. Here's the five shows I think the game will parody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias is eating your AI budget</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/bias-is-eating-your-ai-budget</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aFpeyGhirZFAwW2p9fjGtK</guid>
      <description>The commercial risks of poorly governed automation are now impossible for business leaders to ignore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security has reportedly sent out hundreds of subpoenas to identify ICE critics online</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/homeland-security-has-reportedly-sent-out-hundreds-of-subpoenas-to-identify-ice-critics-online-135245457.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 13:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7c0c8fe-861c-4cd8-bb9d-65429805e3fc</guid>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) has reportedly been asking tech companies for information on accounts posting anti-ICE sentiments. According to The New York Times, DHS has sent hundreds of administrative subpoenas to Google, Reddit, Discord and Meta over the past few months. Homeland Security asked the companies for names, email addresses, telephone numbers and any other identifying detail for accounts that have criticized the US Immigration and Customs Enforcement agency or have reported the location of its agents. Google, Meta and Reddit have  complied with some of the requestsAdmi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scotland vs England Free Streams: How to watch Six Nations 2026 game, TV Channels, Preview, Team News for Calcutta Cup</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/rugby/scotland-vs-england-six-nations-2026-calcutta-cup-free-streams</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZBe8rEiUxE2VST8JgYA9UX</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Scotland vs England live streams online &#8211; including for FREE &#8211; for the Calcutta Cup clash at Murrayfield in the 2026 Six Nations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
