<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:46:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes smartphones : les marchands liquident les stocks de smartphones dont ceux d&#8217;iPhone Air pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-marchands-liquident-leurs-stocks-de-smartphones-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-le-top-20-des-offres</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-marchands-liquident-leurs-stocks-de-smartphones-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-le-top-20-des-offres</guid>
      <description>
La derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d'hiver est lanc&#233;e ! Il ne reste donc plus qu'une semaine avant la fin des promotions programm&#233;e pour le 3 f&#233;vrier. Il reste donc encore un peu de temps pour se d&#233;cider sur le nouveau smartphone qu'on souhaiterait avoir en poche.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect minimalism: I found 32 crisp white home office finds for a calming 'clean desk' aesthetic</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/perfect-minimalism-i-found-32-crisp-white-home-office-finds-for-a-calming-clean-desk-aesthetic</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qpBqqysndNrvr6MgPBGffT</guid>
      <description>Create an ocean of calm in your home office with all-white home-working tech and decor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best smart rings for tracking sleep and health</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/647901/best-smart-rings</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T11:34:32-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=647901</guid>
      <description>So, you&#8217;re thinking of buying a smart ring. Well, some good news. Picking the best of the lot is incredibly easy right now. The &#8220;bad&#8221; news is that, as far as trustworthiness and reliability, your choices are somewhat limited, as this is still a niche and emerging gadget category. Smart rings are in the middle [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Tank X est un monstrueux smartphone avec une batterie XXL et&#8230; un projecteur</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-tank-x-est-un-monstrueux-smartphone-avec-une-batterie-xxl-et-un-projecteur.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323526</guid>
      <description>Au beau milieu de nulle part, on peut quand m&#234;me avoir envie de profiter d'un film comme au cin&#233;ma. Le nouveau smartphone durci du constructeur 8849, le Tank X, est non seulement adapt&#233; aux environnements les plus hostiles, mais il int&#232;gre aussi&#8230; un projecteur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra : admirez deux de ses coloris dans ces visuels tr&#232;s affin&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2961913_samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-admirez-deux-de-ses-coloris-dans-ces-visuels-tres-affines</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2961913_samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-admirez-deux-de-ses-coloris-dans-ces-visuels-tres-affines</guid>
      <description>
Une nouvelle fourn&#233;e de visuels montrent le Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra dans deux coloris tout confirmant quelques caract&#233;ristiques.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belkin&#8217;s Wemo smart devices will go offline on Saturday</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/870890/belkin-wemo-cloud-services-shut-down</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T11:29:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870890</guid>
      <description>As of Saturday, nearly all of Belkin's Wemo smart home devices will lose access to cloud services, including features like remote access and integrations with Google Home and Alexa. Belkin will also end app updates for the Wemo app beginning on January 31st. The shut down was first announced in July and impacts most Wemo [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first season of Amazon's Fallout show is now free on Youtube</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/the-first-season-of-amazons-fallout-show-is-now-free-on-youtube-162920615.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fd94004-2449-4945-8eb6-3bac797c75d9</guid>
      <description>Fallout&#8217;s second season is coming to a close, and it&#8217;s been well worth the wait. But if a reluctance to add yet another subscription to your streaming rotation means you haven&#8217;t watched Amazon&#8217;s surprisingly excellent adaptation yet, you might be interested to know that the company is currently releasing season one for free on the Prime Video YouTube channel.
Whether driven by Amazon wanting even more people to watch what has become one of its biggest TV success stories, or a move that speaks to how few people are actually signed up for Prime Video, it&#8217;s good news for anyone who hasn&#8217;t seen th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If GTA 6 gets delayed again, it may never live up to its hype &#8211; here's exactly why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/if-gta-6-gets-delayed-again-it-may-never-live-up-to-its-hype-heres-exactly-why</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DapddN2nxg9usZoAVaYyN8</guid>
      <description>Another delay for GTA 6 might leave fans losing interest in the game, and our recent poll indicates that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best robot vacuum and mop to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/625409/best-robot-vacuum-mops</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T11:20:11-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=625409</guid>
      <description>Robot vacuums that can both mop and sweep your floors have improved significantly in recent years. While they are still not as effective as good ol&#8217; manual labor, if you run them regularly, they will help keep your floors cleaner with much less effort on your part. The difference is that newer &#8220;combo&#8221; robot vacuum-and-mop [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a Sea of Melting Ice, These Polar Bears Are Doing Something Unexpected</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/in-a-sea-of-melting-ice-these-polar-bears-are-doing-something-unexpected-2000716012</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716012</guid>
      <description>Can&#8217;t remember the last time you heard good news about this threatened species? Well, here you go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone just got 10x optical zoom &#8211; this impressive teleconverter kit previously seen on Vivo phones just landed for Apple fans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/the-iphone-just-got-10x-optical-zoom-this-impressive-teleconverter-kit-previously-seen-on-vivo-phones-just-landed-for-apple-fans</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K4JGxMZKuLqb2c7DREtWUn</guid>
      <description>A new Kickstarter campaign gives you a much higher zoom option for your iPhone 17 Pro or iPhone 16 Pro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windscribe promises users in Iran and Russia "solutions" to ongoing VPN crackdown &#8212; here's everything we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/windscribe-promises-users-in-iran-and-russia-solutions-to-ongoing-vpn-crackdown-heres-everything-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Wq8gLY8TQiq2n6N9qgSVHm</guid>
      <description>As Iran and Russia double down their VPN crackdown, Windscribe confirms it's working on solutions, with wider support for the AmneziaWG protocol being the "highest priority."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redmi Note 15 Pro+ 5G : voici la marche &#224; suivre exacte pour en profiter &#224; prix plancher [Sponso]</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2958515_redmi-note-15-pro-5g-voici-la-marche-a-suivre-exacte-pour-en-profiter-a-prix-plancher</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2958515_redmi-note-15-pro-5g-voici-la-marche-a-suivre-exacte-pour-en-profiter-a-prix-plancher</guid>
      <description>
&#192; peine sorti, le Redmi Note 15 Pro+ 5G s'affiche d&#233;j&#224; avec une belle offre de lancement chez SFR, accompagn&#233; d'un forfait 5G tout illimit&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon discovered a 'high volume' of CSAM in its AI training data but isn't saying where it came from</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazon-discovered-a-high-volume-of-csam-in-its-ai-training-data-but-isnt-saying-where-it-came-from-224749228.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ddb2cb0-004b-40bb-b045-57c0b0313211</guid>
      <description>The National Center for Missing and Exploited Children said it received more than 1 million reports of AI-related child sexual abuse material (CSAM) in 2025. The "vast majority" of that content was reported by Amazon, which found the material in its training data, according to an investigation by Bloomberg. In addition, Amazon said only that it obtained the inappropriate content from external sources used to train its AI services and claimed it could not provide any further details about where the CSAM came from.&#160;Amazon provided Engadget with the following statement to explain why it doesn&#8217;t h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugging Face platform hijacked to send out Android malware - here's what we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hugging-face-platform-hijacked-to-send-out-android-malware-heres-what-we-know-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QZPFKidUfpEHbqnoaDZ7fi</guid>
      <description>Popular AI platform Hugging Face is being used for Android malware which can take over compromised devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owala Tattoos add a new layer of customization to our favorite emotional support FreeSip bottle</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/owala-tattoos-customization</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01ZAt6twkZ29tbj00exPAII</guid>
      <description>Owala Tattoos allow you to customize your water bottle with engraving, an artistic print, a full sleeve, or your own art. Customizations are $10 and are available for the viral Owala FreeSip bottle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 65-inch LG Mini LED 4K TV is the ultimate upgrade at over $400 off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-30-lg-65-inch-qned-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05DNH7AnfxaYEaSYx2MgXPT</guid>
      <description>The LG 65-inch QNED85A Mini LED 4K TV is on sale for just $796.99 at both Amazon and Best Buy. That's a savings of over $400.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monarch Money deal: New users get one year of access for only $50</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/monarch-money-deal-new-users-get-one-year-of-access-for-only-50-204507285.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764214b-3509-4628-8631-8692fa12e904</guid>
      <description>The start of the new year is a great time to get your finances in order, and a good budgeting app can help with that. Instead of laboring over a spreadsheet, you can try one of our favorite budgeting apps for less than usual. Monarch Money is running a sale that gives new users 50 percent off one year of the service, bringing the final cost down to just $50. Just use the code NEWYEAR2026 at checkout to get the discount.
Monarch Money makes for a capable and detailed budgeting companion. You can use the service via apps for iOS, Android, iPadOS or the web, and Monarch also offers a Chrome exten...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Films and Shows You Should Be Streaming in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/best-streaming-tv-movies-february-2026-release-dates-2000715245</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715245</guid>
      <description>We've picked out the best horror, sci-fi, and genre titles coming to Netflix, Hulu, Disney+, and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Minneapolis, Tech CEOs Are Struggling to Stay Silent</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/after-minneapolis-tech-ceos-are-struggling-to-stay-silent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977ce9692c9e19f26b6c459</guid>
      <description>Silicon Valley&#8217;s power brokers spent the past year currying favor with President Trump. Two deadly shootings in Minneapolis are now exposing the price of that bargain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un amas g&#233;ant, cach&#233; par la poussi&#232;re, vient d&#8217;&#234;tre d&#233;couvert aux confins du cosmos et d&#233;range les mod&#232;les actuels</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/univers-amas-geant-cache-poussiere-vient-etre-decouvert-confins-cosmos-derange-modeles-actuels-130716/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 16:59:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/univers-amas-geant-cache-poussiere-vient-etre-decouvert-confins-cosmos-derange-modeles-actuels-130716/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Des astronomes ont pouss&#233; le radiot&#233;lescope le plus sensible du monde jusqu&#8217;&#224; un record. Ils ont ainsi perc&#233; le voile d&#8217;une r&#233;gion du ciel pourtant d&#233;j&#224; bien balay&#233;e par le t&#233;lescope spatial Hubble. Ce qu&#8217;ils ont d&#233;couvert alors que notre Univers n&#8217;avait qu&#8217;un milliard d&#8217;ann&#233;es d&#233;fie toutes les...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Lemon has been arrested for covering an anti-ICE protest</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/870765/don-lemon-arrest-ice-protest</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T10:59:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870765</guid>
      <description>Don Lemon, a former CNN anchor turned independent journalist, was arrested on Thursday night by federal agents in Los Angeles, who alleged that he had violated federal law while covering an anti-ICE protest in Minnesota. Notably, Lemon was not the only journalist targeted by law enforcement for their presence at the Minnesota protest. On Thursday [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold weather in Florida is pushing back the Artemis II launch</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/870767/nasa-artemis-ii-mission-launch-delay-sls-space-launch-system-orion-moon</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T10:59:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870767</guid>
      <description>As a result of cold weather and windy conditions moving through Florida, NASA is now targeting Monday, February 2nd for a wet dress rehearsal of the Artemis II Space Launch System (SLS) rocket. Depending on how Monday's rehearsal goes, NASA will potentially set a launch date for Artemis II. But as a result of the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Windows 10's movable taskbar? You still can't relocate it in Windows 11, but a new PowerToys feature could be the next best thing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/miss-windows-10s-movable-taskbar-you-still-cant-relocate-it-in-windows-11-but-new-powertoys-feature-could-be-the-next-best-thing</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ncr9cQpBYcKu6PuA6nsDMM</guid>
      <description>PowerToys is a nifty suite of add-ons for Windows 11, and a potential new feature could be a welcome addition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CNN anchor Don Lemon arrested by federal agents after covering an anti-ICE protest in Minnesota</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484278/former-cnn-anchor-don-lemon-arrested-federal-agents-after-covering-anti-ice-protest-minnesota</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T15:53:43</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484278/former-cnn-anchor-don-lemon-arrested-federal-agents-after-covering-anti-ice-protest-minnesota</guid>
      <description>Lemon&#8217;s attorney, Abbe Lowell, said the journalist was arrested by federal agents in Los Angeles.
Journalist Don Lemon and three other people were arrested Friday in connection with an anti-immigration protest that disrupted a service at a Minnesota church and increased tensions between residents and the Trump administration, officials said.Lemon was arrested by federal agents in Los Angeles, where he had been covering the Grammy Awards, his attorney Abbe Lowell said. It is unclear what charge or charges Lemon and the others are facing in the Jan. 18 protest at the Cities Church in St. Paul. L...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De l&#8217;Apple Watch lifestyle &#224; la smartwatch Garmin sportive, voici les meilleures offres des soldes d&#8217;hiver sur les montres connect&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2937331_de-lapple-watch-lifestyle-a-la-smartwatch-garmin-sportive-voici-les-meilleures-offres-des-soldes-dhiver-sur-les-montres-connectees</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2937331_de-lapple-watch-lifestyle-a-la-smartwatch-garmin-sportive-voici-les-meilleures-offres-des-soldes-dhiver-sur-les-montres-connectees</guid>
      <description>
Pour celles et ceux qui ont pris la bonne r&#233;solution de se remettre au sport et qui comptent bien s'y tenir, les montres connect&#233;es font office de v&#233;ritables coachs virtuels. Pour la derni&#232;re ligne droite des soldes d'hiver, voici les ultimes offres sur ces accessoires aussi sportifs que lifestyle.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla throws in the towel on car sales</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/870332/tesla-throws-in-the-towel-on-car-sales</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T10:51:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870332</guid>
      <description>Is Tesla still a car company? It's a question we've been asking ourselves more frequently over the past year, especially as the company's car business shrinks and Elon Musk continues to push the message that Tesla should be seen more as an AI and robotics leader and less so as a mere seller of four-wheeled [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Les VPN, c&#8217;est le prochain sujet sur ma liste&#160;&#187; : le gouvernement compte d&#233;clarer la guerre aux VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/les-vpn-cest-le-prochain-sujet-sur-ma-liste-le-gouvernement-compte-declarer-la-guerre-aux-vpn.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323511</guid>
      <description>L'interdiction des r&#233;seaux sociaux aux moins de 15 ans vient d'&#234;tre vot&#233;e, mais la question du contournement technique se pose d&#233;j&#224;. Lucide, la ministre Anne Le H&#233;nanff pr&#233;vient : la r&#233;gulation des VPN est la prochaine bataille de l'ex&#233;cutif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tragic Death of Canadian Backpacker Prompts Dingo Cull. Here&#8217;s Why It&#8217;s the Wrong Move</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tragic-death-of-canadian-backpacker-prompts-dingo-cull-heres-why-its-the-wrong-move-2000715993</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715993</guid>
      <description>Will killing dingoes on Australia&#8217;s K&#8217;gari Island make visitors safer? These experts say it&#8217;s unlikely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Apple AirPods Pro 2 sont &#224; leur meilleur prix pour la fin des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2960935_les-apple-airpods-pro-2-sont-a-leur-meilleur-prix-pour-la-fin-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2960935_les-apple-airpods-pro-2-sont-a-leur-meilleur-prix-pour-la-fin-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Les AirPods Pro 2 incarnent l'ancienne vitrine du savoir-faire audio d'Apple, &#233;quip&#233;s de la puce H2 et d'une r&#233;duction toujours parmi les meilleures du march&#233;. Pour le dernier week-end des soldes, leur prix tombe &#224; 188 euros au lieu de 249&#160;euros, gr&#226;ce &#224; une remise cumul&#233;e &#224; un code promo chez Son-Vid&#233;o.com.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Considers Merging SpaceX With xAI, as He Races to Beat Sam Altman to IPO</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-considers-merging-spacex-with-xai-as-he-races-to-beat-sam-altman-to-ipo-2000715942</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715942</guid>
      <description>The race for the first major AI IPO is on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les meilleures consoles r&#233;trogaming et les jeux r&#233;tro incontournables en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/1560760_retrogaming-les-meilleures-consoles-retro-et-jeux-accessibles</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/1560760_retrogaming-les-meilleures-consoles-retro-et-jeux-accessibles</guid>
      <description>
Le r&#233;trogaming est un pan de l&#8217;univers des jeux vid&#233;o qui passionne beaucoup de joueurs. Nostalgie ou red&#233;couverte de grands classiques, on a tous une bonne raison de se faire plaisir ou d&#8217;offrir un voyage dans le temps avec une console r&#233;trogaming : suivez le guide.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring the theater home with $200 off the Sonos Arc Ultra Soundbar</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-30-sonos-arc-soundbar-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05da9KeSZC1qSVCtpwwWgRm</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 30, get $200 off the Sonos Arc Ultra Soundbar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony Knows You Want a True PlayStation Handheld, Even Though it May Take a While</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-knows-you-want-a-true-playstation-handheld-even-though-it-may-take-a-while-2000715977</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715977</guid>
      <description>Will a PlayStation Portal with an OLED screen tide you over?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lonely promise of cute robots</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/870438/optimizer-mirumi-loneliness-social-companion-robots</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T10:33:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870438</guid>
      <description>This is Optimizer, a weekly newsletter sent every Friday from Verge senior reviewer Victoria Song that dissects and discusses the latest gizmos and potions that swear they're going to change your life. Optimizer arrives in our subscribers' inboxes at 10AM ET. Opt in for Optimizer here. Unboxing Mirumi is like traveling back in time. It's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold is now available to buy at the official Samsung Store with a price tag that will make your bank account cry</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-is-now-available-to-buy-at-the-official-samsung-store-with-a-price-tag-that-will-make-your-bank-account-cry</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">khtARmpdFMAgVvdkB9cTMG</guid>
      <description>There's no escaping the financial blow if you want this stunning device</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ligue 1+ pourrait diffuser toute la Coupe du Monde de football 2026, voici ce que &#231;a implique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/services/2961685_ligue-1-pourrait-diffuser-toute-la-coupe-du-monde-de-football-2026-voici-ce-que-ca-implique</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/services/2961685_ligue-1-pourrait-diffuser-toute-la-coupe-du-monde-de-football-2026-voici-ce-que-ca-implique</guid>
      <description>
Un accord de diffusion de la prochaine Coupe du Monde de football est en bonne voie. C'est la cha&#238;ne Ligue 1+ qui raflerait le contrat.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia, Microsoft et Amazon voudraient investir 60 milliards de dollars dans OpenAI, pour quoi faire ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/openai/2961573_nvidia-microsoft-et-amazon-voudraient-investir-60-milliards-de-dollars-dans-openai-pour-quoi-faire</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/openai/2961573_nvidia-microsoft-et-amazon-voudraient-investir-60-milliards-de-dollars-dans-openai-pour-quoi-faire</guid>
      <description>
Selon des sources proches du dossier, des discussions sont en cours entre les 4 g&#233;ants de la Tech. &#192; quoi pourrait servir une telle somme ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data sovereignty creates an illusion of security: the real battle is software integrity</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/data-sovereignty-creates-an-illusion-of-security-the-real-battle-is-software-integrity</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8J7sddkwDqoTULxytsGKkb</guid>
      <description>The consequences of neglecting software integrity are severe and more visible than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Lego Valentines gift wont wilt (and its under $25)</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-30-lego-looney-tunes-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02ynqkyR4vjK60mOueyOgWu</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 30, you can get the Lego Sweetheart Tweety Bird set for $23.99, down from $34.99, at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows + barre des t&#226;ches fa&#231;on macOS&#160;: l&#8217;arme secr&#232;te de Microsoft pour enfin rendre son OS sexy</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/windows-barre-des-taches-facon-macos-larme-secrete-de-microsoft-pour-enfin-rendre-son-os-sexy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323502</guid>
      <description>Microsoft s&#8217;appr&#234;te &#224; piquer le secret de macOS : une barre de menu universel ultra-personnalisable arrive dans Windows 11 via PowerToys ! Baptis&#233; Command Palette Dock, ce concept modulable (fixable partout et bourr&#233; d&#8217;extensions) veut fluidifier votre quotidien et d&#233;fier Apple sur son terrain. Reste &#224; savoir si le nom &#171;&#8201;Dock&#8201;&#187; survivra aux d&#233;bats qu'il risque de g&#233;n&#233;rer....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is 'Shadow AI' a threat to your business? Report claims workers are increasingly more willing to cut corners and take risks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/is-shadow-ai-a-threat-to-your-business-report-claims-workers-are-increasingly-more-willing-to-cut-corners-and-take-risks</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZXx9EyiYWxtRyy8bqrzRGd</guid>
      <description>Workers and managers are all using unapproved AI tools at work, putting their sensitive company information at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M&#234;me Apple n&#8217;y croit plus : la fin silencieuse de la 5G millim&#233;trique en France</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/services/operateurs-mobiles/2961739_meme-apple-ny-croit-plus-la-fin-silencieuse-de-la-5g-millimetrique-en-france</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/services/operateurs-mobiles/2961739_meme-apple-ny-croit-plus-la-fin-silencieuse-de-la-5g-millimetrique-en-france</guid>
      <description>
On nous l'avait vendue comme le &#171; vrai &#187; futur de la connectivit&#233; mobile, capable de d&#233;bits hallucinants. Pourtant, la 5G millim&#233;trique semble avoir totalement disparu des radars dans l'Hexagone. Entre des contraintes techniques r&#233;dhibitoires et des op&#233;rateurs frileux, cette technologie fait un flop monumental, au point que m&#234;me Apple commence &#224; retirer les composants n&#233;cessaires de ses iPhone.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens Canada with a 50% tariff, escalating a trade war that could impact U.S. air travel</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484238/trump-threatens-canada-with-50-tariff-escalating-trade-war-that-could-impact-u-s-air-travel</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T15:14:10</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484238/trump-threatens-canada-with-50-tariff-escalating-trade-war-that-could-impact-u-s-air-travel</guid>
      <description>In a retaliatory move, Trump said any Canadian aircraft sold in the U.S. would be subject to a 50% tariff.
President Donald Trump on Thursday threatened Canada with a 50% tariff on any aircraft sold in the U.S., the latest salvo in his trade war with America&#8217;s northern neighbor as his feud with Prime Minister Mark Carney expands.Trump&#8217;s threat posted on social media came after he threatened over the weekend to impose a 100% tariff on goods imported from Canada if it went forward with a planned trade deal with China. But Trump&#8217;s threat did not come with any details about when he would impose th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How context-aware agents and open protocols drive real-world success in enterprise AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/how-context-aware-agents-and-open-protocols-drive-real-world-success-in-enterprise-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pN9u7Vh2m8p37uwHLcxGqg</guid>
      <description>As enterprises push AI into production, they're encountering a fundamental constraint: general-purpose models lack the real-time operational context that enterprise decisions require.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 TV deals: The best sales on OLEDs and other smart TVs ahead of kickoff</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/super-bowl-2026-tv-deals-the-best-sales-on-oleds-and-other-smart-tvs-ahead-of-kickoff-160000929.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19a8ed95-5057-4f9e-952b-502d925814e1</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re having people over to watch the Patriots and the Seahawks battle it out in Super Bowl 2026, or you&#8217;re more interested in the Bad Bunny halftime show, your TV will be an important part of the puzzle of putting together an excellent big-game party. If you&#8217;ve been thinking about upgrading your current TV, now&#8217;s a decent time to do it. The weeks leading up to the Super Bowl are typically awash with TV deals to consider.Generally, TV prices steadily decrease after a new model comes out. Some 2026 TV models were announced at CES and are forthcoming things year, making now a good time ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG reportedly stops making 8K OLED panels, as world is surprised to learn that was still an option</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lg-reportedly-stops-making-8k-oled-panels-as-world-is-surprised-to-learn-that-was-still-an-option</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jGKNGgLVFZsgCoHa8Eo6J7</guid>
      <description>LG is reportedly exiting the 8K TV business unless market conditions improve. Is 8K dead?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colin Farrell&#8217;s Detective Show &#8216;Sugar&#8217; Will Finally Have to Address that Wild Twist This Summer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/colin-farrells-detective-show-sugar-will-finally-have-to-address-that-wild-twist-this-summer-2000715869</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715869</guid>
      <description>Apple TV's neo-noir drama about a private eye with a big secret returns for season two June 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything to know about Sugar Season 2</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/sugar-season-2-colin-farrell</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02gSYXfZ7kroJ44rGij43p9</guid>
      <description>"Sugar" Season 2 is on the way. Colin Farrell return as John Sugar for another case to crack on Apple TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Grammy Awards: TV channel, start time, where to stream, nominations list and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-grammy-awards-tv-channel-start-time-where-to-stream-nominations-list-and-more-150015179.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7aa9a65c-d585-4e36-87b2-009a04f2bf1d</guid>
      <description>


  Grammy winner Bad Bunny, seen here accepting his award for Best M&#250;sica Urbana Album for &#8220;Un Verano Sin Ti&#8221; in 2023, is nominated again this year. (Timothy Norris/FilmMagic)
 

  Timothy Norris via Getty Images
 

The 2026 Grammy Awards honor music's biggest achievements of the year, and some of the biggest stars on the planet are nominated this year. Kendrick Lamar leads the way with nine nominations, including for Record and Song of the Year for "luther," his collaboration with SZA. Other top nominees this year include Lady Gaga, Jack Antonoff, and Cirkut with seven nominations apiece, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who&#8217;s afraid of the new TikTok?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/870543/tiktok-us-ownership-oracle-algorithm-trust</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870543</guid>
      <description>The significant problems with the TikTok app last weekend were, according to the company, because of a technical issue stemming from a power outage at a "US data center partner." Users could not upload new videos and view counts were all out of whack, with few answers or explanations. For TikTok, the timing was unfortunate. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s sci-fi detective show Sugar is coming back in June</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/870721/sugar-season-2-apple-tv-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870721</guid>
      <description>Apple TV continues to flesh out its streaming lineup for 2026, this time by announcing that Sugar will be back in the summer. The show's second season will premiere on June 19th and run for eight episodes. Sugar first premiered in 2024. And while it's a noir detective story at its core, thanks to a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last&#160;24 hours&#160;to grab your +1 pass at 50% off to TechCrunch Disrupt 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/30/last-24-hours-to-grab-your-1-pass-at-50-off-to-techcrunch-disrupt-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3088146</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day to lock in a +1 pass at 50% off to TechCrunch Disrupt 2026, happening on October 13-15 in San Francisco. Register here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 new movies and TV shows to watch on Netflix, Prime Video, HBO Max and more this weekend (January 30)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/7-new-movies-and-tv-shows-to-watch-on-netflix-prime-video-hbo-max-and-more-this-weekend-january-30</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VQSpc83jcAogG9R9zeTcPF</guid>
      <description>From Bridgerton's return and 2026's first MCU TV show, to Jason Momoa and Dave Bautista's new movie, there's lots to be excited about this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Saturday, January 31 (game #965)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-31-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wrAFASEp6sApFJSFCjWhtT</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Saturday, January 31 (game #699)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-31-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XZXu5GXk6rtRzfTvFMQHXR</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Saturday, January 31 (game #1468)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-31-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WUwxd7zD3fFqbUPvzTVoDN</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Trump administration is watering down the definition of &#8216;doxxing&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91484198/doxxing-definition-trump-noem-ice-renee-good-killer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-30T15:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91484198/doxxing-definition-trump-noem-ice-renee-good-killer</guid>
      <description>There&#8217;s a big difference between sharing sensitive personal info and naming a public servant. Conflating the two is an impediment to accountability.
Concept creep is literally problematic. It&#8217;s what happens when words like &#8220;problematic&#8221; and &#8220;literally&#8221; expand far beyond their original definitions, eventually becoming so diffuse as to no longer hold any real meaning....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February full moon 2026: See the Snow Moon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/february-full-moon-2026-snow-moon</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00rttAggOychN050UIpt8yy</guid>
      <description>Find out when to catch the peak of the February 2026 Full Moon and what it's called.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;Les VPN, c&#8217;est le prochain sujet sur ma liste&#160;&#187; : apr&#232;s les r&#233;seaux sociaux, le gouvernement a une nouvelle cible</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/politique/2961635_les-vpn-cest-le-prochain-sujet-sur-ma-liste-apres-les-reseaux-sociaux-le-gouvernement-a-une-nouvelle-cible</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/politique/2961635_les-vpn-cest-le-prochain-sujet-sur-ma-liste-apres-les-reseaux-sociaux-le-gouvernement-a-une-nouvelle-cible</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s l'interdiction des r&#233;seaux sociaux aux moins de 15 ans, le gouvernement veut se concentrer sur les VPN, pour &#233;viter tout contournement de la loi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panne mondiale chez Garmin : pourquoi des milliers d&#8217;utilisateurs ont perdu leurs donn&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/garmin/2960913_panne-majeure-chez-garmin-pourquoi-des-milliers-dutilisateurs-diphone-nont-plus-acces-a-leurs-donnees</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/garmin/2960913_panne-majeure-chez-garmin-pourquoi-des-milliers-dutilisateurs-diphone-nont-plus-acces-a-leurs-donnees</guid>
      <description>
Ce jeudi soir, une mise &#224; jour de l'application Garmin Connect sur iPhone a emp&#234;ch&#233; de nombreux utilisateurs de connecter leur montre &#224; leur t&#233;l&#233;phone. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pas vraiment une montre connect&#233;e, pas vraiment une bague&#8230; ce produit hybride vient casser les codes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2961027_cette-montre-connectee-se-porte-a-votre-doigt-comme-une-bague-connectee</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2961027_cette-montre-connectee-se-porte-a-votre-doigt-comme-une-bague-connectee</guid>
      <description>
La marque Rogbid a pr&#233;sent&#233; une bague connect&#233;e tr&#232;s originale, aux allures de montre connect&#233;e avec un &#233;cran et un bracelet ajustable. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les meilleures tablettes tactiles n&#8217;&#233;chappent pas aux soldes d&#8217;hiver. Voici les 11 meilleurs bons plans de la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941463_les-meilleures-tablettes-tactiles-nechappent-pas-aux-soldes-dhiver-voici-les-11-meilleurs-bons-plans-de-la-derniere-demarque</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941463_les-meilleures-tablettes-tactiles-nechappent-pas-aux-soldes-dhiver-voici-les-11-meilleurs-bons-plans-de-la-derniere-demarque</guid>
      <description>
Pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d'hiver, les tablettes tactiles se mettent le mieux possible en avant avec des r&#233;ductions sans commune mesure. Boud&#233;s il n'y a pas si longtemps encore, ces appareils ont maintenant les faveurs des consommateurs, notamment pendant les soldes d'hiver.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
