<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:26:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Sphere Could be Headed to Your City (With a Smaller Footprint)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-sphere-could-be-headed-to-your-city-with-a-smaller-footprint-2000712131</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712131</guid>
      <description>The company behind Vegas&#8217;s Sphere venue announced plans to bring a smaller version of its venue to the National Harbor in D.C, and more could be coming to additional cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rackspace email hosting price hike will be 'devastating', customers say</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/rackspace-email-hosting-price-hike-will-be-devastating-customers-say</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2VTpfjGRpuN6oqw6UCTkHK</guid>
      <description>Rackspace email hosting prices have risen sharply, and volume discounts don't seem to be available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Lore Olympus&#8217; Will Be Prime Video&#8217;s Next Animated Show</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lore-olympus-will-be-prime-videos-next-animated-show-2000712033</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712033</guid>
      <description>Webtoon's hit Greek myth romance is getting animated courtesy of Prime Video and the Jim Henson Company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Cowork is here. And so are the memes</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477813/claude-cowork-is-here-and-so-are-the-memes</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477813/claude-cowork-is-here-and-so-are-the-memes</guid>
      <description>Workers fearful of AI are darkly joking about it on social media.
Anthropic is undoubtedly having a moment right now. First came Claude Code, an AI-powered coding tool for developers, in early 2025, which quickly gained a cult following among that community. &#8220;You spent your holidays with your family? That&#8217;s nice I spent my holidays with Claude Code,&#8221; recently posted one tech-policy expert. But most people aren&#8217;t developers, let alone know their way around a command-line interface.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration admits DOGE may have misused Americans&#8217; Social Security data</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/trump-administration-admits-doge-may-have-misused-americans-social-security-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084155</guid>
      <description>The revelation comes as part of a series of corrections in a legal case over DOGE&#8217;s access to Social Security Administration data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nova Launcher&#8217;s new owner might offer a version with ads</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864585/nova-launcher-instabridge-acquisition-owner-ads</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T15:55:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864585</guid>
      <description>Last year, Nova Launcher founder and sole developer Kevin Barry announced he had left Branch Metrics, Nova's parent company at the time - which followed an announcement from 2024 that nearly everyone working on the project had been laid off. But the launcher is getting new life: in a blog post on Tuesday, the Swedish [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Posting Presidency Has Never Felt More Impotent</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-posting-presidency-has-never-felt-more-impotent-2000712023</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712023</guid>
      <description>From Minnesota to Greenland, Trump knows that he's losing the propaganda war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS signs mega deal with Rio Tinto for the first new copper mine in the US for years - here's what it could do with that windfall</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/aws-signs-mega-deal-with-rio-tinto-for-the-first-new-copper-mine-in-the-us-for-years-heres-what-it-could-do-with-that-windfall</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cNWMXbijuL9r3kVVhDDPy7</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#8217;s Arizona copper deal reveals domestic supply ambitions and how limited mining output remains against expanding AI data center demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UStrive security lapse exposed personal data of its users, including children</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/ustrive-security-lapse-exposed-personal-data-of-its-users-including-children/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084063</guid>
      <description>The online mentoring site UStrive exposed email addresses, phone numbers, and other non-public information to other logged-in users. The nonprofit told TechCrunch that the issue is now fixed, but wouldn't commit to alerting affected individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the AI &#8216;manipulation engine&#8217; here? How chatbots are gearing up to sell ads</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474921/ai-manipulation-engine-here-how-chatbots-are-gearing-up-to-sell-ads</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T20:43:08</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474921/ai-manipulation-engine-here-how-chatbots-are-gearing-up-to-sell-ads</guid>
      <description>We see a future where AI companies profit from manipulating their users&#8217; behavior for the benefit of their advertisers and investors. 
Eighteen months ago, it was plausible that artificial intelligence might take a different path than social media. Back then, AI&#8217;s development hadn&#8217;t consolidated under a small number of big tech firms. Nor had it capitalized on consumer attention, surveilling users, and delivering ads....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best All-Clad Deals From the Factory Seconds Sale (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/all-clad-factory-seconds-sale-january-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fbcd3df507ffd14d374a9</guid>
      <description>All-Clad cookware is fantastic and expensive. This sale makes it more accessible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT&#8217;s new &#8216;recursive&#8217; framework lets LLMs process 10 million tokens without context rot</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/mits-new-recursive-framework-lets-llms-process-10-million-tokens-without</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4TLW2PeVZ1HQ4aNqG1QExR</guid>
      <description>Recursive language models (RLMs) are an inference technique developed by researchers at MIT CSAIL that treat long prompts as an external environment to the model. Instead of forcing the entire prompt into the model's context window, the framework allows the LLM to programmatically examine, decompose, and recursively call itself over snippets of the text.Rather than expanding context windows or summarizing old information, the MIT team reframes long-context reasoning as a systems problem. By letting models treat prompts as something they can inspect with code, recursive language models allow LL...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Netflix brought interactive voting to &#8216;Star Search&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477533/how-netflix-brought-interactive-voting-to-star-search</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477533/how-netflix-brought-interactive-voting-to-star-search</guid>
      <description>Netflix&#8217;s &#8216;Star Search&#8217; reboot will let viewers vote with their remote controls. The company wants to repurpose the tech for other live events in the future.
On January 20, Netflix is bringing back the popular talent competition Star Search, with a twist: For the first time in its history, Netflix will let its audience decide the outcome of a show with live voting. However, unlike how shows have done this in the past, audiences won&#8217;t have to send text messages or call a special number to make their votes count. Instead, viewers will vote with their TV&#8217;s remote control, or right within the Netf...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethernovia raises $90M as investors rush to fund &#8216;physical AI&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/ethernovia-raises-90m-as-investors-rush-to-fund-physical-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084036</guid>
      <description>The automotive-focused company is looking to expand its Ethernet-based processors to fields like robotics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Swiss Suicide Pod Gets an AI-Powered Mental Fitness Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/controversial-swiss-suicide-pod-gets-an-ai-powered-mental-fitness-upgrade-2000712092</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712092</guid>
      <description>It's better than ChatGPT encouraging you to kill yourself, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build your deep reading and critical thinking skills to better resist misinformation</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476506/how-to-build-your-deep-reading-critical-thinking-skills-to-resist-misinformation</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T20:01:14</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476506/how-to-build-your-deep-reading-critical-thinking-skills-to-resist-misinformation</guid>
      <description>Practicing deep reading, such as reading novels, can open you up to new perspectives and ideas.
The average American checks their phone over 140 times a day, clocking an average of 4.5 hours of daily use, with 57% of people admitting they&#8217;re &#8220;addicted&#8221; to their phone. Tech companies, influencers, and other content creators compete for all that attention, which has incentivized the rise of misinformation....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Taken So Long to Find a New James Bond, Riz Ahmed Made a TV Show About It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/bait-riz-ahmed-james-bond-prime-video-2000712006</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712006</guid>
      <description>Prime Video's 'Bait' follows an actor who may just be the next man to play Bond, James Bond, for Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 Best Shows on Apple TV, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (January 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63cf1b483f042fa5827033d7</guid>
      <description>Hijack, Pluribus, and The Morning Show are among the best shows on Apple TV this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The northern lights could be visible in dozens of states tonight&#8212;here&#8217;s why this storm is different</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477722/the-northern-lights-could-be-visible-in-dozens-of-states-tonight-heres-why-this-storm-is-different</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T19:56:23</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477722/the-northern-lights-could-be-visible-in-dozens-of-states-tonight-heres-why-this-storm-is-different</guid>
      <description>A severe geomagnetic storm is pushing the aurora borealis far south, putting roughly two dozen states in the viewing zone.
The northern lights have been viewable from locations you don&#8217;t normally see them on a number of recent occasions, and on the evening of January 20, the same will be true.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Tying Your Shoelaces Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/are-you-tying-your-shoelaces-wrong-2000712041</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712041</guid>
      <description>And will it matter when everything comes crashing down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Veronika&#8217; Is the First Cow Known to Use a Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/veronika-is-the-first-cow-known-to-use-a-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fc71753fb9d147ff09b31</guid>
      <description>This is the first recorded instance of a bovine using tools from her environment to relieve an itch&#8212;leaving scientists astonished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google has finally killed the Stadia Bluetooth tool &#8212; but this person rescued it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/864543/google-has-finally-killed-the-stadia-bluetooth-tool-but-this-person-rescued-it</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T14:50:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864543</guid>
      <description>Did you save your Google Stadia controller like I told you last month? It's still not too late. This week, Google has finally removed the tool that converts the now-useless controller into a decent Bluetooth gamepad. But there's another way. Christopher Klay, who previously developed the Stadia Enhanced browser extension, is one of many who [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon CEO Andy Jassy says tariffs are starting to drive up product prices</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/amazon-ceo-andy-jassy-says-tariffs-are-starting-to-drive-up-product-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083995</guid>
      <description>Jassy said on Tuesday that while Amazon is trying to keep prices low, price hikes may be unavoidable in some cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon CEO Says Tariff Price Increases Likely to Hit Your Wallet This Year</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-ceo-says-tariff-price-increases-likely-to-hit-your-wallet-this-year-2000712020</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712020</guid>
      <description>Tariffs are starting to "creep in" to product prices as companies' efforts to absorb price increases run out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want some AI with your Pi? Raspberry Pi 5 gets an LLM upgrade with new AI HAT+ 2 - but will it be powerful enough?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/want-some-ai-with-your-pi-raspberry-pi-5-gets-an-llm-upgrade-with-new-ai-hat-2-but-will-it-be-powerful-enough</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pGnqRHuocgXSR6SbAAPcy4</guid>
      <description>Raspberry Pi AI HAT+ 2 enables local LLM and VLM workloads with 40 TOPS, 8 GB memory, and PCIe connectivity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
