<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:21:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>En promo &#224; moins de 400 &#8364;, mieux vaut glisser sous le sapin le Google Pixel 9a ou le Nothing Phone (3a) ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2916595_en-promo-a-moins-de-400-e-mieux-vaut-glisser-sous-le-sapin-le-google-pixel-9a-ou-le-nothing-phone-3a</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2916595_en-promo-a-moins-de-400-e-mieux-vaut-glisser-sous-le-sapin-le-google-pixel-9a-ou-le-nothing-phone-3a</guid>
      <description>
Nothing Phone (3a) d&#8217;un c&#244;t&#233;, et Google Pixel 9a de l&#8217;autre&#160;: deux milieu de gamme parfaits pour les personnes qui recherchent un smartphone &#233;quilibr&#233; avec un budget plut&#244;t serr&#233;. Mais lequel de ces deux mod&#232;les en promotion m&#233;rite votre argent ? D&#233;couvrez notre comparatif afin de d&#233;terminer lequel est fait pour vous.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Christmas gift ideas everyone on your 2025 holiday shopping list will love</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-best-christmas-gift-ideas-everyone-on-your-2025-holiday-shopping-list-will-love-170018978.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4160f992-6cb7-4c9c-b2bb-281bf7cf66e1</guid>
      <description>This time of year has a lot of merry and bright things to be excited about, but it can be stressful if you&#8217;re stumped on what to get your mom, dad, best friend, coworker or kids&#8217; teacher as a holiday gift. Whether you enjoy or dread buying gifts for people, it&#8217;s safe to say we all want to give our loved ones things they will enjoy and appreciate. But there&#8217;s a lot of noise, junk and bad deals disguised as good deals to sift through as we get closer and closer to the holidays.Allow us at Engadget to help you through it. Here, you&#8217;ll find all of our holiday gift guides collected in one place, so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogpile&amp;#8217;s puzzles mix Balatro, Tetris, and a pile of puppies</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/848041/dogpile-review-inde-game-steam-balatro-puppies</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-20T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848041</guid>
      <description>One day, video game critics and journalists will put together a comprehensive study on the impact Balatro had on the industry - of how so many games that came after tried to capture its essence by adding complex systems to otherwise simple, easily understood games. Until then, I'm gonna play Dogpile. Dogpile is a deckbuilding [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can buy your Xbox Ally an official pair of anti-drift joysticks</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/848568/xbox-ally-gulikit-tmr-joysticks</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-20T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848568</guid>
      <description>Even at $1,000, the Xbox Ally X handheld didn't ship with magnetic drift-resistant joysticks, and neither did the $600 model. But for an extra $20 at Amazon, you can change that today - with officially Asus-approved and sanctioned TMR joysticks from Gulikit, the company that's made a name for itself by supplying aftermarket drift-resistant sticks. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirTags are back on sale for $65 for a four-pack</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airtags-are-back-on-sale-for-65-for-a-four-pack-202333618.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Most Apple products are pretty expensive, but some of the most affordable (and useful) ones are AirTags. The Bluetooth trackers are priced pretty reasonably even when not on sale, but they can be a steal if you can get them on a discount &#8212; like right now. A four pack of AirTags is on sale for $65 at Amazon, which is only a few dollars more than the record-low price we saw during Black Friday this year.


If you place an order quickly, the AirTags should arrive in time for Christmas, making this a solid choice as a gift for someone with a tendency to misplace stuff. AirTags can also be useful f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattaques en France&#160;: les derni&#232;res fuites de donn&#233;es et entreprises touch&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/cyberattaques-france-dernieres-fuites-donnees-entreprises-touchees.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1235307</guid>
      <description>Les cyberattaques continuent de se multiplier en France. De nombreuses entreprises se sont retrouv&#233;es dans le viseur des cybercriminels. Ces attaques ont abouti au vol des donn&#233;es personnelles de la plupart des Fran&#231;ais. Ci-dessous, on fait le point sur les derni&#232;res victimes et l'&#233;volution de la situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 17 Best Gifts for Plant Lovers We&#8217;d Buy Ourselves (2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-gifts-for-plant-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68b728958cb239c3e51df20b</guid>
      <description>Plant parents don&#8217;t always want another plant&#8212;up your gift-giving game with these favorite plant presents we've tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Friend slop&#8217; made co-op gaming goofier than ever in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/845347/friend-slop-co-op-games-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-20T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845347</guid>
      <description>When a friend invited me to play a new game called REPO earlier this year, I thought I was wasting my money - not because the game looked bad, but because it looked like Lethal Company. The surprise-hit 2024 co-op survival horror game has players wander through unnerving ruined structures collecting trash while evading monsters. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The switch from Google Assistant to Gemini on Android devices has been pushed back to next year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/android/the-switch-from-google-assistant-to-gemini-on-android-devices-has-been-pushed-back-to-next-year</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ewyS2Nfdigj2g2jiEpARv6</guid>
      <description>Google has said it's revising the timeline for moving Android phones and tablets over to Gemini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirPods Pro 3 drop to a record low of $199</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airpods-pro-3-drop-to-a-record-low-of-199-222806196.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42f7f263-d7c8-4a21-ad07-9121207a6244</guid>
      <description>If you haven't yet upgraded to Apple's AirPods Pro 3, you can pick up the company's latest model at a discount through a deal on Amazon right now. The AirPods Pro 3, which came out in September, are currently down to $199. That's $50 off and the best price we've seen. With the new AirPods Pro, Apple made some big improvements, including better battery life and sound quality, and introduced useful new features, such as Live Translation.


The AirPods Pro 3 are the best AirPods available today, with Apple's H2 chip, and earned a score of 90 out of 100 in Engadget's review this fall. Active noise...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; le nouveau v&#233;lo cargo &#233;lectrique Tern GSD S10 (2025) : le graal &#224; prix sal&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tern/2896697_on-a-teste-le-nouveau-velo-cargo-electrique-tern-gsd-s10-2025-le-graal-a-prix-sale</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tern/2896697_on-a-teste-le-nouveau-velo-cargo-electrique-tern-gsd-s10-2025-le-graal-a-prix-sale</guid>
      <description>
Qui ne conna&#238;t pas Tern en 2025 ? C'est la marque qui a d&#233;mocratis&#233; les v&#233;los cargos &#233;lectriques petit format. Apr&#232;s le Quick Haul Long qui offrait enfin un mod&#232;le plus abordable, place cette fois au meilleur de la gamme chez Tern : le GSD. C'est le mod&#232;le iconique de la marque sur son segment cargo. Cette nouvelle version est-elle &#224; la hauteur de nos attentes ? La r&#233;ponse dans ce test complet.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Image Generators Default to the Same 12 Photo Styles, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ai-image-generators-default-to-the-same-12-photo-styles-study-finds-2000702012</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702012</guid>
      <description>Anything your imagination desires, as long as it's one of just a few options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Nintendo Switch 2 Controllers (2025), Tested and Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-nintendo-switch-2-controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6424b1a8182e869345a24e1f</guid>
      <description>Get a grip on gaming with the best controller options for Nintendo&#8217;s latest handheld console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 3 best De'Longhi coffee makers you can buy &#8211; recommended by a barista</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/the-3-best-delonghi-coffee-makers-you-can-buy-recommended-by-a-barista</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6LRG9cxoRtQZzSox9T6nTa</guid>
      <description>De'Longhi makes some of the best espresso machines I've ever used, and these are my top picks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Assistant will stick around a bit longer than expected for some Android users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-assistant-will-stick-around-a-bit-longer-than-expected-for-some-android-users-130000178.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cfc214f-51d2-4d9d-92d8-16789627b754</guid>
      <description>Google wanted to remove Assistant from most Android phones by the end of 2025 and replace it with Gemini. But now the company has announced that it needs a bit more time to make its AI assistant the new default digital helper for most of its users. Google said that it's adjusting its previously announced timeline to "make sure [it delivers] a seamless transition" and that updates to convert Assistant to Gemini on Android devices will continue into the next year. The company also said that it's sharing more details in the "coming months," so it's possible that the transition will go past early ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed the MSI Pro MP165 E6 - and this lightweight budget portable monitor is perfect for business travel</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/msi-pro-mp165-e6-portable-monitor-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QcpKGUrnDNYcXrbNcDThj9</guid>
      <description>The MSI Pro MP165 E6 is designed for a professional with a lot of different gear, who could benefit from a bit more screen real estate. This could be for a tablet, a gaming console, a computer, a camera, or more, all while staying within a budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Outlaws : l&#8217;un des plus beaux jeux de la Switch 2 a droit &#224; une belle baisse de 42 % pour No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2916973_star-wars-outlaws-lun-des-plus-beaux-jeux-de-la-switch-2-a-droit-a-une-belle-baisse-de-42-pour-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2916973_star-wars-outlaws-lun-des-plus-beaux-jeux-de-la-switch-2-a-droit-a-une-belle-baisse-de-42-pour-noel</guid>
      <description>
Embarquez aux c&#244;t&#233;s de Kay Vess, hors-la-loi de la Bordure ext&#233;rieure, dans une aventure en monde ouvert qui pousse la Switch 2 dans ses retranchements. Apr&#232;s Cyberpunk 2077, c&#8217;est l&#8217;un des plus beaux jeux &#224; tourner sur la nouvelle console de Nintendo. Et comme un bon tir de blaster bien plac&#233;, son prix s&#8217;effondre : 34,99 euros au lieu de 59,99 euros chez la Fnac.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meze's walnut-cupped wired headphones impress with a bassy sound, but their headband dings my noggin</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/headphones/meze-audio-99-classics-2nd-gen-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KW74qDYPRYW7zaQ6tEdMPY</guid>
      <description>The Meze Audio 99 Classics 2nd Gen wired headphones remain homely, walnut-earcupped beauties &#8211; but how have they improved from the original?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Assistant : voil&#224; un sursis inattendu qui prouve que Gemini n&#8217;est pas pr&#234;t</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/google-gemini/2917415_google-assistant-voila-un-sursis-inattendu-qui-prouve-que-gemini-nest-pas-pret</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/intelligence-artificielle/google-gemini/2917415_google-assistant-voila-un-sursis-inattendu-qui-prouve-que-gemini-nest-pas-pret</guid>
      <description>
Google Assistant n'est pas encore mort. Alors que tout indiquait une ex&#233;cution programm&#233;e pour la fin de l'ann&#233;e 2025 au profit de Gemini, Google vient discr&#232;tement de mettre &#224; jour son calendrier. Le grand remplacement par l'IA ? Ce ne sera pas pour tout de suite.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
