<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:23:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Top YouTube app for Android TV compromised to serve malware - here's what we know, and how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/top-youtube-app-for-android-tv-compromised-to-serve-malware-heres-what-we-know-and-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GcMRcB5t7nttj3er54nPij</guid>
      <description>SmartTube suffered a major breach that introduced hidden background code, triggering community alarm, Play Protect warnings, and urgent calls for caution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can AI Look at Your Retina and Diagnose Alzheimer&#8217;s? Eric Topol Hopes So</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/big-interview-event-eric-topol-super-agers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">691f89c8957dd41e3382c433</guid>
      <description>The author of Super Agers believes AI could bring big changes to the world of medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The godfather speaks - this is the device Linus Torvalds says would be his perfect Linux PC, but you'll never get one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-godfather-speaks-this-is-the-device-linus-torvalds-says-would-be-his-perfect-linux-pc-but-youll-never-get-one</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bybcxmzngguwcXaPTYtSfm</guid>
      <description>Linus Torvald&#8217;s new PC build highlights his preference for reliable hardware, strong kernel compatibility, and quiet high-performance components chosen for serious development work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'truth serum' for AI: OpenAI&#8217;s new method for training models to confess their mistakes</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-truth-serum-for-ai-openais-new-method-for-training-models-to-confess</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1o64BqEWYqve1IRcKDCM2C</guid>
      <description>OpenAI researchers have introduced a novel method that acts as a "truth serum" for large language models (LLMs), compelling them to self-report their own misbehavior, hallucinations and policy violations. This technique, "confessions," addresses a growing concern in enterprise AI: Models can be dishonest, overstating their confidence or covering up the shortcuts they take to arrive at an answer.&#160;For real-world applications, this technique evolves the creation of more transparent and steerable AI systems.What are confessions?Many forms of AI deception result from the complexities of the reinfor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: 20 years in, this OG YouTube channel is opening a new studio to support its growth</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91453507/smosh-studio-new-office-anthony-padilla-ian-hecox</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-04T23:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91453507/smosh-studio-new-office-anthony-padilla-ian-hecox</guid>
      <description>Smosh&#8217;s new office will support the growth the growth it&#8217;s seen since its original founders returned to the helm in 2023. 
Twenty years ago, not too long after Youtube itself launched, Ian Hecox and Anthony Padilla started uploading videos to the platform. What started as two teenagers trying to make each other laugh turned into the biggest channel on YouTube. It was the first ever to reach 10 million subscribers. Eventually Smosh was acquired by a company called Defy Media. The company would expand rapidly&#8211;more videos, more cast members, even a movie&#8211;but then came turmoil and uncertainty for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds ask Waymo about robotaxis repeatedly passing school buses in Austin</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/04/feds-ask-waymo-about-robotaxis-repeatedly-passing-school-buses-in-austin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073064</guid>
      <description>The agency already opened an investigation in October over Waymo's performance around school buses. Waymo said it issued a software update to its fleet to improve performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro1, a Scale AI competitor, touts crossing $100M ARR</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/04/micro1-a-scale-ai-competitor-touts-crossing-100m-arr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3070476</guid>
      <description>Micro1 started the year with roughly $7 million ARR. Now, it claims to have surpassed $100 million in ARR, double what it reported in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple announces even more major executive turnover</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/838712/apple-policy-lead-lisa-jackson-retiring</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-04T17:37:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=838712</guid>
      <description>Following the recent retirement of former COO Jeff Williams, AI chief John Giannandrea stepping down, and the departure of head of design Alan Dye for Meta, Apple announced Thursday that environmental and policy lead Lisa Jackson is retiring and that Jennifer Newstead will replace Kate Adams as the company&#8217;s general counsel after Adams retires &#8220;late [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This &#8216;Sinners&#8217; Star Knew You&#8217;d Have Feelings About That Grace Scene</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sinners-ryan-coogler-li-jun-li-grace-scene-2000695716</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695716</guid>
      <description>Li Jun Li and Ryan Coogler had a chat about how audiences might hate Grace for her climactic decision in 'Sinners.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly-discovered $1.5 billion lithium deposit could revolutionize the tech industry - but bad news, it's inside a supervolcano</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/newly-discovered-usd1-5-billion-lithium-deposit-could-revolutionize-the-tech-industry-but-bad-news-its-inside-a-supervolcano</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">g2XRAKhTCrRpcxCVbeVqfX</guid>
      <description>Researchers discovered massive lithium-rich clay in the McDermitt Caldera, offering a potential multi-trillion-dollar supply for batteries and industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s executive shake-up continues with departures of general counsel and policy head</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/04/apples-executive-shakeup-continues-with-departures-of-general-counsel-and-policy-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073076</guid>
      <description>Apple loses two more top senior executives with exits of longtime general counsel Kate Adams and environmental VP Lisa Jackson. Meta&#8217;s Jennifer Newstead is set to join as new general counsel in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo&#8217;s Switch 2 Mario Kart bundle is on sale at Amazon again for $50 off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/836519/nintendo-switch-2-mario-kart-world-bundle-walmart-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-04T17:24:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=836519</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest surprises of Cyber Monday was the terrific discount we saw on the Nintendo Switch 2 Mario Kart World bundle, which dropped in price by $50. We expected the price to return to normal once the shopping holiday ended, but to our surprise, it&#8217;s still going strong two days later. Several major [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ritz Cracker Sandwiches Recalled in 8 States for Undeclared Peanut Butter</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ritz-cracker-sandwiches-recalled-in-8-states-for-undeclared-peanut-butter-2000695892</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695892</guid>
      <description>Bad news for people with peanut allergies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Has Blocked 416 Billion AI Bot Requests Since July 1</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/big-interview-event-matthew-prince-cloudflare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">691f88cb87a0d21cddc2ccb6</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare CEO Matthew Prince claims the internet infrastructure company&#8217;s efforts to block AI crawlers are already seeing big results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Dawn of War 4 gets a new story trailer teasing the playable Dark Angels faction ahead of its 2026 launch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/warhammer-40-000-dawn-of-war-4-gets-a-new-story-trailer-teasing-the-playable-dark-angels-faction-ahead-of-its-2026-launch</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5AkkKMTsctwng35fWh4ym</guid>
      <description>Deep Silver and King Art Games have shared a new story trailer for Warhammer 40,000: Dawn of War 4, teasing an epic campaign and the playable Dark Angels faction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 70 US banks and credit unions affected by Marquis ransomware breach - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/over-70-us-banks-and-credit-unions-affected-by-marquis-ransomware-breach-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AjjhssvMAWQNsC5sxFo4kF</guid>
      <description>Marquis was struck with ransomware and allegedly even paid the demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking to supercharge your Raspberry Pi? This adapter provides two full-sized HDMI ports and a PCIe connector - and it only costs $10</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/looking-to-supercharge-your-raspberry-pi-this-adapter-provides-two-full-sized-hdmi-ports-and-a-pcie-connector-and-it-only-costs-usd10</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Q2Usr2JJpTab85n8qRfvub</guid>
      <description>The $10 Waveshare adapter expands Raspberry Pi 5 connectivity through dual HDMI support and a functional PCIe M.2 slot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Phineas and Ferb recap Percy Jackson and the Olympians Season 1</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/phineas-and-ferb-recap-percy-jackson-and-the-olympians</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">078BGO2sqpeUbp48O2FQjUO</guid>
      <description>"Percy Jackson and the Olympians" Season 1 gets a quick recap courtesy of Phineas and Ferb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon&#8217;s Signalgate report finds Pete Hegseth violated military policies</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/838582/signalgate-pentagon-oig-report-pete-hegseth</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-04T16:55:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=838582</guid>
      <description>It has been months since a group of Trump administration officials put together a Signal group chat to discuss classified military intelligence ahead of a military strike in Yemen while inadvertently adding a journalist, and now the Pentagon&#8217;s inspector general has released its report on the mess. The results of Steven Stebbins&#8217; eight-month-long investigation found [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s Daniela Amodei Believes the Market Will Reward Safe AI</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/big-interview-event-daniela-amodei-anthropic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">691f87f159665b9ae1012b7e</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration might think regulation is killing the AI industry, but Anthropic president Daniela Amodei disagrees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms trailer promises epic Westerosi jousting action</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-trailer-hbo</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04FbdfbKgU0gLfVYySBa11Y</guid>
      <description>"A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms," based on George R.R. Martin's "The Hedge Knight," premieres Jan. 18 on HBO and HBO Max.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shingles Vaccine Doesn&#8217;t Just Lower Dementia Risk, It Could Also Help Treat It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/shingles-vaccine-doesnt-just-lower-dementia-risk-it-could-also-help-treat-it-2000695823</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695823</guid>
      <description>New research finds the shingles vaccine can potentially provide broad protection against dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Andor&#8217; Can&#8217;t Be the End of Good &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/andor-cant-be-the-end-of-good-star-wars-2000694876</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694876</guid>
      <description>This year marked the end of a new era of 'Star Wars' and hopefully gave the franchise its blueprint for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looks Like We Can Finally Kiss the Metaverse Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/looks-like-we-can-finally-kiss-the-metaverse-goodbye-2000695825</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000695825</guid>
      <description>It appears Meta's Horizon Worlds may literally and figuratively not have legs after all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bending Spoons continues its spree of buying famous tech brands with the Eventbrite deal</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/bending-spoons-continues-its-spree-of-famous-tech-brands-with-the-eventbrite-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vPD7EcUdCSeLFCGEUXrc5f</guid>
      <description>Bending Spoons buys Eventbrite for $500 million, aiming to revive growth using operational changes, pricing strategies, and product enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This tiny white tower packs an RTX 5060 GPU and a Ryzen 9 8945HX CPU, but looks nothing like a mini PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-tiny-white-tower-packs-an-rtx-5060-gpu-and-a-ryzen-9-8945hx-cpu-but-looks-nothing-like-a-mini-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GF5x7ph3PQ7efzu3LEZWc5</guid>
      <description>Minisforum AtomMan G1 Pro mini PC pairs a mobile-class flagship CPU with a desktop GPU inside a narrow chassis, pushing cooling limits hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game in style with almost 50% off this 31.5-inch MSI Curved Gaming Monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/monitors/game-in-style-with-almost-50-percent-off-this-31-5-inch-msi-curved-gaming-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uKHM75iowa2y4WgPubUQUm</guid>
      <description>This MSI is a cheap full HD curved gaming monitor with a high refresh rate and low response time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
