<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:36:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>'This is a gimbal inside a smartphone' &#8212; Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra Super Steady Horizontal Lock really can handle a 360-degree turn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/this-is-a-gimbal-inside-a-smartphone-samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-super-steady-horizontal-lock-really-can-handle-a-360-degree-turn</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AXSec4rUCM2mJbXcs8UjZU</guid>
      <description>I put Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra's new Super Steady Horizontal Lock video mode to the test and color me impressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Says iPhone and iPad Are Approved to Handle Some Classified Data</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/apple-says-iphone-and-ipad-are-approved-to-handle-some-classified-data-2000727267</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727267</guid>
      <description>No assembly required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone sales could be in for their biggest drop ever</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/885638/smartphone-decline-ram-shortage-idc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T16:22:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885638</guid>
      <description>The smartphone industry could experience a record-breaking decline in 2026 as a result of the RAM shortage stemming from memory-hungry AI giants. That's according to the latest report from the International Data Corporation (IDC), which forecasts smartphone shipments to plummet 12.9 percent this year, marking its "lowest annual shipment volume in more than a decade." [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta sues advertisers in Brazil and China over 'celeb bait' scams</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-sues-advertisers-in-brazil-and-china-over-celeb-bait-scams-190000268.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88ee3eff-08ff-4e55-9039-e876ca0e4132</guid>
      <description>Meta has sued the people and groups behind three scam operations that used images and deepfakes of celebrities to lure users to scam websites. According to the company, the three entities were based in China and Brazil and targeted people in the US, Japan and other countries. The ads promoted fraudulent investment schemes and fake health products.Meta said that it had filed lawsuits against several people in Brazil who promoted fake or unapproved healthcare products and online courses promoting them. The company also sued a China-based entity it says used ads featuring celebrities "as part of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Wake Up to 800,000 Notifications From Observatory Watching the Night Skies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/astronomers-wake-up-to-800000-notifications-from-observatory-watching-the-night-skies-2000727018</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727018</guid>
      <description>The first batch of alerts from the Vera Rubin Observatory drew attention to new asteroids, supernovae, and active galactic nuclei.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google paid startup Form Energy $1B for its massive 100-hour battery</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/google-paid-startup-form-energy-1b-for-its-massive-100-hour-battery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097617</guid>
      <description>The deal paves the way for Form Energy to raise a new funding round before potentially going public next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Therapist Will Be Hearing About &#8216;Smiling Friends&#8217; Ending</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/my-therapist-will-be-hearing-about-smiling-friends-ending-2000727119</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727119</guid>
      <description>The creators of Adult Swim's smash-hit animated comedy series announced the series is ending after season three, with two 'straggler' episodes to follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung exec confirms you can blame RAM &#8212; and other materials &#8212; for the Galaxy S26&#8217;s higher pricetag</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885566/samsung-ram-galaxy-s26-price</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:57:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885566</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy S26 and S26 Plus are "more of the same for more money," my colleague Allison Johnson reported this week. Now, Samsung is confirming what we previously only suspected: RAMageddon is partly to blame. Samsung's Won-Joon Choi, the COO of its mobile business, tells The Verge that the memory shortage alone made a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This AI Agent Is Designed to Not Go Rogue</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ironcurtain-ai-agent-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699f224a94854663df474d0d</guid>
      <description>The new open source project IronCurtain uses a unique method to secure and constrain AI assistant agents before they flip your digital life upside down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandisk reveals its next-generation of portable SSDs for creatives on the move &#8212; but there's enough for office workers there too</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sandisk-reveals-its-next-generation-of-portable-ssds-for-creatives-on-the-move-but-theres-enough-for-office-workers-there-too</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7UHwjhNxdRSFwHVctmDzSc</guid>
      <description>Sandisk introduces three portable SSD models with varying speeds, durability, and security features to meet modern creative and everyday storage needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC declines to enforce a kids privacy law for data collected to verify users&#8217; ages</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/885592/ftc-age-verification-childrens-online-privacy-enforcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:42:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885592</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission is encouraging companies to adopt age verification technologies by announcing it will not enforce a children's online privacy law against certain websites that collect and use minors' personal data in order to verify their ages. "Age verification technologies are some of the most child-protective technologies to emerge in decades," Christopher Mufarrige, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis Lost $26.3 Billion Last Year, Says It&#8217;s Pivoting Back to Combustion Engines</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stellantis-lost-26-3-billion-last-year-says-its-pivoting-back-to-combustion-engines-2000727243</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727243</guid>
      <description>Jeep's parent company is struggling as the U.S. swerves away from EVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Death just upped the ante on its collab strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91426588/liquid-death-spotify-collab-strategy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T20:33:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91426588/liquid-death-spotify-collab-strategy</guid>
      <description>A new brand collab with Spotify led to a $495 limited edition Bluetooth speaker urn for your ashes. Because sure, why not?
If the 1990 classic movie Ghost is any indication, the dead love a good tune. We all remember when the recently deceased Sam (Patrick Swayze) had his infamous pottery session with his very alive partner Molly (Demi Moore).&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does the surgeon general nominee actively promote vaccines? Casey Means wouldn&#8217;t say</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499158/would-the-next-surgeon-general-actively-promote-vaccines-casey-means-wouldnt-say</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499158/would-the-next-surgeon-general-actively-promote-vaccines-casey-means-wouldnt-say</guid>
      <description>Means says chronic disease, not infectious illness, should drive federal health priorities, echoing a core &#8216;Make America Healthy Again&#8217; belief.
The &#8220;Make America Healthy Again&#8221; movement wants to name one of its own as America&#8217;s top doctor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualcomm won&amp;#8217;t be announcing Windows gaming handhelds at GDC after all</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/885314/qualcomm-wont-be-announcing-windows-gaming-handhelds-at-gdc-after-all</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T15:25:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885314</guid>
      <description>In January, Qualcomm hinted to The Verge that it might finally bring its powerful Arm-based Snapdragon processors to Windows gaming handhelds at the 2026 Game Developers Conference in San Francisco - just in time to challenge Nvidia's own first Arm gaming CPU and Intel's first dedicated handheld gaming chips. But plans have shifted, Qualcomm now [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opera has turned 30&#8212;and is celebrating with a compelling tribute to web nostalgia</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/opera-has-turned-30-and-is-celebrating-with-a-compelling-tribute-to-web-nostalgia-2000725245</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725245</guid>
      <description>It certainly wasn't like this in the old days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, we&#8217;re getting Prada Meta AI glasses, right?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/so-were-getting-prada-meta-ai-glasses-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097528</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg was at Prada's fashion week event in Milan, leaving everyone to wonder if we're getting Meta AI glasses under the Prada brand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO approves the iPhone and iPad for classified use</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/nato-approves-the-iphone-and-ipad-for-classified-use-200857276.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d60a12-647a-4d50-bc41-47df7dd9a4c8</guid>
      <description>Apple's mobile devices are secure enough for NATO. Following extensive testing by the German government, the iPhone and iPad are now considered secure enough for the NATO-restricted classified level.Germany's Federal Office for Information Security (Bundesamt f&#252;r Sicherheit in der Informationstechnik, or BSI) tested the devices. BSI first approved the iPhone and iPad for governmental use by German authorities in 2022. To take the additional step of NATO approval, Apple says BSI conducted exhaustive technical assessments, comprehensive testing and deep security analysis.Unless you work for NATO...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Chinese AI Chatbots Censor Themselves</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-how-chinese-ai-chatbots-censor-themselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a08892157af8f83feddbc8</guid>
      <description>Researchers from Stanford and Princeton found that Chinese AI models are more likely than their Western counterparts to dodge political questions or deliver inaccurate answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuite massive de donn&#233;es m&#233;dicales&#160;: jusqu&#8217;&#224; 15 millions de Fran&#231;ais touch&#233;s, dont des personnalit&#233;s publiques</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fuite-massive-de-donnees-medicales-jusqua-15-millions-de-francais-touches-dont-des-personnalites-publiques.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1328501</guid>
      <description>&#192; chaque jour suffit sa fuite des donn&#233;es. Aujourd'hui, c'est une base de donn&#233;es m&#233;dicales qui serait en acc&#232;s libre sur le dark web. Les informations de sant&#233; de millions de Fran&#231;ais sont en danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney World&#8217;s Villains Land Is Pivoting Away From Scaring Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-worlds-villains-land-is-pivoting-itself-away-from-scaring-kids-2000727140</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727140</guid>
      <description>Inspired by the rival Epic Universe, Disney's Villains Land is reportedly becoming a little less evil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s Eddy Cue calls F1 &#8216;unscripted drama at its best&#8217; &#8212; here&#8217;s our first look at the Apple TV race-day experience and a rare Netflix collaboration for Drive to Survive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/apples-eddy-cue-calls-f1-unscripted-drama-at-its-best-heres-our-first-look-at-the-apple-tv-race-day-experience-and-a-rare-netflix-collaboration-for-drive-to-survive</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cxnp44AAEHseoMjMWmF8Ah</guid>
      <description>With the Australian Grand Prix around the corner, Apple TV is readying its formal launch of broadcasting Formula 1 in the US, with multi-camera angles, and Eddy Cue teasing "this will be the highest quality."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditching Discord? Make sure you take this one important step before deleting your account</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/ditching-discord-make-sure-you-take-this-one-important-step-before-deleting-your-account</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EXvKbqcpET6KPTE2Y7ikSX</guid>
      <description>Discord isn't pulling out of its age verification plans, so here's how to delete your account and messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We want to create a new Android OS&#8217;: Samsung says it&#8217;s going to beat Apple with its bold new Google-powered 'AI OS'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/we-want-to-create-a-new-android-os-samsung-says-its-going-to-beat-apple-with-its-bold-new-google-powered-ai-os</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MV4XmTB8RJnjeXZxsBV966</guid>
      <description>Samsung has spoken about its vision for an AI OS that can help you out without even being asked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI-generated Resident Evil Requiem review briefly made it on Metacritic</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/an-ai-generated-resident-evil-requiem-review-briefly-made-it-on-metacritic-194414929.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a6afb98-195e-496a-9169-b0f47fa77c16</guid>
      <description>Review aggregator Metacritic has removed a review of Resident Evil Requiem because it was AI-generated, Kotaku reports. The review was published by UK gaming site VideoGamer, but appears to be "written" by a fake AI journalist rather than a real person.While it's unfortunately difficult to confirm with 100 percent accuracy whether a piece of text is AI-generated, you don't have to read VideoGamer's review for long to notice all the ways it feels off. The biggest giveaway, beyond heavy use of contrived metaphors, is a striking lack of detail beyond what you could glean from a trailer for the ga...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Space raises $10M seed to demo novel space computers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/sophia-space-raises-10m-seed-to-demo-novel-space-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096833</guid>
      <description>The company's modular computer tiles offer a new vision for space data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS detained a Columbia University student and content creator</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/885525/columbia-university-student-detained-dhs-influencer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:49:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885525</guid>
      <description>Department of Homeland Security agents "made misrepresentations" to gain access to a Columbia University residential building and detained a student early Thursday morning, according to a statement issued by the school. "Our understanding at this time is that the federal agents made misrepresentations to gain entry to the building to search for a 'missing person,'" [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Cybercab Program Manager Exits, Brags About Pushing the Boundaries of Safety</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-cybercab-program-manager-exits-brags-about-pushing-the-boundaries-of-safety-2000727134</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727134</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's xAI has also seen a number of departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory shortage could cause the biggest dip in smartphone shipments in over a decade</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/memory-shortage-could-cause-the-biggest-smartphone-shipments-dip-in-over-a-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097542</guid>
      <description>IDC says phone makers will ship only 1.12 billion smartphones as compared to 1.26 billion last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla sues Calif. DMV after agency called its autopilot deceptive marketing</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tesla-sues-california-dmv-autopilot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">046Y09xVIXfAOkNtWOldUvZ</guid>
      <description>Tesla is fighting back against a California decision that blocked using "autopilot" to advertise vehicles, even after the company complied with demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&amp;#8217;s F1 series Drive to Survive will stream on Apple TV, too</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/885538/netflix-f1-drive-to-survive-apple-tv-streaming</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:40:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885538</guid>
      <description>Netflix's sports docuseries obsession started a few years ago with F1: Drive to Survive, but when the eighth season premieres after midnight tonight, it will also be available on Apple TV. Now that Apple TV has a five-year deal to be the US streaming home for F1 races, subscribers in the US will be able [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
