<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:26:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I tested several cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T16:25:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Sure, it can take away from the slick design. But using a case relieves me of the worry that the console will accumulate tons of little scratches, or worse. I&#8217;ve tested several types of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes Defiance Act for a second time to address Grok deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/senate-passes-defiance-act-for-a-second-time-to-address-grok-deepfakes-212151712.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0a6c06b-3e97-4086-bf22-8cfdc6be3dba</guid>
      <description>The Senate has passed the Disrupt Explicit Forged Images and Non-Consensual Edits (DEFIANCE ) Act with unanimous consent, according to the bill&#8217;s co-sponsor Senator Dick Durbin (D-IL). The bill lets the subjects of nonconsensual, sexually explicit deepfakes take civil action against the people who create and host them.Deepfakes are a known issue online,  but without the proper protections, easy access to AI-powered image and video generation tools has made it possible for anyone to create compromising content using another person's likeness. This has become a particular problem on X, where the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8217;28 Years Later: The Bone Temple&#8217; Is Smaller, Gorier, and More Fun Than Its Predecessor</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/28-years-later-the-bone-temple-is-smaller-gorier-and-more-fun-than-its-predecessor-2000709678</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709678</guid>
      <description>Ralph Fiennes and Jack O'Connell star in the zombie sequel directed by Nia DaCosta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marc Andreessen to Tech Founders: &#8216;Raise Prices, Raise Prices, Raise Prices&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marc-andreessen-to-tech-founders-raise-prices-raise-prices-raise-prices-2000709835</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709835</guid>
      <description>Just what the consumer wants to hear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bone Temple turns 28 Years Later into a terrifying crisis of faith</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/859756/28-years-later-the-bone-temple-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859756</guid>
      <description>Because there was such a long gap between the releases of 28 Weeks Later and 28 Years Later, it was surprising to hear that writer-director duo Alex Garland and Danny Boyle already had plans for their latest collaboration to be the first chapter of a new horror trilogy. Sony seemed keen on fast-tracking the pair's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I heard, and felt, Victrola's new 'soundbase for turntables' speaker &#8212; and this risky idea just might work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/speakers/i-heard-and-felt-victrolas-new-soundbase-for-turntables-speaker-and-this-risky-idea-just-might-work</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HyhPiEJkZUgLdQQfLzucQE</guid>
      <description>A beefy speaker you rest your turntable on top of, but vibrations aren't really a concern, based on my time with it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes a bill that would let nonconsensual deepfake victims sue</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/861531/defiance-act-senate-passage-deepfakes-grok</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:53:10-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861531</guid>
      <description>The Senate passed a bill that could give people who've found their likeness deepfaked into sexually-explicit images without their consent a new way to fight back. The Disrupt Explicit Forged Images and Non-Consensual Edits Act (DEFIANCE Act), would let victims sue the individuals who created the images for civil damages. The bill passed with unanimous [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best phone to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:51:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</guid>
      <description>Haven&#8217;t you heard? Phones are boring now. And that&#8217;s just fine! Most people buying a new phone just want something familiar that works better than the device they&#8217;re replacing. If that&#8217;s your MO, then you&#8217;re sure to find something reliable in my recommendations below. But even if you&#8217;re looking for something a little more extra, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing the GMKtec NucBox M5 Ultra made me realize just how flexible an entry-level mini PC can be</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gmktec-nucbox-m5-ultra-mini-pc-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ApoJjhCPLumCY6LYgjdnMM</guid>
      <description>The GMKTec M5 Ultra delivers plenty of functionality at an affordable price for those willing to source their own memory, storage and OS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give the Internet an Infinite Word Search and the Internet Will Draw a Dick on It</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/give-the-internet-an-infinite-word-search-and-the-internet-will-draw-a-dick-on-it-2000709697</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709697</guid>
      <description>Because of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Book a Hotel on the Moon? This Startup Is Now Taking $250K Deposits</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/want-to-book-a-hotel-on-the-moon-this-startup-is-now-taking-250k-deposits-2000709632</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709632</guid>
      <description>An upcoming space tech startup is looking to build the first hotel on the lunar surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic shakes up C-suite to expand its internal incubator</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/861475/anthropic-ai-c-suite-internal-incubator-labs-team-mike-krieger</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861475</guid>
      <description>Mike Krieger, the Instagram co-founder who joined Anthropic two years ago as its chief product officer, is moving to a new focus at the AI startup: co-leading its internal incubator, dubbed the "Labs" team. The Anthropic Labs team started in mid-2024 with just two members; now, the company has decided to expand it, with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta has closed three VR studios as part of its metaverse cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ar-vr/meta-has-closed-three-vr-studios-as-part-of-its-metaverse-cuts-202720670.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7129ad-5b4d-4ae8-b8a4-80cc0b970d30</guid>
      <description>Several of Meta's VR studios have been affected by the company's metaverse-focused layoffs. The company has shuttered three of its VR studios, including Armature, Sanzaru and Twisted Pixel. VR fitness app Supernatural will no longer be updated with fresh content.Employees at Twisted Pixel, which released Marvel's Deadpool VR in November, and Sanzaru, known for Asgard's Wrath, posted on social media about the closures. Bloomberg reported that Armature, which brought Resident Evil 4 to Quest back in 2021 has also closed and that the popular VR fitness app Supernatural will no longer be updated w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best noise-canceling headphones to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:25:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones</guid>
      <description>Whether you&#8217;re wearing them for the morning commute, while traveling, or if you&#8217;re simply trying to find some peace and quiet while working at home, noise-canceling headphones are a more essential piece of kit nowadays than ever before. And you&#8217;ve got a slew of great options to pick from; it&#8217;s hard to make a bad [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigabyte debuts a consumer motherboard which supports 256GB DDR5 in dual channel &#8212; but you may need to sell a kidney to buy the memory</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/gigabyte-debuts-a-consumer-motherboard-that-supports-256gb-ddr5-in-dual-channel-but-you-may-need-to-sell-a-kidney-to-buy-the-memory</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sqvkA5XM3R92QYrmHprS2A</guid>
      <description>Gigabyte&#8217;s Z890 AORUS Tachyon ICE CQDIMM motherboard supports 256GB DDR5-7200 using two 128GB modules, achieving extreme capacity and frequency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's 13-inch MacBook Air M4 was crowned our best AI laptop of the year &#8212; and it's $200 off at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/apples-13-inch-macbook-air-m4-was-crowned-our-best-ai-laptop-of-the-year-and-its-usd200-off-at-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pDs8mVN8wxVg5KiKrztFGU</guid>
      <description>Apple's MacBook Air M4 was named TechRadar's best AI laptop of the year, and Amazon is offering a $200 discount, bringing the price down to $799.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft announces glut of new data centers but says it won&#8217;t let your electricity bill go up</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/13/microsoft-announces-glut-of-new-data-centers-but-says-it-wont-let-your-electricity-bill-go-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082319</guid>
      <description>The tech giant has pledged to be a "good neighbor" as it continues to invest in AI infrastructure throughout the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Center Project Cancellations Quadrupled in 2025 as Locals Fight Back</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/data-center-project-cancellations-quadrupled-in-2025-as-locals-fight-back-2000709669</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709669</guid>
      <description>A win for advocacy!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.&#8217;s new food pyramid could be a disaster for the environment &#8212; if Americans actually follow it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/861326/meat-food-pyramid-protein-nutrition-guideline-climate-beef-whole-milk-tallow</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T15:01:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=861326</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration announced last week that it wants Americans to consume more protein, churning out a colorful illustration of an inverted food pyramid that prominently features a big, red steak, a wedge of cheese, and a carton of whole milk at the top and claiming it's "ending the war on protein." It may seem [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, You Fools, There Is No &#8216;Lord of the Rings&#8217; Extended Extended Edition</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lord-of-the-rings-extended-editions-new-cuts-rumors-peter-jackson-2000709813</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709813</guid>
      <description>Peter Jackson has debunked the idea that there are extra-extra-long versions of his Oscar-winning Tolkien adaptations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Star Trek Real&#8217;: Hegseth Praises Grok for Allowing Users to Fight Wars</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-real-hegseth-praises-grok-for-allowing-users-to-fight-wars-2000709787</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709787</guid>
      <description>"We will win this race by becoming an AI-first war-fighting force across all domains," the Defense Secretary said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 new Prime Video movies to stream in January 2026 &#8212; including an iconic 80s comedy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/amazon-prime-video/3-new-prime-video-movies-to-stream-in-january-2026-including-an-iconic-80s-comedy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ntkbBa87HgxcKWr9qJavME</guid>
      <description>The Breakfast Club leads my recommendations of the best new movies to stream on Prime Video in January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These new GRWM TikTok videos take on a charged political issue&#8212;not fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473588/these-new-grwm-tiktok-videos-take-on-a-charged-political-issue-not-fashion</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473588/these-new-grwm-tiktok-videos-take-on-a-charged-political-issue-not-fashion</guid>
      <description>Social media videos mocking ICE agents and their uniforms are garnering huge numbers of fews following the shooting of Renee Good.
&#8220;Get ready with me as an absolute piece of shit ICE agent,&#8221; one such video begins, posted by comedian Adam Macias. These videos are comedic skits, rather than from the social media accounts of actual ICE agents, but have quickly racked up hundreds of thousands of views as the US Immigration and Customs Enforcement agency faces intense backlash after the shooting of Renee Good in Minneapolis....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars aurait abrit&#233; un oc&#233;an g&#233;ant : une nouvelle &#233;tude apporte des indices difficile &#224; contester</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/mars-mars-aurait-abrite-ocean-geant-nouvelle-etude-apporte-indices-difficile-contester-130114/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/mars-mars-aurait-abrite-ocean-geant-nouvelle-etude-apporte-indices-difficile-contester-130114/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Par le pass&#233;, la Plan&#232;te rouge &#233;tait bleue, mais &#224; quel point ? Les scientifiques s'interrogent toujours sur la quantit&#233; d'eau disponible &#224; la surface de Mars il y a quelques milliards d'ann&#233;es, et certains pensent avoir trouv&#233; un d&#233;but de r&#233;ponse dans les marques qui restent &#224; la surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Trump&#8217;s obsession with Greenland an &#8216;excuse&#8217;? What&#8217;s really behind the bizarre land grab</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91474194/trump-greenland-obsession-whats-really-behind-the-bizarre-land-grab</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-13T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91474194/trump-greenland-obsession-whats-really-behind-the-bizarre-land-grab</guid>
      <description>President Trump is doubling down on his longstanding threat to take over Denmark&#8217;s semi-autonomous territory &#8216;one way or the other.&#8217;
A political showdown over Greenland, and possibly a military one, is looking increasingly possible as President Donald Trump doubles down on his longstanding threat to take over Denmark&#8217;s semi-autonomous territory &#8220;one way or the other.&#8220;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel 10a : prix, date de sortie et premi&#232;re image officielle en fuite</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2941697_google-pixel-10a-prix-date-de-sortie-et-premiere-image-officielle-en-fuite</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2941697_google-pixel-10a-prix-date-de-sortie-et-premiere-image-officielle-en-fuite</guid>
      <description>
On sait d&#233;sormais presque tout du Pixel 10a. Une fuite massive vient de nous livrer le prix, la date de sortie et m&#234;me le premier rendu presse officiel. Si la baisse de tarif annonc&#233;e fait plaisir, le design, lui, risque de piquer un peu les yeux pour un smartphone de 2026.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A consumer watchdog issued a warning about Google&#8217;s AI agent shopping protocol &#8212; Google says she&#8217;s wrong</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/13/a-consumer-watchdog-issued-a-warning-about-googles-ai-agent-shopping-protocol-google-says-shes-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3082268</guid>
      <description>A consumer economics watchdog says Google's new Universal Commerce Protocol is ripe for misuse where consumers could pay more for items. Google denies this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed legislation opens the door to robotaxi services in New York</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/proposed-legislation-opens-the-door-to-robotaxi-services-in-new-york-193804671.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e055e1aa-7ca7-4431-925a-29b8b0037b75</guid>
      <description>Waymo, Alphabet's self-driving car company, tested its autonomous vehicles in New York City in 2025, and as part of proposed legislation from New York Governor Kathy Hochul, the company could soon offer its services across the state, Wired reports.Governor Hochul's proposed legislation was formally announced during a State of the State address covering policy proposals for the upcoming year. The new law, if passed, would loosen the state's restrictions on self-driving car companies by forming a pilot program that would allow for "the limited deployment of commercial for-hire autonomous passeng...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70 milliards de dollars plus tard, Meta acte le d&#233;c&#232;s du m&#233;tavers</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/meta/2941689_70-milliards-de-dollars-plus-tard-meta-acte-le-deces-du-metavers</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/meta/2941689_70-milliards-de-dollars-plus-tard-meta-acte-le-deces-du-metavers</guid>
      <description>
Meta vient d'annoncer la suppression de 10 % des effectifs de sa division r&#233;alit&#233; virtuelle. Le g&#233;ant am&#233;ricain abandonne ses ambitions de monde persistant pour se concentrer sur des produits qui se vendent enfin : les lunettes connect&#233;es.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, it's not your new thermostat &#8212; mini PC vendor delivers clean-looking, minimalist, affordable device unlike any other on the market with a Core i9 CPU inside</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/no-its-not-your-new-thermostat-mini-pc-vendor-delivers-clean-looking-minimalist-affordable-device-unlike-any-other-on-the-market-with-a-core-i9-cpu-inside</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DXL57ZLE9RiotKf5ANuo5c</guid>
      <description>Ayaneo AM03 mini PC combines minimalist design with Intel Core i9 performance, high-speed memory, and flexible connectivity options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft shutters fan favorite deployment platform, to the dismay of many</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-shutters-fan-favorite-deployment-platform-to-the-dismay-of-many</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3UZGgDzBBrBrAJVkNb7VY</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Deployment Toolkit (MDT) has been retired with immediate effect, but we knew this was coming a long time ago.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
