<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:27:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix earned $1.5 billion from ads in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864451/netflix-advertising-revenue-doubled-q4-2025-earnings</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T18:06:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864451</guid>
      <description>Netflix's advertising business more than doubled its advertising revenue to $1.5 billion from 2024 to 2025 - and it's on track to keep growing. "We expect that [advertising] business to roughly double again in '26 to about $3 billion," Netflix co-CEO Greg Peters said during an earnings call on Tuesday, hours ahead of its live [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#8217;t Believe This Is What Is Getting Right Wing Weirdos Mad About &#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-glasses-stephen-miller-william-shatner-2000712197</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712197</guid>
      <description>Of all the controversies the new 'Star Trek' show could reach, just one week in we've already hit one of the stupidest, thanks to Stephen Miller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Supreme Court wants your take on banning users</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/meta-permanent-ban</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05v7kRd40dnKnxpFR5XV3h9</guid>
      <description>Meta's Oversight Board tackles the question of how and when users should be permanently banned &#8212; and seeks public input.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin admits DOGE employees had access to off-limits Social Security data</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864643/doge-social-security-data-misuse</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T17:52:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864643</guid>
      <description>Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) staffers working at the Social Security Administration (SSA) broke protocols, had more access to sensitive data on Americans than previously disclosed, and were in touch with a political advocacy group hunting for election fraud, the Trump administration admitted in a recent court filing. Justice Department officials told a federal court [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Goons May Have Shared Stolen Social Security Data With Political Group: Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doge-goons-may-have-shared-stolen-social-security-data-with-political-group-report-2000712166</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712166</guid>
      <description>Two DOGE members have been referred to authorities for Hatch Act violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FTC isn't giving up on its antitrust case against Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-ftc-isnt-giving-up-on-its-antitrust-case-against-meta-225020769.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d64c66a-897c-4aa6-b297-3452f7cef571</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission lost its antitrust case against Meta last year, but the regulator hasn't given up on its attempts to punish the social media company for its acquisitions of WhatsApp and Instagram. The FTC is appealing a ruling last year in which a federal judge found that the government hadn't proven that Meta is currently operating as a monopoly.&#160;"Meta has maintained its dominant position and record profits for well over a decade not through legitimate competition, but by buying its most significant competitive threats," the FTC's Bureau of Competition Director Daniel Guarnera sa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix will revamp its mobile UI this year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864646/netflix-mobile-ui-revamp-design-vertical-video</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T17:46:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864646</guid>
      <description>Netflix is working on a new mobile UI set to roll out later this year that will "better serve the expansion of our business over the decade to come," co-CEO Greg Peters said in an earnings call on Tuesday. The new mobile UI follows last year's big TV revamp that put a new banner front [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Google Gemini security flaw let hackers use calendar invites to steal private data</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-google-gemini-security-flaw-let-hackers-use-calendar-invites-to-steal-private-data</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5QccWrUEa2oUywtfQWCV2b</guid>
      <description>Another prompt injection variant was discovered and remedied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Savings on This Unique Air Fryer That Cooks Food in Heat-Proof Glass</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ninja-crispi-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fb9e4d7d826b74e82ff01</guid>
      <description>Ninja turns the air fryer on its head with the semi-portable Crispi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 ways to finish what you started, according to a productivity expert</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478057/5-ways-to-finish-what-you-started-according-to-a-productivity-expert</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T22:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478057/5-ways-to-finish-what-you-started-according-to-a-productivity-expert</guid>
      <description>The science of intention is quite beautiful and powerful, but it shows as well that there are reasons that we procrastinate on the things that we intend to do.
Below, Chris Bailey shares five key insights from his new book,&#160;Intentional: How to Finish What You Start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is launching age prediction for ChatGPT accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-is-launching-age-prediction-for-chatgpt-accounts-222650340.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef7cd33c-f557-42a6-82bc-a3bc5841eeba</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is the latest company to hop on the bandwagon of gating access by users' age. The AI business is beginning a global rollout of an age prediction tool to determine whether or not a user is a minor. &#8220;The model looks at a combination of behavioral and account-level signals, including how long an account has existed, typical times of day when someone is active, usage patterns over time,and a user&#8217;s stated age,&#8221; the company&#8217;s announcement states. If an individual is incorrectly characterized by ChatGPT as underage, they will need to submit a selfie to correct the mistake through the Persona ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clap de fin pour OnePlus&#160;? Une enqu&#234;te choc r&#233;v&#232;le un d&#233;mant&#232;lement silencieux</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/clap-de-fin-pour-oneplus-une-enquete-choc-revele-un-demantelement-silencieux.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321393</guid>
      <description>Une enqu&#234;te explosive affirme que OnePlus est en train d'&#234;tre &#171; d&#233;branch&#233; &#187; par OPPO. Malgr&#233; le lancement d'un tr&#232;s bon OnePlus 15, la marque semble se retirer des march&#233;s occidentaux, y compris la France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC says it will appeal Meta antitrust loss</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864622/ftc-meta-antitrust-ruling-appeal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T17:21:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864622</guid>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission will appeal its loss in a landmark antitrust case against Meta, the agency announced Tuesday. US District Court Judge James Boasberg ruled in November that the government failed to prove that Meta had an illegal monopoly over a subset of social networking services meant for connecting with friends and family online. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir CEO Says AI Will Somehow Be So Great That People Will Stop Immigrating</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/palantir-ceo-says-ai-will-somehow-be-so-great-that-people-will-stop-immigrating-2000712148</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712148</guid>
      <description>Don't bother trying to figure out how that makes any sense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk says Tesla&#8217;s restarted Dojo3 will be for &#8216;space-based AI compute&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/elon-musk-says-teslas-restarted-dojo3-will-be-for-space-based-ai-compute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084200</guid>
      <description>Tesla aims to restart work on Dojo3, its previously abandoned third-generation AI chip. Only this time, Dojo3 won&#8217;t be aimed at training self-driving models on Earth. Instead, Musk says it will be dedicated to &#8220;space-based AI compute.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close-up pictures of AMD's only branded PC have emerged, and I cannot believe that it is so small - Ryzen AI Halo sits comfortably in the palm of one's hand and has all the connectors you can expect, but no Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/close-up-pictures-of-amds-only-branded-pc-have-emerged-and-i-cannot-believe-that-it-is-so-small-ryzen-ai-halo-sits-comfortably-in-the-palm-of-ones-hand-and-has-all-the-connectors-you-can-expect-but-no-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GcjUjxh4TtrDY22x4HEuLX</guid>
      <description>AMD Ryzen AI Halo mini PC is compact, developer-focused, supports 128GB memory, full connectivity, and allows OS choice for AI workloads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How anti-doomscrolling influencers are combatting social media addiction</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478030/how-anti-doomscrolling-influencers-are-combatting-social-media-addiction</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T22:09:47</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478030/how-anti-doomscrolling-influencers-are-combatting-social-media-addiction</guid>
      <description>Olivia Yokubonis is part of a growing group of content creators who make videos encouraging viewers to close out the app they&#8217;re on.
It&#8217;s simple to accidentally become entranced by an endless loop of videos on Instagram or TikTok. But sometimes, that mindless scroll is interrupted by a reminder that what you thought was a 10-minute break spent on your phone was closer to 30 minutes....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Closeup of the &#8216;Eye of God&#8217; Reveals Fiery Pillars in Stunning Detail</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/extreme-closeup-of-the-eye-of-god-reveals-fiery-pillars-in-stunning-detail-2000712155</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712155</guid>
      <description>The new image offers a rare look at the fate of our own star and planetary system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Reminder of When &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Takes Place</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-timeline-game-of-thrones-house-of-the-dragon-2000712068</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712068</guid>
      <description>The latest 'Game of Thrones' spinoff eschews the busier eras of Westeros for some peace and quiet&#8212;with some interesting ramifications for the world as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Hoosiers&#8217; college football championship by the numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478012/indianas-football-national-championship-by-the-numbers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478012/indianas-football-national-championship-by-the-numbers</guid>
      <description>Here are some key numbers behind Indiana&#8217;s victory&#8212;and one of the greatest seasons in college sports history.
The state of Indiana is no stranger to underdog stories. Hoosiers&#160;and Rudy, two of the most iconic underdog sports films ever made, both take place in the state, and both are based on true stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $28 app takes notes and summarizes them for you for life</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-20-my-notes-ai-pro-plan-lifetime-subscription</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HZ2hZUHso0qZRxoaDmk6N</guid>
      <description>Outsource your note-taking with a lifetime subscription to My Notes AI Pro Plan, on sale now for $27.97 (reg. $299) through Jan. 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X open sources its algorithm while facing a transparency fine and Grok controversies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/x-open-sources-its-algorithm-while-facing-a-transparency-fine-and-grok-controversies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083924</guid>
      <description>In a post to GitHub on Tuesday, the social media giant purported to share its secret sauce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Reveals Bizarre January Drought Hitting 130 Million Americans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/map-reveals-bizarre-january-drought-hitting-130-million-americans-2000712162</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712162</guid>
      <description>You won&#8217;t believe which state is completely unaffected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI launches age prediction for teen safety</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/open-ai-age-prediction-teens</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04nQthaHiPJAo6MH38cKWoO</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT's age prediction model tries to identify teen users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luminar founder Austin Russell agrees to accept subpoena in bankruptcy case</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/luminar-founder-austin-russell-agrees-to-accept-subpoena-in-bankruptcy-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084181</guid>
      <description>The agreement comes two weeks after Luminar accused its billionaire founder of dodging information requests, as it evaluates potential legal claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#160;beats revenue estimates as subscriber count climbs 325 million</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478117/netflix-beats-revenue-estimates-subscribers-reach-325-million</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T21:31:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478117/netflix-beats-revenue-estimates-subscribers-reach-325-million</guid>
      <description>Netflix revenue came in at $12.1 billion for October through December&#8212;topping forecasts of $11.97 billion for the quarter.
Netflix exceeded Wall Street&#8217;s revenue estimates for its holiday quarter, as it crossed 325 million subscribers, the company said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Serve Robotics is&#160;acquiring&#160;a hospital assistant robot company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/why-serve-robotics-is-acquiring-a-hospital-assistant-robot-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083932</guid>
      <description>Diligent Robotics is a startup that builds robots designed to assist in hospitals by delivering lab samples, supplies, and other tasks. The deal values Diligent's common stock at $29 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Ject's Scorpions themed turntable is ready to rock you like a hurricane</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/pro-jects-scorpions-themed-turntable-is-ready-to-rock-you-like-a-hurricane</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">D8FiAgTVTsK6ksx8ba9JHJ</guid>
      <description>Pro-Ject's new Scoprions turntable is out na-na-na-na-na-na-now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows detachable crawling robot hand thats giving Addams Family meets Terminator vibes</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/detachable-crawling-robot-hand</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01Qk15ZmYnMhQYbOX4BBqvq</guid>
      <description>Scientists unveiled a very unsettling robot hand that can detach from its arm and crawl around like a spider.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
