<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:35:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Corsair made a keyboard with a built-in Stream Deck</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/corsair-made-a-keyboard-with-a-built-in-stream-deck-163158296.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">254cd9d0-603e-47a4-b6c3-14f0cbd26156</guid>
      <description>Corsair just revealed a gaming keyboard with a built-in Stream Deck controller at CES 2026. The Galleon 100 SD is a mechanical keyboard with a 5-inch screen, two rotary encoders and a full complement of Stream Deck buttons.
For the uninitiated, the Stream Deck is basically a collection of hot keys that execute various commands. It's been incredibly popular for streamers and the like, but it's also become a boon for PC gamers.
Corsair is advertising the Galleon 100 SD directly to gamers, so it boasts of hot keys being used to "access abilities, call in airstrikes and manage inventory without di...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commonwealth Fusion Systems installs reactor magnet, lands deal with Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/commonwealth-fusion-systems-installs-reactor-magnet-lands-deal-with-nvidia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080246</guid>
      <description>The fusion power frontrunner said that construction on its Sparc reactor was proceeding as planned. Meanwhile, it's building a digital twin to help dial it in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon has a massive Fitbit sale &#8212; up to 40% off its best-selling smartwatches and activity trackers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/amazon-has-a-massive-fitbit-sale-up-to-40-percent-off-its-best-selling-smartwatches-and-activity-trackers</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">D4sGdQDMhAN2whNtqpzun</guid>
      <description>There's a massive Fitbit sale on Amazon, and I've rounded up the best deals, including up to 40% off the Charge 6, Sense 2, Versa 3, and Versa 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mauvaise nouvelle : cette d&#233;couverte remet en cause les possibilit&#233;s d'une vie extraterrestre &#224; cet endroit du Syst&#232;me solaire</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-mauvaise-nouvelle-cette-decouverte-remet-cause-possibilites-vie-extraterrestre-cet-endroit-systeme-solaire-129847/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:29:08 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-mauvaise-nouvelle-cette-decouverte-remet-cause-possibilites-vie-extraterrestre-cet-endroit-systeme-solaire-129847/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Parmi les corps du Syst&#232;me solaire o&#249; l'on peut esp&#233;rer trouver des formes de vie, Europe fait partie des candidats les plus prometteurs. Malheureusement, cette lune de Jupiter n'aurait aucune activit&#233; tectonique, ce qui pourrait emp&#234;cher le d&#233;veloppement d'une vie extraterrestre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious hacking collective returns - but researchers say they fell for a honeypot</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/notorious-hacking-collective-returns-but-researchers-say-they-fell-for-a-honeypot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hGgJ2pzH7wUcMkY6xjUQsX</guid>
      <description>Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters fell for a honeypot and exposed IP addresses and other valuable data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElevationLabs' TimeCapsule extended battery case for AirTags is 30 percent off.</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/elevationlabs-timecapsule-extended-battery-case-for-airtags-is-30-percent-off-162308689.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12d3fe53-c0b1-4919-880c-16749c440b85</guid>
      <description>ElevationLab makes a battery case for your AirTag that can power it for 10 years and the accessory is on sale now for 30 percent off. Normally retailing for $23, you can pick one up for $16.


The TimeCapsule case uses two AA batteries to offer up to 14 times the lifespan of the CR2032 battery that powers an AirTag. The company based those estimates on Energizer Ultimate Lithium batteries, so your mileage may vary. Once an AirTag is seated inside the case, which is a compact 4.45 x 1.57 inches, it is sealed shut with four screws at the corners. The case is fiber-reinforced, according to Elevat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami Triggered by Giant Russian Quake Broke the Rules, Satellite Data Shows</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tsunami-triggered-by-giant-russian-quake-broke-the-rules-satellite-data-shows-2000706172</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706172</guid>
      <description>The 2025 tsunami is shattering old models, thanks to observations from space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures montres connect&#233;es pas ch&#232;res en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1941478_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-montres-connectees-pas-cheres</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1941478_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-montres-connectees-pas-cheres</guid>
      <description>
Vous voulez une montre connect&#233;e, mais vous n'avez pas un budget extensif ? Frandroid vous propose 7 mod&#232;les de montres connect&#233;es pas ch&#232;res (sous les 200 euros) pour faire autant plaisir &#224; votre poignet qu'&#224; votre portefeuille.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassin's Creed Hexe director has seemingly been named as Batman: Arkham Origins' director Benoit Richer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/assassins-creed-hexe-director-has-seemingly-been-named-as-batman-arkham-origins-director-benoit-richer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bkZXF5bMzu5pqGAMhq8dMa</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft has reportedly appointed Batman: Arkham Origins' director Benoit Richer as the lead on Assassin's Creed Codename Hexe. The director seemed to confirm his position on his LinkedIn profile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG C6 et G6, des t&#233;l&#233;viseurs OLED toujours plus lumineux mais pas pour toutes les tailles</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2931689_lg-c6-et-g6-des-televiseurs-oled-toujours-plus-lumineux-mais-pas-pour-toutes-les-tailles</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2931689_lg-c6-et-g6-des-televiseurs-oled-toujours-plus-lumineux-mais-pas-pour-toutes-les-tailles</guid>
      <description>
LG rebat les cartes de sa gamme OLED en 2026 avec les s&#233;ries G6 et C6, toutes deux basculant sur des variantes de panneaux Tandem plus lumineux et mieux ma&#238;tris&#233;s en termes de reflets. Les TV LG G6 sont renforc&#233;s en tant que vitrine technologique mais la s&#233;rie C6 est fragment&#233;e. On vous explique tout.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the laptops that caught our eye at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/all-the-laptops-that-caught-our-eye-at-ces-2026-160610752.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9affd700-e6e7-44a9-a3d0-4169004caad8</guid>
      <description>CES remains a key stage for laptop makers to lay out their plans for the year ahead. At CES 2026, that meant new flagship productivity machines, reconsidered gaming notebooks and solid incremental updates across several major lineups. While we&#8217;re still seeing embargoes lift and hands-on time on the show floor, the announcements below reflect the most significant laptops we&#8217;ve seen so far. Plus, the list will grow as more companies reveal details throughout January 6 and beyond.Samsung Galaxy Book6 seriesNew Samsung Galaxy Book6 laptops offer NVIDIA RTX 50-series GPUs.Samsung announced the Gala...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG's UltraGear GX7 is its fastest and brightest OLED gaming monitor to date</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/lgs-ultragear-gx7-is-its-fastest-and-brightest-oled-gaming-monitor-to-date-160059443.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caec6c25-9644-40a5-b7f6-c74a55e73035</guid>
      <description>LG just announced its fastest and brightest OLED gaming monitor yet at CES, the 27-inch UltraGear GX7. The new QHD display, which uses LG Display's 4th-gen RGB Tandem 2.0 OLED tech, can hit 335 nits typical brightness and is DisplayHDR True Black 500 certified. At the same time, it offers an outstanding 540Hz refresh rate at QHD (720Hz at HD) and a .002ms grey-to-grey (GtG) response time. So in other words, about 5,000 times faster than the best human reflexes.&#160;&#160;
Though a gaming monitor by design, the GX7 would make an excellent content creation monitor too thanks to the true 10-bit panel that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s &#8216;Tomb Raider&#8217; Show Has Found Its Cast</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-tomb-raider-show-cast-sophie-turner-sigourney-weaver-jason-isaacs-2000706170</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706170</guid>
      <description>Sophie Turner's Lara Croft is joined by a few familiar faces from the games, and plenty of new ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klipsch is getting back into the hi-fi headphone game</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854158/klipsch-is-getting-back-into-the-hi-fi-headphone-game</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854158</guid>
      <description>Other than some earbuds, Klipsch hasn't made any headphones in a number of years. But the company is teasing a big return for 2026 at CES. Klipsch announced its Atlas series, a family of high-end hi-fi headphones that pick up where its Heritage headphone line left off. The HP-1 are a wireless over-ear model with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG&amp;#8217;s fastest and brightest OLED gaming monitor is $999.99</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856173/lg-27gx790b-oled-monitor-720hz-540hz-modes</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856173</guid>
      <description>LG is launching its dual mode GX7 OLED monitor in the US, with refresh rates up to 720Hz. Based on LG Display's fourth-generation WOLED panel, the 26.5-inch 27GX790B can run at 540Hz in 1440p resolution, or an impressive 720Hz in a not-so-impressive 720p resolution. The dual mode option lets you switch between the 540Hz and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valve fait exploser le jeu vid&#233;o sous Linux gr&#226;ce &#224; son Steam&#8239;Deck</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/valve/2931025_valve-fait-exploser-le-jeu-video-sous-linux-grace-a-son-steam-deck</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/valve/2931025_valve-fait-exploser-le-jeu-video-sous-linux-grace-a-son-steam-deck</guid>
      <description>
Le Steam&#8239;Deck, ce petit PC de poche sign&#233; Valve, continue de prouver qu&#8217;il n&#8217;est pas qu&#8217;une curiosit&#233; pour geeks. Non seulement il fait tourner vos jeux Steam n&#8217;importe o&#249;, mais il a aussi contribu&#233; &#224; un ph&#233;nom&#232;ne inattendu&#8239;: faire de Linux une v&#233;ritable plateforme de jeu.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les joueurs PC fuient les processeurs Intel, AMD se frotte les mains</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2931109_les-joueurs-pc-fuient-les-processeurs-intel-amd-se-frotte-les-mains</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2931109_les-joueurs-pc-fuient-les-processeurs-intel-amd-se-frotte-les-mains</guid>
      <description>
Selon le dernier sondage Steam sur les machines des utilisateurs, les parts d'Intel sont en baisse tandis que celles d'AMD ne cessent de grimper.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today's January sales can save you up to &#163;650 on a brand new laptop - but they're ending soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows-laptops/todays-january-sales-can-save-you-up-to-gbp650-on-a-brand-new-laptop-but-theyre-ending-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RdDEkn3Rb8FCedfrfEmoAE</guid>
      <description>Regardless of whether you're looking for a super-cheap laptop or a high-end MacBook, this week's January sales are well worth considering before they end for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown off a wide ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguar Land Rover sales fall after infamous cyber incident</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/jaguar-land-rover-sales-fall-after-infamous-cyber-incident</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kPpTzQYTcmgBkMZrRKvjdS</guid>
      <description>JLR sales are down globally, but US import tariffs and Jaguar's reinvention are also to blame together with the cyberattack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anker&#8217;s display-equipped Nano Charger is on sale following its CES debut</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/855701/anker-45w-nano-charger-nothing-ear-open-earbuds-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T10:42:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855701</guid>
      <description>Anker just announced three new chargers at CES 2026, and surprisingly, one of them is already on sale ahead of its launch on January 20th launch. Anker&#8217;s latest 45W Nano Charger, the company&#8217;s first Nano Charger to sport a built-in display, is available to preorder from Anker&#8217;s online storefront in one of several colors for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelle manette pour PS5 (DualSense) et PS4 acheter en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/1474330_notre-selection-des-meilleures-manettes-playstation-et-leurs-accessoires</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/1474330_notre-selection-des-meilleures-manettes-playstation-et-leurs-accessoires</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez besoin d&#8217;une nouvelle manette de PlayStation&#8201;? Contrairement aux Xbox, les consoles de Sony n&#8217;ont acc&#232;s qu&#8217;&#224; peu de manettes de constructeurs tiers. Voici les diff&#233;rentes manettes que vous pouvez utiliser sur PS5 et PS4.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Day 1 roundup of the coolest tech on display</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469669/ces-2026-day-1-roundup-coolest-tech-display</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:38:13</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469669/ces-2026-day-1-roundup-coolest-tech-display</guid>
      <description>Highlights included a newly announced partnership between Lego and the Star Wars franchise.
Nvidia, AMD and Intel all had important chip and AI platform announcements on the first day of CES 2026, but all audiences wanted to see more of was Star Wars and Jensen Huang&#8217;s little robot buddies.CES is a huge opportunity annually for companies both large and small to parade products they plan to put on shelves this year. As predicted, artificial intelligence was anchored in nearly everything as tech firms continue to look for AI products that will attract customers.Here are the highlights from Day 1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Tech World at CES 2026 live - we're in Las Vegas for the big event as it happens</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/live/lenovo-tech-world-at-ces-2026-live-were-in-las-vegas-for-the-big-event-as-it-happens</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NzCrseHgTG6ySHHSrk4imK</guid>
      <description>We're live in Las Vegas for Lenovo Tech World at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La nouvelle Samsung Galaxy Tab A11+ avec &#233;cran 90 Hz est d&#233;j&#224; presque &#224; moiti&#233; prix, mais seulement aujourd&#8217;hui</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2893235_la-nouvelle-samsung-galaxy-tab-a11-avec-ecran-90-hz-est-deja-presque-a-moitie-prix-mais-seulement-aujourdhui</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2893235_la-nouvelle-samsung-galaxy-tab-a11-avec-ecran-90-hz-est-deja-presque-a-moitie-prix-mais-seulement-aujourdhui</guid>
      <description>
La Samsung Galaxy Tab A11+ est une r&#233;cente tablette familiale abordable, mais mieux dot&#233;e que sa s&#339;ur, la Tab A11 classique. En cette nouvelle ann&#233;e 2026, vous la trouverez dans un pack &#224; 169,99 euros au lieu de 289,99 euros via ODR.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you're after a gaming headset upgrade this new year, then you won't go wrong with the brilliant SteelSeries Arctis Nova 5 at a massively discounted price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/if-youre-after-a-gaming-headset-upgrade-this-new-year-then-you-wont-go-wrong-with-the-brilliant-steelseries-arctis-nova-5-at-a-massively-discounted-price</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kcZ5VBY2cQ4JHuZiLNDqCa</guid>
      <description>The SteelSeries Arctis Nova 5 is one of my favorite wireless gaming headsets of recent years. You can save a whole lot of money on it right now, too, with it being discounted at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold hands-on: Flexing is believing at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-hands-on-flexing-is-believing-at-ces-2026-224343480.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">358a9f49-439d-4582-ad93-1f442ed611df</guid>
      <description>When I first heard whispers about the Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold, I immediately felt conflicted. On one hand it felt like the natural evolution of bi-fold phones like the Z Fold 7. But on the other, all this fancy tech comes with an even higher price &#8212; around $2,500 based on current conversion rates from Korean won &#8212; not to mention the added bulk you get from a third folding panel. So even as someone who has used a foldable as my daily driver for almost a decade straight, it felt like Samsung&#8217;s latest high-end phone was going backwards in terms of both portability and affordability. But then at ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These understated new desktop speakers have one little feature that'll make them rival your TV's soundbar</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/these-understated-new-desktop-speakers-have-one-little-feature-thatll-make-them-rival-your-tvs-soundbar</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tDr4TKJUAz4CRieDY9gJcj</guid>
      <description>The Edifier M90 adds HDMI eARC to the party, marking the brand's first active speakers with the connection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome : cette fonction ultra pratique sur PC arrive enfin sur Android (mais pas pour tout le monde)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2931263_google-chrome-cette-fonction-ultra-pratique-sur-pc-arrive-enfin-sur-android-mais-pas-pour-tout-le-monde</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2931263_google-chrome-cette-fonction-ultra-pratique-sur-pc-arrive-enfin-sur-android-mais-pas-pour-tout-le-monde</guid>
      <description>
Google pr&#233;pare une nouveaut&#233; pour la version Android du navigateur Chrome. Pratique, elle devrait malheureusement &#234;tre r&#233;serv&#233;e &#224; certains appareils.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jouez directement sur votre TV LG avec une manette certifi&#233;e, c&#8217;est la garantie d&#8217;une exp&#233;rience optimale</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2931587_jouez-directement-sur-votre-tv-lg-avec-une-manette-certifiee-cest-la-garantie-dune-experience-optimale</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2931587_jouez-directement-sur-votre-tv-lg-avec-une-manette-certifiee-cest-la-garantie-dune-experience-optimale</guid>
      <description>
LG inaugure un label de certification pour manettes compatibles avec son Gaming Portal et le d&#233;ploie pour la premi&#232;re fois avec la Razer Wolverine V3 Bluetooth, une manette sans fil optimis&#233;e pour le cloud gaming sur ses t&#233;l&#233;viseurs webOS.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest TV announcements at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/the-biggest-tv-announcements-at-ces-2026-190929976.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecf435a5-d2a0-4321-9064-dcce9611c48e</guid>
      <description>TVs are a staple of CES, and so far, manufacturers have not disappointed with their announcements at CES 2026. Companies including Samsung, LG and others came to the event ready to show off updates to existing display tech and some genuinely new technologies. OLED and Mini LED remain central to most lineups, while Micro RGB has emerged as one of the most talked-about developments at the show so far, especially at the higher end of the TV market.
Below are the TV announcements that stood out most from the pre-show events and early press conferences, with more expected as CES continues.
Samsung ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD CEO welcomes us to the "YottaScale era" - Lisa Su says AI will need YottaFLOPS of compute power soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amd-ceo-welcomes-us-to-the-yottascale-era-lisa-su-says-ai-will-need-yottaflops-of-compute-power-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BGecmWgyF885gTzMBPhGQM</guid>
      <description>AI is only going to get more power-hungry as it grows, AMD CEO warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 ms de latence en Bluetooth ? Razer d&#233;voile la manette ultime pour le cloud gaming sans console</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2931401_3-ms-de-latence-en-bluetooth-razer-devoile-la-manette-ultime-pour-le-cloud-gaming-sans-console</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2931401_3-ms-de-latence-en-bluetooth-razer-devoile-la-manette-ultime-pour-le-cloud-gaming-sans-console</guid>
      <description>
Razer a d&#233;voil&#233; une nouvelle version de sa Wolverine V3 lors du CES 2026 de Las Vegas. Pens&#233;e pour le cloud gaming sur les t&#233;l&#233;viseurs LG, elle se targue d'offrir la meilleure latence pour une manette Bluetooth.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le robot CLOiD de LG se charge (lentement) des corv&#233;es de la maison</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-robot-cloid-de-lg-se-charge-lentement-des-corvees-de-la-maison.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318436</guid>
      <description>Que va-t-on faire &#224; la maison une fois que les robots se seront occup&#233;s de toutes les t&#226;ches ingrates du quotidien ? Nul doute qu'on trouvera comment s'occuper ! Mais il faut d'abord que les robots domestiques fassent leur apparition et se montrent r&#233;ellement efficaces. Le CLOiD de LG n'en est pas encore l&#224; en termes d'efficacit&#233;, mais le constructeur cor&#233;en veut montrer au CES 2026 &#224; quoi pourrait ressembler, &#224; terme, un v&#233;ritable assistant domestique robotis&#233;....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes and distrust: how human provenance can rebuild digital confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/deepfakes-and-distrust-how-human-provenance-can-rebuild-digital-confidence</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Wfbd4RGM5p9CU6Mfxpjm5Q</guid>
      <description>As deepfakes surge, proving humanness may be the only reliable path to digital trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is adding a teleprompter and virtual writing to its Ray-Ban Display glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856422/meta-ray-ban-display-emg-handwriting-teleprompter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T10:11:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856422</guid>
      <description>Meta is giving Ray-Ban Display users an option to text on their glasses without needing their phone or a keyboard, only the Meta Neural Band. The new EMG handwriting feature, announced on Tuesday during CES, allows users to physically write with their hand on any surface, rather than texting. It's currently rolling out as an [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade your TV to the Sony 85-inch Bravia 7 while its at its best price ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-sony-bravia-7-qled-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06iHW1k4RoFsvSLWsPYEEvg</guid>
      <description>The 85-inch Sony Bravia 7 Mini LED TV is on sale for $2,098 at Amazon. That's 25% off its list price and its best price on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway d&#233;gaine un &#171; v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique &#187; high-tech avec radar int&#233;gr&#233;&#8230; mais il y a un mais</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2931369_segway-degaine-un-velo-electrique-high-tech-avec-radar-integre-mais-il-y-a-un-mais</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2931369_segway-degaine-un-velo-electrique-high-tech-avec-radar-integre-mais-il-y-a-un-mais</guid>
      <description>
Au travers d'un v&#233;lo tout-chemin nomm&#233; Segway Myon et bard&#233; d&#8217;&#233;quipements, ainsi que l&#8217;urbain 20 pouces Muxi, la marque Segway double son portefeuille de v&#233;los &#233;lectriques... mais exclut encore une fois l'Europe, pour le moment.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta pauses international expansion of its Ray-Ban Display glasses</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/meta-pauses-international-expansion-of-its-ray-ban-display-glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080212</guid>
      <description>Meta had originally planned to launch the glasses in France, Italy, Canada, and the U.K. in early 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fender just released its first headphones and Bluetooth speakers, but I feel like it forgot something Marshall and Orange knew</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/fender-just-released-its-first-headphones-and-bluetooth-speakers-but-i-feel-like-it-forgot-something-marshall-and-orange-knew</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WQWgZDeEdmW4eaVHvy5RCC</guid>
      <description>Fender-branded consumer products are finally here, as of CES 2026, but they miss a key ingredient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The robots, phones, and Lego of CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/856248/ces-2026-gadgets-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T10:03:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856248</guid>
      <description>This year's Consumer Electronics Show is only just getting into full swing, and we've already seen a deluge of gadget announcements. There are the staples, of course: gigantic TVs, smart home sensors, phone accessories, weirdly elaborate ways to charge your devices. Wouldn't be CES without them. But this year in Las Vegas, there are also [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Tesla devrait s&#8217;inqui&#233;ter &#187; : il a roul&#233; pendant 40 minutes dans une Mercedes CLA &#233;lectrique avec la technologie Nvidia, voici son avis</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mercedes-benz/2931105_tesla-devrait-sinquieter-il-a-roule-pendant-40-minutes-dans-une-mercedes-cla-electrique-avec-la-technologie-nvidia-voici-son-avis</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mercedes-benz/2931105_tesla-devrait-sinquieter-il-a-roule-pendant-40-minutes-dans-une-mercedes-cla-electrique-avec-la-technologie-nvidia-voici-son-avis</guid>
      <description>
Mercedes-Benz profite du CES de Las Vegas pour d&#233;voiler son syst&#232;me de conduite assist&#233;e de niveau 2++ et affiche des ambitions qui pourraient bousculer le march&#233;. Lors d'un essai &#224; San Francisco, la technologie d&#233;velopp&#233;e par Nvidia a d&#233;montr&#233; des capacit&#233;s qui rivalisent directement avec le fameux FSD de Tesla.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 big changes in retirement planning you should know about for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469665/3-big-changes-retirement-planning-you-should-know-about-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:01:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469665/3-big-changes-retirement-planning-you-should-know-about-2026</guid>
      <description>Retirement legislation and the One Big beautiful bill will have impacts.
For retirement savers and retirees, the new year brings more than the usual inflation adjustments to retirement contributions. The retirement legislation known as Secure 2.0 will also continue to phase in, and the One Big Beautiful Bill Act will have impacts too.Here&#8217;s a roundup of three key changes and some moves to consider....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Another Villain Be Coming to &#8216;Spider-Man: Brand New Day?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spider-man-brand-new-day-boomerang-costume-2000705898</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705898</guid>
      <description>Plus, do you dare read a page from the Necronomicon?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures voitures &#233;lectriques pas ch&#232;re disponibles ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/839376_quelles-voitures-electriques-neuves-pour-moins-de-20-000-euros</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/839376_quelles-voitures-electriques-neuves-pour-moins-de-20-000-euros</guid>
      <description>
Vous &#234;tes &#224; la recherche d'une voiture &#233;lectrique pas ch&#232;re ? Gr&#226;ce au bonus &#233;cologique, mais aussi &#224; nos tests sur Frandroid, vous pourrez trouver une voiture &#233;lectrique pas ch&#232;re &#224; moins de 25 000 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Industry&#8217; Takes on the Age Verification Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/hbo-industry-season-4-age-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69405e8c4db6532247cba064</guid>
      <description>In the HBO show&#8217;s fourth season, Industry proves to be more prescient than it&#8217;s ever been.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Wednesday, January 7 (game #675)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-7-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SSGEwbTcdQ5k4Rh8grjcG6</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Wednesday, January 7 (game #941)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-7-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WoUTr86TYCa5vPf2bNCRM3</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Wednesday, January 7 (game #1444)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-7-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Em4CK7tdFGsQ6cWGDvRYm8</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry Season 4 review: HBOs criminally underrated drama thrills in most ambitious season yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/industry-season-4-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06WE9iIgAIi5ci2cPmPOI5A</guid>
      <description>HBO's "Industry" blew itself up in Season 3. But losing Pierpoint means gaining more freedom and more ambition than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hisense RGB MiniLED evo, c&#8217;est quoi cette technologie qui veut vous en faire voir de toutes les couleurs&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hisense/2931471_hisense-rgb-miniled-evo-cest-quoi-cette-technologie-qui-veut-vous-en-faire-voir-de-toutes-les-couleurs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/hisense/2931471_hisense-rgb-miniled-evo-cest-quoi-cette-technologie-qui-veut-vous-en-faire-voir-de-toutes-les-couleurs</guid>
      <description>
Le fabricant chinois a d&#233;voil&#233; au CES 2026 une nouvelle technologie d&#8217;affichage pour ses t&#233;l&#233;viseurs&#160;: l'ajout d'une quatri&#232;me couleur primaire, bouleversant les standards de reproduction chromatique dans l'industrie. On vous explique tout.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent Fasting Isn&#8217;t Doing What You Think It&#8217;s Doing</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/intermittent-fasting-isnt-doing-what-you-think-its-doing-2000706063</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706063</guid>
      <description>Time-restricted eating without a change in how much you eat doesn't seem to do anything for your metabolic health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail sur le Web&#160;: Google supprime cette fonction historique, vos autres bo&#238;tes mail sont bloqu&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/gmail-sur-le-web-google-supprime-cette-fonction-historique-vos-autres-boites-mail-sont-bloquees.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318412</guid>
      <description>Coup de froid sur Gmail en ce mois de janvier 2026. Google met fin au support du POP3 et de Gmailify sur sa version Web. Si vous centralisiez vos comptes Yahoo ou Outlook, la synchronisation est coup&#233;e. Voici comment contourner le probl&#232;me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demain, ce sont les soldes d&#8217;hiver : tout savoir pour faire de bonnes affaires d&#232;s ce d&#233;but d&#8217;ann&#233;e 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/1368255_demain-ce-sont-les-soldes-dhiver-tout-savoir-pour-faire-de-bonnes-affaires-des-ce-debut-dannee-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/1368255_demain-ce-sont-les-soldes-dhiver-tout-savoir-pour-faire-de-bonnes-affaires-des-ce-debut-dannee-2026</guid>
      <description>
Les&#160;soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026&#160;approchent &#224; grands pas&#8239;! Du&#160;7 janvier au 3 f&#233;vrier prochain, les e-commer&#231;ants fran&#231;ais vont d&#233;gainer des&#160;promotions sur une foule de produits Tech. L&#8217;occasion r&#234;v&#233;e de bien commencer l&#8217;ann&#233;e en profitant de belles r&#233;ductions, surtout avec la hausse pr&#233;vue des prix en 2026... Voici tout ce qu&#8217;il faut savoir avant le coup d&#8217;envoi officiel.
...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
