<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:31:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg is all-in on AI as the new social media</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869882/mark-zuckerberg-meta-earnings-q4-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T18:26:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869882</guid>
      <description>Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg's metaverse dreams seem to have been replaced by a new vision: an AI-generated social feed. In an earnings call on Wednesday, Zuckerberg reiterated his belief that AI will become the next big media format, making feeds "more immersive and interactive:" We started with text, and then moved to photos when we [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 has reached 1 billion users faster than Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869889/microsoft-windows-11-1-billion-users</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T18:17:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869889</guid>
      <description>Windows 11 now has 1 billion users. Microsoft hit the milestone during the recent holiday quarter, meaning Windows 11 has managed to reach 1 billion users faster than Windows 10 did nearly six years ago. "Windows reached a big milestone, 1 billion Windows 11 users," said Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella on the company's fiscal Q2, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg teases agentic commerce tools and major AI rollout in 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/zuckerberg-teases-agentic-commerce-tools-and-major-ai-rollout-in-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087558</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg says 2026 will be "a big year for delivering personal super intelligence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the 2 Big Celeb Cameos in &#8216;Wonder Man&#8217; Came About</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-the-2-big-celeb-cameos-in-wonder-man-came-about-2000715062</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715062</guid>
      <description>'Matrix' star Joe Pantoliano and 'Frozen' actor Josh Gad both play themselves in the Marvel series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As an enjoyer of the 3DS original, here are 4 things I want to see from the upcoming Tomodachi Life: Living the Dream Nintendo Direct presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/as-an-enjoyer-of-the-3ds-original-here-are-4-things-i-want-to-see-from-the-upcoming-tomodachi-life-living-the-dream-nintendo-direct-presentation</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PZUjwyx3dMrG448Wp4bSiR</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re learning more about Tomodachi Life: Living the Dream soon. Here&#8217;s everything I hope the upcoming Nintendo Direct shows off for the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We 'want to encourage other people in our generation to be the types of people who do not even want to have an AI friend': Appstinence founder on the fight to help people step back from tech and reconnect with real life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/we-want-to-encourage-other-people-in-our-generation-to-be-the-types-of-people-who-do-not-even-want-to-have-an-ai-friend-appstinence-founder-on-the-fight-to-help-people-step-back-from-tech-and-reconnect-with-real-life</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UTe7gtJ9jBnx9QUQzdTMXA</guid>
      <description>Appstinence Founder Gabriela Nguyen on how the organization is helping people disconnect from addictive apps, platforms, and technologies, and why AI is the fight's next front.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump energy department loosens rules on nuclear safety</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/trump-energy-department-loosens-rules-on-nuclear-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087510</guid>
      <description>The new rules apply to nuclear reactors built on Department of Energy property, which includes several currently being developed by startups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'From biology to black holes, ChatGPT is accelerating research': OpenAI really wants you to use ChatGPT as a research collaborator - and claims 8.4 million messages are sent every week on science and math</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/from-biology-to-black-holes-chatgpt-is-accelerating-research-openai-really-wants-you-to-use-chatgpt-as-a-research-collaborator-and-claims-8-4-million-messages-are-sent-every-week-on-science-and-math</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tB9HGwWixSQDY63aMZgYHe</guid>
      <description>OpenAI claims ChatGPT handles millions of science and math queries weekly, supporting researchers in complex calculations and experiments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla discontinuing Model S and Model X to make room for robots</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/869872/tesla-model-s-model-x-discontinue-optimus-robot-factory</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T17:49:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869872</guid>
      <description>Tesla will discontinue the Model S and Model X in the second quarter of 2026, Elon Musk said in an earnings call with investors today. Musk said the reasons for cancelling the vehicle programs was to make room at Tesla's Fremont factory for production of its Optimus humanoid robot. "It's time to basically bring the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft gained $7.6B from OpenAI last quarter</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/microsoft-earnings-7-6-billion-openai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087517</guid>
      <description>Microsoft, one of OpenAI's major investors, is benefiting greatly from the AI lab's growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPhones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23618862/best-iphone-camera-battery-screen-guide</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T17:45:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23618862/best-iphone-camera-battery-screen-guide</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been holding off on getting a new iPhone, now&#8217;s the perfect time to size up your options. Apple&#8217;s 2025 iPhone lineup is now widely available, which includes the iPhone 17, 17 Pro, 17 Pro Max, and a brand-new model, the ultra-thin iPhone Air. These new phones offer a number of new features over [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla is killing off the Model S and Model X</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tesla-is-killing-off-the-model-s-and-model-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087635</guid>
      <description>The company will stop making the pioneering EVs in the second quarter of 2026, CEO Elon Musk announced Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg says a future without smart glasses is &#8216;hard to imagine&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/mark-zuckerberg-future-smart-glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087229</guid>
      <description>Take Zuckerberg's outlook with a grain of salt. After all, he thought we'd all be hanging out in the metaverse by now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg says Reality Labs will (eventually) stop losing so much money</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/mark-zuckerberg-says-reality-labs-will-eventually-stop-losing-so-much-money-222900157.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">476967e0-b23c-4a75-9f3a-20c86b890732</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg says there's an end in sight to Reality Labs' years of multibillion-dollar losses following the company's layoffs to the metaverse division earlier this year. The CEO said he expects to "gradually reduce" how much money the company is losing as it doubles down on AI glasses and shifts away from virtual reality.Speaking during Meta's fourth-quarter earnings call, Zuckerberg was clear that the changes won't happen soon, but sounded optimistic about the division that lost more than $19 billion in 2025 alone. "For Reality Labs, we are directing most of our investment towards glasse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patreon creators have to switch to subscription billing by November, thanks to Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/patreon-creators-have-to-switch-to-subscription-billing-by-november-thanks-to-apple-203759852.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05720d3d-ef66-4e85-b7fd-998ade177cb9</guid>
      <description>Patreon creators will need to make some changes soon, thanks to Apple. On Wednesday, Patreon said Apple has renewed its requirement that all Patreon creators must move to subscription billing. The deadline to do so is November 1, 2026.Patreon's blog post announcing the change made it clear that it had no other choice. "We strongly disagree with this decision," the company wrote. "Creators need consistency and clarity in order to build healthy, long-term businesses. Instead, creators using legacy billing will now have to endure the whiplash of another policy reversal &#8212; the third such change fro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Gunn Told You Once, He&#8217;s Told You Again: Robert Pattinson Is Not the DCU&#8217;s Batman</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/james-gunn-told-you-once-hes-told-you-again-robert-pattinson-is-not-the-dcus-batman-2000715159</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715159</guid>
      <description>Pattinson's Caped Crusader will stay in the Matt Reeves universe, and the DCU's version will be played by someone else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doom Has Come for Nvidia&#8217;s Graphics Cards, After All</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doom-has-come-for-nvidias-graphics-cards-after-all-2000715184</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715184</guid>
      <description>The latest RTX 50-series is hundreds or thousands of dollars more expensive than at launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audi declares war on &#8216;giant iPad&#8217; dashboards &#8211; as design boss signals return to the analog buttons everyone&#8217;s craving</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/audi-declares-war-on-giant-ipad-dashboards-as-design-boss-signals-return-to-the-analogue-buttons-everyones-craving</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wfZNc7ApFzpFHKVwjRzdMe</guid>
      <description>Audi's design boss sees a return to analog switches and dials for the brand, as massive screens aren't the answer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla invested $2B in Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tesla-invested-2b-in-elon-musks-xai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087539</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's AI company xAI  disclosed earlier this month it had raised $20 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Xbox controller to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23025443/best-xbox-controllers-one-series-x-s</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:46:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23025443/best-xbox-controllers-one-series-x-s</guid>
      <description>We live in a golden age of controllers. The gamepads on the market now are of higher quality, more versatile, and more customizable than anything from even one console generation ago. If you play games on an Xbox Series X or Series S (or a Windows PC), you have the unenviable task of choosing between [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk teases a new image-labeling system for X&#8230; we think?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/elon-musk-teases-a-new-image-labeling-system-for-xwe-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087446</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk says X will begin identifying "manipulated media" but doesn't share details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sea Urchin Apocalypse Is Real, and It Might Be Spreading Globally, Scientists Warn</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-sea-urchin-apocalypse-is-real-and-it-might-be-spreading-globally-scientists-warn-2000715108</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715108</guid>
      <description>New research has uncovered a mass die-off of sea urchins living in the Canary Islands&#8212;one that could signal an ongoing marine pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Is Using Palantir&#8217;s AI Tools to Sort Through Tips</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-is-using-palantirs-ai-tools-to-sort-through-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a474382e93380fc4f4913</guid>
      <description>ICE has been using an AI-powered Palantir system to summarize tips sent to its tip line since last spring, according to a newly released Homeland Security document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Really Needs to Pump the Brakes on That Viral Moltbot AI Agent</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/everyone-really-needs-to-pump-the-brakes-on-that-viral-moltbot-ai-agent-2000715154</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715154</guid>
      <description>It's all fun and games until every aspect of your life is splashed all over the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX is coming to the public markets, and secondaries are already on fire</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/spacex-is-coming-to-the-public-markets-and-secondaries-are-already-on-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3087562</guid>
      <description>paceX is&#160;reportedly lining&#160;up&#160;four major Wall Street banks&#160;for a&#160;2026 IPO&#160;that could provide the&#160;reset&#160;the market needs.&#160; The company just completed a tender offer at an&#160;$800 billion&#160;valuation, and secondary market demand is through the roof. If SpaceX goes public anywhere near its&#160;rumored&#160;$1.5 trillion&#160;valuation, it&#160;could trigger&#160;an IPO cascade for&#160;other&#160;late-stage unicorns like OpenAI, Stripe, and Databricks.&#160; Watch as&#160;Equity&#160;host Rebecca Bellan [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out: hackers are hijacking Microsoft Teams messages to try and get access to your emails - here's what you need to look out for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/watch-out-hackers-are-hijacking-microsoft-teams-messages-to-try-and-get-access-to-your-emails-heres-what-you-need-to-look-out-for</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uJpVATG5WR7knr4QSiXEx8</guid>
      <description>Hackers exploit Microsoft Teams by sending obfuscated invitations and fraudulent billing messages to access emails across multiple global industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers share new insights about the early universe via the Webb Space Telescope</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/astronomers-share-new-insights-about-the-early-universe-via-the-webb-space-telescope-213311848.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58200378-7754-452f-bc21-0d7679f974a9</guid>
      <description>Researchers using the James Webb Space Telescope have found a galaxy that is offering new data about the early stages of the universe's existence. The latest discovery shared by astronomers is about a bright galaxy dubbed MoM-z14. According to the team, this galaxy existed 280 million years after the Big Bang.&#160;The sounds like a long time, but in the context of the universe's estimated 13.8 billion years of existence, that's actually one of the closest examples astronomers have found to the Big Bang's occurrence. As a result, MoM-z14 can offer some insights and some surprises about what the ear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google adds Gemini AI-powered &#8216;auto browse&#8217; to Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869731/google-gemini-ai-chrome-auto-browse</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:32:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869731</guid>
      <description>Google is launching a new "auto browse" feature inside Chrome that can perform multi-step tasks on your behalf. The Gemini AI-powered capability is coming to Google AI Pro and Ultra subscribers in the US, and can do things like research hotel and flight costs, schedule appointments, fill out online forms, manage subscriptions, and more. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
