<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 04:37:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Housemarque's Saros is delayed to April 30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/housemarques-saros-is-delayed-to-april-30-041813989.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 04:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d818b36d-4792-404d-90b0-9f1b845b1efb</guid>
      <description>
PlayStation had said on X that it would have news about Saros at The Game Awards, and unfortunately, fans excited for the new Housemarque project will need to wait a little longer to get their hands on it. The game has been delayed from its planned March release. But there's only a short time until the new date of April 30, and pre-orders are open now. Star Rahul Kohli appeared at The Game Awards to introduce the newest trailer for the game.&#160;
I'm glad we won't be waiting too much longer, because Saros looks very cool. Housemarque made its name on titles like Resogun and Returnal, and Saros se...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4:LOOP is a co-op shooter from the creator of Left 4 Dead and JJ Abrams' Bad Robot</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/4loop-is-a-co-op-shooter-from-the-creator-of-left-4-dead-and-jj-abrams-bad-robot-035835461.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef9c1461-5839-4a91-9ccc-1bbb8d823dc9</guid>
      <description>The next game from Left 4 Dead designer Mike Booth is putting a sci-fi spin on his last game's co-op action, based on a trailer Booth and producer JJ Abrams shared at The Game Awards 2025. The new game is called 4:LOOP, and it's the first project entirely developed by Bad Robot Games, film production company Bad Robot's game studio.
4:LOOP combines the four-player co-op action of Left 4 Dead, with roguelike elements enabled by what seems like a time loop mechanic. Based on the trailer, players fight a mixture of aliens and robots in each mission, all in the hopes of eventually drawing the atte...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: Galactic Racer is a podracing game set for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/star-wars-galactic-racer-is-a-podracing-game-set-for-2026-035508891.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d80f191-b91a-4169-9c64-2f0e193dfd28</guid>
      <description>
Why have one Star Wars game announcement at an edition of The Game Awards when you can have two? Star Wars: Galactic Racer is a podracing (and speeder racing) game from Fuse Games, a studio established in 2023 by former Burnout and Need for Speed developers. It's scheduled to hit PS5, Xbox Series X/S and PC in 2026.
The action here is set after the fall of the Empire. With the galaxy in rebuild mode after dealing with that whole mess, an unsanctioned, underground racing circuit called the Galactic League comes into being in the Outer Rim. Here, according to the game's Steam page, "syndicates ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Star Wars: Galactic Racer&#8217; Is Speeding Into Our Hearts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-galactic-racer-announcement-trailer-game-awards-2026-2000698847</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698847</guid>
      <description>Now this is podracing, among other things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exodus is delayed to early 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/exodus-is-delayed-to-early-2027-032610665.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8293ee8-2bf0-40ca-8ee0-25669873ece3</guid>
      <description>
So there's good news and bad news about the highly anticipated Exodus coming out of The Game Awards this year. The good news is that there's a fresh trailer showcasing more of the game. The bad news is that the game won't be out until early 2027. The game was originally announced two years ago (also at The Game Awards) and had been pegged for release in 2026.
We may be waiting longer to get our hands on Exodus, but the substantial new trailer shows more of what the final product will entail, offering some backstory on main character Jun Aslan. He's the only human who can use the technology de...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider announces two new games</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/843260/tomb-raider-catalyst-trailer-tomb-raider-atlantis</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T22:11:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843260</guid>
      <description>While Geoff Keighley had already announced that Tomb Raider would be making a Game Awards appearance, the surprise was that instead of one game announcement there's two. Crystal Dynamics and Amazon Game Studios are releasing two Tomb Raider games back-to-back in 2026 and 2027. First up, coming in 2026 is Tomb Raider: Legacy of Atlantis. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluribus episode 7 ending explained: what happens to Carol and Manousos in the new Apple TV show?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/apple-tv-plus/pluribus-episode-7-ending-explained</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hhBUGFZnWbcx6Zn7LjmZaa</guid>
      <description>The antepenultimate episode of Pluribus season 1 puts two of its main characters through the physical and emotional wringer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Pips hints, answers for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pips-nyt-games-hints-answers-easy-medium-hard-december-12</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04AGCq4OWVyIjLTHFC6eETJ</guid>
      <description>The New York Times' latest game, Pips, brings domino fun to your desktop. How to play Pips as well as hints in case you get stuck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints today: Clues, answers for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nyt-connections-hint-answer-today-december-12-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03v0kRhd6d411Z52UtBb3op</guid>
      <description>Connections is a New York Times word game that's all about finding the "common threads between words." How to solve the puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints, answers for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/strands-nyt-hint-december-12-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06vVIhh4iSsAOUyQRau4YDM</guid>
      <description>The NYT Strands hints and answers you need to make the most of your puzzling experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordle today: Answer, hints for December 12, 2025</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wordle-today-answer-december-12-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06nLTxgoCMy8aCtPywDSTqa</guid>
      <description>Here's the answer for "Wordle" #1637 on December 12 as well as a few hints, tips, and clues to help you solve it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lara Croft will return in Tomb Raider: Catalyst and a new remake</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/lara-croft-will-return-in-tomb-raider-catalyst-and-a-new-remake-025859998.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85fa4c90-c029-478e-991d-30dd54f94a66</guid>
      <description>The last mainline Tomb Raider game was 2018&#8217;s Shadow of the Tomb Raider, and after spending a few years in video game purgatory, Lara Croft is coming back in two new games. At The Game Awards 2025, Amazon Game Studios announced that Tomb Raider: Legacy of Atlantis will reimagine of one of the hero&#8217;s early adventures in 2026, and Tomb Raider: Catalyst will continue the series in 2027.Catalyst is developed by Crystal Dynamics and follows Lara through Northern India &#8220;in the wake of a mythical cataclysm,&#8221; as she comes into competition with other treasure hunters. Legacy of Atlantis, developed by C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Christmas gifts we love under $50</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/802969/best-gifts-under-50-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:50:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=802969</guid>
      <description>One of the easiest things to do during the holidays is spend too much money. It happens to many of us, even when we swear that things are going to be different this year. We want to help you stay true to your intentions to save money when possible, and we're doing that with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Sweeney on the future of Fortnite after another win over Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843265/apple-epic-games-tim-sweeney-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:48:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843265</guid>
      <description>Shortly after appeals court judges ruled against Apple's contempt appeal in a years-long antitrust dispute against the makers of Fortnite, I got to talk to Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney in an interview. According to Sweeney, today's ruling "completely shuts down" Apple's App Store rules that allow it to collect "junk fees." The three-judge Ninth [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego Batman: Legacy of the Dark Knight swoops onto PC and consoles on May 29</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/lego-batman-legacy-of-the-dark-knight-swoops-onto-pc-and-consoles-on-may-29-024729940.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0f48c50-021d-49a6-9748-df2eb0ab1b8f</guid>
      <description>
It didn't take too long for a game that a whole bunch of people are excited about to swoop into Grand Theft Auto VI's old release week. Or maybe Rockstar had an idea of was what was coming and delayed its blockbuster by six months to get out of the way of Lego Batman: Legacy of the Dark Knight.&#160;
Either way, TT Games and Warner Bros. Games brought a new trailer to The Game Awards and revealed that the Caped Crusader's next adventure will hit PS5, Xbox Series X/S, Steam and the Epic Games Store on May 29. The base game will cost $70 and pre-orders are open as of 11PM ET on December 11.
Lego gam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Deadpool Is Also Coming to &#8216;Marvel Rivals&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/game-awards-2025-marvel-rivals-deadpool-release-date-2000698482</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698482</guid>
      <description>The merc with a mouth will be the next character to join Netease's Marvel comics shooter early next year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
