<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:47:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s 2026 Valentine&#8217;s Day gift guide (for her)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/865281/valentines-day-2026-gift-ideas-for-her-girlfriend-wife-partner</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T15:46:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865281</guid>
      <description>Valentine's Day often comes with more pressure than it needs to. At heart, though, February 14th is about showing appreciation for the people you care about in ways that feel thoughtful and sincere. And while big displays of romance can do that, it's often the quieter, more personal gestures - or a meaningful gift that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Faces Two Key Trials That Could Change Social Media Forever</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meta-faces-two-key-trials-that-could-change-social-media-forever-2000719673</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719673</guid>
      <description>TikTok has already fled the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novo Nordisk Sues Hims &amp; Hers Over Ozempic Copycats as the Weight-Loss Drug Wars Escalate</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/novo-nordisk-hits-hims-hers-with-lawsuit-as-the-weight-loss-drug-wars-escalate-2000719682</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719682</guid>
      <description>The lawsuit is the latest in an escalating feud between the Danish pharmaceutical and telehealth company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple devices are finally getting their first serious discounts of the year &#8212; shop my top picks on AirPods, iPads, and smartwatches starting at $99.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/apple-devices-are-finally-getting-their-first-serious-discounts-of-the-year-shop-my-top-picks-on-airpods-ipads-and-smartwatches-starting-at-usd99-99</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LiFX6VvyDwKxcQApit6qcQ</guid>
      <description>Apple's pricey, highly sought-after devices are finally on sale, and I'm rounding up today's best deals on AirPods, iPads, MacBooks, and smartwatches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toyota made a game engine</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/875995/toyota-fluorite-game-engine</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T15:22:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875995</guid>
      <description>Using a game engine in a "digital cockpit" can be useful for things like step-by-step 3D tutorials about a car, mapping the environment around your car, and offering more natural controls, Jamie Kerber, the lead engineer of a new game engine developed by Toyota Connected North America, said in a recent presentation at the FOSDEM [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT rolls out ads</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/09/chatgpt-rolls-out-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091176</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT ads will display for users on the the free and low-cost "Go" plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haworth Fern office chair review: Incredibly premium ergonomics with great all day comfortability</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/haworth-fern-office-chair-review</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7HhFytsSo52SJw7ZA4Tdf7</guid>
      <description>The Haworth Fern is a beautiful ergonomic office chair with a unique design, Wave Suspension technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lidar-maker Ouster buys vision company StereoLabs as sensor consolidation continues</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/09/lidar-maker-ouster-buys-vision-company-stereolabs-as-sensor-consolidation-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090990</guid>
      <description>Ouster is paying $35 million along with 1.8 million shares.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-two-year-plans-are-up-to-81-percent-off-right-now-180602205.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 81 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $88 for two years, plus four additional free months. The Basic plan is where you'll see the biggest discount: it's $68 for two years, plus the same four additional free months.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. On...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History Behind the Trial of Seven in &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-trial-of-seven-explained-game-of-thrones-2000719744</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719744</guid>
      <description>'Game of Thrones' has prepared us for trials by combat before, but 'A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms' is showing us a version rooted in ancient Westerosi history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark Tank&#160;star Kevin O&#8217;Leary says you&#8217;re &#8216;stupid&#8217; if you work this many hours per day</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486998/shark-tank-star-kevin-oleary-says-if-youre-working-this-many-hours-a-day-its-stupid</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486998/shark-tank-star-kevin-oleary-says-if-youre-working-this-many-hours-a-day-its-stupid</guid>
      <description>The celebrity investor once touted workaholism, but has since changed his tune.
Investor and Shark Tank star Kevin O&#8217;Leary once declared that to succeed in business you must be willing to grind out 25 hour work days. He has since walked back on that idea, calling it, in his own words, &#8220;sheer stupidity.&#8221;&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What a great way to kill your community': Discord users are furious about its new age verification checks &#8212; and are now hunting for alternatives</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/software/what-a-great-way-to-kill-your-community-discord-users-are-furious-about-its-new-age-verification-checks-and-are-now-hunting-for-alternatives</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AoDqwxoiWhsZgnuz8X7tu5</guid>
      <description>Discord has announced that it's rolling out age verification checks globally from March, and the decision has sparked fury from many privacy-conscious users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump meme coin down 96% as Bitcoin and meme coins slide</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91489687/trump-meme-coin-down-bitcoin-slides</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T19:50:53</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91489687/trump-meme-coin-down-bitcoin-slides</guid>
      <description>From Trump and Melania tokens to Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, meme coins are being hit hardest in a volatile crypto downturn.
On Jan. 19, 2025, someone paid $75.35 to buy a Trump meme coin. Today, assuming that investor held the cryptocurrency, the investment has lost 96% of its value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kroger names former Walmart executive Greg Foran as its new CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91489635/kroger-ceo-walmart-foran-mcmullen</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91489635/kroger-ceo-walmart-foran-mcmullen</guid>
      <description>Foran succeeds Ron Sargent, who has been Kroger&#8217;s interim leader since former CEO Rodney McMullen resigned last March. 
Kroger named former Walmart executive&#160;Greg Foran&#160;as its chief executive officer on Monday, 11 months after the&#160;abrupt resignation of its previous CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched the Super Bowl on LG's award-winning C5 OLED TV &#8212; and now I know why it's our best-rated display</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/i-watched-the-super-bowl-on-lgs-award-winning-c5-oled-tv-and-now-i-know-why-its-our-best-rated-display</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abJPr92amGjzTHfJZDARd6</guid>
      <description>One of the best OLED TVs of 2025 is on sale at Best Buy. I already own one and can recommend you jump on this one fast and save even more money than I did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2026: How to watch, full schedule of events, and everything else you need to know about the Winter Games</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/olympics-2026-how-to-watch-full-schedule-of-events-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-the-winter-games-172409424.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eca0487b-e039-4319-89d0-8969baa49f32</guid>
      <description>


  The Milano Cortina 2026 Winter Olympics are coming up. (Mattia Ozbot/Getty Images)
 

  Mattia Ozbot via Getty Images
 

The 2026 Winter Olympics are taking place in Italy this year, with all the action taking place in Milan and the Alpine city of Cortina. This year marks the fourth time Italy has hosted the Winter Games; most recently, Turin hosted in 2006. Of the 16 sports featured at the Winter Olympics, 15 will return, including figure skating, hockey, luge, speed skating, and one entirely new sport, snow mountaineering. (Will it be as big a hit as the 2024 Summer Games' new addition,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why isn&#8217;t the day after the Super Bowl a national holiday?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91489513/why-isnt-the-day-after-the-super-bowl-a-national-holiday</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91489513/why-isnt-the-day-after-the-super-bowl-a-national-holiday</guid>
      <description>Lots of workers are likely staying home &#8220;sick&#8221; today.
It&#8217;s the day after Super Bowl Sunday, otherwise known as National Hangover Day. Because, let&#8217;s face it&#8212;even if you have zero interest in football and can&#8217;t even remember who won the game, if you&#8217;re like many Americans, you probably at least went to a watch party. (If for nothing else than for the joy-bringing halftime show led by the one and only Bad Bunny.)...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI starts testing ads in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-starts-testing-ads-in-chatgpt-191756493.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adbd864e-a512-49a6-bdb0-b4ebd6bfe182</guid>
      <description>Users on ChatGPT's free and Go plans in the US may now start to see ads as OpenAI has started testing them in the chatbot. The company announced plans to bring ads to ChatGPT. At the time, the company said it would display sponsored products and services that are relevant to the current conversations of logged-in users, though they can disable personalization and "clear the data used for ads&#8221; whenever they wish.&#8220;Our goal is for ads to support broader access to more powerful ChatGPT features while maintaining the trust people place in ChatGPT for important and personal tasks,&#8221; OpenAI wrote in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The BBC&#8217;s Not Saying How It&#8217;ll Fund &#8216;Doctor Who&#8217; After Its Disney Breakup</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doctor-who-future-bbc-budget-disney-2000719740</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719740</guid>
      <description>BBC Studios production chief Zai Bennett offers only vague updates on the future of the sci-fi series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is killing the old HomeKit tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/875859/apple-is-killing-the-old-homekit-tomorrow</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-09T14:00:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875859</guid>
      <description>If you haven't yet updated to the new Apple Home, your smart home devices may no longer work in the Home app on your iPhone, iPad, Mac, or Apple Watch starting tomorrow. On February 10, 2026, Apple will end support for the original HomeKit architecture. The biggest impact of the change will be felt by [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft starts the countdown for the end of Exchange Web Services</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-starts-the-countdown-for-the-end-of-exchange-web-services</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zdLhoXfmGXwZRXxpYL7ziY</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has set out its roadmap to fully retire Exchange Web Services from April 2027, after around 20 years of service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's Presidents' Day deals are off with a bang with these exceptional wireless headphones offers &#8212; grab a stellar set of cans from just $49.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/best-buys-presidents-day-deals-are-off-to-a-bang-with-these-exceptional-wireless-headphones-offers-grab-a-stellar-set-of-cans-from-just-usd49-99</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EmMmJNnNgZ7VLNLDAngwAT</guid>
      <description>The Presidents' Day sales have begun at Best Buy, and you can land some serious savings on awesome headphones, starting from just $49.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;C&#8217;est pour votre bien&#160;&#187; : voici comment Discord va v&#233;rifier votre &#226;ge</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/2971645_cest-pour-votre-bien-discord-generalise-la-verification-dage-forcee</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/applications/2971645_cest-pour-votre-bien-discord-generalise-la-verification-dage-forcee</guid>
      <description>
&#192; partir de mars 2026, si vous refusez de prouver que vous &#234;tes majeur, votre compte Discord sera brid&#233;. La plateforme d&#233;ploie un syst&#232;me de scan facial pour s&#233;parer les adultes des mineurs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's how to disable Ring's creepy Search Party feature</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/heres-how-to-disable-rings-creepy-search-party-feature-185420455.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8091802-d458-4a56-ae16-ee541636bbfc</guid>
      <description>Ring aired a Super Bowl ad touting its Search Party feature that didn't quite get the intended buzz. Instead, the commercial scared the pants off of anyone concerned about a mass surveillance state.
The feature is advertised as a way to reunite missing dogs with their owners, a noble cause indeed, but Search Party does this by turning individual Ring devices into a surveillance network. Each camera uses AI to identify pets running across its field of vision and all feeds are pooled together to potentially identify lost animals. I've never seen a slope quite so slippery, as the technology could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $100 On Our Favorite Home Printer</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/epson-et-2980-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698a1cbec2e8a5cd1636410d</guid>
      <description>The Epson ET-2980 is a great value at its full price, and the discount sweetens the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung mise sur la fluidit&#233; avec son &#233;cran QHD Odyssey G5 G50F 32&#8243; en promo qui tourne &#224; 180 Hz</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2971083_samsung-mise-sur-la-fluidite-avec-son-ecran-qhd-odyssey-g5-g50f-32-en-promo-qui-tourne-a-180-hz</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2971083_samsung-mise-sur-la-fluidite-avec-son-ecran-qhd-odyssey-g5-g50f-32-en-promo-qui-tourne-a-180-hz</guid>
      <description>
Les &#233;crans Samsung Odyssey G5 sont de vraies bonnes r&#233;f&#233;rences pour jouer dans d'excellentes conditions et vous retrouvez la version 32 pouces du G5 G50F pour 219,99 euros au lieu de 249,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
