<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:26:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer content is fuel for an internet-obsessed administration</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856948/nick-shirley-minnesota-daycare-fraud-influencer-media-cycle</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T16:24:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856948</guid>
      <description>Just a day after publishing a 40-minute video alleging fraud at Minnesota daycare centers, Nick Shirley had the vice president's attention. In Shirley's video, he and another man identified only as "David" roam Minneapolis with cameras and microphones, demanding entrance to daycare centers they say are operated by members of the local Somali community. With [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobileye acquires humanoid robot startup Mentee Robotics for $900M</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/mobileye-acquires-humanoid-robot-startup-mentee-robotics-for-900m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080151</guid>
      <description>Mentee Robotics was co-founded by Mobileye president Amnon Shashua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think That Coffee&#8217;s Safe on a Plane? Think Again, Researchers Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/think-that-coffees-safe-on-a-plane-think-again-researchers-say-2000706308</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706308</guid>
      <description>A new report finds that many airlines have relatively poor quality drinking water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Ahead in &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-2026-preview-mandalorian-and-grogu-starfighter-2000705592</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705592</guid>
      <description>2026 marks another major transitory period for the galaxy far, far away&#8212;as it tries to return to movie theaters for the first time in almost seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame's latest robot vacuum concept has slightly terrifying legs that can climb full-size stairs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/dreames-latest-robot-vacuum-concept-has-slightly-terrifying-legs-that-can-climb-full-size-stairs-210000399.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efe72a0d-8e7e-44a0-8cf7-e8910908c28b</guid>
      <description>Robot vacuum companies are once again trying to outdo each other at CES 2026. This year, Chinese appliance maker Dreame is showing off a prototype of a device that can climb up and down an entire flight of stairs.The concept, called the Cyber X, was previewed last year at IFA in Berlin. The vacuum sports a somewhat terrifying set of legs with rubber treads that allow it to autonomously navigate multi-story environments. While Dreame has previously shown off vacuums that can move up smaller steps, it says the Cyber X can climb stairs up to 25cm (9.8 inches) high and slopes up to 42 degrees. It ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame's robot vacuum with an arm is back at CES 2026 and it can do more than pick up shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/dreames-robot-vacuum-with-an-arm-is-back-at-ces-2026-and-it-can-do-more-than-pick-up-shoes-210000020.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48f39b83-a16b-4998-91b7-41d31eb4145a</guid>
      <description>Last year at CES, Dreame showed off a robot vacuum prototype with a mechanical arm. But while we were able to see the arm extend and retract, we didn&#8217;t see the device, which was described as a prototype at the time, actually grab anything, which was a bit disappointing.This year, though, the company has made its arm-enabled vacuum a reality with the Cyber 10 Ultra. Dreame previewed it recently at IFA in Berlin, but has now confirmed it will be on sale later this year.&#160;The vacuum has an extendable arm that looks pretty similar to the prototype version we saw last year. It extends from the top o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI says it raised $20B in Series E funding</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/xai-says-it-raised-20b-in-series-e-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080465</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is among the many investors, but xAI has not disclosed if these investments come in the form of equity or debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs&#8217; Plan for Atari &#8216;Astrochart&#8217; Among New Items Up for Auction</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/steve-jobs-plan-for-atari-astrochart-among-new-items-up-for-auction-2000706227</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706227</guid>
      <description>Take a peek at the stuff from the Apple founder's childhood bedroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 day 2: the 11 best gadgets we've seen today, from smart flashlights to new Dell XPS laptops</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/ces-2026-day-2-the-11-best-gadgets-weve-seen-today-from-smart-flashlights-to-new-dell-xps-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eAWzswHS8hQaWVyLAEyBkV</guid>
      <description>The gadgets and gizmos on show at CES 2026 are continuing to impress us, as we tour the Las Vegas show floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inevitable Rise of the Art TV</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/art-frame-tv-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695be40a363a90f378f4766f</guid>
      <description>New televisions from Amazon, Hisense, TCL, and others are designed to display fine art and look like a painting when they&#8217;re switched off. It&#8217;s all thanks to smaller living spaces and new screen tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI teamed with Microsoft to build a unique stylus that doubles as an AI microphone for Copilot &#8212; and you can fully charge it in just 30 seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/msi-teamed-with-microsoft-to-build-a-unique-stylus-that-doubles-as-an-ai-microphone-for-copilot-and-you-can-fully-charge-it-in-just-30-seconds</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">w2qmyFzZEGFwfxKQYMoktF</guid>
      <description>MSI Nano Pen for Prestige Flip laptops combines pressure-sensitive stylus input, tilt support, rapid charging, and built-in Copilot voice commands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At CES, EVs take a backseat to robotaxis and AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856503/ces-2026-robotaxi-ai-ev-car-concepts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856503</guid>
      <description>It says a lot about the current moment when one of the world's largest EV sellers shows up at the world's biggest electronics show to announce not a new, more affordable model or a cool futuristic concept car, but a humanoid robot. And one we've seen already. Hyundai's decision to use its CES keynote to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the largest US broadband providers investigates breach</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/one-of-the-largest-us-broadband-providers-investigates-breach</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DLAa4wc5b56DE9zC7fkmCD</guid>
      <description>Brightspeed is looking into claims of a data breach, made earlier by threat actors Crimson Collective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wi-Fi 8 is appearing at CES before most of us have switched to Wi-Fi 7</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856883/ces-2026-wi-fi-8-asus-broadcom-mediatek</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:26:17-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856883</guid>
      <description>The first Wi-Fi 8 routers and chips made a surprise appearance at CES 2026, and could launch this year, only a couple of years after Wi-Fi 7 debuted. So, if you don't already have a Wi-Fi 7 router - and many of us don't - you might want to consider holding off on upgrading. Rather [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just saw Roborock's new robot vacuum with legs, and it's going to make no-go zones a thing of the past</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/i-just-saw-roborocks-new-robot-vacuum-with-legs-and-its-going-to-make-no-go-zones-a-thing-of-the-past</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EDu6RLzs5rpA3g9RPXaxrd</guid>
      <description>Cleaning stairs is just the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California lawmaker proposes a four-year ban on AI chatbots in kids&#8217; toys</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/california-lawmaker-proposes-a-four-year-ban-on-ai-chatbots-in-kids-toys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080435</guid>
      <description>&#8220;Our children cannot be used as lab rats for Big Tech to experiment on,&#8221; Senator Steve Padilla said. He just introduced a bill to ban AI chatbots in toys until safety regulations are developed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This RV will charge your electric truck after towing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/856487/this-rv-will-charge-your-electric-truck-after-towing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:20:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856487</guid>
      <description>Electric trucks seem to have hit a pothole recently, ignored by truck owners who say they're worried about losing too much ranging from towing. But what if the thing your towing could also pump electrons back into your truck's battery when all's said and done? That what California-company Evotrex is proposing with its new RV, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most bizarre tech announced so far at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/the-most-bizarre-tech-announced-so-far-at-ces-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080421</guid>
      <description>From an AI panda pet to an anime girl hologram for your desk, here are the wildest products at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok is undressing children &#8212; can the law stop it?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/855832/grok-undressing-children-csam-law-x-elon-musk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:08:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855832</guid>
      <description>Grok began 2026 as it began 2025: under fire for its AI-generated images. Elon Musk's chatbot has spent the last week flooding X with nonconsensual, sexualized deepfakes of adults and minors. Circulating screenshots show Grok complying with requests to put real women in lingerie and make them spread their legs, and to put small children [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Music signs a new AI deal with Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856849/universal-music-nvidia-ai-deal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:07:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856849</guid>
      <description>Universal Music Group is partnering with Nvidia to bring a new AI model to one of the world's largest music catalogs. Among other initiatives, Tuesday's announcement touts the extension of Nvidia's music AI model Music Flamingo, which is designed to mimic how humans understand music by recognizing nuanced elements like song structure, harmony, emotional arcs, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Least One &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Kid Thinks Eleven Is Actually Dead</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-ending-sadie-sink-eleven-2000706300</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706300</guid>
      <description>Sadie Sink has no problem taking a pessimistic view on the Netflix finale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 57 Best Shows on Disney+, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (January 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-shows-disney-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">632c75aa74ce5b82a68ef323</guid>
      <description>The End of an Era, Percy Jackson and the Olympians, and The Beatles Anthology are just a few of the shows you should be watching on Disney+ this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES promises the robot butler, but delivers better Roombas instead</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855329/rosey-robot-roomba-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855329</guid>
      <description>If you listen to the CES hype machine this year, you might think that robots are finally ready to take over your domestic duties. To some extent that's true, but take note of the plural: there's no single robot ready to take over all of your household chores yet, but an army of them just [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The organization behind decades of public TV is dissolving&#8212;what comes next</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470010/the-organization-behind-decades-of-public-tv-is-dissolving-what-comes-next</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470010/the-organization-behind-decades-of-public-tv-is-dissolving-what-comes-next</guid>
      <description>The Corporation for Public Broadcasting supported generations of educational and cultural programming before funding cuts forced its dissolution.
Six decades after it was created by Congress, the nonprofit that brought America Mister Rogers&#8217; Neighborhood and Sesame Street will shut down for good.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People are using Grok to create lewd images of women and young girls</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470022/grok-twitter-x-women-elon-musk-pornography</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470022/grok-twitter-x-women-elon-musk-pornography</guid>
      <description>The mere ability to create such images suggests just how harmful it is to remove guardrails on generative AI.
Elon Musk took over X and folded in Grok, his sister company&#8217;s generative AI tool, with the aim of making his social media ecosystem a more permissive and &#8220;free speech maximalist&#8221; space. What he&#8217;s ended up with is the threat of multiple regulatory investigations after people began using Grok to create explicit images of women without their permission&#8212;and sometimes veering into images of underage children....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley files for bitcoin, solana ETFs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470066/morgan-stanley-files-bitcoin-solana-etfs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T19:59:58</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470066/morgan-stanley-files-bitcoin-solana-etfs</guid>
      <description>In the two years since the SEC approved the first U.S.-listed spot bitcoin ETF, a wide array of financial institutions have stepped up to issue such funds.
Morgan Stanley is seeking regulatory approval to launch exchange-traded funds tied to the price of cryptocurrency tokens, according to filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Tuesday, the first such move by a big U.S. bank....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried Neurable&#8217;s brain-sensing headphones at CES</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-neurable-brain-sensing-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">020fNkOXo2sqbayoF42OGlT</guid>
      <description>I tried Neurable&#8217;s brain-sensing headphones at CES</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, Lego, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel is building a handheld gaming platform including a dedicated chip</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/intel-is-building-a-handheld-gaming-platform-including-a-dedicated-chip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080288</guid>
      <description>Intel has been building chips designed for gaming PCs for years but the company is now moving into handheld devices too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMArena lands $1.7B valuation four months after launching its product</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/06/lmarena-lands-1-7b-valuation-four-months-after-launching-its-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080354</guid>
      <description>LMArena, which started as a UC Berkeley research project, has raised about $250 million total and become a unicorn in about seven months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Google Pixel Buds Pro 2 earbuds are on sale for $165</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-google-pixel-buds-pro-2-earbuds-are-on-sale-for-165-193444491.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcfa8124-d118-4e0c-95ba-1799f6041da5</guid>
      <description>Google's Pixel Buds Pro 2 earbuds are on sale for $165 via Amazon. That's a nice discount of $64, which breaks down to 28 percent. There is a spot of bad news. The deal only applies to the hazel colorway. Other colors are discounted, but they aren't as cheap. It's not as if the hazel is hideous. These are standard dark brown-hued earbuds.
The device made our list of the best wireless earbuds, and this is particularly true for those tied into the Pixel ecosystem. These earbuds are on the smaller side and, more importantly, comfortable to wear for long periods of time. They also manage to delive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Luxurious Headphones Are Almost Half Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/bowers-wilkins-px8-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d458389c20eb7bcfd9ce0</guid>
      <description>The Bowers &amp; Wilkins Px8 feature premium materials and luxurious sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Bringing AI Slop Directly to TVs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/googles-bringing-ai-slop-directly-to-tvs-2000706245</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706245</guid>
      <description>The slop is inescapable at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest Nvidia announcements at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/856439/nvidia-ces-2026-announcements-roundup</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T14:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856439</guid>
      <description>We're not even a full week into 2026 yet, but Nvidia has already announced several products and updates to start the new year. Nvidia's new Vera Rubin architecture was launched earlier than expected at CES, joined by announcements for its own Tesla-rivaling self-driving car technology, and the latest updates coming to DLSS, G-Sync display tech, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
