<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:24:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Three billion WhatsApp users are at risk - an expert has developed a tool that could spy on everyone, and you would never know about it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/three-billion-whatsapp-users-are-at-risk-an-expert-has-developed-a-tool-that-could-spy-on-everyone-and-you-would-never-know-about-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">822sGR7GGMcB8royDHJEo7</guid>
      <description>A proof-of-concept tool exploits messaging app receipts to silently track behavior, drain batteries, and increase mobile data usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X was spooked enough by new Twitter to change its terms of service</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/x-was-spooked-enough-by-new-twitter-to-change-its-terms-of-service-231138305.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5832d6eb-ac4b-4876-a786-5a9e89998c99</guid>
      <description>Despite changing its name and using decidedly bird-free branding, X is trying to hold on to its original Twitter trademarks, TechCrunch reports. The xAI-owned social media platform has updated its terms of service to include references to Twitter after previously only mentioning X, and seemingly attempted to counter a startup's petition to cancel the company's Twitter trademarks with a petition of its own.The startup X appears to be responding to is Operation Bluebird, a company cofounded by former Twitter general counsel Stephen Coates that went public last week with plans to capture what rem...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexa Plus&#8217;s website is live for some users</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845678/alexa-dot-com-alexa-plus-website-live</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T18:10:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845678</guid>
      <description>The Alexa.com website appears to be live for some users. The browser-based home for Alexa Plus, the company's revamped digital voice assistant, was first announced at the Alexa Plus launch event in February. But until recently, Alexa.com redirected to an information page. Now, some users, myself included, are seeing a new Alexa Plus web interface. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des TV Micro RGB &#224; partir de 55 pouces chez Samsung d&#232;s 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2912445_des-tv-micro-rgb-a-partir-de-55-pouces-chez-samsung-des-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2912445_des-tv-micro-rgb-a-partir-de-55-pouces-chez-samsung-des-2026</guid>
      <description>
Samsung annonce en amont du CES 2026 une extension exceptionnelle de sa gamme de t&#233;l&#233;viseurs Micro RGB. En effet, jusqu&#8217;&#224; pr&#233;sent, seule la vitrine technologique symbolis&#233;e par le TV de 115 pouces en diagonale &#233;tait disponible. En 2026, il y aura donc des TV de 55 jusqu&#8217;au 115 pouces.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s 2026 Micro RGB LED TVs can actually fit in your living room</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845760/samsung-micro-rgb-led-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845760</guid>
      <description>Following the release of the 115-inch Micro RGB TV back in August, Samsung has revealed today that its Micro RGB technology will extend into smaller sizes ranging from that 115-inch behemoth all the way down to 55 inches. While we all enjoy dreaming big, it's far more reasonable for most of us to consider putting [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's enormous micro-RGB TV is coming to smaller screen sizes, and it borrows one great feature from Samsung OLED TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/samsungs-enormous-micro-rgb-tv-is-coming-to-smaller-screen-sizes-and-it-borrows-one-great-feature-from-samsung-oled-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cFiVKEtjikQBB4w6W2HML</guid>
      <description>Samsung's Micro RGB tech will be coming to TVs as small as 55 inches in 2026, and will feature the same Glare Free screen found in the company's top OLED model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Image Falsely Suggests Bondi Beach Terror Attack Was Staged</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ai-image-falsely-suggests-bondi-beach-terror-attack-was-staged-2000700302</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700302</guid>
      <description>Grok, ChatGPT, and Claude all insist the image is real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Luminar&#8217;s doomed Volvo deal helped drag the company into bankruptcy</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/how-luminars-doomed-volvo-deal-helped-drag-the-company-into-bankruptcy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076392</guid>
      <description>Luminar says trouble with Volvo started as early as 2022, and that the Swedish automaker made -- but then backed away from -- large orders of its lidar sensors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Twitter never left:&#8217; X sues Operation Bluebird for trademark infringement</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845882/x-corp-operation-bluebird-twitter-lawsuit-trademark-infringement</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T17:33:26-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845882</guid>
      <description>X Corp. is suing Operation Bluebird, a recently-announced startup that aims to reclaim the Twitter brand for a new social network. In a lawsuit filed on Tuesday, the Elon Musk-owned company alleges Operation Bluebird is "brazenly attempting to steal" Twitter's trademarks, claiming "Twitter never left and continues to be exclusively owned by X Corp." Last [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s Chief of Staff Reportedly Spouted Off About Elon Musk and Drugs to Vanity Fair</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trumps-chief-of-staff-reportedly-spouted-off-about-elon-musk-and-drugs-to-vanity-fair-2000700235</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700235</guid>
      <description>She calls him "an odd, odd duck" in a newly published article.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers target Leonardo DiCaprio fans with malware-ridden "One Battle After Another" torrent</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/scammers-target-leonardo-dicaprio-fans-with-malware-ridden-one-battle-after-another-torrent</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iqiJ35ujqPMN3M2EPtTunK</guid>
      <description>A fake Leonardo DiCaprio torrent hides PowerShell malware in subtitles, delivering AgentTesla to steal credentials and evade security measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin threatens retaliation against Spotify and others over EU tech regulation</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/845869/ustr-eu-trade-threat-spotify-mistral</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T17:28:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845869</guid>
      <description>The Office of the US Trade Representative posted on X Tuesday, claiming that US service providers have been hit by "a continuing course of discriminatory and harassing lawsuits, taxes, fines, and directives" from the EU. Earlier this month, X was fined $140 million under the EU's Digital Services Act (DSA), in addition to new laws, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Android phones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23674658/best-android-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T17:18:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23674658/best-android-phone</guid>
      <description>The Android ecosystem is all about choice. While iPhone owners have a smaller pool of new devices to pick from when it&#8217;s time to upgrade, there&#8217;s a wider range of choices on Android. Some Android phones even fold in half! Imagine. On the flip side, all that choice can make for some hard decisions. Here&#8217;s [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Oddly Specific Monopoly Set Will Curb Your SDCC Travel Nightmares</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/monopoly-san-diego-edition-comic-con-2000700471</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700471</guid>
      <description>Of course 'Monopoly: San Diego Edition' includes multiple Comic-Con-related locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford Effectively Kills the Biden-Era Dream of All-Electric Trucks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ford-effectively-kills-the-biden-era-dream-of-all-electric-trucks-2000700476</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700476</guid>
      <description>The Ford F-150 Lightning was a symbol of the electric future in pickup truck form. It&#8217;s now dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best e-reader to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23769068/best-ebook-readers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T17:07:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23769068/best-ebook-readers</guid>
      <description>Any ebook reader will let you cram a Beauty and the Beast-sized library&#8217;s worth of books in your pocket, but so will your phone. An ebook reader offers a more book-like reading experience, with fewer distractions and less eye strain, and many include extra features, like adjustable frontlighting. Some really are pocketable. Others are waterproof [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first online chess game happened in December 1844 &#8212; Yes, 181 years ago, two teams played Chess 60km away using the electrical telegraph</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-first-online-chess-game-happened-in-december-1844-yes-181-years-ago-two-teams-played-chess-60km-away-using-the-electrical-telegraph</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4WiMi46imHo2NaE4yvi4SX</guid>
      <description>The 1844 Washington&#8211;Baltimore telegraph chess match started remote play, inspiring later international competitions, teletype games, and massive online platforms today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch NBA Cup Final 2025: live stream Spurs vs Knicks online from anywhere, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/basketball/nba-cup-final-2025-san-antonio-spurs-vs-new-york-knicks</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pjho5wZytpPUPchV9MNwVK</guid>
      <description>How to watch 2025 NBA Cup Final live streams online, with Victor Wembanyama and Jalen Brunson set to light up the Spurs vs Knicks clash in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiFlix shows us what Netflix would have been like 100 years ago</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/wikiflix-shows-us-what-netflix-would-have-been-like-100-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076595</guid>
      <description>On WikiFlix, a Netflix-inspired archive of public domain films, you can watch movies like "It's a Wonderful Life" and "Nosferatu" for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A vague study on Nazi bots created chaos in the Taylor Swift fan universe</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/845725/taylor-swift-gudea-report-rolling-stone-social-media-discourse-bots</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T16:30:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845725</guid>
      <description>On December 9th, Rolling Stone published a story that some saw as a bombshell: a network of coordinated, "inauthentic" social media accounts had a hand in the weekslong discourse that trailed the release of Taylor Swift's recent album, The Life of a Showgirl. It was a big deal for those in the Swiftie/anti-Swiftie universe. Immediately [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data&#8217;s in: And it says the job market is still rough</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461564/the-datas-in-and-it-says-the-job-market-is-still-rough</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461564/the-datas-in-and-it-says-the-job-market-is-still-rough</guid>
      <description>The new jobs report confirms what many workers likely already know: Most employers aren&#8217;t hiring. What does this mean for people who are job hunting? 
The latest employment numbers have dropped&#8212;and the job market still looks tough for workers.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIFA lowers some World Cup ticket prices to $60 after fan backlash</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461657/fifa-world-cup-tickets-60-fan-backlash</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461657/fifa-world-cup-tickets-60-fan-backlash</guid>
      <description>The number of $60 tickets for each game is likely to be in the hundreds, rather than thousands.
FIFA slashed the price of some World Cup tickets for teams&#8217; most loyal fans following a global backlash and some will get $60 seats for the final instead of being asked to pay $4,185.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 16-inch battery-powered portable monitor has a higher resolution than the Liquid Retina XDR display on the Apple MacBook Pro &#8212; and it will last at least 6 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-16-inch-battery-powered-portable-monitor-has-a-higher-resolution-than-the-liquid-retina-xdr-display-on-the-apple-macbook-pro-and-it-will-last-at-least-6-hours</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FohfxJcsh28Nh9CcJVadRD</guid>
      <description>VChance DU16 is a 16-inch 4K portable monitor with HDR, aluminum build, battery operation, USB-C connectivity, and professional usability.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
