<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:24:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I went to the Stranger Things finale in theaters and the strangest thing happened</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/853133/stranger-things-finale-theater-scene-report</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-03T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853133</guid>
      <description>The parking lot was packed. That's the first Strange Thing. A little background. Just about every mall is struggling now, but the Neshaminy Mall in Bensalem, Pennsylvania is more or less comatose. As Defector's Dan McQuade, a lifelong Pennsylvanian and mall fan, wrote in his fond remembrance of the shopping center, the once bustling complex [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Sunday, January 4 (game #1441)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-4-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">m6shKpxWaw3RByQvdAvnJ8</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Sunday, January 4 (game #938)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-4-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">k6K8KdfpMxcnX2qwWcQ6U3</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Sunday, January 4 (game #672)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-4-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb9U7jmxjndHgckBwqQQU5</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce robot-aspirateur 3-en-1 &#233;quip&#233; de 2 serpill&#232;res rotatives et une station de nettoyage aspire 64 % de son prix chez Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925287_ce-robot-aspirateur-3-en-1-equipe-dune-station-de-nettoyage-aspire-64-de-son-prix-chez-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925287_ce-robot-aspirateur-3-en-1-equipe-dune-station-de-nettoyage-aspire-64-de-son-prix-chez-amazon</guid>
      <description>
Entre sa puissance d'aspiration de 20 000 Pa, ses deux serpill&#232;res pour le nettoyage et sa station d'entretien, le Lefant M3 Max n'est pas avare en qualit&#233;s. En plus, il perd 64 % de son prix et tombe &#224; 359,99 euros sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela attack: Trump says U.S. has captured leader Nicol&#225;s Maduro</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468950/venezuela-attack-trump-says-u-s-has-captured-leader-nicolas-maduro</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-03T14:07:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468950/venezuela-attack-trump-says-u-s-has-captured-leader-nicolas-maduro</guid>
      <description>In a stunning American military action, a sitting leader was plucked from office. The legal authority for the strike was not immediately clear.
The United States hit Venezuela with a &#8220;large-scale strike&#8221; early Saturday and said its president had been captured and flown out of the country after&#160;months of intense pressure&#160;on Nicol&#225;s Maduro&#8217;s government &#8212; an extraordinary nighttime operation announced by President Donald Trump on social media hours after the attack....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This smart home controller is literally a piece of wood</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852598/mui-board-smart-home-controller-matter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-03T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852598</guid>
      <description>One of the fun parts of being a tech journalist for over a decade is that occasionally you get to watch a truly unique gadget go from concept to reality - and, eventually, into your living room. That's the case with the Mui Board, a smart home controller built into a piece of wood. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I punched my way through Yakuza Kiwami 2 on Nintendo Switch 2, and it&#8217;s a decent port of an excellent RPG</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/yakuza-kiwami-2-nintendo-switch-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NxaHAGZY4erq5uzz5YuJE8</guid>
      <description>Yakuza Kiwami 2 plays pretty well on Nintendo Switch 2, and being able to take Kiryu&#8217;s adventure on the go is a big bonus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 30 most exciting new shows of 2026: TechRadar's top TV picks on Netflix, Prime Video, HBO Max, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/most-exciting-new-shows-of-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">M4juzVSNAauxzBuAGKQGBh</guid>
      <description>There'll be lots of great new TV shows this year &#8211; here are our top choices for early 2026, plus some to look out for in the months ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: What to expect from tech's big January conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-what-to-expect-from-techs-big-january-conference-120000956.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2645ab40-20b1-4cf0-bdcf-9e9656c79061</guid>
      <description>The new year is upon us, and that means CES 2026 is imminent. The biggest tech trade show of the calendar comes with a bevy of new and notable announcements that set the tone for trends and expectations for the subsequent 12 months. The CES 2026 show floor is officially open from January 6 through 9, but the fun kicks off with events on Sunday January 4, followed by a host of press conferences on Monday. As always, product demos, announcements and networking will be happening at the Las Vegas Convention Center and other hotels all over the city. As usual, Engadget will be covering the event in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new Clicks Power Keyboard can turn your phone into a BlackBerry &#8211; and it doubles as a wireless charger too</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/phone-accessories/the-new-clicks-power-keyboard-can-turn-your-phone-into-a-blackberry-and-it-doubles-as-a-wireless-charger-too</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fRmke7svwkF7jHBq7YoPAZ</guid>
      <description>The Clicks Powerkeyboard will wirelessly charge your phone and gives you a physical keyboard as well.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
