<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:24:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Warnings Mount in Congress Over Expanded US Wiretap Powers</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/warnings-mount-in-congress-over-expanded-us-wiretap-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693adec55885de020c5e2195</guid>
      <description>Experts tell US lawmakers that a crucial spy program&#8217;s safeguards are failing, allowing intel agencies deeper, unconstrained access to Americans&#8217; data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flip's affordable NBN plan pricing doesn't mean you'll be left high and dry if you ever need help</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/wi-fi-broadband/flips-affordable-nbn-plan-pricing-doesnt-mean-youll-be-left-high-and-dry-if-you-ever-need-help</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9tdrtowVjoPfpRwXxAAisD</guid>
      <description>Finding an affordable and reliable NBN service is one thing, but can you be sure you'll get satisfactory support further down the line? This Aussie-owned telco stakes its reputation on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.'s Health Department Is Pondering a National Men's Health Initiative</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/rfk-jrs-health-department-is-pondering-a-national-mens-health-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939e0b327661e7f07f6ab3d</guid>
      <description>At an FDA discussion of testosterone replacement therapy, a top official called for special health centers to address a &#8220;men&#8217;s health crisis.&#8221; Others called to ease men's access to hormones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1X&#160;struck a deal to send its &#8216;home&#8217; humanoids to&#160;factories and warehouses</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/1x-struck-a-deal-to-send-its-home-humanoids-to-factories-and-warehouses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075424</guid>
      <description>Despite launching as a humanoid robot designed to help consumers around the house, 1X's NEO robots are heading to industrial use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best phone to buy right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22163811/best-phone</guid>
      <description>Haven&#8217;t you heard? Phones are boring now. And that&#8217;s just fine! Most people buying a new phone just want something familiar that works better than the device they&#8217;re replacing. If that&#8217;s your MO, then you&#8217;re sure to find something reliable in my recommendations below. But even if you&#8217;re looking for something a little more extra, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's AI-generated recap tool didn't watch Fallout very closely</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazons-ai-generated-recap-tool-didnt-watch-fallout-very-closely-215712958.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">317af2d4-87d3-43fd-b4f4-321618fa824b</guid>
      <description>Amazon's plan to offer AI-generated recaps of Prime Video shows isn't off to a great start. The company's recap of the first season of Fallout features multiple errors, GamesRadar+ writes, including basic facts about the plot of the show.You can watch the recap yourself in the "Extras" section of Amazon's Fallout season two listing in Prime Video. Besides being somewhat dry, the AI-generated recap incorrectly identifies the time period of the show's Los Angeles-set flashbacks as being the 1950s, when they're actually 2077 (the Fallout franchise is set in an alternate history that diverged from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSA imagines AI chatbots as creepy humans who harm kids</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/ai-chatbot-psa</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06HF4Kl75YoBhFJ5RMy3qog</guid>
      <description>President Trump says he won't let states pass AI laws. This ad says they're necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After striking OpenAI deal, Disney demands Google cease and desist from AI infringement</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/disney-cease-and-desist-google-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07xCS2JXPM0k4Wja4YIfeUL</guid>
      <description>Disney has sent a legal threat to Google, telling the company to stop using its characters in its AI models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is the sex in Heated Rivalry so hot?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/why-is-heated-rivalry-show-hbo-max-so-hot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01GY8cuOIucUJAbu4LC44xM</guid>
      <description>Queer sex never looked better than it does in HBO Max's hit 'Heated Rivalry.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How everyday investors are redefining the American dream</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459184/how-everyday-investors-are-redefining-the-american-dream</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:42:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459184/how-everyday-investors-are-redefining-the-american-dream</guid>
      <description>The new wealth builders are relying on software to help easily manage real estate. 
A quiet shift is reshaping the trajectory of wealth in America, but it isn&#8217;t happening in the boardrooms of Wall Street or the halls of Silicon Valley. It&#8217;s unfolding in neighborhoods, driveways, and home offices across the country, powered by teachers, software engineers, nurses, military families, and small-business owners who never expected to become real estate investors at all....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Mogul/Secretary of (*checks notes) the Interior Says AI Will Cure Cancer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/software-mogul-secretary-of-checks-notes-the-interior-says-ai-will-cure-cancer-2000698612</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698612</guid>
      <description>"This is the miracle of AI. We can actually manufacture intelligence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech transformation isn&#8217;t about how many tools you buy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459120/tech-transformation-isnt-about-how-many-tools-you-buy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:35:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459120/tech-transformation-isnt-about-how-many-tools-you-buy</guid>
      <description>A successful implementation requires focus on people more than tools.
Every company is racing to modernize. There&#8217;s a sense that if you aren&#8217;t adopting new technology fast enough, you&#8217;re already behind. From AI and automation to digital platforms, the list keeps growing. Leaders make big investments, employees sit through onboarding sessions, and for a few weeks, excitement fills the air. Then the momentum fades....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atmospheric River That Drenched the Northwest Is Now Supercharging 2 Winter Storms</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/atmospheric-river-that-drenched-the-northwest-is-now-supercharging-2-winter-storms-2000698742</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698742</guid>
      <description>The moisture from this storm system will help two fast-moving winter storms spread snow across the eastern U.S., with another atmospheric river on its way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York&amp;#8217;s new law forces advertisers to say when they&amp;#8217;re using AI avatars</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842848/new-york-law-ai-advertisements-sag-aftra-labor</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T16:30:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842848</guid>
      <description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul signed a bill Thursday that will require advertisers to identify if an ad includes AI-generated people. Hochul's announcement said the bill, S.8420-A/A.8887-B, was the first of its kind in the US, describing it as a "common sense" law that would bring increased transparency and protect consumers. A separate bill also [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney's deal with OpenAI is about controlling the future of copyright</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/disneys-deal-with-openai-is-about-controlling-the-future-of-copyright-213009504.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7536cc3-9fa1-46e3-9d78-c284f35a6c3c</guid>
      <description>This morning Disney and OpenAI announced a three-year licensing agreement: Starting in 2026, ChatGPT and Sora can generate images and videos incorporating Disney IP, including more than 200 characters from the company's stable of Star Wars, Pixar and Marvel brands. To say these companies make for strange bedfellows is an understatement.&#160;&#160;The agreement brings together two parties with very different public stances on copyright. Before OpenAI released Sora, the company reportedly notified studios and talent agencies they would need to opt out of having their work appear in the new app. The compa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 88-core AMD CPU surfaces on eBay, and here's why I think it's the start of something big</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/mysterious-88-core-amd-cpu-surfaces-on-ebay-and-heres-why-i-think-its-the-start-of-something-big</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wRDcfa7tDkgxy4G8YEddCR</guid>
      <description>Recently surfaced AMD processors with unusual core counts hint at rapid hyperscale refresh cycles and possible large-scale recovery of usable DDR4 memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&#8217;s &#8216;Adult Mode&#8217; Is Coming in 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chatgpts-adult-mode-is-coming-in-2026-2000698677</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698677</guid>
      <description>Gooners rejoice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why focusing on business priorities defines lasting success</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459201/why-focusing-on-business-priorities-defines-lasting-success</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T21:03:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459201/why-focusing-on-business-priorities-defines-lasting-success</guid>
      <description>Department metrics are important when they drive company goals.
Early in my career, I learned a valuable lesson that has stayed front and center. I was working for a company struggling to meet its marks. We were doing fine, but not knocking it out of the park. I walked into a quarterly business review, confident in our marketing metrics. We were hitting or surpassing every KPI, and I presented our achievements with pride. My CEO made a statement that stopped me in my tracks: &#8220;Marketing success means nothing unless the company as a whole is winning.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Characters We Think Scarlett Johansson Could Play in &#8216;The Batman Part II&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scarlett-johansson-the-batman-part-2-dc-studios-2000698054</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698054</guid>
      <description>Allow us to indulge in some good old-fashioned fan casting for Matt Reeves' sequel Battinson film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opera Wants $20 a Month for Its New AI Browser. You Probably Shouldn&#8217;t Pay It.</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/opera-wants-20-a-month-for-its-new-ai-browser-you-probably-shouldnt-pay-it-2000698561</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698561</guid>
      <description>It is just way too early to hand over the keys to the kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'47 Ronin' director found guilty of defrauding Netflix out of $11 million</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/47-ronin-director-found-guilty-of-defrauding-netflix-out-of-11-million-205519293.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">743101e9-5446-442b-b58a-86a5a9c27d21</guid>
      <description>A director who was charged with defrauding Netflix out of millions of dollars has been found guilty, Business Insider reports. Carl Rinsch, director of the 2013 Keanu Reeves movie 47 Ronin, now faces up to 90 years in prison.Rinsch began filming the project, White Horse (later renamed Conquest), around 2017. (Its premise: A scientist creates an organic humanoid species that turns on its creators.) The director completed six short-form episodes with his own money and investor funds. He then used those episodes to pitch studios for the money to complete the first season. Netflix ended up buying ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild New Map Shows the Sun&#8217;s &#8216;Point of No Return&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wild-new-map-shows-the-suns-point-of-no-return-2000698673</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698673</guid>
      <description>Astronomers have mapped the turbulent edge of the Sun where solar matter manages to escape the Sun's fierce magnetic grip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who needs Black Friday? The handy Amazon Echo Spot just hit a new record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/who-needs-black-friday-the-handy-amazon-echo-spot-just-hit-a-new-record-low-price</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">amYZbkuWSm4gKUjSDcbnEY</guid>
      <description>The Amazon Echo Spot is now $44.99 at Amazon &#8211; that's even cheaper than the price we saw on Black Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York passes law requiring ads to disclose the use of AI performers</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/new-york-passes-law-requiring-ads-to-disclose-the-use-of-ai-performers-202619826.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d1f27b2-5ab1-42cf-ba11-59902a7c6cab</guid>
      <description>New York is taking steps to regulate the use of AI in the state's entertainment industry. NY State Governor Kathy Hochul passed two pieces of legislation on Thursday that forces certain productions to disclose the use of AI-generated performers, and defines rules around how someone's likeness can be used after their death.Assembly Bill A8887B, now known as S.8420-A, specifically covers the use of AI performers in advertisements. Per Hochul's announcement, the law "requires persons who produce or create an advertisement to identify if it includes AI generated synthetic performers." S.8391, mean...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian Reveals New AI Assistant, Lidar, and Autonomous Driving Coming in 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/rivian-reveals-new-ai-assistant-lidar-and-autonomous-driving-coming-in-2026-2000698658</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698658</guid>
      <description>This EV company is trying to become more affordable and wants to cut Nvidia out of the process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
