<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:34:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers share new insights about the early universe via the Webb Space Telescope</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/astronomers-share-new-insights-about-the-early-universe-via-the-webb-space-telescope-213311848.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58200378-7754-452f-bc21-0d7679f974a9</guid>
      <description>Researchers using the James Webb Space Telescope have found a galaxy that is offering new data about the early stages of the universe's existence. The latest discovery shared by astronomers is about a bright galaxy dubbed MoM-z14. According to the team, this galaxy existed 280 million years after the Big Bang.&#160;The sounds like a long time, but in the context of the universe's estimated 13.8 billion years of existence, that's actually one of the closest examples astronomers have found to the Big Bang's occurrence. As a result, MoM-z14 can offer some insights and some surprises about what the ear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft reports strong cloud earnings in Q2 as gaming declines</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869493/microsoft-q2-2026-earnings-revenue-profits-windows-xbox-gaming-surface</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:23:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869493</guid>
      <description>Microsoft just posted the second quarter of its 2026 fiscal financial results. The software maker made $81.3 billion in revenue and a net income of $30.9 billion during Q3. Revenue is up 17 percent, and net income has increased by 23 percent. The holiday quarter saw PC shipments grow unexpectedly amid an ongoing RAM shortage. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI security startup Outtake raises $40M from Iconiq, Satya Nadella, Bill Ackman and other big names</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/ai-security-startup-outtake-raises-40m-from-iconiq-satya-nadella-bill-ackman-and-other-big-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087428</guid>
      <description>Outtake makes an agentic cybersecurity platform to help enterprises detect identity fraud. Its angel investors are a who's who.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla profit tanked 46% in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tesla-earnings-profit-q4-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087513</guid>
      <description>The company's sales fell for a second year in a row despite CEO Elon Musk spending years promising 50% annual growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Arco&#8217; Is as Close to an Instant Animated Classic as It Gets</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/arco-neon-natalie-portman-mark-ruffalo-animated-movie-review-2000705262</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705262</guid>
      <description>Neon's sci-fi animated feature features the voices of Natalie Portman and Mark Ruffalo and is playing in theaters now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow inks another AI partnership, this time with Anthropic</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/servicenow-inks-another-ai-partnership-this-time-with-anthropic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087398</guid>
      <description>ServiceNow partners with Anthropic just a week after announcing a partnership with OpenAI as the company takes a multi-model approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla hits a grim milestone: its second straight year of losses</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/869603/tesla-q4-2025-earnings-revenue-profit-musk-robotaxis</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:08:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869603</guid>
      <description>Tesla just reported its second consecutive year of declining revenue and profits, further complicating Elon Musk's $1 trillion effort to transform his company into a leader in AI and robotics. Meanwhile, the global EV market continues to grow, seemingly in spite of the pioneering company's setbacks. Tesla said it earned $840 million in net income [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina Measles Outbreak Becomes America&#8217;s Largest in 25 Years</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/south-carolina-measles-outbreak-becomes-americas-largest-in-25-years-2000715084</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715084</guid>
      <description>Thanks, anti-vaxxers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February&#8217;s PS Plus Monthly Games include Undisputed and Subnautica: Below Zero</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/februarys-ps-plus-monthly-games-include-undisputed-and-subnautica-below-zero-205100847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d778183-4789-433b-a1e9-27b44e3900e0</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;ve somehow almost reached the end of January already, which means it&#8217;s time for Sony to divulge the list of PlayStation Plus Monthly Games for February. They are Undisputed, Subnautica: Below Zero, Ultros and Ace Combat 7: Skies Unknown. If you have a PS Plus subscription on any tier, you can claim these starting on February 3. After claiming them, these games will stay in your library as long as your PS Plus plan remains active.&#160;Undisputed (PS5) is a 2024 boxing game with dozens of licensed fighters across several weight classes. They include legendary figures like Muhammad Ali and Sugar R...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube&amp;#8217;s top AI slop channels are disappearing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/869684/youtube-top-ai-channels-removed-kapwing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T15:47:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869684</guid>
      <description>YouTube appears to have taken down two of the most popular AI slop channels on its platform, along with several others. A report from Kapwing found that a channel called CuentosFacianantes no longer exists on the platform after amassing more than 5.9 million subscribers and over 1.2 billion total views. In a November 2025 report, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Wonderful DIY Lego Typewriter Does What Lego Couldn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-wonderful-diy-lego-typewriter-does-what-lego-couldnt-2000715081</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715081</guid>
      <description>When you absolutely have to type a letter using Lego, accept no substitutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now that's a team-up: Samsung and Nvidia expected to join forces to feature 'revolutionary' HBM4 memory modules in upcoming Vera Rubin hardware</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/now-thats-a-team-up-samsung-and-nvidia-expected-to-join-forces-to-feature-revolutionary-nbm4-memory-modules-in-upcoming-vera-rubin-hardware</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qMCVftVxRXZwysLE5dzN6n</guid>
      <description>Samsung and Nvidia coordinate HBM4 memory and Rubin accelerators, emphasizing integration, production timing, and memory bandwidth for AI infrastructure deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luminar sale approved despite last-minute mystery bid</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/luminar-sale-approved-despite-last-minute-mystery-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087141</guid>
      <description>An unidentified bidder submitted a Hail Mary offer that was "substantially higher" than the winning bid at auction. Founder Austin Russell has been circling a bid, but it's not clear he was behind it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patreon creators have to switch to subscription billing by November, thanks to Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/patreon-creators-have-to-switch-to-subscription-billing-by-november-thanks-to-apple-203759852.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05720d3d-ef66-4e85-b7fd-998ade177cb9</guid>
      <description>Patreon creators will need to make some changes soon, thanks to Apple. On Wednesday, Patreon said Apple has renewed its requirement that all Patreon creators must move to subscription billing. The deadline to do so is November 1, 2026.Patreon's blog post announcing the change made it clear that it had no other choice. "We strongly disagree with this decision," the company wrote. "Creators need consistency and clarity in order to build healthy, long-term businesses. Instead, creators using legacy billing will now have to endure the whiplash of another policy reversal &#8212; the third such change fro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s the Company That Sold DHS ICE&#8217;s Notorious Face Recognition App</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/mobile-fortify-face-recognition-nec-ice-cbp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a4a933b7691dd83eb451d</guid>
      <description>Immigration agents have used Mobile Fortify to scan the faces of countless people in the US&#8212;including many citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Might Be Back on the &#8216;Gundam&#8217; Movie, Again</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/gundam-movie-legendary-netflix-deal-2000715137</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715137</guid>
      <description>After its own plans for a live-action take on the iconic mecha anime fell apart, the streamer could be back on board to distribute Legendary's reworked plans for 'Gundam.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Doomsday Clock Is Now 85 Seconds to Midnight. Here&#8217;s What That Means</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-doomsday-clock-is-now-85-seconds-to-midnight-heres-what-that-means/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a41af092cf43348dff594</guid>
      <description>Catastrophic risks are increasing, cooperation is declining, and swift action is needed from global leaders to correct course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX Won&#8217;t Go Public Until the Planets Literally Align, Sources Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spacex-wont-go-public-until-the-planets-literally-align-sources-say-2000715151</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715151</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&#8217;s aerospace company is reportedly targeting a mid-June IPO because there will be a spectacular planetary alignment that month. Yes, really.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I used Claude to vibe-code my wildly overcomplicated smart home</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/869318/claude-vibe-coding-home-assistant-smart-home</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=869318</guid>
      <description>I am not, by any definition, a coder, but when I started seeing people's vibe-coded smart home projects all over my social feeds this month, I was intrigued. From a "master command center" built on a Lutron system to AI controlling a smart oven, people were unleashing AI in their smart homes, using Claude Code [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Spartacus: House of Ashur episode 9 on Starz?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/spartacus-house-of-ashur-episode-9-release-date-time-starz</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dwTToFwseUj3XZEmRH59f</guid>
      <description>After last week's shock death, Spartacus: House of Ashur episode 9 could be the calm before the finale storm. But when does it air on Starz?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview : ce que la mission de Sophie Adenot va changer pour la recherche&#8230; et pour nous</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sophie-adenot-interview-ce-mission-sophie-adenot-va-changer-recherche-nous-130417/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:57:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/sophie-adenot-interview-ce-mission-sophie-adenot-va-changer-recherche-nous-130417/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Dans quelques jours ou semaines, Sophie Adenot partira dans la Station spatiale internationale (ISS). Lors de son s&#233;jour, elle aura de nombreuses exp&#233;riences &#224; mener dans le cadre de sa mission Epsilon, dont des exp&#233;riences fran&#231;aises con&#231;ues depuis le Cnes, &#224; Toulouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The entry-level Samsung Galaxy Buds FE are on sale for $30 off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/868870/samsung-galaxy-buds-fe-kindle-paperwhite-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T14:52:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868870</guid>
      <description>If past timing is any indication, Samsung is likely to hold its next Unpacked event in late February. However, we&#8217;re not expecting the company to shake up its earbuds lineup until the summer &#8212; the winter keynote is typically reserved for smartphone announcements &#8212; which makes today&#8217;s discount on the Galaxy Buds FE far more [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Winter Storm Fern Slowed Down the Bitcoin Network</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-winter-storm-fern-slowed-down-the-bitcoin-network-2000715094</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715094</guid>
      <description>When an immutable blockchain meets unstoppable force of nature.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
