<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:04:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s supposedly &#8216;leaked&#8217; Super Bowl ad with ear buds and a shiny orb was a hoax</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/875615/openai-super-bowl-ai-hardware-leak-hoax-fake</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-08T23:54:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875615</guid>
      <description>As if OpenAI didn't have enough drama around the Super Bowl and advertising, as the game wound down, word spread of a "leaked" ad that actually wasn't leaked at all; it was just a fake. Screenshots of a now-deleted Reddit thread told the tale of a frustrated employee who, while posting about how upset they [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Point USA&#8217;s Halftime Show Was Exactly What You&#8217;d Expect</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/turning-point-usas-halftime-show-was-exactly-what-youd-expect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698124ce8ce44d82662e9276</guid>
      <description>&#8220;The All-American Halftime Show," born out of outrage over Bad Bunny's Super Bowl performance, fell short of the hype. From Kid Rock&#8217;s poor lip synching to Erika Kirk being MIA, it was simply dull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 replay &#8212; how to watch Patriots vs Seahawks full game and highlights for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/super-bowl-2026-replay</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Efpi5RS29zsDGi4go2do6Q</guid>
      <description>Super Bowl 2026 sees the New England Patriots face the Seattle Seahawks. Here's everything you need to know to watch Super Bowl LX full-game replays and highlights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 Gatorade shower color: What it was and why people want to know</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/super-bowl-gatorade-shower-color</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07FUDITLpeM1lT62gkRwhjM</guid>
      <description>Football fans are betting on the Gatorade shower color. What color was it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Super Bowl movie trailers: See the best trailers of 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-super-bowl-movie-trailers-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05YcN8I3rOR09XRmuAawB1D</guid>
      <description>A round-up of the best trailers released during the Super Bowl. Watch them all now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Super Bowl commercials in 2026: See the ads now</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-super-bowl-commercials-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06oVDwK8Xjc0SjJfOFHllFA</guid>
      <description>Super Bowl LX is in the books, but you can relive the best commercials now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2026: How to watch, schedule of events, and everything else you need to know about the Winter Games</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/olympics-2026-how-to-watch-schedule-of-events-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-the-winter-games-172409755.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eca0487b-e039-4319-89d0-8969baa49f32</guid>
      <description>


  The Milano Cortina 2026 Winter Olympics are coming up. (Mattia Ozbot/Getty Images)
 

  Mattia Ozbot via Getty Images
 

The 2026 Winter Olympics are taking place in Italy this year, with all the action taking place in Milan and the Alpine city of Cortina. This year marks the fourth time Italy has hosted the Winter Games; most recently, Turin hosted in 2006. Of the 16 sports that will be featured at the Winter Olympics, there will be 15 returning favorites, including figure skating, Alpine skiing, curling, ice hockey, speedskating, snowboarding, freestyle skiing and ski jumping, and one e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump breaks silence on Bad Bunnys Super Bowl Halftime Show</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/donald-trump-reacts-bad-bunny-super-bowl-halftime-show</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00rpBJJaalQsL0AvXO7qCXF</guid>
      <description>Shocker: Donald Trump didn't like Bad Bunny's Super Bowl Halftime Show.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
