<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:40:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung corrige enfin le plus gros d&#233;faut des &#233;crans pliants</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2930627_samsung-corrige-enfin-le-plus-gros-defaut-des-ecrans-pliants</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2930627_samsung-corrige-enfin-le-plus-gros-defaut-des-ecrans-pliants</guid>
      <description>
Samsung profite du CES 2026 pour d&#233;voiler la nouvelle version de ses &#233;crans pliables sans la caract&#233;ristique pliure centrale avec le Galaxy Z Fold 8.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the new Lego Smart Brick actually do? Here are 3 ways it seriously upgrades your models</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/what-does-the-new-lego-smart-brick-actually-do-here-are-3-ways-it-seriously-upgrades-your-models</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fNagC3ritZEfZP82dvZFMH</guid>
      <description>Like the look of the Lego Smart Brick? These are the key things you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TP-Link brings an AI assistant to its smart home and home networking apps</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854017/tp-link-brings-an-ai-assistant-to-its-smart-home-and-home-networking-apps</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854017</guid>
      <description>Tapo, the smart home brand owned by networking giant TP-Link, is launching an AI assistant at CES this year - because isn't everyone? Aireal is designed to "bring AI into real life" (geddit?), according to the company, and will help you "understand your home, quickly fix Wi-Fi issues and control your devices using natural language." [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus announces new ROG Flow Z13-KJP gaming tablet, along with a stunning collection of gaming accessories in collaboration with Kojima Productions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/asus-announces-new-rog-flow-z13-kjp-gaming-tablet-along-with-a-stunning-collection-of-gaming-accessories-in-collaboration-with-kojima-productions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Bu4yegnmQrmdvMVRxqxisF</guid>
      <description>Asus Republic of Gamers (ROG) has announced its brand new ROG Flow Z13-KJP gaming tablet launching mid-late Q1 2026, along with a collection of limited-edition accessories designed in collaboration with Kojima Productions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP price is on the rise today as crypto markets show early signs of a rebound: Here are 2 reasons why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469658/xrp-price-rising-today-2-reasons-why-crypto-token-going-up</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T13:17:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469658/xrp-price-rising-today-2-reasons-why-crypto-token-going-up</guid>
      <description>After struggling to gain ground since last summer, the token is outpacing Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies this week, likely for a few reasons. 
Popular cryptocurrency XRP had a lackluster 2025, starting the year at around $2.32 per token while finishing at around the $1.84 mark. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing your BlackBerry? The Clicks Communicator brings back the physical keyboard &#8211;and a 3.5mm headphone jack</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/android/missing-your-blackberry-the-clicks-communicator-brings-back-the-physical-keyboard-and-a-3-5mm-headphone-jack</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UaRRTixYDd2eSrRaMVApZU</guid>
      <description>A physical keyboard, a headphone jack, a microSD card slot... what year are we in again?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta reporte le lancement en France de ses nouvelles lunettes Ray-Ban Display</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/meta-reporte-le-lancement-en-france-de-ses-nouvelles-lunettes-ray-ban-display.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318401</guid>
      <description>Il faudra prendre son mal en patience pour porter des Ray-Ban Display en France. Meta a en effet annonc&#233; le report du lancement international de ses lunettes connect&#233;es avec &#233;cran, &#224; l'heure actuelle uniquement commercialis&#233;es aux &#201;tats-Unis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Microslop' is heading for Edge &#8211; major browser redesign is inspired by Copilot, and it's already seriously unpopular</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/microslop-is-heading-for-edge-major-browser-redesign-is-inspired-by-copilot-and-its-already-seriously-unpopular</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zUL52JmaTDFi4GNZrizNc5</guid>
      <description>Revamped browser design is symptomatic of a bigger problem that Microsoft is facing here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;Europe tient-elle son miracle ? Voici la batterie solide qui promet 273 ans de dur&#233;e de vie</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2931023_leurope-tient-elle-son-miracle-voici-la-batterie-solide-qui-promet-273-ans-de-duree-de-vie</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2931023_leurope-tient-elle-son-miracle-voici-la-batterie-solide-qui-promet-273-ans-de-duree-de-vie</guid>
      <description>
On nous promet la batterie solide "pour bient&#244;t" depuis dix ans. Et l&#224;, surprise : une start-up finlandaise affirme que c'est pr&#234;t, l&#224;, tout de suite, sur une moto. Avec une dur&#233;e de vie quasi-infinie de 100 000 cycles. L'annonce est impressionnante, mais elle soul&#232;ve plus de questions qu'elle ne donne de r&#233;ponses.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a subscription-free Whoop band? This screenless rival could be the voice-led wearable you&#8217;re looking for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/looking-for-a-subscription-free-whoop-band-this-screenless-rival-could-be-the-voice-led-wearable-youre-looking-for</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5Azvr7BWm4Rt6ZT4csUvsS</guid>
      <description>Luna has launched a new fitness wearable at CES 2026 that comes with no subscription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#8217;s &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Land Is Serving Up a New Shade of Milk</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-star-wars-land-pink-milk-2000705825</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705825</guid>
      <description>Blue milk made sense. Green milk fit too. But now, starting this week, there's pink milk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway's Navimow brand unveiled a new line of robotic lawn mowers at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/segways-navimow-brand-unveiled-a-new-line-of-robotic-lawn-mowers-at-ces-2026-130007014.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b8854e-85cc-4e08-aee8-992000b9a41f</guid>
      <description>Segway, the maker of Steve Wozniak's favorite mode of self-balancing transport, has released a new series of robotic lawn mowers under its Navimow brand, designed for all manner of Roomba-esque mowing action. The lineup includes four residential series and was unveiled at CES 2026.
Navimow's lineup includes the flagship X4 Series for large yards up to 1.5 acres in size. Its AWD system can handle slopes up to 40 degrees and it sports dual 180-watt cutting motors. The largest mode, the X450 will retail for $3,000. A smaller X430 rated for yards up to 1 acre will go for $2,500.
The Navimow i2 ser...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugreen is expanding into AI-powered smart home surveillance</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/846789/ugree-syncare-indoor-outdoor-cameras-ai-doorbell</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846789</guid>
      <description>Ugreen announced at CES 2026 that it'll be branching into smart home territory with the launch of its SynCare product line of cameras. The series will consist of two indoor cams, the ID500 Pro and ID500 Plus, the OD600 Pro outdoor cam, and the Video Doorbell DB600 Pro. All of this gear will launch in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chamberlain&#8217;s new smart lock will lock your door and shut your garage upon spotting a stranger</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851622/chamberlain-myq-secure-view-smart-lock-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851622</guid>
      <description>Chamberlain is expanding its closed smart home ecosystem with a new lock that doubles as a 2K HDR video doorbell. Announced at CES 2026, the myQ Secure View 3-in-1 Smart Lock costs $279.99 and uses face detection to automatically lock or unlock your door depending on who's approaching. For this to work, you and your [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugreen is now selling an AI NAS with more RAM than my desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/852453/ugreen-ai-nas-idx6011-pro-photo-search</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852453</guid>
      <description>A decade ago, Google Photos changed photo storage for me forever - because I could search for those photos just by typing a few words. But that meant trusting Google cloud servers with my precious memories. Now, a new breed of network-attached storage (NAS) boxes promises to do the same and more with local AI, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsair fit a whole Stream Deck into its new gaming keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854886/corsair-galleon-100-sd-elgato-stream-deck-specs-price-launch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854886</guid>
      <description>Elgato's Stream Deck has come full circle. Almost eight years after the company picked up the pieces of Art Lebedev's ambitious Optimus keyboard and went in a different, cheaper direction with the idea, we're going back to keyboards. Corsair's Galleon 100 SD, announced at CES 2026, is a wired mechanical keyboard that effectively has a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway&#8217;s new e-bikes are impressively high-tech and delightfully low-cost</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/855025/segway-e-bikes-myon-muxi-xaber-300-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855025</guid>
      <description>After causing a splash at last year's CES with a pair of high-tech, high-powered e-bikes, Segway returned to the show with a little something more for everyone. The Ninebot-owned brand announced two new e-bikes - the seemingly conventional-looking Myon, and the low-step, short-tail Muxi - as well as a sharp-looking electric dirt bike called the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugreen launches a smart home security platform at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/ugreen-launches-a-smart-home-security-platform-at-ces-130000389.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b61f0e10-971e-4d0f-a261-02969862e042</guid>
      <description>Ugreen makes plenty of things, but you&#8217;re probably familiar with the name in the context of its NAS systems (should that be NASes? Who knows). Naturally, the company has turned up to CES 2026 with the former, but it&#8217;s also branching out into home security. It&#8217;s announcing SynCare, an AI infused all-in-one surveillance platform which, it rather boldly claims, will become an &#8220;attentive, integrated guardian&#8221; of your home.Leading the pack is the SynCare Video Doorbell with head-to-toe 4K video, intelligent detection and 24/7 recording &#8212; especially if you&#8217;ve got it hooked up to your Ugreen NAS. Tha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segway launches two more e-bikes at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/segway-launches-two-more-e-bikes-at-ces-130000152.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6228cc32-3766-4468-b41d-98a5e95f02c7</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m no psychologist, but I get a sense Segway turned up to CES 2026 with something to prove after last year. Certainly, it&#8217;s gone out of its way to prove its micromobility bona fides with the press, who perhaps were a bit too sniffy that scooter people were launching an e-bike. This year, Segway&#8217;s not just launching two more mainstream e-bikes, but an electric dirt bike, all of which are crammed with the sort of tech that might just make everyone halt their sniffiness.First up, there&#8217;s the Myon, a chunky step-through with a decent-sized pannier rack for folks who want to go far and carry a bit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR, transmission int&#233;grale et pentes de 84 % : ces tondeuses ultra compl&#232;tes sont pr&#234;tes &#224; affronter les jardins ultra-complexes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robots-tondeuses/2926531_lidar-transmission-integrale-et-pentes-de-84-ces-tondeuses-ultra-completes-sont-pretes-a-affronter-les-jardins-ultra-complexes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robots-tondeuses/2926531_lidar-transmission-integrale-et-pentes-de-84-ces-tondeuses-ultra-completes-sont-pretes-a-affronter-les-jardins-ultra-complexes</guid>
      <description>
Oubliez la simple guerre des c&#226;bles p&#233;rim&#233;triques, c'est d&#233;sormais de l'histoire ancienne. Pour ce CES 2026, Segway Navimow passe &#224; la vitesse sup&#233;rieure en injectant des technologies de pointe, LiDAR, IA et transmission int&#233;grale, dans pas moins de quatre nouveaux robots. De la petite pelouse de ville aux terrains de football, la marque veut tout automatiser.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Devenir astronaute, c&#8217;est repousser les limites &#187; : Sophie Adenot pr&#234;te pour une mission hors norme dans l'espace</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-devenir-astronaute-cest-repousser-limites-sophie-adenot-prete-mission-hors-norme-espace-129827/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-devenir-astronaute-cest-repousser-limites-sophie-adenot-prete-mission-hors-norme-espace-129827/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le premier vol de Sophie Adenot approche &#224; grands pas. L'astronaute fran&#231;aise doit partir &#224; bord de la station spatiale internationale le 15 f&#233;vrier prochain. Lors d'une conf&#233;rence de presse, elle a partag&#233; ses impressions et se dit pr&#234;te et impatiente de relever ce d&#233;fi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta hits pause on Ray-Ban Display expansion plans</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/856216/meta-ray-ban-display-smart-glasses-international-expansion-paused</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T07:46:32-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=856216</guid>
      <description>International customers who had their sights set on Meta's Ray-Ban Display smart glasses will have to wait a little longer. Meta announced that it's pausing plans to launch the glasses in France, Italy, Canada, and the UK by early 2026, due to "unprecedented demand and limited inventory." "Since launching last fall, we've seen an overwhelming [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch ASB Classic 2026 in Auckland: live stream WTA tennis online, start time, what TV channel?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tennis/asb-classic-2026-auckland-wta-tennis</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rhmAU86PhM6BojXGGDi7KU</guid>
      <description>Watch free trial tennis streams today in the season's first WTA event from Auckland, New Zeland &#8211; 2026 ASB Classic TV channels, broadcasters and streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Performance defines the PC experience&#8217; &#8212; Samsung aims to take down Apple with its new Galaxy Book6 laptops and Intel&#8217;s latest tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/performance-defines-the-pc-experience-samsung-aims-to-take-down-apple-with-its-new-galaxy-book6-laptops-and-intels-latest-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27LeeQiXgPmu4gsiZ4yKK8</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s new Galaxy Book6 laptops "combine unparalleled speed and power with dependable AI" &#8211; could these be the MacBook-killers PC users have been waiting for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ways to walk for fitness, from rucking to the viral 'Japanese walking' trend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/7-ways-to-walk-for-fitness-from-rucking-to-the-viral-japanese-walking-trend</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UFnHx6Kx3PvVp9ZD3UEok9</guid>
      <description>7 walking workouts you need to know about, from beginner-friendly, low-impact routines to tougher sweat sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Suunto 9 Peak Pro &#224; -60 % : une montre id&#233;ale pour les sportifs au budget serr&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930427_la-suunto-9-peak-pro-a-60-une-montre-ideale-pour-les-sportifs-au-budget-serre</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930427_la-suunto-9-peak-pro-a-60-une-montre-ideale-pour-les-sportifs-au-budget-serre</guid>
      <description>
Propos&#233;e &#224; seulement&#160;199 euros&#160;au lieu de 499 euros, la Suunto 9 Peak Pro devient une vraie bonne affaire et se trouve &#234;tre un choix malin pour les runners et traileurs au budget serr&#233;. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free fait le m&#233;nage&#160;: pourquoi vous pouvez d&#233;sinstaller Freebox Connect d&#232;s aujourd&#8217;hui</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/free-fait-le-menage-pourquoi-vous-pouvez-desinstaller-freebox-connect-des-aujourdhui.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318382</guid>
      <description>C'&#233;tait dans l'air, c'est d&#233;sormais officiel : Free fusionne Freebox Connect avec son application principale. Gestion du Wi-Fi, factures et contr&#244;le parental sont enfin r&#233;unis dans une interface unique et simplifi&#233;e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three new JBL gaming headsets are on the way and one of them is crammed with high-end features</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/three-new-jbl-gaming-headsets-are-on-the-way-and-one-of-them-is-crammed-with-high-end-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i5MEBtJrh4AmtzfFNxVz5V</guid>
      <description>JBL has revealed three new gaming headsets coming to the US this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birdbuddy's new smart bird feeder can ID birds by their songs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/birdbuddys-new-smart-bird-feeder-can-id-birds-by-their-songs-122000692.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5b28b23-f82e-4bdb-881b-cbece313aa42</guid>
      <description>I&#8217;m seeing a ton of smart bird feeders again this year at CES &#8212; and I&#8217;m inexplicably drawn to them. Perhaps because the idea of birds nibbling on seeds and flying away represents a natural purity and freedom that doesn&#8217;t exist within the halls of CES. Birdbuddy was one of the first smart bird feeder brands, with a wildly successful Kickstarter back in 2020. And this year, they&#8217;ve added birdsong to their species identification capabilities. Two new feeders, the Birdbuddy 2 and the Birdbuddy 2 Mini both have the new feature, but the latter is a more affordable, starter version. The Bird Buddy 2 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bose is giving away free Ultra Open earbuds &#8212; heres how to get a pair</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-5-bose-ultra-open-earbuds-free-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02cot66VEjbDluZwWSpsvHO</guid>
      <description>Bose is giving away free refurbished Ultra Open earbuds when you buy the QuietComfort Ultra 2 earbuds. Here's how to get the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pok&#233;mon TCG: Mega Evolutions Phantasmal Flames Booster Display Box is down to market value at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-pokemon-tcg-mega-evolutions-phantasmal-flames-booster-box-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03GCmSdqXrJTP00L8mxeTzH</guid>
      <description>The Pok&#233;mon TCG: Mega Evolutions Phantasmal Flames Booster Display Box is on sale for $254.67 at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Bird Feeding Tips for the Peak of Bird Watching Season (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/our-best-tips-for-winter-bird-feeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69307bd10c11887cee72a781</guid>
      <description>Winter is often the best time for bird-watching at bird feeders&#8212;here&#8217;s what ornithologists recommend to get the most out of the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla met &#224; jour le Model Y : &#233;cran 16 pouces et int&#233;rieur noir pour tous, enfin presque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2930995_tesla-met-a-jour-le-model-y-ecran-16-pouces-et-interieur-noir-pour-tous-enfin-presque</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2930995_tesla-met-a-jour-le-model-y-ecran-16-pouces-et-interieur-noir-pour-tous-enfin-presque</guid>
      <description>
Vous en avez marre de voir la Chine servir de laboratoire pour Tesla ? Moi aussi. Le constructeur vient de mettre &#224; jour silencieusement tous ses Model Y produits &#224; Shanghai. Au menu : la disparition tant attendue du ciel de toit gris et un &#233;cran 16 pouces bien plus s&#233;rieux. Et nous ? On regarde les photos.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta has delayed the international rollout of its display glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-has-delayed-the-international-rollout-of-its-display-glasses-120056833.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3132a727-43db-414f-8c5e-b8a6c0276dc2</guid>
      <description>Meta is pausing release of its Ray-Ban Display smart glasses to the UK, France, Italy and Canada due to "unprecedented demand and limited inventory," the company said on Monday at CES 2026. There's no new date for the expansion that was originally set for early 2026. "We'll continue to focus on fulfilling orders in the US while we re-evaluate our approach to international availability," Meta wrote on its blog.
Since Meta's display glasses first went on sale, acquiring them has been a challenge. They're not available online and can only be found in a limited number of retail outlets including s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timekettle Reveals a Major Upgrade to Its Real-Time, In-Ear AI Translation Technology at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/timekettles-real-time-in-ear-ai-translation-tech-just-got-a-massive-upgrade-2000705424</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705424</guid>
      <description>The Babel fish real-time translator is becoming a reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clarke, the Comet in &#8216;Greenland,&#8217; Wasn&#8217;t Actually Named After the Sci-Fi Legend</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/clarke-the-comet-in-greenland-wasnt-actually-named-after-the-sci-fi-legend-2000705684</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705684</guid>
      <description>Sorry, '2001: A Space Odyssey' fans, but the cosmic menace in the Gerard Butler disaster series has a more ordinary inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta's EMG wristband is moving beyond its AR glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/metas-emg-wristband-is-moving-beyond-its-ar-glasses-120000503.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">917ebb29-267e-4f45-824a-1ae21cbc52a1</guid>
      <description>Meta has been experimenting with EMG technology for years. In 2025, the company commercialized it for the first time in its Meta Ray-Ban Display glasses, which users control via a dedicated neural band that is able to interpret subtle muscle movements in the wrist.Now, at CES 2026, the company is offering its first look at how its neural band could be used to control devices outside of its smart glasses lineup. Meta has teamed up with Garmin, as well as a handful of research partners, to explore some intriguing use cases for its wrist-based controller.The social media company has previously wo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum computing momentum grows: D-Wave announces first major breakthrough of 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469364/d-wave-quantum-computing-first-major-breakthrough-of-2026-scalable-technology</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T12:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469364/d-wave-quantum-computing-first-major-breakthrough-of-2026-scalable-technology</guid>
      <description>D-Wave, one of the industry&#8217;s rising stars, is continuing to make progress toward scalable quantum technology.
A new year, a new quantum computing breakthrough: D-Wave, one of the quantum industry&#8217;s rising stars, announced &#8220;an industry-first breakthrough&#8221; on Tuesday as it works to make quantum computing commercially viable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI says 40 million people use ChatGPT for healthcare every day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/openai/openai-says-40-million-people-use-chatgpt-for-healthcare-every-day</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zsw9vNjeVXbWi8yyqqBGcY</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's latest report states that 40 million people use ChatGPT for health-related questions every day. Should we be worried?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Kimmel gives a 13-minute recap of everything Trump did over the holidays</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/jimmy-kimmel-trump-holiday-recap</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07DVGWXIYtAu8sOibgLVR5e</guid>
      <description>Jimmy Kimmel has recapped everything Donald Trump did over the holidays, including the U.S. attack on Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit your fitness goals with the Fitbit Sense 2, now $60 off at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-6-fitbit-sense-2-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04PVC4OmusiwPvAQlc3apKQ</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 6, the Fitbit Sense 2 is on sale at Amazon for $189.95. This limited-time deal saves you 24% off its list price of $249.95.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung just revealed the first creaseless foldable screen &#8211; and it could be a serious hint towards the iPhone Fold</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/samsung-just-revealed-the-first-creaseless-foldable-screen-and-it-could-be-a-serious-hint-towards-the-iphone-fold</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NZidFuT49QwvHKW8LUZnye</guid>
      <description>Samsung has shown off a foldable screen that appears to have no crease at all, and it's likely to be used by the foldable iPhone.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
