<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:31:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Fictional &#8216;Star Trek&#8217; Sports</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-fake-sports-calica-starfleet-academy-2000713435</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713435</guid>
      <description>After this week's episode of 'Starfleet Academy' introduced official phaser tag into 'Trek' canon, we take a look back at 60 years of boldly sporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asus will no longer add new mobile phone models in the future': CEO confirms no more Zenfone or ROG smartphones are coming as it pivots to focus on AI products</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/asus-will-no-longer-add-new-mobile-phone-models-in-the-future-ceo-confirms-no-more-zenfone-or-rog-smartphones-are-coming-as-it-pivots-to-focus-on-ai-products</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tcCk3rymzCRpLNn9gN338o</guid>
      <description>Asus halts new smartphone production amid shrinking margins, competition, and longer upgrade cycles, shifting focus toward AI servers and related hardware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers say Russian government hackers were behind attempted Poland power outage</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/researchers-say-russian-government-hackers-were-behind-attempted-poland-power-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085628</guid>
      <description>Security researchers have attributed the attempted use of destructive "wiper" malware across Poland's energy infrastructure in late December to a Russian-backed hacking group known for causing power outages in neighboring Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro handheld maker Anbernic has a new gamepad with a screen and heart rate sensor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/retro-handheld-maker-anbernic-has-a-new-gamepad-with-a-screen-and-heart-rate-sensor-201651899.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a54b6574-f246-4f91-a418-69fb2409cbfc</guid>
      <description>File this one under "Things that make you go, 'Hmmm&#8230;'" Retro handheld maker Anbernic is launching a new controller with a screen. But unlike Nintendo's Wii U controller, there's no second-screen gaming capability here. Instead, the display is designed to "make customization intuitive and effortless." Oh, and the controller also has a heart rate sensor. Because, hey, if you're going weird, I say fully commit!The Anbernic RG G01 has a 2.5-inch HD display that the company describes as an "HD smart screen." The idea is to remap buttons, program macros and change other settings without requiring so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Kills Standard Autopilot as It Pushes Buyers to Subscription-Based Option</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-kills-standard-autopilot-as-it-pushes-buyers-to-subscription-based-option-2000713524</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713524</guid>
      <description>If it wasn't bad enough that Elon Musk manufactured your car, it's getting worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched the first trailer for &#8216;The Muppet Show&#8217; &#8212; and it looks like the inspirational, celebrational, muppetsational comeback fans have been waiting for when it comes to Disney+</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/i-watched-the-first-trailer-for-the-muppet-show-and-it-looks-like-the-inspirational-celebrational-muppetsational-comeback-fans-have-been-waiting-for-when-it-comes-to-disney</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6DpLo5kXtCBpQwNxNhnHpV</guid>
      <description>It's time to put on makeup, it's time to light the lights for a new The Muppet Show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did Davos turn into a tech conference?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/how-did-davos-turn-into-a-tech-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3085516</guid>
      <description>The World Economic Forum&#8217;s annual meeting in Davos&#160;felt different this year, and not just because Meta and Salesforce took over storefronts on the main promenade.&#160;AI dominated the conversation in a way that overshadowed traditional topics like climate change and global poverty, and the CEOs&#160;weren&#8217;t&#160;holding back. There was public criticism of trade policy, warnings about AI [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We&#8217;re going to let VR be what it is&#8217; Meta CTO Andrew Bosworth addresses the major VR layoffs &#8211; and teases a new direction for the metaverse</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/were-going-to-let-vr-be-what-it-is-meta-cto-andrew-bosworth-addresses-the-major-vr-layoffs-and-teases-a-new-direction-for-the-metaverse</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TzPndwamUBhjtviNhK49Ui</guid>
      <description>Meta CTO Andrew Bosworth has explained the company's new approach to VR, the metaverse, and XR glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers broke every AI defense they tested. Here are 7 questions to ask vendors.</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/security/12-ai-defenses-claimed-near-zero-attack-success-researchers-broke-all-of-them</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5kKkMrejOtAGuZyavRmPjA</guid>
      <description>Security teams are buying AI defenses that don't work. Researchers from OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google DeepMind published findings in October 2025 that should stop every CISO mid-procurement. Their paper, "The Attacker Moves Second: Stronger Adaptive Attacks Bypass Defenses Against Llm Jailbreaks and Prompt Injections," tested 12 published AI defenses, with most claiming near-zero attack success rates. The research team achieved bypass rates above 90% on most defenses. The implication for enterprises is stark: Most AI security products are being tested against attackers that don&#8217;t behave like r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Nasa met en sc&#232;ne le retour des Am&#233;ricains sur la Lune comme un film&#8230; et le message est clair</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/artemis-ii-artemis-ii-nasa-devoile-retour-vers-lune-comme-bande-annonce-cinema-130502/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:57:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/artemis-ii-artemis-ii-nasa-devoile-retour-vers-lune-comme-bande-annonce-cinema-130502/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>La Nasa a publi&#233; une nouvelle vid&#233;o de pr&#233;sentation d&#8217;Artemis II et le ton est r&#233;solument spectaculaire. En moins d&#8217;une minute, images grandioses, musique dramatique et r&#233;f&#233;rences &#224; Apollo transforment le retour des humains vers la Lune en v&#233;ritable trailer de science-fiction, au service d&#8217;une...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Are Poised to Hit a Mathematical Wall, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ai-agents-are-poised-to-hit-a-mathematical-wall-study-finds-2000713493</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713493</guid>
      <description>LLMs have their limits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is stopping teens from chatting with its AI characters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866906/meta-teens-ai-characters-stop-block-new-version</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T14:50:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866906</guid>
      <description>Meta is "temporarily pausing" the ability for teens to chat with its AI characters as it develops a "new version" of the characters that will offer a "better experience." The company made the announcement in an update to a blog post from October where the company had detailed more parental controls for teen AI use. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is Very Deliberately Told Entirely From Dunk&#8217;s POV</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-interview-dunk-2000713458</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713458</guid>
      <description>Showrunner Ira Parker explained the series' stylistic approach, which stays true to the way George R.R. Martin's novella is written.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#8217;s Next Moon Rocket Runs on Shuttle Engines&#8212;Here&#8217;s the Story Behind Each One</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasas-next-moon-rocket-runs-on-shuttle-engines-heres-the-story-behind-each-one-2000713485</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713485</guid>
      <description>SLS is ready to fly and will feature three shuttle-era engines that have already flown to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From privacy screens to variable apertures and beyond, how likely are these Samsung Galaxy S26 series rumors?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/from-privacy-screens-to-variable-apertures-and-beyond-how-likely-are-these-samsung-galaxy-s26-series-rumors</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">scjmE9kb2XJ4PuNotJ3YWM</guid>
      <description>I've rated all the biggest Samsung Galaxy S26 series rumors to tell you how likely I think they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How America&#8217;s WHO exit could affect flu shots, outbreaks, and future pandemics</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480154/how-americas-who-exit-could-affect-flu-shots-outbreaks-and-future-pandemics</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T19:20:38</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480154/how-americas-who-exit-could-affect-flu-shots-outbreaks-and-future-pandemics</guid>
      <description>The WHO played a quiet but critical role in how the U.S. prepared for emerging health threats. That connection is now gone.
The U.S. is no longer part of the World Health Organization. After the Trump administration declared its intention to pull the country out of the global public health agency one year ago, on Thursday it formally followed through, ending its commitment to the organization after 78 years....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple will begin showing more App Store ads starting in March</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/apple-will-begin-showing-more-app-store-ads-starting-in-march-192031226.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ef6bd4d-733e-429e-a8fc-c6186fee4583</guid>
      <description>More ads are coming to App Store search results starting in March, Apple shared on an advertising help page. The company first said that it would increase the number of App Store ads last month, and this new rollout of search ads will begin on Tuesday, March 3, according to a developer email viewed by MacRumors."Search is the way most people find and download apps on the App Store, with nearly 65 percent of downloads happening directly after a search," Apple says. "To help give advertisers more opportunities to drive downloads from search results, Apple Ads will introduce additional ads across...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Favorite Earbuds for Most People Are Over 25 Percent Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/nothing-ear-a-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6973ba07d13cc77db79fc8d2</guid>
      <description>These excellent earbuds were already a good deal before the discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What TikTok&#8217;s new owners mean for your feed</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/866868/tiktok-usds-new-owners-algorithm-explained</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T14:10:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866868</guid>
      <description>TikTok is officially under new ownership in the US, and that could spell big changes for the video-sharing app. On January 22nd, ByteDance - TikTok's Chinese parent company - and a group of investors closed a $14 billion deal to spin off the platform's US operations, introducing a new slate of American executives. The Silver [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Lamp Visualizes the Perpetual Electromagnetic Storm in Which We Live</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-lamp-visualizes-the-perpetual-electromagnetic-storm-in-which-we-live-2000713462</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713462</guid>
      <description>"We live surrounded by ghosts of our own making."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Traitors UK S4 finale on BBC iPlayer (it's FREE)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/watch-the-traitors-uk-s4-finale-on-bbc-iplayer-its-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QcbUmsZ7ZZHfAgMjwnjXEi</guid>
      <description>Set up by a cliffhanger involving Faithful James Baker and Traitor Rachel Duffy, here's how to watch The Traitors UK S4 finale on BBC iPlayer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this the future of trading? NYSE reportedly building a venue for 24/7 tokenized stock and EDF settling</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/is-this-the-future-of-trading-nyse-reportedly-building-a-venue-for-24-7-tokenized-stock-and-edf-settling</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UL8TDdmYRGnTyBRqGFUbRA</guid>
      <description>NYSE plans a blockchain-based 24/7 trading platform for tokenized stocks and ETFs with instant settlement and stablecoin support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's cheapest 4K streaming stick just dropped to its lowest price since Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/amazons-cheapest-4k-streaming-stick-just-dropped-to-its-lowest-price-since-black-friday</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dNv4dG6LsC4jRXZmFyr7U7</guid>
      <description>Amazon has slashed the Fire TV Stick 4K Select to its lowest price since Black Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok finalizes deal for its US entity</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/tiktok-finalizes-deal-for-its-us-entity-010543484.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d3cfa14-12c1-47e1-9d03-97449ad65157</guid>
      <description>After years of uncertainty over TikTok's future in the United States, a deal for the app's US business has been finalized. The new US entity is called TikTok USDS Joint Venture. ByteDance has retained a 19.9 percent percent stake in the new business, with the rest controlled by a group of non-Chinese investors, including Oracle, Silver Lake and MGX, an Emirati-state owned investment firm, all of which have a 15 percent stake. Dell CEO Michael Dell and other investors have smaller stakes in the new company.&#160;The terms of the deal were first leaked last month, after TikTok CEO Shou Chew reportedl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette d&#233;couverte pourrait enfin expliquer la naissance des trous noirs g&#233;ants</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/trou-noir-cette-decouverte-pourrait-enfin-expliquer-naissance-trous-noirs-geants-130435/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:58:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/trou-noir-cette-decouverte-pourrait-enfin-expliquer-naissance-trous-noirs-geants-130435/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Ils contiennent entre un million et&#160;plusieurs milliards de masses solaires. Les trous noirs supermassifs sont des enfants de la physique d'Einstein mais, depuis des d&#233;cennies, on a bien du mal &#224; dire comment ils sont n&#233;s et plus encore en raison des derni&#232;res observations du James-Webb. Des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cet &#233;cran gaming incurv&#233; de 34 pouces devient la bonne op&#233;ration de ces soldes d&#8217;hiver gr&#226;ce &#224; une r&#233;duction de pr&#232;s de 50 % par rapport &#224; son prix de lancement</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2952749_cet-ecran-gaming-incurve-de-34-pouces-devient-la-bonne-operation-de-ces-soldes-dhiver-grace-a-une-reduction-de-pres-de-50-par-rapport-a-son-prix-de-lancement</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2952749_cet-ecran-gaming-incurve-de-34-pouces-devient-la-bonne-operation-de-ces-soldes-dhiver-grace-a-une-reduction-de-pres-de-50-par-rapport-a-son-prix-de-lancement</guid>
      <description>
Pour vous immerger au maximum dans vos jeux favoris, comptez sur le MSI MAG 341CQP QD-OLED qui poss&#232;de notamment une dalle incurv&#233;e de 34 pouces. Chez Amazon, vous pourrez le retrouver pour 599 euros contre 1 299,99 euros au moment de son lancement en 2024.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vimeo lays off most of its staff just months after being bought by private equity firm</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/vimeo-lays-off-most-of-its-staff-just-months-after-being-bought-by-private-equity-firm-184556023.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">141850da-dc1d-4c95-b098-d03c49952bba</guid>
      <description>Vimeo just got hit by a brutal round of layoffs, according to a report by Business Insider. Staffers are posting on various social media sites that the layoffs have impacted most of the company, including the entire video team. Vimeo is a video-hosting platform, so that sounds bad.
&#8220;Yesterday, following Vimeo&#8217;s recent acquisition by a private equity firm, I learned that I, along with a large portion of the company, was impacted by layoffs,&#8221; wrote the company&#8217;s former vice president of Global Brand &amp; Creative, Dave Brown. He is referring to a firm called Bending Spoons that bought Vimeo for $1....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla paywalls lane centering on new Model 3 and Model Y purchases</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/tesla-paywalls-lane-centering-on-new-model-3-and-model-y-purchases-184000707.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78d0f273-b3ff-45b7-8e9a-76c3fa45d9fd</guid>
      <description>Tesla just objectively decreased the value of the Model 3 and Model Y. On Thursday, the company said it&#8217;s paywalling its lane-centering feature, Autosteer, for new purchases of the two EVs in the US and Canada. This was previously a standard feature. Lane centering is now part of the Full Self-Driving Supervised (FSD) package, which costs $99 per month.Speculating on why Tesla would do this doesn't require much imagination. Remember the pay package Tesla shareholders approved for Musk in November? One of his requirements for receiving up to $1 trillion is reaching 10 million active FSD subscri...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
