<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:16:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the AMD CES 2026 keynote live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-amd-ces-2026-keynote-live-190012078.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c864a817-a6e7-423f-ab33-fb69dbcbdab4</guid>
      <description>AMD is kicking off CES 2026 on Monday, where it'll cover its latest AI developments and perhaps show off its newest Ryzen chips. The company will outline the full scope of its vision for AI implementations from across the full spectrum of consumer and enterprise applications. The presentation &#8212; which is the lead keynote for CES 2026 &#8212; will be led by CEO Dr. Lisa Su.
We'll tell you how to tune in to the livestream and what else you can expect to see.
How to watch AMD's keynote live
Dr. Su will deliver a keynote speech from the Palazzo Ballroom at the Venetian on Monday, January 5 at 9:30PM ET (...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Gian van Veen vs Gary Anderson: live stream 2026 PDC World Darts Championship semifinal online for *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/gian-van-veen-vs-gary-anderson-2026-pdc-world-darts-championship-semifinal-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wmMzAy8JDptuVonhMfqedA</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch Gian van Veen take on Gary Anderson in the second World Darts Championship semifinal at Ally Pally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman wants to pay some lucky person $555,000 a year to look after OpenAI's AI - but obviously, all is not quite as it seems</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sam-altman-wants-to-pay-some-lucky-person-usd555-000-a-year-to-look-after-openais-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5kr3bcXyCnTuLub7qdP9NL</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is hiring a new head to look after model abuse and safety for $555k plus equity, but it'll be high-stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's base Kindle is $20 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/amazons-base-kindle-is-20-off-right-now-183302484.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9865d5d-82c0-47b4-858f-2d61df88bf8c</guid>
      <description>The latest entry-level Kindle ereader is on sale for $90 via Amazon. This is a nice discount of $20. It's not a record-low price, but it's certainly a budget-friendly way to keep that New Year's resolution to read more.
This made our list of the best ereaders, and for good reason. It's an iconic device that gets the job done. It doesn't have much by way of modern bells and whistles, but it ships with 16GB of storage and comes in two snazzy colorways. 


The build is compact and durable. It's also light, which makes it easy to pack and easy to hold up with one hand. It allows access to the vast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble Revives and Revamps Its Short-Lived Circular Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pebble-revives-and-revamps-its-short-lived-circular-smartwatch-2000704903</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704903</guid>
      <description>If you loved the old Pebble Time Round, the new Round 2 smartwatch is better in every way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble unveils Pebble Round 2 &#8212; and fixes all the original's major pitfalls</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/pebble-unveils-pebble-round-2-and-fixes-all-the-originals-major-pitfalls</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VdhzrXmL8ZpYF5P8ooWXvd</guid>
      <description>Pebble Round 2 is official &#8212; we can't believe we have to wait until May for this huge do-over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, new site: how to launch on a budget this weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/new-year-new-site-how-to-launch-on-a-budget-this-weekend</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">L3c2UzE2s6VcdVW8zQAbET</guid>
      <description>How to create a website on a budget before the end of the first weekend of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India orders Musk&#8217;s X to fix Grok over &#8220;obscene&#8221; AI content</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/02/india-orders-musks-x-to-fix-grok-over-obscene-ai-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079459</guid>
      <description>India's IT ministry has given X 72 hours to submit an action-taken report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickle AR Glasses seem to promise a real-life version of Jarvis. The internet is skeptical.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pickle-ar-glasses-learn-how-you-live-ai-companion</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05uNRlVXEXjncZvhDBvTDTF</guid>
      <description>A startup claims its AI-powered AR glasses can see, remember, and anticipate your life, but skeptics aren't sure the technology is quite ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clicks is bringing its first smartphone and a new keyboard to CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/clicks-is-bringing-its-first-smartphone-and-a-new-keyboard-to-ces-2026-182239003.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93572d3f-045d-4cee-958d-ec3f18a91c2e</guid>
      <description>Clicks is bringing its physical keyboard products to CES yet again, and these are chock full of nostalgia. The company has also unveiled its first smartphone, aimed at "communication, not consumption," that it says will function as a second phone used mostly for messaging.
The phone is dubbed the Clicks Communicator and features a tactile keyboard, a 4-inch OLED display, a 3.5mm headphone jack and expandable microSD storage up to 2TB. The interface is built on Android 16 and supports hardware-level encryption.
Even though Clicks says it wants to leave "content capture" to a users' primary devi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Hisense CES 2026 presentation live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-hisense-ces-2026-presentation-live-jan-5-190040858.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9486b306-eae4-49da-a805-9b5cf78d2fb9</guid>
      <description>Xinhua News Agency via Getty Images
Hisense is typically best known for its affordable electronics and home appliances, from TVs to refrigerators. But at CES 2025, the China-based company showed off its premium side with a massive 136-inch micro LED TV &#8212; now available for a jaw-dropping $100,000. So what's in store for this year's show? New leadership, for starters.
The company has two new hires, including Chief Marketing Officer Sarah Larsen and Chief Commercial Officer James Fishler. In a press release, Hisense said Fishler's experience in home entertainment, appliances and HVAC is important...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Finale Really Tried to Be Everything for Everyone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-stranger-things-finale-really-tried-to-be-everything-for-everyone-2000704739</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704739</guid>
      <description>&#8216;The Rightside Up&#8217; brought the Netflix blockbuster to its end with a blend of action and agony&#8212;plus an epilogue stuffed with hazy happiness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Sales Skid Even With Cheaper Models and Deep Discounts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-sales-skid-even-with-cheaper-models-and-deep-discounts-2000704887</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704887</guid>
      <description>China's BYD is breathing down Elon Musk's neck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung HW-QS760F : cette barre de son 5.1.2 compatible Dolby Atmos et DTS:X a le droit &#224; une ristourne de 100 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925897_samsung-hw-qs760f-cette-barre-de-son-5-1-2-compatible-dolby-atmos-et-dtsx-a-le-droit-a-une-ristourne-de-100-e</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925897_samsung-hw-qs760f-cette-barre-de-son-5-1-2-compatible-dolby-atmos-et-dtsx-a-le-droit-a-une-ristourne-de-100-e</guid>
      <description>
S'il y a bien une chose d'int&#233;ressante pour un t&#233;l&#233;viseur, c'est l'ajout d'une barre de son pour avoir un vrai son spatial. Un syst&#232;me 5.1.2 certifi&#233; Dolby Atmos ajoutera une plus-value &#224; n'importe quel t&#233;l&#233;viseur en manque de voix. La Samsung HW-QS760F comporte toutes les fonctions du moment et aussi un prix qui passe de 749 euros &#224; 649 euros chez Boulanger.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Dreame Matrix10 Ultra : Ce robot utilise des serpilli&#232;res diff&#233;rentes selon les pi&#232;ces</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robot-aspirateur/2912253_test-du-dreame-matrix10-ultra-ce-robot-utilise-des-serpillieres-differentes-selon-les-pieces</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/robot-aspirateur/2912253_test-du-dreame-matrix10-ultra-ce-robot-utilise-des-serpillieres-differentes-selon-les-pieces</guid>
      <description>
Avec le Matrix10 Ultra, Dreame innove gr&#226;ce &#224; un robot ultra performant capable de commuter automatiquement entre trois jeux de serpilli&#232;res. Il peut ainsi utiliser des serpilli&#232;res chaudes pour la plupart des sols et les parquets, d'autres en poils de nylon pour la cuisine, et enfin un troisi&#232;me jeu absorbant pour les salles d'eau. Dans ce test complet, voyons si cette approche est vraiment efficace par rapport aux robots laveurs classiques.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Super Flu&#8217; Is Hitting Kids Hard&#8212;and Some Aren&#8217;t Surviving</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-super-flu-is-hitting-kids-hard-and-some-arent-surviving-2000704822</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704822</guid>
      <description>Several states have reported their first pediatric flu deaths this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 useful gadgets for your first apartment</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/02/10-useful-gadgets-for-your-first-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3072282</guid>
      <description>From home security systems and smart smoke detectors to a sunrise alarm gently that wakes you up, here are the must-have gadgets for living in your first apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Nvidia CES 2026 keynote</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/how-to-watch-nvidia-ces-2026-keynote-address</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03MuSrHqKu6v9zfoBO1lzjd</guid>
      <description>The tech world will be tuning in to see Nvidia's CES keynote speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last chance to get Prime Video add-on streaming deals for Paramount+, Starz, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-2-prime-video-add-on-streaming-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04pObdhmCSFy1np6v8xCX56</guid>
      <description>Prime Video add-on streaming deals for Paramount+, Mubi, Starz, and more are still live through the end of the day on Jan. 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Awesome Games Done Quick 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/how-to-watch-awesome-games-done-quick-2026-174938687.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2ad6b11-1f3a-4024-a8a5-44ad7e848062</guid>
      <description>It's time for more speedrunning (and other shenanigans) with the Games Done Quick (GDQ) crew. The first event of the year, Awesome Games Done Quick (AGDQ), kicks off on Sunday, January 4, with Super Mario Sunshine. Donations for this year's shindig will benefit the Prevent Cancer Foundation.AGDQ 2026 has a whole week of 24/7 speedruns on tap. You'll see slots for some of 2025's biggest games: Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, Hollow Knight: Silksong and Hades II are part of the festivities. Metal Gear Solid Delta: Snake Eater gets both a standard run and a "versus" showdown. There's also plenty of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New year, new vibes: Get up to 80% off luxe vibrators at Le Wand</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-2-le-wand-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00OJ4db2UoC5cXf4Xb8HHgU</guid>
      <description>Score up to 80% off luxury vibrators and 60% off bundles during the Le Wand New Year sale. Deals start as low as $5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the first-ever Lego CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/how-to-watch-the-first-ever-lego-ces-2026-press-conference-live-monday-130005336.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02a28a6-f21c-46c9-a5e0-dcff1b13d26a</guid>
      <description>picture alliance via Getty Images
The Lego Group is set to host its very first press conference at CES 2026 &#8212; but exactly what it plans to unveil is still under wraps. The iconic toy brick maker has offered no clues about what's on the agenda, leaving speculation wide open, from new video games to Formula 1 race cars.
Here's how you can watch Lego's presentation at CES, along with what we think the company could reveal.
How to watch The Lego Group's CES 2026 press conference
The Lego CES press conference is scheduled for Monday, January 5 at 1PM ET. While Lego and the Consumer Technology Assoc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips from pharmacists to lower your out-of-pocket&#160;drug costs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461547/prescription-drug-costs-tips-pharmacists</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T17:45:18</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461547/prescription-drug-costs-tips-pharmacists</guid>
      <description>Beyond coupons and assistance programs, you can try direct-to-consumer platforms and cash-payment models.
Even when Americans have health insurance, they can have a hard time affording the drugs they&#8217;ve been prescribed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save some money on your heating bills with the Google Nest Learning Thermostat at its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-2-google-nest-learning-thermostat-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">031NcM8lApj7s3VhKOcXXde</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 2, get the Google Nest Learning Thermostat at its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX Will Move Thousands of Starlinks Closer to Earth in 2026. Here&#8217;s Why</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spacex-will-move-thousands-of-starlinks-closer-to-earth-in-2026-heres-why-2000704872</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704872</guid>
      <description>The reconfiguration will reduce the orbital altitude of nearly half of the Starlink megaconstellation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette cam&#233;ra 2K &#224; double objectif est une solution tr&#232;s abordable pour surveiller l&#8217;int&#233;rieur de votre domicile gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925559_cette-camera-2k-a-double-objectif-est-une-solution-tres-abordable-pour-surveiller-linterieur-de-votre-domicile-grace-a-cette-offre</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925559_cette-camera-2k-a-double-objectif-est-une-solution-tres-abordable-pour-surveiller-linterieur-de-votre-domicile-grace-a-cette-offre</guid>
      <description>
La s&#233;curit&#233; a un prix et chez Boulanger, il est de 64,99 euros gr&#226;ce &#224; la cam&#233;ra Ezviz H7C et ses deux objectifs qui suppriment tous les angles morts pr&#233;sents dans une pi&#232;ce.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG made up a new word for its next ultralight Gram laptops: 'Aerominum'</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lg-made-up-a-new-word-for-its-next-ultralight-gram-laptops-aerominum-172323577.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">660d691d-b86e-4c25-ac0e-3bb9024697e8</guid>
      <description>LG just announced some new Gram AI laptops ahead of CES 2026. These are incredibly portable laptops that the company says are the "lightest in their class." This is largely thanks to a proprietary material that LG has dubbed Aerominum.
This material reportedly "reduces the laptop's weight while reinforcing" structural strength. In other words, these computers are both light and durable. Each model offers improved scratch resistance, while providing a "sleek metallic finish." The laptops have also been designed to meet military-grade durability standards.
The AI in the name refers to the inclus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla loses title as world&#8217;s biggest electric carmaker</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468534/tesla-loses-title-as-worlds-biggest-electric-car-maker</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T17:19:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468534/tesla-loses-title-as-worlds-biggest-electric-car-maker</guid>
      <description>Tesla sales have dropped for a second year in row.
Tesla lost its crown as the world&#8217;s bestselling electric vehicle maker on Friday as a customer revolt over&#160;Elon Musk&#8217;s right-wing politics, expiring U.S. tax breaks for buyers, and stiff overseas competition pushed sales down for a second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney World Employee Injured by Runaway &#8216;Indiana Jones&#8217; Boulder</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-world-indiana-jones-boulder-accident-video-2000704890</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704890</guid>
      <description>You don't have to be a professor of archaeology to become the victim of a rolling boulder trap these days.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
