<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:19:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Focused work in a distracted world &#8212; my one secret weapon for staying on task</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/lola</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7p3wzraAwVoLfyrbZan2JR</guid>
      <description>Homescreen Heroes: Lola is a low-fidelity music solution to high-frequency distractions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms &#8212; stream Game of Thrones prequel from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GLozMH7VryZoLUbQGJCSM5</guid>
      <description>Westeros returns with a smaller, character-driven tale. Here&#8217;s how you can watch A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms online and from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Fujifilm X-T30 III : un petit bo&#238;tier &#224; moins de 1000 &#8364; qui filme en 6K comme un grand</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fujifilm/2944897_test-du-fujifilm-x-t30-iii-un-petit-boitier-a-moins-de-1000-e-qui-filme-en-6k-comme-un-grand</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fujifilm/2944897_test-du-fujifilm-x-t30-iii-un-petit-boitier-a-moins-de-1000-e-qui-filme-en-6k-comme-un-grand</guid>
      <description>
Le Fujifilm X-T30 III marque le retour d'une s&#233;rie qu'on croyait remplac&#233;e. Quatre ans apr&#232;s le X-T30 II et l'arriv&#233;e du X-T50 et son capteur de 40 MP, Fujifilm ressuscite sa ligne X-T30 avec un processeur X-Processor 5 et des capacit&#233;s vid&#233;o 6K. Un bo&#238;tier d'entr&#233;e de gamme qui tape au-dessus de sa cat&#233;gorie. Mais il y a des compromis.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face &#224; la crise, ce SSD NVMe M.2 4 To aux performances premium pour PC et PS5 est plus cher que d&#8217;habitude, mais &#231;a sera encore pire apr&#232;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944877_face-a-la-crise-ce-ssd-nvme-m-2-4-to-aux-performances-premium-pour-pc-et-ps5-est-plus-cher-que-dhabitude-mais-ca-sera-encore-pire-apres</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944877_face-a-la-crise-ce-ssd-nvme-m-2-4-to-aux-performances-premium-pour-pc-et-ps5-est-plus-cher-que-dhabitude-mais-ca-sera-encore-pire-apres</guid>
      <description>
On le sait, c'est la crise de la m&#233;moire vive et du stockage : pour autant, Cdiscount propose le SSD WD_Black SN7100 4 To pour 399,99 euros au lieu de 799,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three months of Audible is on sale for $3 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/three-months-of-audible-is-on-sale-for-3-right-now-193859793.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>Have a hankering for some audiobooks? Audible is holding one heck of a sale right now, giving users three months of access for $3. That's a dollar per month. This is something of a winter tradition for the Amazon-owned platform and the promotion ends on January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated titles. Think of it like N...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This UGreen 3-in-1 wireless charger is 32 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/this-ugreen-3-in-1-wireless-charger-is-32-percent-off-right-now-214707378.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc4c398-0e79-409e-bf43-095a0740d354</guid>
      <description>You can easily spruce up your nightstand or desk by decluttering a bit, replacing some of those annoying charging cables with a good wireless charging setup. One of our favorites that can handle three devices at once is the UGREEN MagFlow Qi2 3-in-1 Charger Station 25W. Normally $140, it's on sale right now for $95; that's 32 percent off and only about $5 more than its record-low price.


This is our top pick for a 3-in-1 charging pad thanks to its versatility. The UGREEN can work equally well as a permanent fixture in your home or act as a portable charging station. It boasts a foldable desig...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disclosure of Aliens Could Cause a Bitcoin Rush, Former Bank of England Analyst Says</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-disclosure-of-aliens-could-cause-a-bitcoin-rush-former-bank-of-england-analyst-says-2000711471</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711471</guid>
      <description>She warned of "extreme price volatility in financial markets due to catastrophising or euphoria, and a collapse in confidence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington is the latest state pursuing an age verification law for porn sites</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/washington-is-the-latest-state-pursuing-an-age-verification-law-for-porn-sites-174423529.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e41e4a87-0fb9-438f-9be1-e6f6d924d592</guid>
      <description>Washington state residents may soon be forced to produce IDs before getting onto websites with pornographic content. Within the state's House of Representatives, Rep. Mari Leavitt introduced House Bill 2112, which is informally known as the Keep Our Children Safe Act. Similar to the initiatives seen in other states, the bill proposes to restrict access to "online sexual material harmful" to anyone under 18.
In practical terms, those living in Washington state could see websites asking for digital identification or demanding the user go through an age verification system that requests a governm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This may be the reason why Netflix ditched wireless casting &#8211; but Google is still backing the tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/this-may-be-the-reason-why-netflix-ditched-wireless-casting-but-google-is-still-backing-the-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jK3p7RGiamFCUayFU9nvRc</guid>
      <description>Netflix dropping Google Cast support for modern Google TV devices may be because it wasn't being used much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Zootopia 2&#8217; Is Hollywood&#8217;s Biggest Animated Movie Ever</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/zootopia-2-is-the-biggest-animated-movie-ever-2000711544</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711544</guid>
      <description>The world has had 'Zootopia 2' fever for months, and now it's broken the biggest milestone for animated movies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
