<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:22:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes Leveled up in 2025&#8212;Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Coming&#160;Next</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/deepfakes-leveled-up-in-2025-heres-whats-coming-next-2000703649</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703649</guid>
      <description>Fake images, videos, and audio files crossed the &#8220;indistinguishable threshold" this year. Where do we go from here?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York State will require warning labels on social media platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/new-york-state-will-require-warning-labels-on-social-media-platforms-210306716.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">800eb432-6e82-4126-a6ad-b50b196bae7b</guid>
      <description>The State of New York will now require social media platforms to display warning labels similar to those found on cigarettes. The bill was passed by the New York Legislature in June and signed into law by Gov. Kathy Hochul on Friday. It will apply to any platforms that feature infinite scrolling, auto-play, like counts or algorithmic feeds. The labels will caution those on the platform about potential harm to young users' mental health.
Social media companies will be required to display these warning labels when a user first interacts with any of the features the state considers predatory. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've been a Windows user for over 15 years &#8212; these are the 7 key things to check on a new gaming PC</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/ive-been-a-windows-user-for-over-15-years-these-are-the-7-key-things-to-check-on-a-new-gaming-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WF4Yuma9VL6VAkuiw2pENR</guid>
      <description>If you just landed a new gaming PC, these are the most important things to do before you game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Star Jamie Campbell Bower on Playing Vecna&#8217;s Variations</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-star-jamie-campbell-bower-on-playing-vecnas-variations-2000703553</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703553</guid>
      <description>The actor behind Vecna, Henry, and Mr. Whatsit breaks down his complex role in season five.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle&#8217;s AI Push Is Leading to Its Worst Quarter Since 2001</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oracles-ai-push-is-leading-to-its-worst-quarter-since-2001-2000703605</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703605</guid>
      <description>Delayed AI infrastructure projects, rising debt, and weaker-than-expected earnings are reviving dot-com-era fears on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG&#8217;s Monstrous 52-Inch 5K Gaming Monitor Will Swallow Up Your Desk</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lgs-monstrous-52-inch-5k-gaming-monitor-will-swallow-up-your-desk-2000703616</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703616</guid>
      <description>Bigger is better, right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a knob! Startup shoves circular controller in tiny laptop dock to create perfect desktop companion &#8212; shame you have to wait four months to get it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/what-a-knob-startup-shoves-circular-controller-in-tiny-laptop-dock-to-create-perfect-desktop-companion-shame-you-have-to-wait-four-months-to-get-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XAnb8LVKYxpwnt46rctwoc</guid>
      <description>HubKey Pro 2 is a crowdfunded circular controller with fully customizable keys and a dual-4K multi-functional hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What we listened to in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/music/what-we-listened-to-in-2025-201308584.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dcacbf8-c8f4-4944-b5c8-3117aa1edf32</guid>
      <description>If streaming services&#8217; year-in-review campaigns have shown us anything, it&#8217;s that we&#8217;ve spent a staggering amount of time drowning out the hum of everyday life with music, podcasts and audio series. And with some incredible new releases this year, we were really eatin&#8217; good. Here are some of the Engadget team&#8217;s favorite things we listened to in 2025.Spiritbox - Tsunami SeaI became aware of Spiritbox in late 2024 shortly before the band dropped its latest album, Tsunami Sea. At the time, I was in a deep Sleep Token phase, and I don&#8217;t remember how I stumbled upon Spiritbox, but I&#8217;m sure glad I d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starlink Rival Launches Its Largest Satellite Yet for Space-Based Cellular Network</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starlink-rival-launches-its-largest-satellite-yet-for-space-based-cellular-network-2000703460</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703460</guid>
      <description>AST SpaceMobile wants to launch up to 60 of its satellites in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just unwrapped a new laptop? These are the perfect accessories under $70 I recommend you get</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/laptops/just-unwrapped-a-new-laptop-these-are-the-perfect-accessories-under-usd70-i-recommend-you-get</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">A9pAzHgaPgmdzSdmrz6jTn</guid>
      <description>Got a new laptop for Christmas? These are the must-have accessories I recommend to everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As flu cases surge, doctors say there&#8217;s more than one way to treat it</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467284/as-flu-cases-surge-doctors-say-theres-more-than-one-way-to-treat-it</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T19:56:18</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467284/as-flu-cases-surge-doctors-say-theres-more-than-one-way-to-treat-it</guid>
      <description>From generic Tamiflu to IV treatments used in hospitals, flu medication prices vary wildly depending on how and where they&#8217;re given.
As cases of a new, highly contagious &#8220;super flu&#8217;&#8221; surge across the nation this holiday season, more and more Americans are looking for ways to treat the symptoms, which include everything from fever and chills,&#160;to headaches and vomiting.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. demand for graphite renews amid battery boom</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467310/graphite-mining-us-demand-renews-battery-boom-china</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T19:43:53</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467310/graphite-mining-us-demand-renews-battery-boom-china</guid>
      <description>The Department of Energy has said the need for graphite is critical, and the Department of the Interior lists it as one of 60&#160;&#8216;critical minerals.&#8217;
Graphite mines in the United States largely closed down seven decades ago. Mining the ubiquitous mineral found in everything from nuclear reactors to pencils seemed to make little sense when it could be imported inexpensively from other nations, especially China....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the &#8216;Demon Slayer&#8217; Studio Broke Laws of Anime Physics to Bring &#8216;Infinity Castle&#8217; Fights to Life</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/demon-slayer-infinity-castle-anime-ufotable-trilogy-akaza-tanjiro-2000703501</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 19:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703501</guid>
      <description>Ufotable digs into the technical and artistic magic that propelled the film's generational battle between Tanjiro and Akaza.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
