<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:28:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders federal agencies to drop Anthropic services amid Pentagon feud</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/trump-orders-federal-agencies-to-drop-anthropic-services-amid-pentagon-feud-222029306.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dbf0d01-bed8-4724-80e0-86c32ff84976</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump has ordered all US government agencies to stop using Claude and other Anthropic services, escalating an already volatile feud between the Department of Defense and company over AI safeguards. Taking to Truth Social on Friday afternoon, the president said there would be a six-month phase out period for federal agencies, including the Defense Department, to migrate off of Anthropic's products.&#160;&#8220;The Leftwing nut jobs at Anthropic have made a DISASTROUS MISTAKE trying to STRONG-ARM the Department of War, and force them to obey their Terms of Service instead of our Constituti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minisforum MS-S1 Max Mini Workstation, with AMD Ryzen AI Max+ 395 processor, 128GB LPDDR5 RAM and 2TB SSD is almost half price right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/minisforum-ms-s1-max-mini-workstation-with-amd-ryzen-ai-max-395-processor-128gb-lpddr5-ram-and-2tb-ssd-is-almost-half-price-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TwuAWRczsydVQQnwC3Q9gA</guid>
      <description>Powered by the AMD Ryzen AI Max+ 395, the MS-S1 Max is built for intensive multitasking and demanding professional workloads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA just released a whole heap of smart new kitchen lighting and storage solutions &#8212; with prices starting at just $2</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/ikea-just-released-a-whole-heap-of-smart-new-kitchen-lighting-and-storage-solutions-with-prices-starting-at-just-usd2</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RU6fx9tqQhaJ3q72K3cS8G</guid>
      <description>It's the perfect time to start spring cleaning and brighten up your cooking space with these bargain storage and lighting options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new Stuff Your Kindle Day is live for 1 day only &#8212; score dark romance books for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/stuff-your-kindle-day-dark-romance-books-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07E480Z455ePSP3dXuQjTgM</guid>
      <description>The latest Stuff Your Kindle Day is live on Feb. 28. Indulge in the Darkness is offering free dark romance books for one day only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $20 lifetime ad blocker gives the whole family a more peaceful internet experience</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-27-adguard-family-plan-lifetime-subscription</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02fYYdu7Rma3cZhXpeKd9Yv</guid>
      <description>Give your family a more peaceful internet experience with this lifetime subscription to AdGuard Family Plan, on sale now for just $19.97 through March 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount agrees to buy Warner Bros. Discovery, pays Netflix $2.8 billion for breakup</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/paramount-agrees-to-buy-warner-bros-discovery-pays-netflix-28-billion-for-breakup-215936514.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">868aa77b-0e56-4b37-af60-1b569fcf2e5a</guid>
      <description>Paramount Skydance and Warner Bros. Discovery are officially merging. The studio paid Netflix the $2.8 billion termination fee it was owed for breaking its original deal to buy Warner Bros. earlier today, and the historic film studio has now formally accepted Paramount&#8217;s offer.Along with the deal, which values Warner Bros. Discovery at $31 per share, Paramount is making several commitments to assuage the fears of regulators and the entertainment community. Those include a guarantee that the new company will produce 30 theatrical films annually, that theatrical releases will have a minimum 45-d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Deals Can Have You Zipping Around on a New E-Scooter This Spring</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/electric-scooters-spring-deals-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a1ce0651e2b656613d587c</guid>
      <description>With spring just around the corner, now's the smart time to snag an electric scooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate &#8216;Boner&#8217; Syrup Recalled for Actually Containing Viagra Ingredient</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chocolate-boner-syrup-recalled-for-actually-containing-viagra-ingredient-2000727848</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727848</guid>
      <description>This week, Lockout Supplements issued a voluntary recall of its "Boner Bears Chocolate Syrup" for having unlabeled amounts of sildenafil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Trump orders federal agencies to stop using Anthropic after Pentagon dispute</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/27/president-trump-orders-federal-agencies-to-stop-using-anthropic-after-pentagon-dispute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3098106</guid>
      <description>"We don't need it, we don't want it, and will not do business with them again," the president wrote in the post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Discovery agrees to $110 billion Paramount merger</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/886478/warner-bros-discovery-paramount-merger-agreement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T16:43:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=886478</guid>
      <description>Warner Bros. Discovery and Paramount Skydance's merger agreement is now official. On Friday, the two companies announced plans to merge into a massive media company that will fold WBD's studio, linear channels, streaming service, and gaming segment into Paramount. Though WBD initially signed onto an $83 billion agreement to merge part of Warner Bros. with [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says US Is Cutting Off Anthropic for Refusing to Drop AI Safeguards</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-threatens-criminal-consequences-for-anthropic-over-ai-safety-guard-fight-2000727947</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727947</guid>
      <description>The President said the AI startup is filled with "leftwing nut jobs."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Moves to Ban Anthropic From the US Government</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-moves-to-ban-anthropic-from-the-us-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a093144a77d405a1150272</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump&#8217;s sudden order comes after the Defense Department pressured Anthropic to drop restrictions on how its AI can be used by the military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders federal agencies to drop Anthropic&#8217;s AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/886489/pentagon-anthropic-trump-dod</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T16:30:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=886489</guid>
      <description>On Friday afternoon, Donald Trump posted on Truth Social, accusing Anthropic, the AI company behind Claude, of attempting to "STRONG-ARM" the Pentagon and directing federal agencies to "IMMEDIATELY CEASE" use of its products. At issue is Anthropic CEO Dario Amodei's refusal of an updated agreement with the US military agreeing to "any lawful use" of [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#8217;s Talk About the Ending of &#8216;Scream 7&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lets-talk-about-the-ending-of-scream-7-2000727690</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727690</guid>
      <description>Who is Ghostface? What was their objective? Did any of it make sense? Let's dig in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch The Turkish Detective from anywhere &#8211; it's *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/the-turkish-detective-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vkqiePUjj6WMuQcExFWtPA</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch The Turkish Detective online from anywhere in the world, completely FREE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Modernizing a COBOL system once required armies of consultants spending years mapping workflows... AI changes this': Anthropic says AI could help keep COBOL running for a long time to come &#8212; but IBM won't be happy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/modernizing-a-cobol-system-once-required-armies-of-consultants-spending-years-mapping-workflows-ai-changes-this-anthropic-says-ai-could-help-keep-cobol-running-for-a-long-time-to-come-but-ibm-wont-be-happy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">L3pjUimzePXCt3JA3Taat6</guid>
      <description>AI now allows engineers to modernize complex COBOL systems efficiently, automating code analysis, testing, and incremental implementation for long-term operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter Mission Captures Rare Shot of Interstellar Comet 3I/Atlas on Its Way Out</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jupiter-probe-spots-interstellar-comet-spewing-gas-and-dust-2000727797</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727797</guid>
      <description>The JUICE mission snapped photos of Comet 3I/Atlas after surviving its closest approach to the Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Roku Is $20 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/roku-ultra-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a1de67a1f07be8b2d1f004</guid>
      <description>The Roku Ultra isn&#8217;t just speedier, it also offers some advanced features that some viewers will find really handy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tech Elite Aren&#8217;t on the Secret Guest List at Bohemian Grove: Report</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-tech-elite-arent-on-the-secret-guest-list-at-bohemian-grove-report-2000727408</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727408</guid>
      <description>A leaked list of Bohemian Grove camp attendee list shows some surprising guests and a noticeable absence of tech titans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Films and Shows You Should Be Streaming in March 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-films-and-shows-you-should-be-streaming-in-march-2026-2000726198</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 20:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726198</guid>
      <description>We've picked out the best horror, sci-fi, and genre titles coming to Netflix, Hulu, Disney+, and beyond.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
