<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:35:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>January's PS Plus Monthly Games include Need for Speed Unbound and Disney Epic Mickey: Rebrushed</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/januarys-ps-plus-monthly-games-include-need-for-speed-unbound-and-disney-epic-mickey-rebrushed-182335673.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0abd41e-aa15-43e4-9207-23de76881669</guid>
      <description>Sony has revealed the first batch of PlayStation Plus Monthly Games for 2026. There are three titles to play this month, all of which drop on January 6. As always, you&#8217;ll retain access to these games as long as your subscription remains active.

First up, there's Need For Speed Unbound. This is a racing game that came out at the tail-end of 2022 and was the first entry in the franchise for several years before that. It has a unique visual style, thanks to cel-shaded graphics, with all kinds of vehicles to choose from. There are street racing challenges, weekly qualifiers and a minigame that ha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This SmarterMail vulnerability allows Remote Code Execution - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/this-smartermail-vulnerability-allows-remote-code-execution-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sK6asFAvDaCFCkgzJwYuC7</guid>
      <description>A maximum-severity flaw was just patched, and users are urged to apply the fix immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From robovacs for small homes to a Roomba for your lawn, here are 4 things we can expect to see from iRobot &#8211; according to the CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/from-robovacs-for-small-homes-to-a-roomba-for-your-lawn-here-are-4-things-we-can-expect-to-see-from-irobot-according-to-the-ceo</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oNDgjRWsu8qaPHr2wX3Hgf</guid>
      <description>Exclusive: There are some intriguing plans for the original robot vacuum brand following recent company takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 10 Most Anticipated Movies of Early 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/our-10-most-anticipated-movies-of-early-2026-2000702768</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702768</guid>
      <description>Sam Raimi, Pixar, Ghostface, and Ryan Gosling all check in with big movies in the next three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got a 4K Blu-ray player for Christmas? Here are 6 discs I've tested that should get you started</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/got-a-4k-blu-ray-player-for-christmas-here-are-6-discs-ive-tested-that-should-get-you-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XsdsGc64MKkn5aqvW3L4sR</guid>
      <description>If you're just getting into the world of 4K Blu-ray, I've picked 6 discs you should buy to kickstart your collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG reveals its version of Samsung's Frame TV &#8212; but the screen tech might not be what you're hoping for</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/lg-reveals-its-version-of-samsungs-frame-tv-but-the-screen-tech-might-not-be-what-youre-hoping-for</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yPrcTykgMmR2i8KESontwm</guid>
      <description>LG's Gallery TV doesn't have OLED: it's a mini-LED TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a USPS rule change could impact election ballots in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468030/how-a-usps-rule-change-could-impact-election-ballots-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T17:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468030/how-a-usps-rule-change-could-impact-election-ballots-in-2026</guid>
      <description>Many states rely on postmarks to validate ballots&#8212;but that system is about to change.
It&#8217;s the sort of thing you might not notice until it really matters, but the U.S. Postal Service recently changed how it defines the &#8220;postmark&#8221; on a piece of mail&#8212;warning that the postmark date is not a reliable indicator of when you actually mailed something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the LG press conference at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-lg-press-conference-at-ces-2026-190159474.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6eb7981-0913-4e7b-bd66-4bc9abdcb17b</guid>
      <description>LG
For years, LG has kicked off CES press day with the first event of the morning &#8212; and 2026 will be no different. The Korea-based corporation is theming its presentation as  "Innovation in Tune with You," and &#8212; if it follows the template of past presentations &#8212; it will highlight both the consumer electronics and large appliance sides of its mammoth global businesses.
Like nearly all tech-centric events these days, expect AI to be the binding theme of the LG presentation at CES 2026. Just be aware that, like Apple, LG has its own customized abbreviation for AI: "Affectionate Intelligence." The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay true to your New Years cleaning resolutions with $150 off the Dyson Ball Animal 3 vacuum</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-31-dyson-ball-animal-3-vacuum-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002VXBXSinXBT24fIntjC4V</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 31, save $150 on the the Dyson Ball Animal 3 vacuum at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: What to expect when tech's biggest conference starts on January 4</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ces-2026-what-to-expect-when-techs-biggest-conference-starts-on-january-4-120000189.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2645ab40-20b1-4cf0-bdcf-9e9656c79061</guid>
      <description>The new year is upon us, and that means CES 2026 is imminent. The biggest tech trade show of the calendar comes with a bevy of new and notable announcements that set the tone for trends and expectations for the subsequent 12 months. The CES 2026 show floor is officially open from January 6 through 9, but the fun kicks off with events on Sunday January 4, followed by a host of press conferences on Monday. As always, product demos, announcements and networking will be happening at the Las Vegas Convention Center and other hotels all over the city. As usual, Engadget will be covering the event in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Away from 2025's biggest and best, here's what we actually played most this year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/away-from-2025s-biggest-and-best-heres-what-we-actually-played-most-this-year</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">k2DaPZY5uJD969cPPNprpB</guid>
      <description>Away from the big ones of 2025, here&#8217;s what we&#8217;ve actually been playing this year, from older multiplayer games to timeless classics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $10 deal that makes taking down the Christmas tree less depressing</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-31-christmas-tree-storage-bag-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03o2NrobhoLl4ufZPqdfAR8</guid>
      <description>Whether you take your tree down on New Year's or Candlemas, this 47% off ZOBER storage bag deal at Amazon makes the cleanup easy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Phone (3a) Pro + Buds 2a : le pack immanquable &#224; -30% pour finir l&#8217;ann&#233;e en beaut&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2889977_nothing-phone-3a-pro-buds-2a-le-pack-immanquable-a-30-pour-finir-lannee-en-beaute</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2889977_nothing-phone-3a-pro-buds-2a-le-pack-immanquable-a-30-pour-finir-lannee-en-beaute</guid>
      <description>
&#192; 429 euros au lieu de 629 euros, ce pack Nothing Phone (3a) Pro + Buds 2a s&#8217;impose comme l&#8217;une des meilleures affaires de cette fin d&#8217;ann&#233;e, avec un excellent smartphone milieu de gamme et des &#233;couteurs sans fil avec ANC pour un prix canon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 fitness apps to help with your 2026 New Year&#8217;s resolutions</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/2026-new-years-resolutions-fitness-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04gQjKPnLzrRnx78xNEvgpc</guid>
      <description>Fitness and wellness apps for your 2026 New Year's resolutions &#8212; if you even have them &#8212; including Strava, Hevy, habit tracker, calm, and Apple Fitness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy has unlocked iPhones for up to $180 off in rare sale</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-31-unlocked-apple-iphone-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00OXr8UPX9hz2OkSihGGvJS</guid>
      <description>You can get a new, unlocked Apple iPhone 14, 15, 16, 16e, or 16 Plus at Best Buy for up to $180 off in its year-end sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors predict AI&#160;is coming for labor in 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/31/investors-predict-ai-is-coming-for-labor-in-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078821</guid>
      <description>The exact impact AI will have on the enterprise labor market is unclear but investors predict trends will start to emerge in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm up with these space heater deals from Vornado, Shark, Dreo, and more that take up to $150 off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-31-space-heater-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0705rh7wALD9miy7YBTs1nq</guid>
      <description>Save up to $150 on space heaters at Amazon from brands like Vornado, Shark, Dreo, Lasko, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
