<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:22:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung and Sandisk are set to integrate rival HBF technology into AI products from Nvidia, AMD, and Google within 24 months, and that's a huge deal</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/samsung-and-sandisk-are-set-to-integrate-rival-hbf-technology-into-ai-products-from-nvidia-amd-and-google-within-24-months-and-thats-a-huge-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WGHr9VHwSLPbf5B8LP9Cnc</guid>
      <description>HBF stacks multiple 3D NAND dies to provide high-capacity, high-bandwidth memory for AI accelerators, complementing HBM for GPUs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress doesn&#8217;t seem to know if the TikTok deal complies with its law</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866977/tiktok-deal-congress-china</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T17:08:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866977</guid>
      <description>TikTok finally closed a deal meant to bring it into compliance with the law that should have banned it a year ago, and the lawmakers who passed that law still don't seem to know what's going on. The company announced Tuesday that its US service is now part of the separate TikTok USDS Joint Venture [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Appears to Have Moved Its Robotaxi Safety Monitors to a More Sneaky Location</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-appears-to-have-moved-its-robotaxi-safety-monitors-to-a-more-sneaky-location-2000713566</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713566</guid>
      <description>Just what everyone wants, their own personal tail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audeze is upgrading its legendary LCD headphones range with its new SLAM tech for silky bass &#8212; these promise 'mastering-grade precision', with a price to match</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/headphones/audeze-lcd-5s-with-slam</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HCKwaMqnDzJ93FCvFFRdU8</guid>
      <description>Audeze makes its highly acclaimed planars even more desirable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo probed by National Transportation Safety Board over illegal school bus behavior</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/waymo-probed-by-national-transportation-safety-board-over-illegal-school-bus-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085535</guid>
      <description>The NTSB joins the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in investigating Waymo vehicles illegally passing stopped school buses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Photos can now turn you into a meme</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-photos-can-now-turn-you-into-a-meme-213930935.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84b0ee39-a76c-455a-881d-868a3836dde6</guid>
      <description>In Big Tech's never-ending quest to increase AI adoption, Google has unveiled a meme generator. The new Google Photos feature, Me Meme, lets you create personalized memes starring a synthetic version of you.Google describes Me Meme as "a simple way to explore with your photos and create content that's ready to share with friends and family." You can choose from a variety of templates or "upload your own funny picture" to use in their place.The feature isn't live for everyone yet, so you may not yet have access to it. (A Google representative told TechCrunch that the feature will roll out to An...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now That &#8216;Sinners&#8217; Broke Oscars Records, Warner Bros. Really Wants You to See It in Theaters Again</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sinners-oscars-record-imax-rerelease-2000713578</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713578</guid>
      <description>Ryan Coogler's extremely nominated vampire sensation will give audiences yet another chance to experience it in 70mm IMAX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Pepper used a TikTok creator&#8217;s jingle. Now everyone wants to get in on the act</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480175/dr-pepper-used-a-tiktok-creators-jingle-now-everyone-wants-to-get-in-on-the-act</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-23T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480175/dr-pepper-used-a-tiktok-creators-jingle-now-everyone-wants-to-get-in-on-the-act</guid>
      <description>TikTok creator Romeo Bingham made up a new jingle for Dr. Pepper that was so good the soda company used it in a TV ad. Now other TikTok creators are flooding the app with their own jingles to have the same thing happen to them.
For the first time in Dr Pepper&#8217;s 140-year history, the brand is the second-most-popular soda in America. Now it has a shiny new jingle to match.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Is Now Collecting Even More Data About Its Users. Here Are the 3 Biggest Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-new-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6973cbc9a24600323e658444</guid>
      <description>According to its new privacy policy, TikTok now collects more data on its users, including their precise location, after majority ownership officially switched to a group based in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Reportedly Turned Over BitLocker Encryption Keys to the FBI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsoft-reportedly-turned-over-bitlocker-encryption-keys-to-the-fbi-2000713550</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713550</guid>
      <description>Microsoft claims it receives about 20 requests for BitLocker keys a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm not sure anyone expected this - an unlikely new entrant enters the flash drive market, and it's one for true Raspberry Pi fans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/im-not-sure-anyone-expected-this-an-unlikely-new-entrant-enters-the-flash-drive-market-and-its-one-for-the-true-raspberry-pi-fans</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CUfj8aXQantZvF4M6j949K</guid>
      <description>The Raspberry Pi Flash Drive is a compact USB 3.0 device offering fast speeds, durability, and flexibility for Pi projects..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rippling/Deel corporate spying scandal may have taken another wild turn</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/the-rippling-deel-corporate-spying-scandal-may-have-taken-another-wild-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085598</guid>
      <description>The Department of Justice may be conducting a criminal investigation. This is arguably the biggest drama between two HR startups ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta hits pause on its AI characters for teens</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/meta-ai-characters-teens</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04bidRAwEelRpBKIePM4aeu</guid>
      <description>Meta's AI characters are no longer accessible to Teen Account users &#8212; but the company says they'll be back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I watched Disneyland Handcrafted &#8212; and it&#8217;s the kind of documentary you want to rewatch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/i-watched-disneyland-handcrafted-and-its-the-kind-of-documentary-you-want-to-rewatch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">StrBTqDMXYM72kYiPfQE28</guid>
      <description>Using raw archival footage restored with the Walt Disney Archives, Disneyland Handcrafted &#8211; directed by Leslie Iwerks and now streaming on Disney+ and YouTube &#8211; explores how Disneyland was built and why the ideas behind the original park still matter today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch UFC 324 for FREE</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/theres-a-sneaky-way-to-watch-ufc-324-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZsLKK7RH4LXWsoFancKZ6K</guid>
      <description>We uncovered a sneaky way to watch UFC 324 for FREE &#8211; from anywhere in the world, without coughing up for a Premium streaming subscription. Here's the trick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rival smart glasses company is suing Meta over its Ray-Ban products</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/a-rival-smart-glasses-company-is-suing-meta-over-its-ray-ban-products-205000997.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5998982e-0cd6-462c-a0ee-418106e6e5d6</guid>
      <description>Meta is being sued by Solos, a rival smart glasses maker, for infringing on its patents, Bloomberg reports. Solos is seeking "multiple billions of dollars" in damages and an injunction that could prevent Meta from selling its Ray-Ban Meta smart glasses as part of the lawsuit.Solos claims that Meta's Ray-Ban Meta Wayfarer Gen 1 smart glasses violate multiple patents covering "core technologies in the field of smart eyewear." While less well known than Meta and its partner EssilorLuxottica, Solos sells multiple pairs of glasses with similar features to what Meta offers. For example, the company'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behold, the Lego x Crocs footwear collab that dreams are made of</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/lego-crocs-announce-partnership</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00Yz3GZlwDNhIVthQbCPlAc</guid>
      <description>Lego and Crocs announced the launch of a multi-year partnership with the launch of the new Lego Brick Clogs. Find out how to buy the collectible Crocs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Prep for This Weekend&#8217;s Big Winter Storm: Power, Heat, and Underwear</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-prep-for-a-winter-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6972acf52144cba86fd9342f</guid>
      <description>Bitter cold, power outages, and impassible roads are a terrible cocktail. Here&#8217;s how to prep and bunker in for an extreme winter storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about Netflix&#8217;s landmark acquisition of Warner Bros.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/23/what-to-know-about-netflixs-landmark-acquisition-of-warner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085519</guid>
      <description>Learn more about Netflix's acquisition of Warner Bros., considered the most historic megadeal in Hollywood, as it continues to develop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Fictional &#8216;Star Trek&#8217; Sports</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-fake-sports-calica-starfleet-academy-2000713435</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713435</guid>
      <description>After this week's episode of 'Starfleet Academy' introduced official phaser tag into 'Trek' canon, we take a look back at 60 years of boldly sporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asus will no longer add new mobile phone models in the future': CEO confirms no more Zenfone or ROG smartphones are coming as it pivots to focus on AI products</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/asus-will-no-longer-add-new-mobile-phone-models-in-the-future-ceo-confirms-no-more-zenfone-or-rog-smartphones-are-coming-as-it-pivots-to-focus-on-ai-products</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tcCk3rymzCRpLNn9gN338o</guid>
      <description>Asus halts new smartphone production amid shrinking margins, competition, and longer upgrade cycles, shifting focus toward AI servers and related hardware.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
