<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:27:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Instacart Says It Is Pulling the Plug on Its AI-Powered Price Tests</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/instacart-says-it-is-pulling-the-plug-on-its-ai-powered-price-tests-2000702649</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702649</guid>
      <description>After an investigation found some customers were charged nearly 25% more for identical items, Instacart says it&#8217;s ending its controversial price-testing program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite the &#8216;M3GAN&#8217; Sequel&#8217;s Big Bust, Blumhouse Notched a Billion-Dollar Year for Horror</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/despite-the-m3gan-sequels-big-bust-blumhouse-notched-a-billion-dollar-year-for-horror-2000702585</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702585</guid>
      <description>Even with a so-so showing for 'M3GAN 2.0,' the Blumhouse-Atomic Monster alliance ended up having a fantastic 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration suspends 5 offshore wind projects, citing national security risks</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465120/trump-administration-suspends-5-offshore-wind-projects-east-coast</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465120/trump-administration-suspends-5-offshore-wind-projects-east-coast</guid>
      <description>Wind supporters called the administration&#8217;s actions illegal.
The Trump administration on Monday suspended leases for five large-scale offshore wind projects under construction along the East Coast due to what it said were national security risks identified by the Pentagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount renews bid for Warner Bros, ensuring $40 billion Larry Ellison backing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/paramount-renews-bid-for-warner-bros-ensuring-40-billion-larry-ellison-backing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078323</guid>
      <description>It's the latest attempt by one major Hollywood superpower to acquire another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ fans express disappointment in Nicki Minaj after she appears with Erika Kirk at Turning Point USA event</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91464983/nicki-minaj-erika-kirk-turning-point-usa-queer-fans-express-disappointment</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T19:47:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91464983/nicki-minaj-erika-kirk-turning-point-usa-queer-fans-express-disappointment</guid>
      <description>The star, who once positioned herself as a queer ally, is generating quite an intense reaction from fans who feel betrayed. Here&#8217;s why.
Over the weekend, rapper Nicki Minaj made a surprise appearance at Turning Point USA&#8217;s AmericaFest convention, where she praised President Donald Trump and Vice President J.D. Vance, mocked California Governor Gavin Newsom, and instructed listeners, &#8220;If you are born a boy, be a boy.&#8221; ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin does cultural diplomacy in a dive bar</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/849133/pubkey-dc-opening-bitcoin-bar</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T14:43:43-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849133</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin culture, by nature, is anarchical and chaotic. It has to be, given the nature of Bitcoin itself and the people who adopted it: free-market libertarians who've gone all in on turning computer code into a form of money divorced from central banks, government intervention, and traceability. In short, it's the exact opposite culture of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Justice Department Just Released More Epstein Files</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-justice-department-just-released-more-epstein-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">694594efd2ae1c7afe304d3d</guid>
      <description>The latest Epstein Files release appears to contain hundreds of photographs along with court records and other materials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banksy unveils a new mural in London</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465110/banksy-new-murals-art-london-stargazing</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T19:42:25</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465110/banksy-new-murals-art-london-stargazing</guid>
      <description>While his work is often critical of government policy on migration and war, the latest artwork did not seem to carry an overt political message.
Elusive street artist&#160;Banksy&#160;appeared to confirm Monday that a new mural in London, depicting two children lying down and pointing up at the sky, is his latest work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large External SSDs are now cheaper than internal ones as 4TB SATA SSD face extinction due to negligible price difference</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/large-external-ssds-are-now-cheaper-than-internal-ones-as-4tb-sata-ssd-face-extinction-due-to-negligible-price-difference</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sRnrPeszvppmPJSTesuFdS</guid>
      <description>External 4TB SSDs costing less than internal SATA models shows shifting NAND priorities and increasing market pressures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate library rips 86 million of the most popular songs on Spotify</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849141/spotify-scrape-attack-breach-annas-archive-music-300tb-download</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T14:23:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849141</guid>
      <description>Spotify says it has launched new protections against "anti-copyright attacks" after the open-source library / pirate activist group Anna's Archive announced it's ripped 86 million songs from the platform that it plans to make available in torrents, as reported earlier by Billboard. According to the group, "We have archived around 86 million songs from Spotify, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birdfy&#8217;s Hum Bloom captures 120fps slow motion footage of hummingbirds</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849140/birdfy-smart-birdfeeder-hum-bloom-hummingbird-feeder-vista-slow-motion</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T14:21:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849140</guid>
      <description>Ahead of CES 2026 getting underway in early January, Birdfy has announced two new camera-equipped smart bird feeders that can identify and capture visitors in slow motion. The Birdfy Hum Bloom is specifically designed to attract and record hummingbirds using a nectar bulb that mimics flowers they're naturally attracted to, while the Feeder Vista introduces [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the Burning Questions We Have After &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/all-the-burning-questions-we-have-after-avatar-fire-and-ash-2000696733</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696733</guid>
      <description>Let's dig deep into some spoilers for James Cameron's sci-fi action blockbuster, now in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Ellison Revives Paramounts&#8217; Bid on Warner as His Son Hollows Out CBS News</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/larry-ellison-revives-paramounts-warner-bid-as-his-son-hollows-out-cbs-news-2000702602</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702602</guid>
      <description>They're probably promising Trump a producer credit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arm sheds billions in market capitalization after Qualcomm hints at RISC-V adoption with Ventara Micro acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/arm-sheds-billions-in-market-capitalization-after-qualcomm-hints-at-risc-v-adoption-with-ventara-micro-acquisition</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KZbDZRZcPf2XwBAEibWcN4</guid>
      <description>Arm stock declines as Qualcomm picks up Ventana, raising questions about future customer reliance on Arm architectures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet buys data center energy specialist Intersect for $4.75 billion to help power AI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91465081/alphabet-google-intersect-ai-data-centers-energy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T19:03:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91465081/alphabet-google-intersect-ai-data-centers-energy</guid>
      <description>Alphabet will allow Intersect to operate independently while continuing its efforts to secure the energy sources for AI data centers. 
Google&#8216;s corporate parent on Monday announced an agreement to buy data center energy specialist Intersect for $4.75 billion as part of its effort to secure the&#160;vast amounts of electricity&#160;needed to power artificial intelligence technology....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT launches a year-end review like Spotify Wrapped</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/chatgpt-launches-a-year-end-review-like-spotify-wrapped/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078322</guid>
      <description>The experience includes awards, poems, and pictures referencing your year in chat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify affirme que des activistes ont pirat&#233; son catalogue</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-22/spotify-affirme-que-des-activistes-ont-pirate-son-catalogue.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:49:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1151f249f8d3dbdb7d3996d104cb53e</guid>
      <description>Le service de diffusion musicale en continu Spotify a annonc&#233; lundi avoir d&#233;sactiv&#233; les comptes d&#8217;un groupe de pirates qui affirmait avoir &#171;&#160;sauvegard&#233;&#160;&#187; des millions de fichiers musicaux et de m&#233;tadonn&#233;es de la plateforme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Game Awards retracts Expedition 33 prizes due to generative AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/849144/indie-game-awards-game-of-the-year-expedition-33-generative-ai-chantey-modretro</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-22T13:47:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849144</guid>
      <description>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 had earned another Game of the Year award by the Indie Game Awards last week, but the organization has since announced that the award would be retracted because developer Sandfall Interactive used generative AI during development. The Indie Game Awards also rescinded the Debut Game award given to Expedition 33. Here [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of SpaceX rival United Launch Alliance resigns</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/22/ceo-of-spacex-rival-united-launch-alliance-resigns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078304</guid>
      <description>Tory Bruno's abrupt departure comes after 12 years in the role. The company, a Boeing-Lockheed Martin joint venture, has had to fight to keep pace with Elon Musk's SpaceX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motherboards from Gigabyte, MSI, ASUS, ASRock at risk from new UEFI flaw attack - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/motherboards-from-gigabyte-msi-asus-asrock-at-risk-from-new-uefi-flaw-attack-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZtjNyvPEFsWPBKGZnptLfN</guid>
      <description>Many popular devices are now vulnerable to direct memory access attacks, but there is a patch.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
