<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:30:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox shakeup: Phil Spencer and Sarah Bond are leaving Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/882363/xbox-microsoft-phil-spencer-out</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T16:29:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=882363</guid>
      <description>After nearly 40 years at Microsoft, Xbox chief and Microsoft Gaming CEO Phil Spencer is leaving the company, along with Xbox president Sarah Bond. Spencer&#8217;s retirement was announced in a memo from Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella on February 20th, stating, &#8220;Last year, Phil Spencer made the decision to retire from the company, and since then [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox head Phil Spencer is leaving Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/xbox-head-phil-spencer-is-leaving-microsoft-212838419.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e2f6507-5c25-4268-9eb1-24aa6c806c96</guid>
      <description>Phil Spencer, CEO of Microsoft Gaming, is retiring, Satya Nadella has announced. Asha Sharma, the President of Microsoft's CoreAI division is taking over Spencer's role, while Sarah Bond, the current President of Xbox, is resigning."I am long on gaming and its role at the center of our consumer ambition, and as we look ahead, I&#8217;m excited to share that Asha Sharma will become Executive Vice President and CEO, Microsoft Gaming, reporting to me," Nadella says. "Over the last two years at Microsoft, and previously as Chief Operating Officer at Instacart and a Vice President at Meta, Asha has helpe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2026: The Galaxy S26 and other devices that might launch on February 25</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-2026-the-galaxy-s26-and-other-devices-that-might-launch-on-february-25-130000063.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b516dbb-4749-48f0-b5c0-b244aed8b2b9</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s 2025 was filled with new foldables, an ultra-thin new form factor and the launch of Google's XR platform. After making some announcements at CES 2026, the company has announced its first Galaxy Unpacked of the year will take place on February 25, where it is expected to introduce the Galaxy S26 lineup. Official invites have  been shared, but actual information on what devices are arriving then is still not completely confirmed. But as usual, we know a lot about what&#8217;s expected at Unpacked.Engadget will be covering Galaxy Unpacked live from San Francisco next week, and we'll most like...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&#233;isme chez Microsoft : Phil Spencer prend sa retraite, Sarah Bond s&#8217;en va et une experte de l&#8217;IA prend les r&#234;nes d&#8217;Xbox</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2985357_seisme-chez-microsoft-phil-spencer-prend-sa-retraite-sarah-bond-sen-va-et-une-experte-de-lia-prend-les-renes-dxbox</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2985357_seisme-chez-microsoft-phil-spencer-prend-sa-retraite-sarah-bond-sen-va-et-une-experte-de-lia-prend-les-renes-dxbox</guid>
      <description>
C&#8217;est une annonce choc que vient de faire Microsoft.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Didn&#8217;t Want Tony Gilroy to Say &#8216;Fascism&#8217; While Promoting &#8216;Andor&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-didnt-want-tony-gilroy-to-say-fascism-while-promoting-andor-2000724719</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724719</guid>
      <description>A new interview with the 'Star Wars' series creator digs deep into its political parallels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Virtual Boy for Switch 2 Review: An Incredible Recreation of a Terrible Console</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nintendo-virtual-boy-for-switch-2-review-an-incredible-recreation-of-a-terrible-console-2000724146</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724146</guid>
      <description>You'll enjoy Nintendo's $100 Virtual Boy if you enjoy digging through gaming history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Bet Against Trump's Tariffs. Now They Stand to Make Millions</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/they-bet-against-trumps-tariffs-now-they-stand-to-make-millions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69989bb06dc08b373371fbb4</guid>
      <description>After the US Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump&#8217;s tariff regime, investment firms are in line for a whopping return on a niche trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember HQ? &#8216;Quiz Daddy&#8217; Scott Rogowsky is back with TextSavvy, a daily mobile game show</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/remember-hq-quiz-daddy-scott-rogowsky-is-back-with-textsavvy-a-daily-mobile-game-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094936</guid>
      <description>The former HQ host Scott Rogowsky is back with TextSavvy, a live mobile game show that he's building on his own terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft says today&#8217;s Xbox shake-up doesn&#8217;t mean game studio layoffs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/882377/microsoft-says-todays-xbox-shakeup-doesnt-mean-game-studio-layoffs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:58:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882377</guid>
      <description>Xbox has new leaders today, now that Phil Spencer and Sarah Bond are out - and you'd be forgiven for assuming that means yet another round of layoffs and shuttered studios, especially one day after Sony jettisoned a beloved developer. Not yet, it seems. "To be clear, there are no organizational changes underway for our [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More fun, shorter waits: Disneyland says it added 1.5 million ride experiences in 2025 without new builds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/disneyland-says-it-added-1-5-million-ride-experiences-in-2025-without-new-builds</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vNPN47iJkibwiQLTxr4VTN</guid>
      <description>Disneyland is investing heavily in reliability upgrades that are already delivering more rides, shorter waits, and smoother visits &#8211; even as major new attractions remain years away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic-funded group backs candidate attacked by rival AI super PAC</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/anthropic-funded-group-backs-candidate-attacked-by-rival-ai-super-pac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095184</guid>
      <description>Dueling pro-AI PACs have centered around backing or targeting one New York congressional bid: Alex Bores, whose RAISE Act requires AI developers to disclose safety protocols and report serious system misuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;I didn&#8217;t get a graduation&#8217;: How the Class of 2020 turned their pandemic loss into a running joke on TikTok</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496234/class-of-2020-tiktok-pandemic</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T20:48:18</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496234/class-of-2020-tiktok-pandemic</guid>
      <description>Five years later, Gen Z is still joking about its most defining COVID-era rite of passage.
The Class of 2020 still aren&#8217;t over the COVID-19 pandemic cancelling their graduation. Apparently they never stop bringing it up, according to TikTok. Now their complaints are being used as a punchline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Reviewers&#8217; Top TV Pick for Gamers Is at Its Lowest Price in Months</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-s90f-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6998a20f3e8bc0874c1c64ac</guid>
      <description>This Samsung OLED comes loaded with features specifically for gamers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOTUS rules Trump&#8217;s tariffs are illegal &#8212; but the fight is far from over</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/882227/scotus-trump-tariffs-ruling-imports-small-businesses-refunds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:45:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882227</guid>
      <description>The US Supreme Court struck down some of Donald Trump's tariffs on foreign imports, which have become a hallmark of the chaos of the second Trump administration. The court's ruling deals specifically with duties levied using a law called the International Emergency Economic Powers Act (IEEPA), something no other president has done - the 1977 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon wants swarms of voice-controlled AI drones, and is offering a $100 million prize as a reward &#8212; and Elon Musk's SpaceX is taking pole position</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-pentagon-wants-swarms-of-voice-controlled-ai-drones-and-is-offering-a-usd100-million-prize-as-a-reward-and-elon-musks-spacex-is-taking-pole-position</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iLnKp6cVdA9wJXnvKcciDD</guid>
      <description>The Pentagon has launched a $100 million contest to develop voice-controlled autonomous drone swarms amid unresolved technical challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Microsoft gaming CEO Asha Sharma&amp;#8217;s first memo on the future of Xbox</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/882326/read-microsoft-gaming-ceo-asha-sharma-first-memo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:30:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882326</guid>
      <description>Microsoft gaming boss Phil Spencer has just announced he's leaving the company after 12 years leading Xbox and nearly 40 at Microsoft in total. His replacement: Asha Sharma, formerly head of development for Microsoft's AI enterprise teams. Before that, she was COO of Instacart for three years, and spent four at Meta in charge of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Xbox chief Phil Spencer&#8217;s memo about leaving Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/882340/xbox-phil-spencer-microsoft-retirement-memo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:30:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882340</guid>
      <description>Xbox chief Phil Spencer has just announced to employees that he's leaving Microsoft after 38 years. In a memo entitled "A new chapter for Microsoft Gaming," Spencer reveals to Xbox employees that he made the decision to retire from Microsoft last fall. He also reveals Xbox president Sarah Bond is leaving Microsoft, triggering a big [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox chief Phil Spencer is leaving Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/882241/microsoft-phil-spencer-xbox-leaving-retirement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:30:04-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882241</guid>
      <description>Xbox chief Phil Spencer is leaving Microsoft after nearly 40 years at the software giant. Xbox president Sarah Bond is also leaving Microsoft, in what is a major shake-up to the management of Xbox and Microsoft's gaming efforts. Asha Sharma, currently president of CoreAI product, is taking over as CEO of Microsoft Gaming. Microsoft CEO [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump revives alien debate with order to release government files</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496206/trump-revives-alien-debate-with-order-to-release-government-files</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496206/trump-revives-alien-debate-with-order-to-release-government-files</guid>
      <description>The announcement comes as Congress continues to scrutinize unexplained aerial phenomena.
It&#8217;s been a big week for aliens in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Bond is leaving Xbox</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/882281/xbox-sarah-bond-leaving-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:29:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882281</guid>
      <description>Sarah Bond, the president and COO of Xbox, is leaving the organization, along with CEO of Microsoft Gaming Phil Spencer. Her departure is being announced at the same time as Spencer's, with Asha Sharma moving into the EVP and CEO of Gaming role and Matt Booty being promoted to EVP and chief content officer. Microsoft [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read &#8216;Claymore,&#8217; Manga&#8217;s Best-Kept Dark Fantasy Secret</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/read-claymore-mangas-best-kept-dark-fantasy-secret-2000724567</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724567</guid>
      <description>A PSA to experience Norihiro Yagi&#8217;s gatekept series before the live&#8209;action adaptation breaches containment and has its fandom sweating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is making coal plants even dirtier as AI demands more energy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/882288/trump-ai-data-center-power-plant-pollution-mercury-mats</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:18:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882288</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration just tossed out Biden-era restrictions on mercury and other toxic pollutants from power plants. It's repealing Mercury and Air Toxics Standards (MATS) just as electricity demand in the US ticks up with the buildout of new AI data centers. Those standards are particularly impactful when it comes to pollution from coal plants [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;AI injury attorneys&#8217; sue ChatGPT in another AI psychosis case</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ai-injury-attorneys-ai-psychosis-case-chatgpt-openai-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06vcRaUU0sJrERPl6qlN9eZ</guid>
      <description>AI injury lawyers have filed a new lawsuit against OpenAI over an AI Psychosis case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down Trump tariffs 6-3. Tech stocks rally, but will prices drop?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/supreme-court-strikes-down-trump-tariffs-tech-stocks-rally</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01bzGzHZSjwjveRMWOsWZYS</guid>
      <description>Many of President Trump's sweeping tariffs have been struck down in a 6-3 decision from the Supreme Court. What does the decision mean for consumers?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web scraper sued by Google claims Google is the one scraping the web</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/882300/serpapi-google-lawsuit-web-scraper-motion-to-dismiss</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T15:06:46-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=882300</guid>
      <description>SerpApi, a company that offers tools to scrape content on the web, is fighting back against Google's copyright lawsuit that accuses it of vacuuming up search results "at an astonishing scale." In a motion to dismiss filed on Friday, SerpApi argues that Google doesn't hold a copyright on its search results, alleging that the engine [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Wants a Single Search Engine to Flag Faces and Fingerprints Across Agencies</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/dhs-wants-a-single-search-engine-to-flag-faces-and-fingerprints-across-agencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69977cb46682b7d0faefb42e</guid>
      <description>Homeland Security aims to combine its face and fingerprint systems into one big biometric platform&#8212;after dismantling centralized privacy reviews and key limits on face recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite being designed to 'connect and just work', it turns out IKEA's new smart home sensors actually have some specific, confusing hub requirements</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/despite-being-designed-to-connect-and-just-work-it-turns-out-ikeas-new-smart-home-sensors-actually-have-some-specific-confusing-hub-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wUjABjYNnKPvc6pYSzW4dj</guid>
      <description>Those temptingly cheap sensors aren't quite such a bargain if you have to buy IKEA's own $109 / &#163;60 hub to make them work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reese Witherspoon says &#8216;don&#8217;t chase your dreams&#8217;&#8212;do this instead</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496107/reese-witherspoon-says-dont-chase-your-dreams-do-this-instead</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496107/reese-witherspoon-says-dont-chase-your-dreams-do-this-instead</guid>
      <description>In a new viral Instagram post, the Oscar winner has some advice for folks just starting out their careers.
We&#8217;re told from a young age to follow our dreams. But for Oscar-winning actress Reese Witherspoon, chasing your dreams is overrated. Instead, she recommends a different approach, especially for young people: &#8220;Chase your talents, not your dreams.&#8221;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can save $30 on Sony&#8217;s DualSense Edge controller by buying refurbished</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/815676/sony-playstation-dualsense-edge-controller-refurbished-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T14:55:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=815676</guid>
      <description>If the PlayStation 5 is your console of choice &#8212;&#160;and you&#8217;re not satisfied with the DualSense gamepad it comes with &#8212; the DualSense Edge may be what you&#8217;re looking for. Luckily, if its high asking price of $199 was keeping you away, Sony is now offering the white and black controller via the PlayStation Direct [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why urban planners should strive for &#8216;the photo album standard&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91489505/why-urban-planners-should-strive-for-the-photo-album-standard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-20T19:53:23</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91489505/why-urban-planners-should-strive-for-the-photo-album-standard</guid>
      <description>Designers need to measure success by the memorable moments their work creates.
My family had Slide Show Night when I was growing up. Not every Saturday, but a whole bunch of Saturdays. Either my sister or I would be in charge of setting up the projector, the screen, and loading the carousel. During the show, there&#8217;d be a few landscapes or skylines taken during vacations, but almost all the shots were up close. Like most dads, mine wasn&#8217;t a professional photographer, but he did a good job of capturing memory triggers: faces, gestures, and decorations.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Reportedly Pins the Blame for AI-Caused Outage on Humans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-reportedly-pins-the-blame-for-ai-caused-outage-on-humans-2000724681</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724681</guid>
      <description>Allegedly, the coding assistant decided to &#8220;delete and recreate the environment&#8221; that was causing problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CDC Has a Leadership Crisis</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-cdc-has-a-leadership-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699786e93a099f5ddd9e73ff</guid>
      <description>A 2023 law championed by Republicans requires the CDC have a director confirmed by the Senate. For months, though, it&#8217;s had only acting directors&#8212;and the White House won&#8217;t say when that will change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s iOS 26.4 arrives in public beta with AI music playlists, video podcasts, and more</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/20/apples-ios-26-4-arrives-in-public-beta-with-ai-music-playlists-video-podcasts-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095036</guid>
      <description>Several updates are introduced in iOS 26.4, including an AI-powered playlist-generation feature in Apple Music, support for video content in the Podcasts app, end-to-end encryption (E2EE) for RCS messages, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
