<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:20:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.2 is here with Liquid Glass, AirDrop, and Apple Music updates</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/839534/apple-iphone-ipad-mac-update-26-2</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T14:18:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839534</guid>
      <description>Today, Apple officially released iOS 26.2 for iPhone 11 and newer devices, which includes new Lock Screen customizations for you to adjust the opacity level, as well as the ability to use AirDrop with people who aren't in your contacts by sharing a one-time code with them instead. There are also new updates going out [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft buys 3.6M metric tons of carbon removal from bioenergy plant</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/microsoft-buys-3-6m-metric-tons-of-carbon-removal-from-bioenergy-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075667</guid>
      <description>Microsoft's data center ambitions have imperiled its 2030 pledge to remove more carbon than it generates, making carbon removal credits all but necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mmm, Qi donuts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843720/ikea-qi-2-wireless-charger-vastmarke-silicone</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T14:10:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843720</guid>
      <description>After announcing new Matter-compatible smart home devices and stylish wireless speakers over the past few months, Ikea continues to expand its consumer electronics offerings with three new wireless chargers. They're limited to 15W Qi2.0 charging rates but are well priced and feature designs that look more like home decor accents than traditional tech accessories. The [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanning Beds Are Giving Us Skin Cancer Where the Sun Doesn&#8217;t Shine</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tanning-beds-are-giving-us-skin-cancer-where-the-sun-doesnt-shine-2000699139</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699139</guid>
      <description>New research highlights the unique dangers of the UV radiation provided by tanning beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Government Websites Are Hosting PDFs Promoting Porn and Scams</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/u-s-government-websites-are-hosting-pdfs-promoting-porn-and-scams-2000699133</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699133</guid>
      <description>Not exactly a public service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33 practical smart home gifts that make everyday life a little easier</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/800449/best-practical-smart-home-gift-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T14:00:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800449</guid>
      <description>Smart home products are all about making everyday life a little easier, which is why they're some of the best and most thoughtful gifts you can give. Some people go all out building a multi-gadget IoT kingdom (like our resident smart home expert, Jen Pattison Tuohy), but a smart home is whatever your recipient wants [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube finally gets the TV update we've been waiting for &#8211;and there are 5 handy upgrades</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/youtube-finally-gets-the-tv-update-weve-been-waiting-for-and-there-are-5-handy-upgrades</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CJuf7NXHnwsHjWWC2NPQLG</guid>
      <description>The YouTube app for TVs is finally getting a long-promised makeover&#8211;here are all the handy improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move over, Bang &amp; Olufsen: Germany's Loewe is expanding to the US and it's bringing its super-premium OLED TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/move-over-bang-and-olufsen-germanys-loewe-is-expanding-to-the-us-and-its-bringing-its-super-premium-oled-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gxDmvpwQmUGLbZvHM5oNPK</guid>
      <description>Loewe's high-end OLEDs include some very striking designs and unusual materials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone is wrong about AI regulation, and the history of the Internet proves it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/everyone-is-wrong-about-ai-regulation-and-the-history-of-the-internet-proves-it</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RkDo5rGXohW6bwjAkZ7hRb</guid>
      <description>The US White House wants to stop states from regulating AI, and the states want their own AI regulation. What if they're both wrong?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director found guilty of scamming Netflix out of $11 million</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843923/hollywood-director-netflix-conviction-fraud-carl-rinsch</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:54:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843923</guid>
      <description>Hollywood director Carl Erik Rinsch was convicted of scamming $11 million from Netflix to spend on luxury items, including five Rolls-Royces and a Ferrari, as reported earlier by Deadline. A New York jury found Rinsch guilty of several charges on Thursday, including fraud and money laundering. Rinsch, who's known for directing 47 Ronin, was charged [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best gifts for dads that have everything (but deserve more)</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780847/best-dad-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:45:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780847</guid>
      <description>What do you get the man who says he has everything? It's a tough question - and one you have a limited amount of time to answer, given the holidays are nearly upon us. You could try dropping subtle hints or asking friends and family for suggestions, but they might save their best ideas for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why SpaceX Is Finally Gearing Up to Go Public</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/why-spacex-is-finally-gearing-up-to-go-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693c4753199888f1c10473e2</guid>
      <description>Like so many things in Elon Musk's orbit, a lot of it may come down to AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 devs dropped a big update after sweeping The Game Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/clair-obscur-expedition-33-devs-dropped-a-big-update-after-sweeping-the-game-awards-183628313.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b93d5a9-bdea-476a-8fc8-9849a55a04d8</guid>
      <description>Sandfall Interactive, the developer of Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, knows how to ride the wave. Right after the visually stunning RPG finished dominating The Game Awards, the team dropped a free "Thank You" content update for fans.This is no minor patch. It adds a playable environment and new boss battles for late-game players. The "Thank You" update also adds new music tracks, a Photo Mode and new text and UI localizations. On top of that, you'll find quality-of-life tweaks, including improved performance on handheld PCs.Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 won a record-breaking nine categories at The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday shoppers: Try these smart money-saving tips this holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459800/holiday-shopping-save-money-tips-experts</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T18:33:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459800/holiday-shopping-save-money-tips-experts</guid>
      <description>You can take advantage of websites that give you cash back on your grocery shopping or buy gifts in advance, experts say.
The holiday season means time with family and new memories, but it can also mean lots of spending&#8212;sometimes too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh Great, Smart Glasses That Record Everything You Say</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/oh-great-smart-glasses-that-record-everything-you-say-2000699011</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699011</guid>
      <description>It's just audio for now, but the Mira set an icky precedent for always-on recording in smart glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The all-new Apple Watch 11 would make a great Christmas gift &#8212; and it's on sale for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/the-all-new-apple-watch-11-would-make-a-great-christmas-gift-and-its-on-sale-for-its-lowest-price-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CezhoGSXS8CUBPXqzMCP3A</guid>
      <description>The all-new Apple Watch 11 is now on sale at its lowest price ever on Walmart, making it a great gift idea and arriving before Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 34 best gifts that your teen will actually use</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/785418/best-teen-gift-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:24:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=785418</guid>
      <description>Between keeping up with TikTok trends and whatever new gadget just dropped, it's tough to know exactly what teens are into these days. Luckily, we can help. We may be older than teenagers, but many of us here at The Verge are kids at heart. Plus, we've also got a few staffers with older kids. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel, AMD accused of 'willful ignorance' in allowing chips to get to Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/intel-amd-accused-of-willful-ignorance-in-allowing-chips-to-get-to-russia</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vAQtfwH44Tc27Dm96YQmFK</guid>
      <description>The Ukrainians are suing US tech firms over Russian bombs allegedly carrying their tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Zootopia 2&#8217; Has Reached $1 Billion in Record-Breaking Time</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/zootopia-2-box-office-records-disney-2000699178</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699178</guid>
      <description>The animated Disney sequel hit the box-office milestone after just 17 days in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Translate brings real-time speech translations to any headphones</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/843483/google-translate-live-speech-translations-headphones</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T13:11:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843483</guid>
      <description>Google Translate's latest update brings live speech translations, originally available only on the Pixel Buds, to any headphones you want, with support for over 70 languages. It's rolling out today in beta and just requires a compatible Android phone with the Translate app (unlike Apple's similar feature, which requires AirPods). It's one of a few [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best stocking stuffers you can get for $50 or less</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/the-best-stocking-stuffers-you-can-get-for-50-or-less-130049325.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32df60b9-ebc7-4bd2-a9e6-0777477036d5</guid>
      <description>While it&#8217;s probably tempting to go all-out and give a loved one their most desired gadget this year, doing so could put a big dent in your budget. And it would be wrong to assume that you have to spend hundreds to get a good tech gift that anyone will appreciate. There are plenty of gadgets and accessories out there that don&#8217;t cost an arm and a leg and that will also make good additions to their kits. Here are some of our favorite tech gift ideas that come in at $50 or less.
Best stocking stuffers for $50 or less


























Check out the rest of our gift ideas here. This article...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman&#8217;s Eyeball-Scanning Startup Launches &#8216;Super App&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altmans-eyeball-scanning-startup-launches-super-app-2000699091</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699091</guid>
      <description>Want to chat with your friends? Please look into this orb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new fashion-forward Target is a glimpse of the retailer&#8217;s future</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459199/nyc-target-is-glimpse-of-the-retailers-future</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459199/nyc-target-is-glimpse-of-the-retailers-future</guid>
      <description>Target is ending a tough 2025 by launching a new store format in NYC it hopes will convince customers it&#8217;s a fun place to shop again.
This week, a new fashion boutique quietly opened in SoHo. Much like its neighbors, H&amp;M and American Eagle, the new shop features racks of affordably priced, trendy apparel. You&#8217;d be forgiven for thinking it was another fast fashion label, but it&#8217;s not: it&#8217;s Target....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Rare Video of Orcas Teaming Up With Dolphins to Hunt Giant Salmon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/watch-rare-video-of-orcas-teaming-up-with-dolphins-to-hunt-giant-salmon-2000699100</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699100</guid>
      <description>The two top predators seem to be working together to track, kill, and feast on salmon, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto founder Do Kwon sentenced to 15 years in prison for $40 billion Terraform Labs fraud</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459737/do-kwon-sentenced-15-years-in-prison-terraform-crypto-stablecoin-fraud</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T17:52:27</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459737/do-kwon-sentenced-15-years-in-prison-terraform-crypto-stablecoin-fraud</guid>
      <description>Kwon&#160;pleaded guilty&#160;in August to fraud charges stemming from the collapse of Terraform Labs, the Singapore-based firm he cofounded in 2018. 
Onetime cryptocurrency mogul Do Kwon was sentenced Thursday to 15 years in prison after a&#160;$40 billion crash&#160;revealed his crypto ecosystem to be a fraud. Victims said the 34-year-old financial technology whiz weaponized their trust to convince them that the investment &#8212; secretly propped up by cash infusions &#8212; was safe....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hisenses 65-inch The Frame dupe is down to a record-low $699 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-hisense-canvas-tv-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02t2Kqh31Gaab4FQWO6Iazu</guid>
      <description>The Hisense 65-inch Canvas TV is down to just $699.99 at Amazon, a new best price ever. That beats its Black Friday price by nearly $200.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 best gift ideas for mom this holiday season</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/802964/best-mom-gift-ideas</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T12:45:20-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=802964</guid>
      <description>Your mom deserves the best, and we're going to help you get them something special. The right gift can make family or friend time more valuable, after all, or it can greatly enrich time spent alone. If your mom says that she has all that she needs, don't take her word for it and show [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Batch of Epstein Photos Include Bill Gates, Richard Branson, and Segway Inventor</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-batch-of-epstein-photos-include-bill-gates-richard-branson-and-segway-inventor-2000699130</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699130</guid>
      <description>President Trump is in there too, but you could probably guess that by now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hisense&#8217;s CanvasTV is a great Samsung Frame TV alternative at nearly half off</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/843667/hisense-s7n-canvas-tv-tomtoc-fancycase-g05-slim-case-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T12:36:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843667</guid>
      <description>Samsung&#8217;s Frame TV is one of the coolest-looking TVs you can buy, doubling as wall art when you&#8217;re not watching &#8212;&#160; but it&#8217;s pricey. If you like the idea of a TV that displays art when not in use but is far more affordable, Hisense&#8217;s S7N CanvasTV delivers a similar vibe for a lot less, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data breach at credit check giant 700Credit affects at least 5.6 million</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/data-breach-at-credit-check-giant-700credit-affects-at-least-5-6-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075630</guid>
      <description>700Credit, a company that runs credit checks and identity verification services for auto dealerships across the U.S., had a data breach that allowed a hacker to steal names, addresses, dates of birth, and Social Security numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Translate is now better at translating slang terms and idioms using AI</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/google-translate-is-now-better-at-translating-slang-terms-and-idioms-using-ai-173428316.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45a8c511-994c-4cec-b1b4-42c2732ee35a</guid>
      <description>Google is rolling out new Gemini-assisted functionality to Search and its Translate app. It says its AI can now provide more natural and accurate text translations for phrases that have more "nuanced meanings."&#160; Translate will now take slang terms and colloquial expressions into consideration rather than provide sometimes unhelpful direct translations.
The latest update to its text translation feature is rolling out first in the US and India, translating between English and just under 20 other languages, including German, Spanish, Chinese and Arabic. It works in the Translate app for iOS and A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple loses contempt ruling appeal, but could revisit iPhone app fees</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459732/apple-loses-appeal-contempt-epic-iphone-app-fees</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T17:34:09</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459732/apple-loses-appeal-contempt-epic-iphone-app-fees</guid>
      <description>Apple continued to fight the alternative payment option in appeals before being&#160;rebuffed by the U.S. Supreme Court in January 2024.
A federal appeals court on Thursday backed a ruling that held Apple in civil contempt for brazenly defying an order designed to open its iPhone app store to other payment systems besides its own, but the decision also reopened a door for the company to collect commission from the rival options....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New MacOS malware exploits trusted AI and search tools</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/new-macos-malware-exploits-trusted-ai-and-search-tools</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42yeGSUGsXbmjuLMAGVhkH</guid>
      <description>Mac users are being targeted with AMOS again, this time through a dubious combination of malvertising and AI results poisoning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Kindles are back on sale at Amazon for holiday shoppers &#8212; prices start at $89</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-12-amazon-kindle-paperwhite-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03mxxDPlFlksdmjQcA5TNfd</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 12, get the Amazon Kindle Paperwhite for just $134.99. That saves you $25 off its list price. The savings aren't quite as abundant as they were on Black Friday, but it's a great last minute deal to close out the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant-Based Diets Can Work for Kids, but New Study Outlines Concerning Risks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/plant-based-diets-can-work-for-kids-but-new-study-outlines-concerning-risks-2000699057</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699057</guid>
      <description>There are several nutrients that vegan and vegetarian kids can miss out on without careful planning, a review of the evidence finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce says per-user pricing will be new AI norm</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/salesforce-says-per-user-pricing-will-be-new-ai-norm</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8SLMNvtTpt4uQpVijcm6e8</guid>
      <description>Marc Benioff expects to increase AI monetization while delivering more value for customers on their preferred pricing model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le flash de votre smartphone est nul : voici pourquoi &#231;a pourrait enfin changer avec le retour du x&#233;non</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2909257_le-flash-de-votre-smartphone-est-nul-voici-pourquoi-ca-pourrait-enfin-changer-avec-le-retour-du-xenon</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2909257_le-flash-de-votre-smartphone-est-nul-voici-pourquoi-ca-pourrait-enfin-changer-avec-le-retour-du-xenon</guid>
      <description>
Le flash LED de votre smartphone sert surtout de lampe torche pour trouver vos cl&#233;s. Pour la photo ? C'est une catastrophe. Mais Samsung travaille sur une technologie, le Global Shutter, qui pourrait ressusciter le l&#233;gendaire flash au x&#233;non. Et l&#224;, on parle de vraie photographie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ford is fighting off F-150 thieves with amped up tech</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91459722/how-ford-fighting-off-f-150-thieves-amped-up-tech</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T17:22:27</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91459722/how-ford-fighting-off-f-150-thieves-amped-up-tech</guid>
      <description>In 2024, Ford&#8217;s F-150 pickup truck was in the top 10 of most stolen models.
Ford Motor Co. has stepped up technology in its popular F-150 pickup to combat the ever-evolving techniques car thieves have at their disposal.It is the latest cat-and-mouse move that the automaker hopes will help customers avoid the costly and frustrating process that occurs when vehicles are swiped and includes a feature that won&#8217;t allow an engine to start even if a key fob is in the pickup.Motor vehicle thefts recently have been on the decline in the U.S. after several years of increases. Still, the National Highway...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
