<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:22:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo to issue software recall over how robotaxis behave around school buses</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/waymo-to-issue-software-recall-over-how-robotaxis-behave-around-school-buses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073505</guid>
      <description>The voluntary recall comes as scrutiny by federal regulators and local school district officials increases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"There is 'no way'" - IBM CEO says current AI data center trends are unsustainable, and he would know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/there-is-no-way-ibm-ceo-says-current-ai-data-center-trends-are-unsustainable-and-he-would-know</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cMWmL2i5THF9wtW3WwnomU</guid>
      <description>IBM CEO Arvind Krishna warns that massive AI data center expansions carry unsustainable costs and hardware replacement challenges globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRED Roundup: DOGE Isn&#8217;t Dead, Facebook Dating Is Real, and Amazon&#8217;s AI Ambitions</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-wired-roundup-doge-facebook-dating-amazon-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6933348596e8ec52361ed144</guid>
      <description>In this episode of Uncanny Valley, we bring you the news of the week, then dive into how some DOGE operatives are still at work in the federal government&#8212;despite reports claiming otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce CEO Mulls Changing Name to AI-Flavored &#8216;Agentforce&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/salesforce-ceo-mulls-changing-name-to-ai-flavored-agentforce-2000696360</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696360</guid>
      <description>Put "AI" in your name and watch the stock price climb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 1977 cut of Star Wars will return to theaters in 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/the-1977-cut-of-star-wars-will-return-to-theaters-in-2027-221113091.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b1caa18-52fb-4fd0-818b-67439ba88ca6</guid>
      <description>Here's some good news for the "Han shot first" crowd. The original cut of Star Wars (1977), the film known today as A New Hope, is coming back to theaters. We first learned in August that some version of the film would be screened again in 2027 for its 50th anniversary. But we know now this will indeed be the version everyone saw before George Lucas made those questionable, CGI-heavy changes in the 1997 Special Editions. The re-release arrives in theaters on February 19, 2027.In a short update posted Friday on the official Star Wars website, Lucasfilm all but clarified that this will be the or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the big leagues, Netflix</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/839480/netflix-warner-bros-acquisition-hbo-theatrical-releases-layoffs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T17:02:58-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=839480</guid>
      <description>Warner Bros. has an infamous history of being bought by other companies and then quickly ending up back on the market after its new owners realize how difficult it is to capitalize on a legacy production studio's assets. Those challenges are part of what doomed WB's mergers with AOL and AT&amp;T, who bought the studio [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Studios Is Trying to Move to Other Theme Parks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dc-studios-universal-theme-park-negotations-2000696312</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696312</guid>
      <description>DC-themed rides are now currently in Six Flags parks, but that may change. Could Universal scoop them up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS needs you to believe in AI agents</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/aws-needs-you-to-believe-in-ai-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3073407</guid>
      <description>AWS announced a wave of new AI agent tools at re:Invent 2025, but can Amazon actually catch up to the AI leaders? While the cloud giant is betting big on enterprise AI with its third-gen chip and database discounts that got developers cheering, it&#8217;s still fighting to prove it can compete beyond infrastructure.&#160; This week [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CEO of Chief on how the business world can better support women executives</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452735/the-ceo-of-chief-on-how-the-business-world-can-better-support-women-executives</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452735/the-ceo-of-chief-on-how-the-business-world-can-better-support-women-executives</guid>
      <description>Chief CEO Alison Moore unpacks how evolving career paths are being misread, the impact of market disruption, and why women-centered spaces remain vital.
A recent New York Times headline&#8212;&#8220;Did Women Ruin the Workplace?&#8221;&#8212;sparked a firestorm across social media. Alison Moore, CEO of Chief, the prestigious network for senior women executives, is pushing back on this notion with data and nuance. Drawing from an exclusive nationwide survey of women leaders, Moore unpacks how evolving career paths are being misread, the impact of market disruption, and why women-centered spaces remain vital....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds find more complaints of Tesla&#8217;s FSD running red lights and crossing lanes</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/05/feds-find-more-complaints-of-teslas-fsd-running-red-lights-and-crossing-lanes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073463</guid>
      <description>The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration has identified at least 80 incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia Has Its Own Version of &#8216;Wrapped&#8217; Now, But There&#8217;s One Little Problem</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wikipedia-has-its-own-version-of-wrapped-now-but-theres-one-little-problem-2000696361</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696361</guid>
      <description>The online encyclopedia is offering personalized stats on users' reading habits, along with a list of the year&#8217;s most-read articles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science says these Christmas songs tank productivity at work</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455739/science-says-these-christmas-songs-tank-productivity-at-work</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455739/science-says-these-christmas-songs-tank-productivity-at-work</guid>
      <description>Do you hear what I hear, indeed.
It&#8217;s the first week of December. If you don&#8217;t already have the Christmas tunes blasting in the office, what are you waiting for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC panel overturns 1991 newborn vaccine policy, triggering warnings of a public health backslide</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91455886/cdc-panel-overturns-1991-newborn-vaccine-policy-triggering-warnings-of-a-public-health-backslide</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91455886/cdc-panel-overturns-1991-newborn-vaccine-policy-triggering-warnings-of-a-public-health-backslide</guid>
      <description>Members appointed under RFK Jr. argued universal guidance was too broad, while medical groups said the change jeopardizes decades of near-eradication.
A powerful advisory group within the CDC voted Friday to overturn a longstanding precaution designed to protect newborn babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta's latest acquisition suggests hardware plans beyond glasses and headsets</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/metas-latest-acquisition-suggests-hardware-plans-beyond-glasses-and-headsets-212930339.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fdc07f4-40aa-4b0e-8f22-de045ef52f74</guid>
      <description>Meta has acquired Limitless, the maker of an AI-powered "Pendant," to work on building consumer hardware for the company, the startup announced via a YouTube video and blog post. So far, Meta has focused on selling VR headsets and AI smart glasses. Now the company seems interested in branching out."Meta recently announced a new vision to bring personal superintelligence to everyone and a key part of that vision is building incredible AI-enabled wearables. We share this vision and we'll be joining Meta to help bring our shared vision to life," Limitless CEO Dan Siroker said in the post announci...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
