<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:24:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Sunday, January 18 (game #1455)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-18-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TiSGfS6FvV4chQKGmSR9KM</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Sunday, January 18 (game #952)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-18-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8n8uoiP8LZ7kQJdGQQUiST</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Sunday, January 18 (game #686)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-18-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nTL7ai2eMvv7hddSSb8VLP</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What exactly is a canister vacuum, and what are they good for?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/what-exactly-is-a-canister-vacuum-and-what-are-they-good-for</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c72dEkuoP7jNDdXA95KoxN</guid>
      <description>This flexible type of vacuum goes where uprights can't reach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The plan for a gaming-themed Atari hotel in Las Vegas has reportedly been scrapped</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-plan-for-a-gaming-themed-atari-hotel-in-las-vegas-has-reportedly-been-scrapped-214212269.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee574e38-b6ad-4b84-bd36-bf42e11b7d55</guid>
      <description>Six years after the announcement of plans to build Atari Hotels in eight cities across the US, including Las Vegas, only one now seems to be moving forward, in Phoenix, Arizona. The Las Vegas deal ultimately "didn't come to fruition," spokesperson Sara Collins told Las Vegas Sun this week, and Atari Hotels is putting its focus into the Phoenix site "for the time being."Phoenix was always meant to be the first site, followed by other hotels in Austin, Chicago, Denver, Las Vegas, San Francisco, San Jose and Seattle. But Las Vegas is now apparently off the table, and there haven't been any signs ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A laser that can fire light pulses in one billionth of a second is set to produce structures 1000 times stronger, 1000 times faster &#8212; novel technique has applications for high-performance computing, quantum devices, and AI chip cooling</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/a-laser-that-can-fire-light-pulses-in-one-billionth-of-a-second-is-set-to-produce-structures-1000-times-stronger-1000-times-faster-novel-technique-has-applications-for-high-performance-computing-quantum-devices-and-ai-chip-cooling</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cBJM3ZWBbgPPzQPgZbQL54</guid>
      <description>Researchers demonstrate a laser-based method that alters heat flow in thin silicon films using scalable nanoscale surface patterning techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Returns to &#8216;Magic: The Gathering&#8217; and Secret Lair</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-returns-to-magic-the-gathering-and-secret-lair-2000711431</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711431</guid>
      <description>For the 'Magic' fans, Secret Lair is dropping some new 'Fallout'-themed card packs at the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report Shows Massive Increase in Iranian Bitcoin Adoption Amid Nationwide Unrest</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iranian-bitcoin-adoption-amid-nationwide-unrest-2000711457</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711457</guid>
      <description>Turns out people might like to circumvent centralized financial infrastructure in times of political upheaval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAM prices set to almost double by March 2026, and yes, we all have our AI overlords to thank for that wonderful news</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dram-prices-set-to-almost-double-by-march-2026-and-yes-we-all-have-to-thank-our-ai-overlords-for-that-wonderful-news</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RQDZLMHMVDHKvbkKrVJPM</guid>
      <description>AI-driven data center demand has intensified DDR5 DRAM prices, while server memory prioritization reduces availability for PC-focused products globally.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
