<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:29:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NASA finally has a leader, but its future is no more certain</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-finally-has-a-leader-but-its-future-is-no-more-certain-201109072.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07817bf3-9e80-4ca4-bce4-810a0aea5a02</guid>
      <description>After a rudderless year and an exodus of around 4,000 employees due to Trump administration cuts, NASA got what may be its first piece of good news recently. On December 17, the Senate confirmed billionaire Jared Isaacman as the agency's new administrator. He now holds the power to rehabilitate a battered engine of scientific research, or steer it towards even more disruption.&#160;Considering the caliber of President Trump's other appointees, Isaacman is probably the best candidate for the job. Outside of being a successful entrepreneur, he has flown fighter jets and been to space twice as part of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media follower counts have never mattered less, creator economy execs say</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/29/social-media-follower-counts-have-never-mattered-less-creator-economy-execs-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078997</guid>
      <description>&#8220;I think that 2025 was the year where the algorithm completely took over, so followings stopped mattering entirely,&#8221; LTK CEO Amber Venz Box said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s a 'secret' sleep timer hidden in your iPhone and iPad &#8211; here's how to unlock it for Netflix</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/ios/theres-a-secret-sleep-timer-hidden-in-your-iphone-and-ipad-heres-how-to-unlock-it-for-netflix</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BfZXkjh4JKZyz6hgz65R5Q</guid>
      <description>Some iOS and iPadOS apps like Netflix don't have built-in sleep timers, but fortunately this lesser-known feature lets you create your own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cameron Is Also Mad About the Opening of &#8216;Alien 3&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/james-cameron-alien-3-reaction-2000703999</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703999</guid>
      <description>The 'Aliens' director told friend and star Michael Biehn his feelings about how the franchise followed their sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Dev Loses His Mind Over AI Agent&#8217;s Unsolicited &#8216;Act of Kindness&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/legendary-dev-loses-his-mind-over-ai-agents-unsolicited-act-of-kindness-2000704001</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704001</guid>
      <description>Just fuck you. Fuck you all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers say they have stolen 40 million Cond&#233; Nast Records - here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-say-they-have-stolen-40-million-conde-nast-records-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ziNpUHyjTRPWpoaAtHFnkf</guid>
      <description>A hacker claims to have good intentions - but do they, really?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collecting Social Security? These 2026 changes could affect your money</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467502/collecting-social-security-these-2026-changes-could-affect-your-money</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T19:28:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467502/collecting-social-security-these-2026-changes-could-affect-your-money</guid>
      <description>A delayed cost-of-living adjustment grabbed headlines, but four other Social Security updates could affect retirees and future claimants alike.
Roughly 75 million Americans will receive a 2.8% boost to their income in 2026, thanks to the upcoming cost-of-living adjustment for Social Security benefits and Supplemental Security Income (SSI) payments. But other changes afoot to the program will affect people who are still working, without a glint of retirement yet in their eyes....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voiture &#233;lectrique chinoise : l&#8217;astuce de Deepal pour &#233;chapper totalement aux taxes de l&#8217;Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2922005_voiture-electrique-chinoise-lastuce-de-deepal-pour-echapper-totalement-aux-taxes-de-leurope</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2922005_voiture-electrique-chinoise-lastuce-de-deepal-pour-echapper-totalement-aux-taxes-de-leurope</guid>
      <description>
Bient&#244;t commercialis&#233; en Europe, le Deepal S05 ne devrait pas &#234;tre soumis aux droits de douane chez nous. Mais comment cela est-il possible pour la voiture &#233;lectrique chinoise&#160;? On vous explique tout&#160;!
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the LG CES 2026 press conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-lg-ces-2026-press-conference-190159378.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6eb7981-0913-4e7b-bd66-4bc9abdcb17b</guid>
      <description>LG
For years, LG has kicked off CES press day with the first event of the morning &#8212; and 2026 will be no different. The Korea-based corporation is theming its presentation as  "Innovation in Tune with You," and &#8212; if it follows the template of past presentations &#8212; it will highlight both the consumer electronics and large appliance sides of its mammoth global businesses.
Like nearly all tech-centric events these days, expect AI to be the binding theme of the LG presentation at CES 2026. Just be aware that, like Apple, LG has its own customized abbreviation for AI: "Affectionate Intelligence." The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 was the year AI got a vibe check</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/29/2025-was-the-year-ai-got-a-vibe-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078961</guid>
      <description>AI&#8217;s early-2025 spending spree featured massive raises and trillion-dollar infrastructure promises. By year&#8217;s end, hype gave way to a vibe check, with growing scrutiny over sustainability, safety, and business models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 of the best free movies to stream on Tubi, Pluto TV, Samsung TV Plus, and more this week (December 29)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/5-of-the-best-free-movies-to-stream-on-tubi-pluto-tv-samsung-tv-plus-and-more-this-week-december-29</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">o3e5ymgNZ7FhiTc9SKfqVN</guid>
      <description>There's action movies, horrors and more to stream this week. And the best part is, they're all completely free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft engineer clarifies speculation around plans to 'eliminate' C, C++ languages by 2030</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cloud-computing/microsoft-engineer-clarifies-speculation-around-plans-to-eliminate-c-c-languages-by-2030</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Tr6FbrCouqvWUhwPvAYTzg</guid>
      <description>Details have been clarified by a Microsoft engineer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why silver prices surged, then dropped overnight</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467525/why-silver-prices-surged-then-dropped-overnight</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T18:34:55</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467525/why-silver-prices-surged-then-dropped-overnight</guid>
      <description>Safe-haven demand, industrial use, and dollar weakness fueled the rally&#8212;but profit-taking may be kicking in.
In a record weird year for the economy, the price of silver is the latest thing to behave strangely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOG&amp;#8217;s Steam-alternative PC game store is leaving CD Projekt, staying DRM-free</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850832/gog-cd-projekt-acquisition-steam</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T13:34:20-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850832</guid>
      <description>GOG is splitting from CD Projekt, the game company that launched the preservation-focused PC gaming marketplace in 2008. In an update on Monday, GOG announced that its co-founder, Micha&#322; Kici&#324;ski, has acquired the digital storefront and its online gaming platform GOG Galaxy from CD Projekt - which he also co-founded - for $25.2 million. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give your pup a fresh start in 2026 with The Farmer&#8217;s Dog</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/ad/deals/the-farmers-dog-half-off-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">024NgLazJ1Bvj6Jqp9X5iy9</guid>
      <description>Get 50% off your first box of human-grade pet food from The Farmer's Dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Things We Liked, and 5 We Didn&#8217;t, About &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Season 5, Volume 2</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/15-things-we-liked-and-5-we-didnt-about-stranger-things-season-5-volume-2-2000703631</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703631</guid>
      <description>The final battle begins December 31&#8212;but first, we have praise and a few nitpicks to pass along to Netflix and the Duffer Brothers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftBank to acquire DigitalBridge for $4 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467591/softbank-digitalbridge-acquisition-ai-infrastructure</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467591/softbank-digitalbridge-acquisition-ai-infrastructure</guid>
      <description>SoftBank founder Masayoshi Son is seeking to capitalize on surging demand for the computing capacity that underpins AI.
SoftBank Group will acquire digital infrastructure investor DigitalBridge Group in a deal valued at $4 billion, the companies said on Monday, as the Japanese investment firm looks to deepen its AI-related portfolio.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
