<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:58:44 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google ajoute deux fonctions tr&#232;s attendues dans YouTube Premium Lite, sans frais suppl&#233;mentaires</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/google-ajoute-deux-fonctions-tres-attendues-dans-youtube-premium-lite-sans-frais-supplementaires.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327883</guid>
      <description>Google am&#233;liore la formule YouTube Premium Lite en y ajoutant deux fonctions tr&#232;s int&#233;ressantes : la lecture en arri&#232;re-plan et le t&#233;l&#233;chargement de vid&#233;os. Des nouveaut&#233;s qui enrichissent une offre qui permettait d&#233;j&#224; de regarder le contenu de la plateforme (hors musique) sans pub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For All Mankind's latest trailer teases a war on Mars</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/for-all-mankinds-latest-trailer-teases-a-war-on-mars-174822481.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4d3c88b-c7d0-4ea8-b8e7-536ab1e6d1a5</guid>
      <description>Apple just dropped a full trailer for the fifth season of its hit sci-fi show For All Mankind. This is the first real look at the upcoming batch of episodes, which premiere on March 27. We got an extremely short teaser trailer last month but that only showed a guy on a motorcycle riding across Mars.
This is the first real-deal trailer and it's absolutely stuffed with footage indicating where the next season will take viewers. I'm going to get into some spoilers here, so read at your own risk.
For the uninitiated, For All Mankind is an alternate history show that started with a simple premise. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI COO says &#8216;we have not yet really seen AI penetrate enterprise business processes&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/openai-coo-says-we-have-not-yet-really-seen-ai-penetrate-enterprise-business-processes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095557</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, OpenAI launched a new platform called OpenAI Frontier for enterprises to build and manage agents, but OpenAI COO Brad Lightcap said that businesses haven&#8217;t yet seen AI adoption at scale. &#8220;One of the interesting things and some of the inspiration for the work we&#8217;ve been doing lately around OpenAI Frontier is we [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Lost Women of Alaska &#8212; stream chilling true-crime investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/lost-women-of-alaska</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mcWhUcQEnqtGWzv9wRbLp3</guid>
      <description>Dive into a chilling true-crime investigation docuseries. Here&#8217;s how to watch Lost Women of Alaska online from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Gigamaser&#8212;the Brightest Microwave Laser Ever Spotted in Deep Space</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meet-the-gigamaser-the-brightest-microwave-laser-ever-spotted-in-deep-space-2000725916</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725916</guid>
      <description>A lucky alignment of galaxies allowed researchers to identify the most powerful and distant "space laser" ever found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s Claude Comes for Knowledge Work as Markets Freak Out</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anthropics-claude-comes-for-knowledge-work-as-markets-freak-out-2000725881</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725881</guid>
      <description>Claude Cowork's industry-specific plug-in freaked out investors. Now, there is more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit fined $19.6 million over age verification checks in the UK</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/reddit-fined-196-million-over-age-verification-checks-in-the-uk-173705048.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab807f26-a5ba-44cb-bf96-2794ef0c4703</guid>
      <description>A common theme in online age verification laws is the tension between user privacy and preventing children from accessing harmful or inappropriate content. Now the UK is sending a not-so-subtle message to Reddit on the subject, to the tune of &#163;14.5m ($19.6 million). The nation's Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) accused the company of using children&#8217;s data and potentially exposing them to inappropriate content.&#8220;Children under 13 had their personal information collected and used in ways they could not understand, consent to or control,&#8221;  UK Information Commissioner John Edwards wrote in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the Limited Edition DualSense controllers I covet the most has had its price slashed at PlayStation Direct</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/one-of-the-limited-edition-dualsense-controllers-i-covet-the-most-has-had-its-price-slashed-at-playstation-direct</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sp36akzzKoFPnSbW7piGNi</guid>
      <description>Even though I have loads of PS5 controllers already, I can't help but want this limited edition variant &#8212; which is reduced at PS Direct right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec cette remise de 30 %, le Sony Inzone H9 II gomme un de ses principaux d&#233;fauts</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2987807_avec-cette-remise-de-30-le-sony-inzone-h9-ii-gomme-un-de-ses-principaux-defauts</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2987807_avec-cette-remise-de-30-le-sony-inzone-h9-ii-gomme-un-de-ses-principaux-defauts</guid>
      <description>
Critiqu&#233; &#224; sa sortie pour son manque d'autonomie et son prix assez important, le Sony Inzone H9 II profite de cette remise de cent euros sur Amazon pour corriger ce dernier d&#233;faut.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripe&#8217;s valuation soars 74% to $159 billion</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/stripes-valuation-soars-74-to-159-billion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096138</guid>
      <description>Stripe has conducted another tender offer, where employees sell shares. Investors include Thrive Capital, Coatue, a16z, and Stripe itself</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation&#8217;s Wolverine game hits PS5 in September</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/883760/playstation-marvels-wolverine-release-date-insomniac-games</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T12:23:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883760</guid>
      <description>Marvel's Wolverine, the next superhero game from Marvel's Spider-Man developer Insomniac Games, will be released on PS5 on September 15th. Insomniac announced that it would be making a Wolverine game way back in 2021, so it's been a long wait in the leadup to an official release date. Sony gave a vague fall 2026 release [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Jony Ive&#8217;s advice to young creatives</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497758/read-jony-ives-advice-to-young-creatives</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T17:19:06</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497758/read-jony-ives-advice-to-young-creatives</guid>
      <description>Two new books, freely released by the Steve Jobs Archive, feature invaluable advice to aspiring minds. In this exclusive excerpt, we hear from Jony Ive.
The advice you get early in your career can disproportionately shape your future. I can recall two or three conversations from when I was a college kid who liked writing that melted away ambiguity and set my vague ambitions on a path into the fog like a compass.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capcom was initially 'skeptical' about Resident Evil Requiem running well on the Nintendo Switch 2, but was pleasantly surprised, says director &#8212; 'With specs like these in handheld mode, it looks great'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/capcom-was-initially-skeptical-about-resident-evil-requiem-running-well-on-the-nintendo-switch-2-but-was-pleasantly-surprised-says-director-with-specs-like-these-in-handheld-mode-it-looks-great</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jYRay76SxSkivmKFamPkub</guid>
      <description>Resident Evil Requiem director Koshi Nakanishi has revealed that Capcom was initially "skeptical" about the game's Nintendo Switch 2 performance, but was pleasantly surprised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archer Aviation accuses rival Vertical Aerospace of ripping off its air taxi designs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/883648/archer-vertical-patent-infringement-air-taxi</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T12:16:20-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883648</guid>
      <description>Look at the two air taxi designs above. Look similar? The company that designed the one on the left sure thinks so, which is why it's accusing the firm that designed the one on the right of patent infringement. On Monday, Archer Aviation filed a complaint in the US District Court Eastern District of Texas [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;This should terrify you&#8217;: Meta Superintelligence safety director lost control of her AI agent&#8212;it deleted her emails</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497841/meta-superintelligence-lab-ai-safety-alignment-director-lost-control-of-agent-deleted-her-emails</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T17:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497841/meta-superintelligence-lab-ai-safety-alignment-director-lost-control-of-agent-deleted-her-emails</guid>
      <description>OpenClaw nearly wiped out the AI alignment employee&#8217;s entire inbox, in an incident that social media is calling ironic.
As built-in AI pops up in more aspects of everyday life, laymen are counting on the experts to keep technology safe to use. But one Meta employee&#8217;s misadventure with AI has social media users fearful for the future of AI alignment....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google claims it's building data centers that barely use any water</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-claims-its-building-data-centers-that-barely-use-any-water-171411965.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a885e088-5d1d-479a-b6a5-4e7410133086</guid>
      <description>Google is building another data center in Texas and says this one will use "advanced air-cooling technology" to limit water consumption. Google is claiming that water use will be limited to "critical campus operations" like kitchens.
These specifics follow the previously announced two-year $40 billion investment the company has pledged in the Lone Star State. The company is also touting some 7,800 megawatts of net energy generation and capacity it has contracted with utility providers to add to the Texas grid.
The company's resource-conscious commitments come as communities nationwide are push...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s AI Slop Machine Is Coming for Your Music</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-ai-slop-machine-coming-for-your-music-2000725892</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725892</guid>
      <description>The AI slop apparatus knows no bounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI signs up the world's biggest consultancy firms to help roll out ChatGPT to enterprises</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/openai-signs-up-the-worlds-biggest-consultancy-firms-to-help-roll-out-chatgpt-to-enterprises</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kC2yMjRYLXNpYywKxDXCg7</guid>
      <description>Accenture, BCG, Capgemini and McKinsey will be OpenAI Frontie partners to help enterprises with agentic AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He built a hit podcast about the Epstein files. It&#8217;s entirely AI-generated</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497873/epstein-files-ai-podcast-adam-levy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T17:06:42</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497873/epstein-files-ai-podcast-adam-levy</guid>
      <description>Built by a data entrepreneur, the automated show is publishing episodes at a pace traditional newsrooms can&#8217;t match.
The Epstein Files are dominating nightly news broadcasts and newspaper front pages. But in the media ecosystem there&#8217;s another format that&#8217;s proving a massive draw to news consumers: a podcast run by a non-journalist and entirely generated by AI....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI sues over the FCC&#8217;s decision to block new drone imports</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/883734/dji-fcc-lawsuit-drone-import-ban</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T12:01:44-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883734</guid>
      <description>DJI wants a federal court to toss out the Federal Communications Commission's decision to ban imports of its China-made drones and components, as reported earlier by Reuters. In a petition filed in an appeals court this week, DJI claims the FCC "exceeded its statutory authority" last December when adding drones made in foreign countries to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai test&#233; la Tesla Model 3 Propulsion, s&#251;rement la meilleure voiture &#233;lectrique du moment</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2984777_jai-teste-la-tesla-model-3-propulsion-pourquoi-cest-peut-etre-la-meilleure-voiture-electrique-du-moment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2984777_jai-teste-la-tesla-model-3-propulsion-pourquoi-cest-peut-etre-la-meilleure-voiture-electrique-du-moment</guid>
      <description>
J'ai test&#233; la Tesla Model 3 Propulsion, la voiture &#233;lectrique la moins ch&#232;re de l'histoire de la marque. En la proposant au m&#234;me prix qu'une citadine &#233;lectrique, Tesla tient-il le meilleur rapport qualit&#233; / prix du moment ou est-il all&#233; trop loin dans les sacrifices ? Voici notre avis.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube's Premium Lite tier gets background play and downloads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/youtubes-premium-lite-tier-gets-background-play-and-downloads-170051755.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eec36e40-5835-4f1f-9399-070cde9e3228</guid>
      <description>YouTube is adding new features to its Premium Lite plan. The tier will offer background play and downloads for the mostly ad-free plan. The update comes a year after YouTube first launched the lower-cost plan.
The Premium Lite tier is notable because for $8 per month you get most videos ad-free, emphasis on most. Currently, it still uses ads for YouTube music (along with random other videos), but the new update is bringing more Premium tier features without the $14 per month price tag.
As a Lite user, you will be able to use background play on most videos. Notably, this announcement comes less...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#8217;t Stop Thinking About the &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; T-Shirt in This 2004 Hilary Duff Movie</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hilary-duff-cinderella-story-star-wars-shirt-2000722994</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722994</guid>
      <description>'A Cinderella Story' includes a very weird 'Star Wars' reference and we're determined to get to the bottom of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube&amp;#8217;s cheaper subscription is getting background play and downloads</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/883316/youtube-premium-lite-background-play-offline-downloads</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883316</guid>
      <description>YouTube is adding background playback and offline downloads to YouTube Premium Lite, its $7.99-per-month subscription. With the change, you'll be able to keep YouTube videos going while you use another app on your phone or save videos to watch when you're offline. YouTube Premium Lite came to the US just about a year ago as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube beefs up its $7.99/month Lite subscription with offline downloads and background play</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/youtube-beefs-up-its-7-99-month-lite-subscription-with-downloads-and-background-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096090</guid>
      <description>Now the only reason to get the full Premium subscription is ad-free music and music videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese firms are quietly making a huge bet on the U.S. housing market</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497771/america-housing-market-bet-by-japanese-homebuilders</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497771/america-housing-market-bet-by-japanese-homebuilders</guid>
      <description>Japanese builders are rapidly acquiring U.S. homebuilders&#8212;now Daiwa House is buying United Homes.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music generator ProducerAI joins Google Labs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/music-generator-producerai-joins-google-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096117</guid>
      <description>Wyclef Jean used Google's AI music tools on his new song "Back in Abu Dhabi."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Have Discovered the Bed Bug&#8217;s Greatest Fear</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-have-discovered-the-bed-bugs-greatest-fear-2000725898</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725898</guid>
      <description>Water is "intrinsically aversive" to bed bugs, a recent study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La s&#233;lection des meilleurs watercooling et ventirads pour PC gamer en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-hardware/884159_meilleurs-ventirads-watercooling-refroidissement-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-hardware/884159_meilleurs-ventirads-watercooling-refroidissement-pc</guid>
      <description>
Avoir un CPU surpuissant dans votre PC gaming, c'est bien, mais encore faut-il pouvoir le refroidir efficacement. Nous avons s&#233;lectionn&#233; pour vous les meilleurs compromis entre refroidissement et silence dans ce comparatif des meilleurs ventirads et watercooling AIO.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS Bridge&#160;: Xiaomi veut connecter ses appareils &#224; l&#8217;iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/ios-bridge-xiaomi-veut-connecter-ses-appareils-a-liphone.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1327877</guid>
      <description>Xiaomi veut se rapprocher de l'&#233;cosyst&#232;me Apple. &#192; la faveur d'HyperOS 3.1, le constructeur devrait lancer plusieurs nouvelles fonctions qui facilitent la connexion entre ses appareils (tablettes, PC, smartphones) et ceux d'Apple &#8212; iPhone et AirPods en t&#234;te.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked live &#8212; Galaxy S26 Ultra and what else to expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-february-2026-live-blog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZK2NvvCdCPnpn3mTeueeak</guid>
      <description>Samsung is holding its annual winter Unpacked event in San Francisco on February 25. We have live reports from the ground and around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Wednesday, February 25 (game #724)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-25-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sS4AjWsRMmYRYjiGi6M96K</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Wednesday, February 25 (game #1493)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-25-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">datXAN86Kxo8kXH4e6XehG</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Wednesday, February 25 (game #990)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-25-february-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hP9KLynTsP2xoFvjs55AVM</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Madison trailer takes Taylor Sheridan far away from the world of Yellowstone &#8212; and much closer to Netflix's most successful drama of all time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/the-madison-trailer-taylor-sheridan</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zjjbke7CxAnT58j9qKK5CF</guid>
      <description>The first trailer for the new Taylor Sheridan Paramount+ show The Madison has finally been released, and it's nothing like what I was expecting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&amp;#8217;s Claude Cowork is plugging AI into more boring enterprise stuff</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/883707/anthropic-claude-cowork-updates</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T11:43:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883707</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Anthropic announced updates to its Claude Cowork platform that allow the AI to help with a wider range of office tasks. Claude Cowork can now connect with several popular office apps, including Google Workspace, Docusign, and WordPress. New pre-built plug-ins can also automate tasks in a range of fields, including HR, design, engineering, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping for a new TV? Here are 9 TVs from Amazon that I'd buy with my own money, from $79.99</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/shopping-for-a-new-tv-here-are-9-tvs-from-amazon-that-id-buy-with-my-own-money-from-usd79-99</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">thDbABt9tadnNCVq7xizV7</guid>
      <description>If you're shopping for a new TV, I've rounded up my 9 favorite top-rated HD, 4K, and QLED displays from Amazon, with prices starting at just $79.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquis sues firewall provider SonicWall, alleges security failings with its firewall backup led to ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/24/marquis-sonicwall-lawsuit-ransomware-firewall-breach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096139</guid>
      <description>Fintech giant Marquis is suing its firewall provider SonicWall, claiming that an earlier breach with SonicWall allowed hackers to deploy ransomware on Marquis' network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new Overwatch game has just been revealed, but I wouldn't be surprised if you missed it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/mobile-gaming/a-new-overwatch-game-has-just-been-revealed-but-i-wouldnt-be-surprised-if-you-missed-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HrWJeLZ37RTaNqky7JpFud</guid>
      <description>A new Overwatch mobile game, Overwatch Rush, has been officially unveiled by Blizzard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple killed Dark Sky. Now its creators are trying again with a new weather app</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91497860/acme-weather-launch-dark-sky-apple</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-24T16:32:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91497860/acme-weather-launch-dark-sky-apple</guid>
      <description>Acme Weather brings back the team behind the cult-favorite forecast app, with new features designed to show uncertainty.
Dark Sky was a rarity in the app world. Universally beloved, the weather app had an uncanny ability to tell you when to expect rain, down to the minute. So when Apple announced plans to buy it six years ago, there was a collective sigh of frustration....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Mystery of Antarctica&#8217;s &#8216;Blood Falls&#8217; Has Finally Been Solved</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-last-mystery-of-antarcticas-blood-falls-has-finally-been-solved/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699db4cfa901a52a4c5a5b52</guid>
      <description>New research sheds light on what drives reddish water to emerge from underground to pour onto the Taylor Glacier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to tell Spotify&#8217;s algorithm where to go? Soon, you may be able to do just that</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/spotify/want-to-tell-spotifys-algorithm-where-to-go-soon-you-may-be-able-to-do-just-that</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ES5CmJ4fDHHiRYHChHfpe</guid>
      <description>Great recommendations, no notes? Thought not &#8211; and Spotify could actually be testing a way to change that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard finally revealed its long-rumored Overwatch mobile game</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/blizzard-finally-revealed-its-long-rumored-overwatch-mobile-game-162938590.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">434feac9-350a-4c17-b311-07297ac85f8f</guid>
      <description>Blizzard is finally bringing Overwatch to mobile devices, but not exactly in the way you think. The company isn't making a port of the mainline game. Rather, it just announced a spinoff called Overwatch Rush, which is being described as a "top-down hero shooter designed specifically for mobile set in the Overwatch universe."
There have been rumors about an Overwatch mobile game for what seems like a lifetime. Most people assumed this would appear as a straight port, but a brand-new game is also great. It's not being developed by Team 4, the group that works on the mainline game, but is being m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zendure devient fournisseur d&#8217;&#233;lectricit&#233; en Europe avec sa nouvelle offre &#224; prix dynamique Zenwave</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2988401_zendure-devient-fournisseur-delectricite-en-europe-avec-sa-nouvelle-offre-a-prix-dynamique-zenwave</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2988401_zendure-devient-fournisseur-delectricite-en-europe-avec-sa-nouvelle-offre-a-prix-dynamique-zenwave</guid>
      <description>
Le fabricant chinois Zendure, bien connu pour ses syst&#232;mes de stockage solaire domestique, franchit une nouvelle &#233;tape. Avec son offre &#171; Zenwave &#187;, la marque va proposer des contrats d'&#233;lectricit&#233; &#224; tarification dynamique en Europe. Une &#233;volution logique pour rentabiliser au maximum ses batteries, m&#234;me sans soleil.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The powerful Roborock Qrevo Curv S5X Robot Vacuum and Mop is on sale at Amazon for a major $500 off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-24-roborock-qrevo-curv-s5x-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02pKUUiPRcfCE0uQFfK42VK</guid>
      <description>The Roborock Qrevo Curv S5X Robot Vacuum and Mop is on sale at Amazon for $649.99, down from the normal price of $1,149.99. That's a 43% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're working with an infinite set of minds': Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella says AI can offer your business so much more than you ever thought possible</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/were-working-with-an-infinite-set-of-minds-microsoft-ceo-satya-nadella-says-ai-can-offer-your-business-so-much-more-than-you-ever-thought-possible</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KnmeQH8nach77ruH7a7hv3</guid>
      <description>AI can offer, &#8220;a new metaphor for how we work with applications and computers&#8221;, says Microsoft's Satya Nadella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#192; moins de 75 &#8364;, cette cam&#233;ra de s&#233;curit&#233; connect&#233;e 2K dop&#233;e &#224; l&#8217;IA ne loupe aucun intrus</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2987607_a-moins-de-75-e-cette-camera-de-securite-connectee-2k-dopee-a-lia-ne-loupe-aucun-intrus</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2987607_a-moins-de-75-e-cette-camera-de-securite-connectee-2k-dopee-a-lia-ne-loupe-aucun-intrus</guid>
      <description>
L'Ezviz HB8 Lite est une cam&#233;ra connect&#233;e outdoor qui peut non seulement filmer en 2K, mais aussi d&#233;tecter les humains et les v&#233;hicules gr&#226;ce &#224; l'IA. Un mod&#232;le complet que Boulanger propose &#224; 74,99 euros au lieu de 129,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dreame X50 Ultra just dropped to $899.99 &#8212; now $450 less than the X60 version that just came out</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-24-dreame-x50-ultra-robot-vacuum-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Eonji2ETKx8vUYvAASzyd</guid>
      <description>The Dreame X50 Ultra has just as powerful suction as the brand new Roborock Qrevo Curv 2 Flow, but the Dreame is $100 cheaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report claims Microsoft's 'This Is an Xbox' campaign was hated by employees</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-industry/new-report-claims-microsofts-this-is-an-xbox-campaign-was-hated-by-employees</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jhduYX85m75z2ovHML6TVL</guid>
      <description>Microsoft's 'This Is an Xbox' campaign was reportedly disliked by many employees who were even 'offended' by the initiative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth&#8217;s Largest Land-Based Carbon Sink Has Sprung a Disturbing Leak</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/earths-largest-land-based-carbon-sink-has-sprung-a-disturbing-leak-2000725905</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725905</guid>
      <description>The Congo Basin&#8217;s peatlands have stored carbon for millennia, but new research suggests much of it is now escaping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best price ever alert: Save over $53 on the Garmin Vivoactive 6 smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-24-garmin-vivoactive-6-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04Rf0OxgPP7IUozqEWANFgu</guid>
      <description>The Garmin Vivoactive 6 smartwatch is down to $246.95 at Amazon, which is the lowest price on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le prix des &#233;quipements Wi-Fi 7 va tr&#232;s bient&#244;t augmenter selon ce rapport</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2988045_le-prix-des-equipements-wi-fi-7-va-tres-bientot-augmenter-selon-ce-rapport</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2988045_le-prix-des-equipements-wi-fi-7-va-tres-bientot-augmenter-selon-ce-rapport</guid>
      <description>
Si vous envisagez d'acheter des appareils compatibles Wi-Fi 7, ne tardez pas trop.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top ad tech firm Optimizely hit by data breach - around 10,000 companies possibly affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/top-ad-tech-firm-optimizely-hit-by-data-breach-around-10-000-companies-possibly-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5E3v5R4E3anW5743bfiJhL</guid>
      <description>Attack points to another breach by ShinyHunters, but the group has not yet claimed responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare for power outages, road trips, and off-grid weekends &#8212; the EcoFlow Delta 2 Max handles it all, and it&#8217;s got a massive half-price discount right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/prepare-for-power-outages-road-trips-and-off-grid-weekends-the-ecoflow-delta-2-max-handles-it-all-and-its-got-a-massive-half-price-discount-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">k2ksnyYMyKnVroUnWrjf3Z</guid>
      <description>Get your home ready for the next outage with the EcoFlow Delta 2 Max portable power station, currently half-price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix, Disney+ and other major streaming services face stricter UK oversight</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/netflix-disney-and-other-major-streaming-services-face-stricter-uk-oversight-160121268.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70c5ebe8-e98c-4293-a298-541fa478c105</guid>
      <description>Netflix, Disney+, Amazon's Prime Video and other major video on-demand (VOD) streaming services are set to face stricter regulation in the UK. Platforms with a monthly average of more than 500,000 UK viewers will be deemed &#8220;Tier 1" services that are subject to similar oversight as broadcasters like the BBC and ITV under the eye of media watchdog Ofcom.&#160;Streaming services run by public broadcasters like ITVX and Channel 4 will have to abide by the new rules as well. BBC services such as iPlayer are exempt for now as they&#8217;re regulated under the Broadcasting Code, which broadcasters have to adher...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's no gaming chair quite like the ThunderX3 Core, and after two years, I'm still stuck to it like glue</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/thunderx3-core-gaming-chair-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8hW9AsxpHoCvECNQnVnS6W</guid>
      <description>The ThunderX3 Core gaming chair is an excellent ergonomic seat that adapts to your awkward positioning and ensures you're comfy and supported while you game.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
