<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:24:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle has one last Ampere hurrah - new cloud platforms offer up to 192 custom Arm cores, and aren't OCI exclusive, unlike Graviton or Cobalt</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/oracle-has-one-last-ampere-hurrah-new-cloud-platforms-offer-up-to-192-custom-arm-cores-and-arent-oci-exclusive-unlike-graviton-or-cobalt</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JGsv6yN6ZqpPvjP8m5uZQj</guid>
      <description>Oracle launches A4 Standard cloud instances with AmpereOne M cores, offering high-performance CPU configurations and emphasizing silicon neutrality for flexible deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok CEO&amp;#8217;s memo tells employees it will be sold in January</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847858/tiktok-sale-deal-memo-january-close</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T18:18:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847858</guid>
      <description>TikTok has finalized the deal to sell its US business, according to reports from Axios, The Hollywood Reporter, and CNBC. In an internal memo seen by the outlets, TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew wrote that the deal will close on January 22nd, with Oracle, Silver Lake, and Abu Dhabi's MGX owning 45 percent of the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Winter Sale discounts Clair Obscur, Silent Hill f and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/steam-winter-sale-discounts-clair-obscur-silent-hill-f-and-more-230834279.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fff0866f-f12e-4610-a91e-6d492ad68e23</guid>
      <description>Holiday shopping is in full swing, which means it's about time for the Steam Winter Sale. This go-around, Valve&#8217;s sale runs from December 18, 2025 through January 5, 2026, and includes discounts on some of this year's hit games, like Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, Silent Hill f and Assassin's Creed Shadows.Clair Obscur is available for $40, down from its normal $50, Silent Hill f is 40 percent off, bringing its price down to $42, and the normally $70 Assassin's Creed Shadows is selling for $35, a solid deal on what was somewhat of a comeback for the long-running Ubisoft series. On top of those s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried the Apple Music app for ChatGPT, and it felt like talking to a music&#8209;obsessed friend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/i-tried-the-apple-music-app-for-chatgpt-and-it-felt-like-talking-to-a-music-obsessed-friend</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iwt4FGDnRTbeBtejnapkSK</guid>
      <description>I tested the newly launched Apple Music app inside ChatGPT and found it to be a surprisingly intuitive way to discover and build playlists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s NotebookLM introduces Data Tables feature</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/googles-notebooklm-introduces-data-tables-feature-225548565.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c24b2e7-64c5-478a-8677-a8c8da41e9aa</guid>
      <description>Google's latest addition to its NotebookLM artificial intelligence research platform is a feature called Data Tables. The tool can collect and synthesize information across multiple sources into a chart that can be exported to Google Sheets. All Pro and Ultra users will have access to the feature today, and Data Tables will roll out to all users over the coming weeks.In practice, Google suggested that Data Tables can be used to organize scattered notes, create price comparison charts or aggregate results from multiple research projects. The example of the interface shows the desired table comp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just in time for Christmas, the Apple Watch 11 is up to AU$132 off &#8211; a new Aussie low that's better than Black Friday!</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/just-in-time-for-christmas-the-apple-watch-11-is-up-to-au-aud132-off-a-new-aussie-low-thats-better-than-black-friday</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KPA2XWkgQ3ALEC88CbkgaW</guid>
      <description>The Apple Watch Series 11 is a fantastic health and fitness addition to pair with your iPhone, offering plenty of insight into your activity levels &#8211; it's on sale now at a record-low price starting at just AU$547.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Bluey&#8217; Game Celebrates a Story Anyone Can Play With</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-new-bluey-game-celebrates-a-story-anyone-can-play-with-2000701020</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701020</guid>
      <description>'Quest for the Gold Pen' leverages a beloved 'Bluey' premise to help embrace your inner child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's about time! Microsoft finally kills off encryption cipher blamed for multiple cyberattacks - RC4 bites the dust at last</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/its-about-time-microsoft-finally-kills-off-encryption-cipher-blamed-for-multiple-cyberattacks-rc4-bites-the-dust-at-last</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8E5TEoTtyBTuP93xU7sHuc</guid>
      <description>Microsoft moves to disable RC4 after decades of exploitation, implementing AES-SHA1 encryption, tools, and network protections for safer systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads wants to be the app you can&#8217;t wait to open in the morning</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/847806/head-of-threads-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T17:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847806</guid>
      <description>This is an excerpt of Sources by Alex Heath, a newsletter about AI and the tech industry, syndicated just for The Verge subscribers once a week. By all measures, Meta's Threads app had a very good year. The app was Apple's second-most-downloaded iOS app of the year, trailing only ChatGPT. Threads now has 400 million [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh snap, I have a new favorite phone grip</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/847777/oh-snap-i-have-a-new-favorite-phone-grip</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T17:29:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847777</guid>
      <description>In 2022, we called a simple magnetic ring from Anker the best MagSafe phone grip, but things have evolved dramatically since then! You can buy two or even three magnetic rings joined at the hip these days to wield your iPhone, recent Pixel, or really any phone if you stick a magnetic case or included [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying New Photos Emerge From the Jeffrey Epstein Estate</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/house-oversight-jeffrey-epstein-photos-december-18-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6944381a17f8230f56a8494a</guid>
      <description>The latest photo dump from Democrats in the House Oversight Committee includes more famous men and upsetting Lolita quotes written on a woman's body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to downgrade marijuana, breaking with GOP hardline stance</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463266/trump-moves-to-downgrade-marijuana-breaking-with-gop-hardline-stance</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T22:22:18</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463266/trump-moves-to-downgrade-marijuana-breaking-with-gop-hardline-stance</guid>
      <description>The president signed an executive order reclassifying marijuana as a Schedule III drug, opening the door to more research and limited Medicare reimbursement for CBD.
The days of Republicans&#8217; hard stances against marijuana have seemingly gone up in smoke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh, the Irony: Microsoft&#8217;s Push for Copilot+ PCs Could Stall Laptop Sales</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/microsofts-push-for-copilot-plus-pcs-could-stall-laptop-sales-2000701505</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701505</guid>
      <description>Windows users can't go back to 8GB of RAM, but laptop makers may not have a choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam&#8217;s annual winter sale is here &#8212; these are the best games to get</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/846242/best-steam-winter-sale-game-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T17:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846242</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re lucky enough to have a bit of time off around the holidays, we have great news: Steam&#8217;s annual winter sale kicked off today, and will run through Monday, January 5th at 1PM ET. Now&#8217;s a great time to stock up on some of the best games of 2025 at a solid discount, or [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new &#8216;smallest&#8217; subwoofer packs deep bass into a 10-inch cube &#8211; 1 driver, 2 radiators, 25Hz, 200W of power</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/this-new-smallest-subwoofer-packs-deep-bass-into-a-10-inch-cube-1-driver-2-radiators-25hz-200w-of-power</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">p9g3GAteH4aLohpL6isaGX</guid>
      <description>IK Multimedia's small iLoud Sub promises big booms, but with accuracy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI and Anthropic will start predicting when users are underage</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/847780/openai-anthropic-teen-safety-chatgpt-claude</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T16:55:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=847780</guid>
      <description>OpenAI and Anthropic are rolling out new ways to detect underage users. As OpenAI has updated its guidelines on how ChatGPT should interact with users between the ages of 13 and 17, Anthropic is working on a new way to identify and boot users who are under 18. On Thursday, OpenAI announced that ChatGPT's Model [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG will let you delete the previously unremovable Microsoft Copilot shortcut on its smart TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/lg-will-let-you-delete-the-previously-unremovable-microsoft-copilot-shortcut-on-its-smart-tvs-215352944.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c09589-49ec-43d9-b897-fb88b2ee50dc</guid>
      <description>Several LG smart TV owners, including some Engadget staff, were surprised to find what looked like an unremovable Microsoft Copilot app suddenly installed on their devices earlier this week. After all the raised eyebrows, a representative from LG has reached out to say that the company "will take steps to allow users to delete the shortcut icon if they wish."
According to the spokesperson, the Copilot icon is a shortcut for launching the AI chatbot in the TV's web browser rather than an application embedded in the appliance. We've asked for more specifics about when people will be able to get ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can eating cheese lower your dementia risk? A new study says maybe</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462848/can-eating-cheese-lower-your-dementia-risk-a-new-study-says-maybe</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T21:50:37</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462848/can-eating-cheese-lower-your-dementia-risk-a-new-study-says-maybe</guid>
      <description>Researchers say the benefits may come from eating cheese instead of processed meats, not from cheese itself.
Don&#8217;t beat yourself up if you do some serious damage on a cheese plate during holiday festivities this year: You just may do your future self a favor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Has a New Chief. Here&#8217;s What He Could Do in His First 20 Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-has-a-new-chief-heres-what-he-could-do-in-his-first-20-days-2000701547</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701547</guid>
      <description>Newly minted NASA administrator Jared Isaacman has expressed a desire to shake things up at NASA. It appears he&#8217;ll hit the ground running.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Is Going Into the New Year With Some Real Loser Energy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-is-going-into-the-new-year-with-some-real-loser-energy-2000701439</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701439</guid>
      <description>The slop machine giveth, and the slop machine taketh away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's not just RAM getting more expensive - the tools to make chips are set to explode in cost too, experts warn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/its-not-just-ram-getting-more-expensive-the-tools-to-make-chips-are-set-to-explode-in-cost-too-experts-warn</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vKihdx5Ex3m98G5cmtJziM</guid>
      <description>Chipmakers are spending more as components become more advanced and demand for AI hardware continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugh Jackman&#8217;s New Movie Has a Bunch of Talking Sheep Solve His Murder</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hugh-jackmans-new-movie-has-a-bunch-of-talking-sheep-solve-his-murder-2000701407</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701407</guid>
      <description>What the flock is even happening in 'The Sheep Detectives'?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
