<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:24:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>California AG sends Musk&#8217;s xAI a cease-and-desist order over sexual deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/california-ag-sends-musks-xai-a-cease-and-desist-order-over-sexual-deepfakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083559</guid>
      <description>The flood of AI-generated sexual imagery has spurred concern from state and Congressional officials alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Phone Is Still (Checks Notes) a Deflating Vortex of BS</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-trump-phone-is-still-checks-notes-a-deflating-vortex-of-bs-2000711144</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711144</guid>
      <description>In the latest headache-inducing update, there are now dubious figures surrounding this ultra-dubious phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George R.R. Martin Will Either Finish &#8216;The Winds of Winter&#8217; or Die Trying</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/george-rr-martin-winds-of-winter-progress-2026-2000710720</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710720</guid>
      <description>As 'A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms' arrives on HBO, the author is once again addressing that long-awaited next entry in his 'A Song of Ice and Fire' book series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Google&#8217;s 'internal RL' could unlock long-horizon AI agents</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/how-googles-internal-rl-could-unlock-long-horizon-ai-agents</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zcu3WDQn2x9j1YRDXvXbn</guid>
      <description>Researchers at Google have developed a technique that makes it easier for AI models to learn complex reasoning tasks that usually cause LLMs to hallucinate or fall apart. Instead of training LLMs through next-token prediction, their technique, called internal reinforcement learning (internal RL), steers the model&#8217;s internal activations toward developing a high-level step-by-step solution for the input problem.&#160;Ultimately, this could provide a scalable path for creating autonomous agents that can handle complex reasoning and real-world robotics without needing constant, manual guidance.The limi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Campaign to Destroy Renee Good</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-campaign-to-destroy-renee-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6966a3a3f9b5628c6957b31f</guid>
      <description>After an ICE agent shot and killed the Minneapolis mother, conservative media launched an all-out attack on her reputation. Her identity as a queer woman was central to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is appealing a judge&#8217;s search monopoly ruling</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863710/google-search-antitrust-monopoly-appeal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T17:36:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863710</guid>
      <description>Google is appealing a federal court's decision ruling it an illegal online search monopolist. The company filed a notice to appeal on Friday, requesting a pause on the court-ordered remedies meant to restore competition to the online search market. "As we have long said, the Court's August 2024 ruling ignored the reality that people use [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN service for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/best-vpn-130004396.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad91508b-bbe1-44e8-a716-02724cbca3ac</guid>
      <description>As frustrating as it is that governments and businesses are running roughshod over our online freedoms, at least we have plenty of good VPNs to choose from to keep us protected online. There are so many fast, intelligently designed, full-featured and affordable services on the market that the biggest problem is picking one. For any use case, you can bet at least two providers will be neck-and-neck for first place.On the other hand, the VPN world is still the Wild West in some ways. It's easy enough to slap a cheap VPN together that the market is flooded with low-quality apps that put more mone...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Live as NASA&#8217;s Artemis 2 Moon Rocket Rolls Out to the Launch Pad</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/watch-live-as-nasas-artemis-2-moon-rocket-rolls-out-to-the-launch-pad-2000711257</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711257</guid>
      <description>The final stage of launch preparations officially kicks off tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA's $10 speaker reminded me of my first Bluetooth audio love &#8212; and yes, it still makes beautiful music</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/ikeas-usd10-speaker-reminded-me-of-my-first-bluetooth-audio-love-and-yes-it-still-makes-beautiful-music</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R9zVsiuP6qvYtYAcnFFmnP</guid>
      <description>Remember the Jawbone Jambox? It was an iconic Bluetooth speaker 15 years ago, and probably influenced many of the modern portable speakers, like IKEA's Kallsup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ReRAM is the replacement for (NAND) flash': $170 billion US tech company backs tiny startup in race to find the holy Grail of universal memory</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/reram-is-the-replacement-for-nand-flash-usd170-billion-us-tech-company-backs-tiny-startup-in-race-to-find-the-holy-grail-of-universal-memory</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TxDYQkPRBGufDosV6oGNzQ</guid>
      <description>Weebit&#8217;s ReRAM shows higher speed, density, and reliability than flash memory, gaining backing from TI and industry-wide attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Launches Cheaper Subscriptions, Starts Testing Ads Because It&#8217;s Time to Pay the Piper</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-launches-cheaper-subscriptions-starts-testing-ads-because-its-time-to-pay-the-piper-2000711284</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711284</guid>
      <description>The inevitable is beginning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X is fully online after going down for most of the morning</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/x-is-fully-online-after-going-down-for-most-of-the-morning-171843711.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">814237b9-63ca-4ae5-9c95-a454783a5e0b</guid>
      <description>X seems to be working again after struggling with an outage that took the service offline and made it slow to load for much of the morning. According to X&#8217;s developer platform page,  there is an ongoing incident related to streaming endpoints that&#8217;s caused increased errors. The incident started at 7:39AM PT, according to the page.That roughly coincides with a spike in reports at Down Detector. The issues seemed to be somewhat intermittent. At some points, X&#8217;s website loaded partially and only showed older posts. At other times, the app and website failed to load at all. As of 9:30AM PT, X&#8217;s Ex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s Tariffs Just Opened the Door for Chinese EVs in Canada</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trumps-tariffs-just-opened-the-door-for-chinese-evs-in-canada-2000711286</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711286</guid>
      <description>Our neighbors to the north are slashing tariffs on Chinese EVs as tensions with the U.S. continue to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake, Databricks challenger ClickHouse hits $15B valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/snowflake-databricks-challenger-clickhouse-hits-15b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083539</guid>
      <description>The $400 million round was led by Dragoneer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I played the Nintendo DS game threatening Clair Obscur: Expedition 33&#8217;s Metacritic ranking &#8212; here&#8217;s how it went</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/i-played-the-nintendo-ds-game-threatening-clair-obscur-expedition-33s-metacritic-ranking-heres-how-it-went</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6MXh53258AKGND2Kt3U3TP</guid>
      <description>I played the Disney game threatening Clair Obscur: Expedition 33&#8217;s top Metacritic ranking &#8212; is it actually good?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA commissioner&#8217;s drug review plan sparks alarm across the agency</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476805/fda-commissioners-drug-review-plan-sparks-alarm-across-the-agency</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T21:57:37</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476805/fda-commissioners-drug-review-plan-sparks-alarm-across-the-agency</guid>
      <description>Questions about the legality of the program led the FDA&#8217;s then-drug director,&#160;Dr. George Tidmarsh, to decline to sign off on approvals under the pathway.
The Food and Drug Administration&#160;commissioner&#8217;s effort to&#160;drastically shorten&#160;the review of drugs&#160;favored by President Donald Trump&#8217;s administration&#160;is causing alarm across the agency, stoking worries that the plan may run afoul of legal, ethical, and scientific standards long used to vet the safety and effectiveness of new medicines....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is appealing the ruling from its search antitrust case to avoid sharing data with rivals</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/google-is-appealing-the-ruling-from-its-search-antitrust-case-to-avoid-sharing-data-with-rivals-215107905.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21fa5385-9409-4dc8-8d6c-bc2d0d139dac</guid>
      <description>Google has filed its appeal to the Department of Justice&#8217;s antitrust case that ended with a federal judge ruling that the company was maintaining a monopoly with its search business. While the company goes through the appeals process, it&#8217;s also asking that implementation of the remedies from the case, which include a requirement that Google share search data with its competitors, also be paused.&#8220;As we have long said, the Court&#8217;s August 2024 ruling ignored the reality that people use Google because they want to, not because they&#8217;re forced to,&#8221; Google said in a statement. &#8220;The decision failed to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic (an AI Company) Warns That AI Will Worsen Inequality</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anthropic-an-ai-company-warns-that-ai-will-worsen-inequality-2000710841</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710841</guid>
      <description>It's a shame it's being forced at gunpoint to build the inequality machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Seems Pleased With How Those &#8216;Avengers: Doomsday&#8217; Teasers Did</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marvel-seems-pleased-with-how-those-avengers-doomsday-teasers-did-2000711225</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711225</guid>
      <description>The four clips got over a billion views online, mostly from Instagram and TikTok instead of YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok is rolling out a new age-detection system in the EU</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tiktok-rolling-out-age-detection-system-to-keep-underage-users-off-the</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07ugUAa02GoM5ASbFWUANLE</guid>
      <description>TikTok's new age detection system will attempt to keep users under the age of 13 off the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellites Capture the Hidden World Beneath Antarctica&#8217;s Ice</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/satellites-capture-the-hidden-world-beneath-antarcticas-ice-2000711270</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711270</guid>
      <description>A new map of the landscape beneath the continent's ice sheet reveals a previously undiscovered terrain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your ChatGPT is about to get ads &#8212; here's what you need to know and how to opt out</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/your-chatgpt-is-about-to-get-ads-heres-what-you-need-to-know-and-how-to-opt-out</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MiszEavTH44BCSKzEQv2Bd</guid>
      <description>After countless rumors, OpenAI has confirmed that ads are coming to ChatGPT and they'll be a part of conversations. Here's how they will work and how you can opt out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens tariffs for countries if they oppose U.S. control of Greenland</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476786/trump-says-he-may-punish-countries-with-tariffs-if-they-dont-back-the-us-controlling-greenland</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T21:27:16</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476786/trump-says-he-may-punish-countries-with-tariffs-if-they-dont-back-the-us-controlling-greenland</guid>
      <description>Trump had not previously mentioned using tariffs to try to force the issue.
U.S. President Donald Trump suggested Friday that he may punish countries with tariffs if they don&#8217;t back the U.S. controlling&#160;Greenland, a message that came as a bipartisan Congressional delegation sought to lower tensions in the Danish capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good news! RAM prices seem to have finally stabilized - bad news, it's probably because memory prices are so high, that it's forcing most of us to give up buying anything</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/good-news-ram-prices-seem-to-have-finally-stabilized-bad-news-its-probably-because-memory-prices-are-so-high-that-its-forcing-most-of-us-to-give-up-buying-anything</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XyKFs8A6rgRTYvGWjycDZg</guid>
      <description>DDR5 prices surged dramatically in late 2025, then stabilized at extreme levels as buyers resisted further increases in high-capacity kits.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
