<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:40:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : les iPhone d&#8217;Apple, Samsung Galaxy et Google Pixel sont &#224; prix cass&#233; dans cette liste des meilleurs bons plans</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-soldes-dhiver-2026-demarrent-aujourdhui-voici-les-meilleures-offres-sur-les-smartphones-apple-samsung-et-xiaomi</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931029_les-soldes-dhiver-2026-demarrent-aujourdhui-voici-les-meilleures-offres-sur-les-smartphones-apple-samsung-et-xiaomi</guid>
      <description>
Du 7 janvier au 3 f&#233;vrier, les soldes d'hiver promettent de faire de bonnes affaires dans la tech, particuli&#232;rement aupr&#232;s des e-commer&#231;ants fran&#231;ais. C'est par exemple l'occasion de mettre la main sur un smartphone que le P&#232;re No&#235;l aurait oubli&#233; de d&#233;poser au pied du sapin.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; la nouvelle version des Ray-Ban Meta et leur bracelet neuronal qui ne sont pas encore disponibles en France</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/on-a-teste-la-nouvelle-version-des-ray-ban-meta-et-leur-bracelet-neuronal-qui-ne-sont-pas-encore-disponibles-en-france.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318980</guid>
      <description>Au CES 2026 Meta et Ray Ban ont d&#233;voil&#233; la derni&#232;re mise &#224; jour des lunettes et de leur Neural Band, le bracelet connect&#233; qui les accompagne. Dot&#233;es de nouvelles fonctionnalit&#233;s, elles s&#8217;imposent comme le mod&#232;le le plus avanc&#233; du march&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the tech trends we saw at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859244/ces-2026-highlights-trends</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:27:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=859244</guid>
      <description>CES&#160;is a lot &#8212; a deluge of consumer tech surrounded by lots of bad carpeting.&#160;The Verge&#8217;s on-the-ground team of super nerds covered so many new products and technologies that it&#8217;s understandable if it was all a little overwhelming. That&#8217;s why we&#8217;ve gathered up a collection of trend reports from the show to help make sense [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macy&#8217;s store closures 2026: See the full list of doomed locations in 12 states as clearance sales begin</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471941/macys-stores-closing-in-2026-full-list-of-doomed-locations-states</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T13:25:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471941/macys-stores-closing-in-2026-full-list-of-doomed-locations-states</guid>
      <description>The department store chain continues to reduce its physical footprint as part of a &#8220;Bold New Chapter.&#8221; Shares have risen 48% over the last 12 months.
Fans of Macy&#8217;s Inc. will be disappointed to learn that the iconic department store has announced its next round of store closures. Fourteen Macy&#8217;s locations in 12 states will shutter as a result of this move. Here&#8217;s why and when the closures will take place....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernize your business communication for less with Quo&#8217;s all-in-one phone system</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/phone-communications/modernize-your-business-communication-for-less-with-quos-all-in-one-phone-system</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EVddNF6oS3tumvLqxVGhec</guid>
      <description>Try the platform&#8217;s bells and whistles risk-free and get an exclusive 20% discount on your first three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cornichon, phare, m&#233;t&#233;orite&#160;: voici les futurs emojis d&#8217;iOS et d&#8217;Android</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/cornichon-phare-meteorite-voici-les-futurs-emojis-dios-et-dandroid.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319118</guid>
      <description>Nouvelle ann&#233;e, nouveaux &#233;mojis : le consortium Unicode a publi&#233; la liste des nouveaux emojis qui seront (probablement) int&#233;gr&#233;s dans de futures versions d'iOS, d'Android, dans les applications de messageries et ailleurs. Au menu : un cornichon, un phare, une m&#233;t&#233;orite ou encore un visage qui plisse les yeux.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"I have never seen such a thing in my life" &#8211; Iran completely shuts down the internet amid protests, Starlink also affected</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/i-have-never-seen-such-a-thing-in-my-life-iran-completely-shuts-down-the-internet-amid-protests-starlink-also-affected</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xxt8hvS4hXgFNuSA9NsCNg</guid>
      <description>Iranians have been offline for over 12 hours, with broadband, mobile and Starlink services affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, Grok hasn&amp;#8217;t paywalled its deepfake image feature</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/859309/grok-undressing-limit-access-gaslighting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:09:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859309</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's X has partially restricted access to Grok's image editing capabilities amid growing backlash to the flood of nonconsensual, sexualized deepfakes of adults and minors generated by the platform. As of this writing, it no longer generates images as @grok replies for free, but Grok's image editing tools remain readily available for any X [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft simplifie &#224; l&#8217;extr&#234;me l&#8217;ajout d&#8217;un lien dans un document Word</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/microsoft-simplifie-a-lextreme-lajout-dun-lien-dans-un-document-word.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319113</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;entreprise de Redmond est en train de tester un nouveau syst&#232;me, beaucoup plus simple, pour ins&#233;rer un lien hypertexte dans un document Word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where is the Trump phone? Golden iPhone rival misses another release date &#8211; as experts suggest it may never arrive</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/where-is-the-trump-phone-golden-iphone-rival-misses-another-release-date-as-experts-suggest-it-may-never-arrive</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">phqSUwbLnLF5RZwKFwecFW</guid>
      <description>The Trump Mobile T1 Phone still hasn&#8217;t shipped and its future appears to be uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu la nouvelle Peugeot 408 &#233;lectrique : elle a de la gueule, mais voici pourquoi &#231;a ne suffira pas</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2936113_on-a-vu-la-nouvelle-peugeot-408-electrique-elle-a-de-la-gueule-mais-voici-pourquoi-ca-ne-suffira-pas</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2936113_on-a-vu-la-nouvelle-peugeot-408-electrique-elle-a-de-la-gueule-mais-voici-pourquoi-ca-ne-suffira-pas</guid>
      <description>
C'est le probl&#232;me des voitures "coup de c&#339;ur" : on a tendance &#224; leur pardonner beaucoup. La nouvelle Peugeot 408, d&#233;voil&#233;e ce matin, mise tout sur son physique ravageur pour vous s&#233;duire. Le souci ? En 2026, face &#224; une Tesla Model 3 ou une Mercedes CLA, avoir de beaux yeux ne suffit plus. Surtout quand la technique fait du surplace.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should you upgrade to Gemini for Home? Tread carefully &#8211; some users are still reporting major bugs and problems</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/should-you-upgrade-to-gemini-for-home-tread-carefully-some-users-are-still-reporting-major-bugs-and-problems</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uLDTJMCtjUXATJ7hs7zCpU</guid>
      <description>Users who've made the jump to Gemini on their smart home are reporting several issues with functionality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Tangled&#8217; Casts Its Villain, and It Was Agatha All Along</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tangled-casts-its-villain-and-it-was-agatha-all-along-2000707887</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707887</guid>
      <description>Marvel's own Kathryn Hahn is in talks to play Mother Gothel in the live-action 'Rapunzel' remake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kia's budget EV2 arrives with up to 240 miles of range</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/kias-budget-ev2-arrives-with-up-to-240-miles-of-range-130038144.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc213d6-9e25-48cd-a9b4-512be70476b3</guid>
      <description>Kia has unveiled its new entry level electric vehicle, the EV2. The boxy model strongly resembles the company's Soul (Kia did make an electric Soul at one point) and has very similar dimensions, though it's slightly shorter in height and length. It's not exactly a range monster and will charge a bit slower than the competition. The EV2 launched at the Brussels Motor Show and the company said it has no plans for US availability at this point.&#160;
The EV2 uses Kia/Hyundai's E-GMP platform and slots into the bottom of its EV lineup as an "entry point to electric mobility," according to the automaker...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality still matters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/859055/minneapolis-renee-good-ice-shooting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859055</guid>
      <description>The first video I saw of the Minneapolis shooting was bad enough. Shortly after I saw it, I had the terrible realization that there were multiple people in the clip holding their phones up - another angle was bound to surface. Within minutes, a second video was all over social media, and it was even [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The venture firm that ate Silicon Valley just raised another $15 billion</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/09/the-venture-firm-that-ate-silicon-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081401</guid>
      <description>In a blog post published Friday morning, Ben Horowitz writes that "as the American leader in Venture Capital, the fate of new technology in the United States rests partly on our shoulders." It's the kind of statement certain to cause agita at rival firms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego is trying to make tech invisible with Smart Play</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/lego-is-trying-to-make-tech-invisible-with-smart-play-130000979.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a9113c-bd2c-4f18-a977-5b967ad4c25e</guid>
      <description>Probably my favorite thing about the Lego Smart Play system unveiled this week at CES is that it was designed for kids, first and foremost. In the past 10 years or so, Lego has increasingly courted an older audience with more expensive and elaborate sets. But when it was time to bring more advanced technology to Lego, the idea right from the beginning was more social and interactive play.&#160;If you haven&#8217;t heard about Smart Play yet, its a way for Lego to make its sets more interactive. A Smart Brick filled with sensors makes it so sets can respond to each other, know when they&#8217;re moving, play so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify is no longer running ads for ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/spotify-is-no-longer-running-ads-for-ice-130000672.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a2fcac3-5bc8-430d-87b7-0bb821f33b35</guid>
      <description>There are no recruitment ads for Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) running on Spotify at the moment, the streaming service has told Variety. A spokesperson has confirmed the news after an ICE agent fatally shot Renee Good in Minneapolis, but they also clarified that the ads stopped running in late 2025. &#8220;The advertisements mentioned were part of a US government recruitment campaign that ran across all major media and platforms,&#8221; they explained. Spotify caught flak back in October for playing ICE ads, asking people to &#8220;join the mission to protect America,&#8221; in between songs for users on ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 hands-on: Xreals world-first 240 Hz AR smart glasses made my jaw drop</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-xreal-1s-asus-r1-ar-smart-glasses-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06PYs8wMBypvN34Ko0Tk21G</guid>
      <description>Xreal brought out the big guns for CES 2026. The brand debuted the world's first AR glasses with a 240 Hz refresh rate, plus a new 3D conversion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigabyte may have just solved my biggest issue with OLED monitors at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/monitors/gigabyte-may-have-just-solved-my-biggest-issue-with-oled-monitors-at-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4WzRtRBT5JA5wAhCtjxLS</guid>
      <description>OLED monitors need fine tuning with brightness dimming issues, and Gigabyte may just have cracked this at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take five! Soundpeats&#8217; new affordable audiophile earbuds up the H3's driver count by two</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/our-favorite-affordable-audio-brands-new-earbuds-have-more-drivers-than-a-horse-has-legs</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wpJiD824WqvzygpqhwapuU</guid>
      <description>Soundpeats' Aura Nebula features a five-driver design for a temptingly low price</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Eintracht Frankfurt vs. Borussia Dortmund online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/eintracht-frankfurt-borussia-dortmund-bundesliga-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04Yo4FqrMZogec3df4IKMBg</guid>
      <description>How to watch Bundesliga for free. Watch Eintracht Frankfurt vs. Borussia Dortmund in the Bundesliga for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce SSD de Samsung avec une vitesse de lecture de 14,8 Go/s s&#8217;offre une baisse de 50 euros chez Amazon &#224; l&#8217;occasion des soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936687_ce-ssd-de-samsung-avec-une-vitesse-de-lecture-de-148-go-s-soffre-une-baisse-de-50-euros-chez-amazon-a-loccasion-des-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936687_ce-ssd-de-samsung-avec-une-vitesse-de-lecture-de-148-go-s-soffre-une-baisse-de-50-euros-chez-amazon-a-loccasion-des-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Chez Amazon, ce SSD 9100 Pro s'offre une baisse de 21 % et tombe &#224; 190,99 euros. L'occasion est donc parfaite pour se ruer sur un SSD capable de lire vos fichiers ou de lancer vos jeux favoris en un rien de temps.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brick-and-mortar bookshops look better than ever in the Amazon age</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468520/amazon-vs-local-bookstores</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T12:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468520/amazon-vs-local-bookstores</guid>
      <description>Digital books haven&#8217;t killed print ones. And even the smallest local stores can transcend Amazon&#8217;s increasingly chaotic shopping experience.
Welcome to the first Fast Company&#8217;s Plugged In of 2026, and Happy New Year to you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leapmotor B03X (2026) : on a vu la rival de la Renault 4 &#224; moins de 30 000 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/leapmotor/2937071_leapmotor-b03x-2026-on-a-vu-la-rival-de-la-renault-4-a-moins-de-30-000-e</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/leapmotor/2937071_leapmotor-b03x-2026-on-a-vu-la-rival-de-la-renault-4-a-moins-de-30-000-e</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que le segment B &#233;tait satur&#233; ? Attendez de voir le Leapmotor B03X. Pr&#233;sent&#233; &#224; Bruxelles, il devrait afficher un Cx de 0,26 et promettre 400 km d'autonomie r&#233;elle. Mais ce qui choque, c'est la finition. Pour une voiture annonc&#233;e sous les 30 000 euros, regardons ce qui a &#233;t&#233; pr&#233;sent&#233;.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honor Magic 8 Pro&#160;: il arrive bient&#244;t en France avec un zoom 200 Mpx et une batterie (presque) XXL</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/honor-magic-8-pro-il-arrive-bientot-en-france-avec-un-zoom-200-mpx-et-une-batterie-presque-xxl.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1319098</guid>
      <description>Le Honor Magic 8 Pro arrive &#224; l'international et notamment en Europe. S'il impressionne par son zoom 200 Mpx et sa batterie, il confirme aussi l'abandon de l'ouverture variable, un point technique qui fait d&#233;bat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the tech and gadgets announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/all-the-tech-and-gadgets-announced-at-ces-2026-130124023.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown off a wide ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsidian's Avowed is leaping from Xbox to PS5 next month</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/obsidians-avowed-is-leaping-from-xbox-to-ps5-next-month</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dVFuh4wkypsnSTZ5STXwb4</guid>
      <description>Yet another Xbox Game Studios title is coming to PS5 next month and it's one I like quite a bit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The OnePlus Turbo 6 has landed, with a 9,000mAh battery and serious gaming credentials</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/oneplus-phones/the-oneplus-turbo-6-has-landed-with-a-9-000mah-battery-and-serious-gaming-credentials</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QRCFQ4Dc7kCJfnnD5TMoAe</guid>
      <description>The OnePlus Turbo 6 and the OnePlus Turbo 6V combine big batteries with high refresh rates and surprisingly low prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not going to say prices across all these components will remain flat': AMD exec suggests price rises for Radeon GPUs are coming</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/im-not-going-to-say-prices-across-all-these-components-will-remain-flat-amd-exec-suggests-price-rises-for-radeon-gpus-are-coming</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aj4tzL5ZagFGfaswwa8LyC</guid>
      <description>In the face of the RAM crisis, AMD exec assures us Radeon GPU stock shortages aren't a concern &#8211; but price rises are likely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score over $30 off Samsung Galaxy Buds FE right now at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-samsung-galaxy-buds-fe-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02z6RLNgP6QrbK2CCHx08so</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 9, the Samsung Galaxy Buds FE are on sale at Amazon for $68.99, 31% off their list price of $99.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth Meyers has strong words for the Trump admins response to ICE shooting</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/seth-meyers-ice-shooting-trump-response</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02f14r5R5H5D8vO2hrCJtbO</guid>
      <description>Seth Meyers has reacted to the Trump administration's response to ICE fatally shooting 37-year-old mother Renee Good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Silent Hill 2 remake is now at its lowest-ever price on Amazon &#8212; save over $20</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-9-silent-hill-2-remake-ps5-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03GLfIVUtQ909qTdksm5W0J</guid>
      <description>Normally $49.99, the Silent Hill 2 remake on PS5 has had 45% cut off its price tag, now only $27.39.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beatbot Announces Two New Smart Pool Cleaners and a Major Rebrand at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/beatbot-announces-two-new-smart-pool-cleaners-and-a-major-rebrand-at-ces-2026-2000704799</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704799</guid>
      <description>Let these Beatbot devices do the hard work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Duffer Brothers Were Worried &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Fans Had &#8216;Demogorgon Fatigue&#8217; Before the Finale</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-duffer-brothers-were-worried-stranger-things-fans-had-demogorgon-fatigue-before-the-finale-2000707850</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707850</guid>
      <description>Turns out the opposite was true&#8212;and those flower-headed monsters being absent from the Abyss actually became a point of contention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Lawmakers Want Porn Taxes. Critics Say They&#8217;re Unconstitutional</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/conservative-lawmakers-want-porn-taxes-critics-say-theyre-unconstitutional/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d7cdd7dcfa58c62e92d06</guid>
      <description>Alabama passed a 10 percent porn tax last year, as Utah and Pennsylvania eye similar bills. Half the country has enacted age-verification laws to prevent minors from viewing porn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge Awards at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858494/ces-2026-best-new-tech-tv-car-wearable</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T07:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858494</guid>
      <description>Every January, the world of consumer electronics heads to Las Vegas to spend the first full week of the year in the desert presenting, prodding, and gawking at all the new gadgets and gear debuting at CES. The show has once again delivered an avalanche of products, both innovative and vaporous, that will shape the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2026 BAFTA Film Awards longlist has been announced &#8212; and Netflix fans might be surprised about one big absence</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/the-2026-bafta-film-awards-longlist-has-been-announced-and-netflix-fans-will-be-furious-about-one-big-absence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">p8LqsKSCXD7R6PsZQxdDQG</guid>
      <description>One Battle After Another leads this year's BAFTAs longlist, but fans might be confused about a big Netflix film's exclusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox is bringing Avowed to PS5</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/xbox-is-bringing-avowed-to-ps5-120000035.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a83ae4-ede9-449f-85d9-46d647e9efcb</guid>
      <description>Another first-party Xbox game is making the leap to PlayStation 5. This time around, Obsidian&#8217;s Avowed &#8212; one of our favorite games of last year &#8212; is crossing the great divide. The fantasy action RPG will hit Sony&#8217;s console on February 17, one day shy of the game&#8217;s first anniversary.&#160;As it happens, an anniversary update is set to go live on all platforms at the same time. This includes a new game+ mode (allowing those who have beaten the RPG to replay it with all their gear and upgrades from their previous run), a photo mode, a new weapon type and more.&#160;Avowed is set in the same universe as Obs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea&#8217;s best-selling donut lamp is getting a colorful upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470587/ikea-donut-lamp-colorful-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T12:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470587/ikea-donut-lamp-colorful-upgrade</guid>
      <description>The viral lamp will now come with smart tech that lets it cycle through dozens of colors.
One of Ikea&#8217;s most popular lamps of the past several years&#8212;nicknamed the &#8220;donut lamp&#8221;&#8212;is about to get a smart, colorful upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-blog-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03weFCUbfFvR5jPHEa0V0Ce</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu ce Roborock sur pattes, sauter, danser et monter les escaliers</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2935193_jai-vu-ce-roborock-sur-pattes-sauter-danser-et-monter-les-escaliers</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2935193_jai-vu-ce-roborock-sur-pattes-sauter-danser-et-monter-les-escaliers</guid>
      <description>
En plus de sa nouvelle gamme d'aspirateurs robots et un nouveau laveur de sols, Roborock a pr&#233;sent&#233; un prototype de robot avec des jambes extensibles et articul&#233;es, capable de sauter, monter les escaliers et m&#234;me danser. J'ai pu le voir en action au CES 2026 et il se d&#233;marque clairement des autres prototypes concurrents.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The weirdest tech of CES: It gets very weird, very fast</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-weird-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">072DGH89cKcfrrbdwYwFeU0</guid>
      <description>We've collected all the truly strange tech we saw this year in Vegas at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
