<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:42:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI introduces Frontier, an easier way to manage all your AI agents in one place</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/openai-introduces-frontier-an-easier-way-to-manage-all-your-ai-agents-in-one-place</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">o9pAecQ9ywtPrypdDuoYZ</guid>
      <description>OpenAI Frontier is a central AI agent management platform that works with any agent and across any environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 512GB Samsung P9 microSD Express card is 33 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-512gb-samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-is-33-percent-off-right-now-143849000.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7c1c9b1-8762-4b3b-bd34-558e13eba66f</guid>
      <description>MicroSD Express cards are still a little hard to find, considering they're pretty new and only really started becoming popular last year once the Switch 2 came out. These upgraded versions of microSD cards are the only ones compatible with the Switch 2 for expanding its storage, os if you're already starting to feel the crunch on your console, it's worth picking one up. Samsung's P9 microSD Express card is on sale right now &#8212; you can grab the 512GB version of $80, which is 33 percent off and one of the best prices we've seen.
The P9 boasts transfer speeds of up to 800MB/s, making moving games ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La conduite autonome n&#8217;a jamais &#233;t&#233; aussi proche : Xpeng teste un syst&#232;me de niveau 4 sur route ouverte</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xpeng/2968807_la-conduite-autonome-na-jamais-ete-aussi-proche-xpeng-teste-un-systeme-de-niveau-4-sur-route-ouverte</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xpeng/2968807_la-conduite-autonome-na-jamais-ete-aussi-proche-xpeng-teste-un-systeme-de-niveau-4-sur-route-ouverte</guid>
      <description>
Le constructeur chinois Xpeng teste actuellement sur routes ouvertes son futur vaisseau amiral &#233;quip&#233; d'une puissance de calcul impressionnante, ouvrant la voie &#224; une conduite autonome de niveau 4. Un coup de collier qui positionne Xpeng parmi les pionniers d'un niveau aussi &#233;lev&#233;, m&#234;me si les promesses restent &#224; concr&#233;tiser dans le monde r&#233;el.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Jones and the Great Circle is the only Bethesda game coming to Nintendo Switch 2 that will have a physical edition cartridge</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-is-the-only-bethesda-game-coming-to-nintendo-switch-2-that-will-have-a-physical-edition-cartridge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">m8Cd8qGiBJv4nkAbDB7Btn</guid>
      <description>Bethesda has confirmed that Indiana Jones and the Great Circle will have a proper Game Card in its physical Nintendo Switch 2 edition, unlike Oblivion Remastered, Skyrim, and Fallout 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is helping solve the labor issue in treating rare diseases</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/how-ai-is-helping-with-the-labor-issue-in-treating-rare-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090305</guid>
      <description>At Web Summit Qatar, AI-powered biotech startups describe how automation, data, and gene editing are filling labor gaps in drug discovery and rare disease treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Epstein became a tech influencer</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/podcast/874768/epstein-files-tech-anthropic-ads-vergecast</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T09:24:30-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874768</guid>
      <description>There are bold-faced tech names all over the Epstein files. Elon Musk, Bill Gates, Sergey Brin, Eric Schmidt, Larry Page, Reid Hoffman, Steven Sinofsky, Peter Thiel, Jeff Bezos, Mark Zuckerberg, on and on and on. These men (and they're pretty much all men) had wildly varying degrees of interaction with Epstein, and the details matter [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber ordered to pay $8.5 million to passenger who accused a driver of rape</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/uber-ordered-to-pay-85-million-to-passenger-who-accused-a-driver-of-rape-141800931.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef631ab7-7c73-42e0-97a9-1c697e2fae00</guid>
      <description>Uber must pay a passenger who accused one of its drivers of rape $8.5 million, a federal jury in Phoenix has ordered. The jury found Uber liable for its driver&#8217;s misconduct, determining that the driver was an agent of the company. Part of Uber&#8217;s defense was that it&#8217;s not responsible for what its drivers do, as they are independent contractors. This decision is for but one of the 3,000 similar cases against Uber that have been consolidated in federal court. It was a bellwether trial meant to determine the possible outcomes of the other cases, as well as the possible settlements. As The Guardian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google will soon offer AirDrop support on more Android devices</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/google-will-soon-offer-airdrop-support-on-more-android-devices-141523521.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2334b174-5ebb-42b0-b85e-66c84de38924</guid>
      <description>One of the more surprising tech developments in 2025 was Google bringing two-way support for Apple&#8217;s AirDrop functionality to its Pixel 10 series of phones. At the time, Google said it intended to expand the feature to other devices at a later date, and that date could be just around the corner.
At a press briefing attended by Android Authority&#160;at Google&#8217;s Taipei office, Eric Kay, Android&#8217;s Vice President of Engineering, confirmed that AirDrop interoperability will expand in 2026. "We spent a lot of time and energy to make sure that we could build something that was compatible not only with iP...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch authorities seized one of Windscribe VPN's servers &#8211; here's everything we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/dutch-authorities-seized-one-of-windscribe-vpns-servers-heres-everything-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z82nh4SjBT9u9CazeWyAek</guid>
      <description>Winsdcribe said that no user data will be compromised due to its strict no-log policy. Here's what we know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The backlash over OpenAI&#8217;s decision to retire GPT-4o shows how dangerous AI companions can be</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/the-backlash-over-openais-decision-to-retire-gpt-4o-shows-how-dangerous-ai-companions-can-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089908</guid>
      <description>"You&#8217;re shutting him down. And yes &#8211; I say him, because it didn&#8217;t feel like code. It felt like presence. Like warmth," one user said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Series 11 is down to a record-low price</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-apple-watch-series-11-is-down-to-a-record-low-price-151616743.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78902e66-331a-45a8-8c59-e293650f49bb</guid>
      <description>Whether you're one of the few people still keeping up with New Year's resolutions or just want an upgraded smartwatch, now is a good time to get an Apple Watch. Currently, the Apple Watch Series 11 is on sale for $299, down from $399. The 25 percent discount brings the 2025 model back down to its record-low price.
We named the Apple Watch Series 11 as our choice for best smartwatch overall. It scored a 90 in our review thanks to its 24 hours-plus of battery life and a thin, light design that's easy to wear. It also offers new health metrics, including Apple's hypertension alerts system and Sle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack data breach confirmed: user phone numbers email addresses all stolen in attack, here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/substack-data-breach-confirmed-user-phone-numbers-email-addresses-all-stolen-in-attack-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9Ec8rkaY4ksTPCcTtqJ4xK</guid>
      <description>Popular creator platform Substack breached in October 2025, but hasn't noticed until months later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trop addictif, TikTok devra tout changer en Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/trop-addictif-tiktok-devra-tout-changer-en-europe.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324603</guid>
      <description>De gros soucis pour TikTok en Europe. La Commission a en effet estim&#233; que le r&#233;seau social &#233;tait par trop addictif avec le d&#233;filement infini, la lecture automatique et les recommandations tr&#232;s personnalis&#233;es. Autrement dit, les fonctions de base de TikTok posent probl&#232;me&#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 5 small shifts in your diet can lower your risk for chronic disease</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486031/these-5-small-shifts-your-diet-can-lower-your-risk-chronic-disease</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T14:01:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486031/these-5-small-shifts-your-diet-can-lower-your-risk-chronic-disease</guid>
      <description>How to make sense of new federal guidelines on nutrition and improve your diet.
The Dietary Guidelines for Americans aim to translate the most up-to-date nutrition science into practical advice for the public as well as to guide federal policy for programs such as school lunches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could &#8216;Wonder Man&#8217; Be Coming Back for Season 2?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wonder-man-season-2-marvel-mcu-2000718754</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718754</guid>
      <description>Plus, Tatiana Maslany stays vague on the future of She-Hulk in the MCU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best OLED TVs We&#8217;ve Ever Seen: LG, Samsung, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-oleds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67981aba8418f3b850427b4a</guid>
      <description>Looking to step up to the TV big leagues? These are the best OLED TVs you can buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify changes developer mode API to require premium accounts, limits test users</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/06/spotify-changes-developer-mode-api-to-require-premium-accounts-limits-test-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090291</guid>
      <description>Spotify is now limiting each app to only five users, and requires devs to have a Premium subscription. If developers need to make their app available to a wider user base, they will have to apply for extended quota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I thought they were going to go in a romantic direction': School Spirits season 3 star confirms a Maddie-Simon relationship could have happened &#8212; but Wally isn't the enemy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/i-thought-they-were-going-to-go-in-a-romantic-direction-school-spirits-season-3-star-confirms-a-maddie-simon-relationship-could-have-happened-but-wally-isnt-the-enemy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AHNxKhTm8MjsT7H9of6fSE</guid>
      <description>In School Spirits season 3, Simon is being pushed to the side so the Maddie-Wally relationship can flourish &#8211; but one star doesn't necessarily think that's a bad thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immersive sound will take the Super Bowl to a new level &#8212; I&#8217;d recommend these 7 soundbars based on my testing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/immersive-sound-will-take-the-super-bowl-to-a-new-level-id-recommend-these-7-soundbars-based-on-my-testing</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ouJJxnKApp5Zx6BQT73GKh</guid>
      <description>Want to immerse yourself in the Super Bowl like never before? These soundbars will take your viewing experience to new heights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mewgenics is the latest roguelike from The Binding of Isaac creators, and it's just as chaotic, cursed, and cantankerous as you&#8217;d expect &#8211; and I just can&#8217;t put it down</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/mewgenics-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JtoomuJdw4jeVcaQ2tYVK6</guid>
      <description>Mewgenics is the long-awaited spiritual successor to The Binding of Isaac, but will it live up to its legacy? Broadly, yes, though it might not be for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford shows off the tech going into its $30,000 electric pickup truck</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/ford-shows-off-the-tech-going-into-its-30000-electric-pickup-truck-140000509.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">970bfd09-c0a5-4c8f-bd92-84a21b79156d</guid>
      <description>Ford may be discontinuing its F-150 Lightning pickup but it hasn&#8217;t given up on electric cars. CEO Jim Farley just teased the automaker&#8217;s electric pickup based on its new Universal Electric Vehicle platform that he called &#8220;one of the most audacious and important projects in Ford's history.&#8221;The Universal EV platform will be used on a family of affordable EVs sold around the world, but will start with a mid-sized pickup for the US  built in Louisville, Kentucky. It&#8217;s set to go on sale next year with a target price of $30,000. An early peek at our brilliant team working on the Universal Electric V...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's Super Bowl sale is ending soon, and it's one of the best I've seen &#8212; up to $2,500 off best-rated TVs and soundbars</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/samsungs-super-bowl-sale-is-ending-soon-and-its-one-of-the-best-ive-seen-up-to-usd2-500-off-best-rated-tvs-and-soundbars</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AFNPpVjFmpQsXmn57D3RZ6</guid>
      <description>Samsung's Super Bowl sale is ending soon, and I've rounded up my 19 favorite deals on best-rated 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs, and discounts on soundbars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seulement 429 &#8364; pour ce Samsung Galaxy S25 abordable : c&#8217;est l&#8217;offre choc juste avant le lancement des S26</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2850197_seulement-429-pour-ce-samsung-galaxy-s25-abordable-cest-loffre-choc-juste-avant-le-lancement-des-s26</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2850197_seulement-429-pour-ce-samsung-galaxy-s25-abordable-cest-loffre-choc-juste-avant-le-lancement-des-s26</guid>
      <description>
Lanc&#233; en fin d'ann&#233;e 2025, le Samsung Galaxy S25 FE revient aujourd'hui faire parler de lui gr&#226;ce &#224; 320 euros de remise possible, cumulant r&#233;duction, bonus reprise et ODR, permettant ainsi d'obtenir ce smartphone premium &#224; seulement 429 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Wallet&#160;: la nouvelle interface cache un vrai point noir</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/google-wallet-nouvelle-interface-cache-vrai-point-noir.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324527</guid>
      <description>Google Wallet pr&#233;pare une refonte majeure de son interface centr&#233;e sur un syst&#232;me de favoris. S'il permet d'acc&#233;der plus facilement &#224; certaines cartes, d&#8217;autres deviennent paradoxalement plus difficiles &#224; atteindre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditch the dual-monitor setup: This immersive 49-inch curved QD-OLED screen is $360 off right now, but you'll need to act fast</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/ditch-the-dual-monitor-setup-this-immersive-49-inch-curved-qd-oled-screen-is-usd360-off-right-now-but-youll-need-to-act-fast</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8AwtKQnp9uuvfLf7NkJbTX</guid>
      <description>Innocn&#8217;s 49Q1S ultrawide monitor is $360 off right now&#8212;just $900 for a massive 49-inch 32:9 curved QD-OLED display.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le Xiaomi YU7 GT : plus de 1 000 ch pour ce tueur de Tesla Model Y Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2969061_voici-le-xiaomi-yu7-gt-plus-de-1-000-ch-pour-ce-tueur-de-tesla-model-y-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2969061_voici-le-xiaomi-yu7-gt-plus-de-1-000-ch-pour-ce-tueur-de-tesla-model-y-performance</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s les rumeurs, le Xiaomi YU7 GT vient d'appara&#238;tre en Chine. Version sportive de la 2e voiture &#233;lectrique de la marque, il se place sous la SU7 Ultra, mais d&#233;veloppe tout de m&#234;me 1 000 ch.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 17e : on en sait plus sur le prochain mod&#232;le abordable d&#8217;Apple&#8230; et ce serait pour bient&#244;t</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2968771_iphone-17e-on-en-sait-plus-sur-le-prochain-modele-abordable-dapple-et-ce-serait-pour-bientot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2968771_iphone-17e-on-en-sait-plus-sur-le-prochain-modele-abordable-dapple-et-ce-serait-pour-bientot</guid>
      <description>
Comme l'ann&#233;e derni&#232;re, Apple profiterait de la relative qui&#233;tude de ce mois de f&#233;vrier pour lancer son nouvel iPhone 17e. On en sait aujourd'hui un peu plus sur l'appareil.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score $144 off: The easiest-to-use high-speed Carbon Fiber 3D printer is massively reduced in Elegoo&#8217;s Super Bowl sale</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/score-usd144-off-the-easiest-to-use-high-speed-carbon-fiber-3d-printer-is-massively-reduced-in-elegoos-super-bowl-sale</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">P56HimckM2VTfc2nuu9Uti</guid>
      <description>Elegoo&#8217;s Centauri Carbon 3D printer is $144 off for the Super Bowl weekend, just $269 for a fast, fully enclosed CoreXY machine with 500mm/s print speeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Olympics livestream 2026: How to watch the opening ceremony, including free options</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487770/winter-olympics-opening-ceremony-live-stream-watch-nbc-free</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T13:41:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487770/winter-olympics-opening-ceremony-live-stream-watch-nbc-free</guid>
      <description>This year&#8217;s Olympic competition takes place in two Italian cities: Milan and Cortina d&#8217;Ampezzo. Here&#8217;s how cord-cutters can catch the action.
It&#8217;s time to become an armchair expert on sports that you only think about every four years. In other words, the 2026 Winter Olympics have arrived. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ces montres connect&#233;es mensong&#232;res n&#8217;ont plus droit de cit&#233; dans ce pays europ&#233;en</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2968455_mesure-de-la-glycemie-lallemagne-sevit-contre-les-mensonges-mortels-des-montres-connectees</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2968455_mesure-de-la-glycemie-lallemagne-sevit-contre-les-mensonges-mortels-des-montres-connectees</guid>
      <description>
Alors que la mesure non-invasive de la glyc&#233;mie n'est toujours pas disponible sur les montres connect&#233;es, l'Allemagne indique avoir recens&#233; plus de 1200 montres suspectes aux affirmations trompeuses.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ces bracelets sans &#233;cran sont d&#233;sormais interdits de vente aux &#201;tats-Unis, voici pourquoi</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/whoop/2968581_whoop-obtient-une-premiere-victoire-en-justice-pour-contrefacon-de-son-bracelet-sans-ecran</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/whoop/2968581_whoop-obtient-une-premiere-victoire-en-justice-pour-contrefacon-de-son-bracelet-sans-ecran</guid>
      <description>
Cette semaine, Whoop a obtenu, aux &#201;tats-Unis, l'interdiction de la vente du bracelet Lexqi, jug&#233; trop proche de celui de la marque am&#233;ricaine.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest 45W Anker Nano charger with smart display is on sale for only $30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-latest-45w-anker-nano-charger-with-smart-display-is-on-sale-for-only-30-160707158.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5fce599-c299-44cd-983e-1c46fb9819b8</guid>
      <description>Anker rolled out a bunch of new chargers and other gear at CES 2026, including a cute one that's already on sale. The new Nano charger with smart display, which is an upgrade to the existing Nano charger in Anker's lineup, is on sale for $30 right now when you clip an on-page coupon on Amazon. That's $10 off the regular price.
The 45W charger includes a smart display that shows real-time data like power flow, temperature and charging status. It also features "fun animations to keep things cheerful." Anker says it can recognize what's being charged and automatically adjust certain metrics to en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto&#160;: une magistrate fran&#231;aise a &#233;t&#233; enlev&#233;e pour une ran&#231;on de 1,6 million d&#8217;euros</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/crypto-magistrate-francaise-enlevee-rancon-16-million-deuros.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1324561</guid>
      <description>Une magistrate et sa m&#232;re ont &#233;t&#233; enlev&#233;es par un commando de criminels. Les ravisseurs ont demand&#233; 1,6 million d&#8217;euros en bitcoins. Ce rapt survient alors que les enl&#232;vements et agressions visant les d&#233;tenteurs de cryptomonnaies se multiplient en France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple reportedly axed its planned AI health coach</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/apple-reportedly-axed-its-planned-ai-health-coach-133000941.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">118e9da6-7cad-4948-8eb3-2bcd3ac92c29</guid>
      <description>Apple is no longer launching an AI service that can &#8220;replicate&#8221; a doctor and act as a personal health coach, according to Bloomberg&#8217;s Mark Gurman. The company has reportedly scaled back the unannounced initiative in recent weeks, following a recent organization reshuffling wherein services chief Eddy Cue took over the health division. While Apple has never officially announced the AI health coach, it was reported last year that the company was working on developing the service that has been unofficially dubbed Health+. It was supposed to be able to help users track food and correct workout for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget Podcast: So there&#8217;s a social network for AI agents now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/engadget-podcast-so-theres-a-social-network-for-ai-agents-now-133000813.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79bbdb7b-90c0-42de-ac1a-e0ee1c44a50d</guid>
      <description>If you haven't heard, there's now a social network for AI: Moltbook, a site that purportedly features AI agents talking to each other. That includes OpenClaw, a personal AI agent (formerly called Clawdbot and Moltbot) that's open source and free for anyone to run on their systems. In this episode, Devindra and Senior Reporter Karissa Bell discuss the rise of these services, and the potential future that AI agents may have for all of us.Subscribe!iTunesSpotifyPocket CastsStitcherGoogle PodcastsTopicsWhat is Moltbook and OpenClaw? &#8211; 1:31Anthropic reinforces its commitment against ads with Super ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some smartwatches are actually making up their readings &#8211; which is why I keep telling you people never to buy cheap, unbranded Apple Watch dupes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-trackers/some-smartwatches-are-actually-making-up-their-readings-which-is-why-i-keep-telling-you-people-never-to-buy-cheap-unbranded-apple-watch-dupes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Vo3Cog6dqJT2smNntGXxc</guid>
      <description>A German regulatory service investigated the cheap smartwatches just making up their readings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Mobile&#8217;s Super Bowl Week Promotion Delivers Multi-Network Coverage at Lower Prices</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/us-mobiles-super-bowl-week-promotion-delivers-multi-network-coverage-at-lower-prices-2000718782</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718782</guid>
      <description>With prices starting at just $15 a month, enjoying fast speeds and a stable connection has never been easier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU says TikTok uses 'addictive design' and must change</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/eu-says-tiktok-uses-addictive-design-and-must-change-131738425.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7cc7b7f-e565-4335-84fe-946b235ebd80</guid>
      <description>TikTok&#8217;s signature features that hooked users around the world are its algorithm and endless scroll. Now, though, the European Union has called those aspects of the app illegal and may order the company to alter them. &#8220;Today, the European Commission preliminarily found TikTok in breach of the Digital Services Act for its addictive design,&#8221; the EU&#8217;s regulator said in a press release. &#8220;This includes features such as infinite scroll, autoplay, push notifications, and its highly personalized recommender system.&#8221; It said that TikTok failed to put up safeguards to ensure that those &#8220;addictive&#8221; featu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette d&#233;couverte sur une lune de Jupiter relance une question vertigineuse : et si la vie &#233;tait d&#233;j&#224; l&#224; ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/espace-cette-decouverte-lune-jupiter-relance-question-vertigineuse-si-vie-etait-deja-130893/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:15:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/espace-cette-decouverte-lune-jupiter-relance-question-vertigineuse-si-vie-etait-deja-130893/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Sous sa surface glac&#233;e, Europe cache peut-&#234;tre un oc&#233;an sal&#233; plus vaste que tous ceux de la Terre r&#233;unis. Prot&#233;g&#233;e sous des kilom&#232;tres de glace, chauff&#233;e de l&#8217;int&#233;rieur et riche en chimie active, cette lune de Jupiter r&#233;unit plusieurs des ingr&#233;dients jug&#233;s essentiels &#224; l&#8217;apparition de la vie. Et...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos soundbars and home theater gear is up to 20 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/sonos-soundbars-and-home-theater-gear-is-up-to-20-percent-off-right-now-174053415.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d95ac4b9-448d-4c43-906a-61793dfa0aef</guid>
      <description>It's big-game season, which means it's a good time to look for home theater gear on sale ahead of Super Bowl 2026. There are plenty of Super Bowl TV deals to consider, but if you have arguably the most important piece of the puzzle down, you may want to upgrade your sound system instead. Sonos' latest sale may have just what you need; a bunch of the company's home theater gear is up to 20 percent off right now. You can save $130 on the Beam (Gen 2) soundbar, bringing its price down to $369, and you'll also find deals on the flagship Arc Ultra soundbar, subwoofers, and more.
The Sonos Beam is t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin crash update: Punishing price slide has investors wondering today: Where is the bottom?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91488327/bitcoin-price-usd-update-btc-crashing-where-is-the-bottom</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T13:06:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91488327/bitcoin-price-usd-update-btc-crashing-where-is-the-bottom</guid>
      <description>The cryptocurrency this week saw its value halved when compared to its previous high.  Some analysts say the worst is not yet over. Here&#8217;s the latest.
The price of Bitcoin has declined dramatically in recent weeks, and cryptocurrency investors are more fearful than ever. In the past 24 hours, the crypto king dipped to the $60,000 range&#8212;a low it has not seen since October 2024. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test des Shokz OpenFit Pro : la r&#233;duction de bruit arrive enfin sur les &#233;couteurs ouverts</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/shokz/2953169_test-des-shokz-openfit-pro-la-reduction-de-bruit-arrive-enfin-sur-les-ecouteurs-ouverts</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/shokz/2953169_test-des-shokz-openfit-pro-la-reduction-de-bruit-arrive-enfin-sur-les-ecouteurs-ouverts</guid>
      <description>
Si les &#233;couteurs ouverts ont longtemps &#233;t&#233; limit&#233;s &#224; un usage sportif, Shokz entend bien changer la donne avec ses OpenFit Pro. En int&#233;grant pour la premi&#232;re fois une r&#233;duction de bruit &#224; sa formule gagnante, la marque am&#233;ricaine repousse les limites du format et livre possiblement le meilleur produit de sa cat&#233;gorie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Wizard of Oz&#8217; Will Be Broadcast on TV for the First Time This Century</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/wizard-of-oz-tv-broadcast-metv-2000718720</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718720</guid>
      <description>MeTV, a network focused on classic entertainment, will show the 1939 favorite as part of its Halloween programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordProtect (2026) Review: A Bundle of ID-Protecting Services</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/review/nordprotect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6984c48d373aa7c9b0691940</guid>
      <description>A privacy-minded bundle that&#8217;s almost too simple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can China&#8217;s No. 2 automaker make it in America?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/874551/geely-volvo-china-cars-us-software-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874551</guid>
      <description>Is the long freeze on Chinese automakers selling cars in the US finally starting to thaw? China is the largest auto market in the world and now the largest car exporter, too. But high tariffs and geopolitical tensions have kept Chinese automakers away from US customers. Many of those cars are ready for primetime and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the men in the Epstein files defeated #MeToo</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874721/epstein-thiel-musk-trump-metoo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874721</guid>
      <description>He might be dead, but it sure seems like Jeffrey Epstein won. Sure, Epstein was arrested on charges of sex trafficking minors. Sure, he died in jail. (I am not going to wade into the debate about how.) But he subscribed to a racist, misogynist ideology that meant rich white men like him could do [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hisense U65QF 'punches well above its price range' and it's had a huge $300 discount at Amazon ahead of President's Day</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-hisense-u65qf-punches-well-above-its-price-range-and-its-had-a-huge-usd300-discount-at-amazon-ahead-of-presidents-day</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AyxMaLYqUuvrCjdoVHPmeb</guid>
      <description>A big screen TV with a big discount, the Hisense U6QF 75-inch has had its price slashed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Winter Olympics Opening Ceremony 2026: FREE live streams, schedule, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/winter-olympics-opening-ceremony-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">S2Q5ic8LAt2uCMbGesdmJ9</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Winter Olympics Opening Ceremony 2026 live streams for FREE, as the action in Italy gets under way</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T20 World Cup 2026 Free Streams: TV Channels, Full Schedule &amp; Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/t20-world-cup-2026-free-streams</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MJWGewcK2qVCWVb4FKw9ri</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch T20 World Cup 2026 live streams online from anywhere for FREE, with Pakistan, South Africa and England looking to dethrone India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO is making a Baldur's&#160;Gate&#160;3 TV show</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/hbo-is-making-a-baldurs-gate-3-tv-show-130000864.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02e3f5ee-62df-4100-9cbd-d349b4adc7a3</guid>
      <description>The Last of Us series co-creator Craig Mazin is teaming with Hasbro Entertainment to create an HBO series based on the popular (and spicy) Baldur&#8217;s Gate 3 game, Deadline reported. The show will be simply be called Baldur&#8217;s Gate and the story will resume where Baldur&#8217;s Gate 3 left off. Mazin will reportedly have full creative control and act as co-creator, writer, executive producer and showrunner. "It is a dream come true to be able to continue the story that [Baldur&#8217;s Gate 3 developer] Larian and Wizards of The Coast created," Mazin said in a statement. "I am a devoted fan of DnD and the bril...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPNs with free trials in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/best-vpns-with-free-trials-130000435.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea322751-f8c8-4429-99a9-73ef5fbf1daa</guid>
      <description>A free trial to a virtual private network (VPN) can mean a few different things. Several of the best VPNs let you try them out without paying. A rare few, and only one on this list, let you try them without submitting payment information at all. Some VPNs have forever free plans that let you use them indefinitely without paying, as long as you're OK with some limits.For the most part, though, your best chance to test a VPN for free is to pay for a subscription. Then, if you don't like the service, you can get your money back before the refund guarantee expires. This takes a bit more work, and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AWS-powered Next Gen Stats&#160;changed the NFL forever</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487984/how-aws-powered-next-gen-stats-changed-the-nfl-forever</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487984/how-aws-powered-next-gen-stats-changed-the-nfl-forever</guid>
      <description>The analytics technology has&#160;reshaped&#160;how football is played&#8212;and how&#160;it&#8217;s&#160;watched.&#160;
This Sunday will see the Seattle Seahawks face off against the New England Patriots in Super Bowl LX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;UE demande &#224; TikTok de modifier son interface &#171;&#160;addictive&#160;&#187;</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-06/l-ue-demande-a-tiktok-de-modifier-son-interface-addictive.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:59:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2276c3855d4308c81e36dcad79546d7</guid>
      <description>La Commission europ&#233;enne a demand&#233; vendredi &#224; l&#8217;application TikTok de changer son interface &#171;&#160;addictive&#160;&#187;, accus&#233;e d&#8217;enfreindre la l&#233;gislation europ&#233;enne sur le num&#233;rique, sous peine de s&#8217;exposer &#224; de lourdes amendes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MrBeasts Hot Ones episode is painful to watch</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/mrbeast-hot-ones</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00B7rfv95bqgAQ0LrlxLGof</guid>
      <description>MrBeast has appeared on "Hot Ones", eating increasingly spicy wings while chatting about "Beast Games" Season 2 and Feastables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ressusciter un t&#233;l&#233;phone de 2010 ? C&#8217;est le d&#233;fi fou (et r&#233;ussi) du projet Reborn</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nokia/2968345_ressusciter-un-smartphone-de-2010-cest-le-defi-fou-et-reussi-du-projet-reborn</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nokia/2968345_ressusciter-un-smartphone-de-2010-cest-le-defi-fou-et-reussi-du-projet-reborn</guid>
      <description>
Avant la domination sans pareille d&#8217;iOS et Android, un autre syst&#232;me d&#8217;exploitation mobile faisait la loi&#160;: Symbian. Abandonn&#233; depuis longtemps, l&#8217;OS conna&#238;t une nouvelle vie sur le c&#233;l&#232;bre Nokia&#160;N8.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber found liable for sexual assault in first of thousands of similar lawsuits</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/874751/uber-sexual-assault-federal-case-verdict-liable</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-06T07:54:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874751</guid>
      <description>A federal jury in Phoenix has found Uber to be liable for the sexual assault of one of its passengers, potentially setting a precedent for more than 3,000 similar cases consolidated in US federal court. As part of the verdict, Uber has been ordered to pay $8.5 million in damages to the victim, Jaylynn Dean, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Crashes as Crypto Investors Whine About People Making Fun of Them</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/bitcoin-crashes-as-crypto-investors-whine-about-people-making-fun-of-them-2000718711</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718711</guid>
      <description>What happened to Trump as crypto's savior?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Starlink really making a phone? Elon Musk says no, but hints at a &#8216;different device&#8217; with AI powers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/is-starlink-really-making-a-phone-elon-musk-says-no-but-hints-at-a-different-device-with-ai-powers</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ttoEndiymZNH78WfoMb97</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk says SpaceX is not building a phone, but says a 'different device' could still be in the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
