<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:23:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Open source Qwen-Image-2512 launches to compete with Google's Nano Banana Pro in high quality AI image generation</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/open-source-qwen-image-2512-launches-to-compete-with-googles-nano-banana-pro</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61RzMvhZ52ZjtGa4mQkP4G</guid>
      <description>When Google released its newest AI image model Nano Banana Pro (aka Gemini 3 Pro Image) in November, it reset expectations for the entire field. For the first time, uses of an image model could use natural language to generate dense, text-heavy infographics, slides, and other enterprise-grade visuals without spelling errors. But that leap forward came with a familiar tradeoff. Gemini 3 Pro Image is deeply proprietary, tightly bound to Google&#8217;s cloud stack, and priced for premium usage. For enterprises that need predictable costs, deployment sovereignty, or regional localization, the model rais...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street slides on the final day of 2025 to close out a record year</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468133/wall-street-slides-final-day-2025-record-year</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468133/wall-street-slides-final-day-2025-record-year</guid>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500, which set 39 record highs in 2025, is up about 17%&#160;for the year, it&#8217;s third straight double-digit annual gain.
U.S. stocks are slipping in afternoon trading Wednesday as Wall Street closes out a banner year for markets driven by both optimism and uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims drop to one-month low to cap a tough year for job market</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468130/jobless-claims-one-month-low-bumpy-year-job-market</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468130/jobless-claims-one-month-low-bumpy-year-job-market</guid>
      <description>Claims have been volatile in recent weeks amid challenges in adjusting the data for seasonal fluctuations ahead of the holiday season.
Americans filed the fewest new jobless claims in a month last week, and while the number of unemployed workers collecting relief payments has eased from recent highs, there is little indication of a break from the weak hiring environment that settled in over the course of President Donald Trump&#8216;s first year back at the White House....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram chief: AI is so ubiquitous 'it will be more practical to fingerprint real media than fake media'</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/instagram-chief-ai-is-so-ubiquitous-it-will-be-more-practical-to-fingerprint-real-media-than-fake-media-202620080.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f349227-b021-4270-a8fc-3fa8bea3d692</guid>
      <description>It's no secret that AI-generated content took over our social media feeds in 2025. Now, Instagram's top exec Adam Mosseri has made it clear that he expects AI content to overtake non-AI imagery and the significant implications that shift has for its creators and photographers.Mosseri shared the thoughts in a lengthy post about the broader trends he expects to shape Instagram in 2026. And he offered a notably candid assessment on how AI is upending the platform. "Everything that made creators matter&#8212;the ability to be real, to connect, to have a voice that couldn&#8217;t be faked&#8212;is now suddenly acces...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Jujutsu Kaisen Modulo&#8217; Is Better Than the OG Manga Series</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jujutsu-kaisen-modulo-jjk-gege-akutami-yuji-iwasaki-manga-sequel-culling-game-shonen-jump-2000704291</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704291</guid>
      <description>Gege Akutami and Yuji Iwasaki's sequel manga remembered to make a worthwhile story the connective tissue of its sorcery fighting series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Football Bowl Games Free Streams: TV Channels, Schedule &amp; Preview for Cotton, Orange, Rose and Sugar Bowl</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/college-football-bowl-games-free-cotton-orange-rose-sugar</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">igxMYzxeS2busUq4HksBPR</guid>
      <description>As Cotton, Orange, Rose and Sugar will see eight teams become four, here's how to watch College Football Bowl games 2025/26 for free and from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hisense L9Q projector beams a bright, refined-looking picture and has incredible built-in sound</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/projectors/hisense-l9q-projector-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7CJSXPYD5vhpkmEB4pBGJm</guid>
      <description>The Hisense L9Q brings top-shelf projection and robust audio to a convenient ultra short throw footprint.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
