<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:28:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit looks to AI search as its next big opportunity</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/reddit-looks-to-ai-search-as-its-next-big-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090181</guid>
      <description>Reddit says its search business, including AI answers, is an "enormous" opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roblox is working to pull in adult players</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/874675/roblox-earnings-q4-2025-increasing-adult-players</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:14:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874675</guid>
      <description>After rolling out age verification last year, Roblox is aiming to grow the number of players over 18 on its platform. As noted in its 2025 year-end earnings report, 45 percent of Roblox's daily active users have completed an age check as of January 31st. Of those who have verified their age, 27 percent are [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS&#160;revenue continues to soar&#160;as cloud demand&#160;remains&#160;high</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/aws-revenue-continues-to-soar-as-cloud-demand-remains-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090209</guid>
      <description>AWS recorded its best quarter, in terms of revenue growth, in 13 quarters in Q4 2025 as AI drives AWS adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doom Overtakes 3 Very Different Planets, Earth Included, in This Eerie Sci-Fi Short Story</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doom-overtakes-3-very-different-planets-earth-included-in-this-eerie-sci-fi-short-story-2000716898</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716898</guid>
      <description>Read 'Death Echoes Overlapping' by Megan Chee, courtesy of Lightspeed Magazine, right here on io9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon and Google are winning the AI capex race &#8212; but what&#8217;s the prize?</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/amazon-and-google-are-winning-the-ai-capex-race-but-whats-the-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089705</guid>
      <description>In 2026, Amazon plans to spend $200 billion in capex. Google is just behind at $175 billion to $185 billion. It's a lot of money!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X's latest Community Notes experiment allows AI to write the first draft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/xs-latest-community-notes-experiment-allows-ai-to-write-the-first-draft-210605597.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">858633a6-0d81-4f6b-8496-9422e3005804</guid>
      <description>X is experimenting with a new way for AI to write Community Notes. The company is testing a new "collaborative notes" feature that allows human writers to request an AI-written Community Note.&#160;It's not the first time the platform has experimented with AI in Community Notes. The company started a pilot program last year to allow developers to create dedicated AI note writers. &#160;X&#8217;s Keith Coleman tells me that AI writers are &#8220;prolific&#8221; and that one has contributed more than 1,000 notes that were rates as helpful by other contributors. But the latest experiment sounds like a more streamlined proce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT caricatures are taking over social media&#8212;but at what cost?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487696/chatgpt-caricature-trend-tiktok-ai-generated-pictures</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T22:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487696/chatgpt-caricature-trend-tiktok-ai-generated-pictures</guid>
      <description>The latest trend is likely flooding your feed with AI-generated images. Here&#8217;s what&#8217;s behind it.
Have you seen larger-than-life depictions of your friends lately? They might have been sucked into the latest social trend: creating AI-generated caricatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic Launches New Model That Spots Zero Days, Makes Wall Street Traders Lose Their Minds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anthropic-launches-new-model-that-spots-zero-days-makes-wall-street-traders-lose-their-minds-2000718648</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718648</guid>
      <description>Opus 4.6 has arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GeekBook X14 Pro is one of the lightest laptops I&#8217;ve tested, and it packs plenty of power at a reasonable price</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/geekom-geekbook-x14-pro-laptop-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f8Nh8yvMt5bsfxfocF7QS</guid>
      <description>The GeekBook X14 Pro is an ultra-lightweight 14-inch display laptop featuring Windows 11 Pro and a premium build with a stylish magnesium alloy outer. Inside, an impressive CPU and GPU offer a powerful combination, making it a great option for business and creative use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Plot of &#8216;The Darwin Incident&#8217; Is Bananas, But I&#8217;ve Gotta See What This Monkey Does Next</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-plot-of-the-darwin-incident-is-bananas-but-ive-gotta-see-what-this-monkey-does-next-2000718445</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718445</guid>
      <description>The Prime Video anime series has everything: a human-chimpanzee lead, vegan eco-terrorists, and high school drama with a blush of romance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify your AI workflow with this one powerful Chrome extension</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-5-chatplayground-ai-unlimited-plan-lifetime-subscriptions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02J3cWmMEuN05l5wnIpUj60</guid>
      <description>Make AI even more efficient with this lifetime subscription to the ChatPlayground AI Unlimited Plan, on sale now for just $79.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Possible Lunar Impact in 2032 Could Spark Days of Meteor Showers on Earth</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-possible-lunar-impact-in-2032-could-spark-days-of-meteor-showers-on-earth-2000718658</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718658</guid>
      <description>The space rock has a 4.3% chance of striking the Moon in six years&#8212;and it could generate a flash nearly as bright as Venus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why one Anthropic update wiped billions off software stocks</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487960/why-one-anthropic-update-wiped-billions-off-software-stocks</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T21:48:50</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487960/why-one-anthropic-update-wiped-billions-off-software-stocks</guid>
      <description>Investors fear Claude Cowork&#8217;s new agentic features threaten entire categories of SaaS tools.
Tech workers have been worried for years about the AI tidal wave coming for their jobs, but their bosses are starting to worry too.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NordVPN review 2025: Innovative features, a few missteps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/nordvpn-review-2025-innovative-features-a-few-missteps-163000578.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd3be014-d14b-4ac2-ad5d-4ae3aa73cc14</guid>
      <description>When we say that NordVPN is a good VPN that's not quite great, it's important to put that in perspective. Building a good VPN is hard, as evidenced by all the shovelware VPNs flooding the market. NordVPN may not be perfect, but it's easily top-five caliber and excels in certain use cases.
First, the bad: NordVPN's apps could all stand to undergo a little more quality control, with elements distracting from other elements and inconsistent designs from platform to platform. At least one of its FAQ pages directly contradicts itself. And while all the server locations could unblock Netflix, the on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans attack &amp;#8216;woke&amp;#8217; Netflix &#8212; and ignore YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/874655/netflix-warner-bros-republican-culture-war-ted-sarandos-hearing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T16:40:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874655</guid>
      <description>When Netflix co-CEO Ted Sarandos entered the Senate office building on Tuesday, he got thrown a curveball. What started as a standard antitrust hearing relating to the Warner Bros. merger quickly devolved into a performative Republican attack about the spread of "woke" ideology on the streaming service. At the same time, arguably a much more [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Post is retreating from Silicon Valley when it matters most</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/the-washington-post-is-retreating-from-silicon-valley-when-it-matters-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090063</guid>
      <description>The Bezos-owned newspaper gutted its San Francisco bureau and coverage of tech &#8212; including journalists reporting on Amazon and Blue Origin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit Details Horrifying 911 Call Before Tesla Driver Died While Trapped Inside Car</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lawsuit-details-horrifying-911-call-before-tesla-driver-died-while-trapped-inside-car-2000718671</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718671</guid>
      <description>A wrongful death lawsuit claims a 20-year-old driver was unable to escape a burning vehicle due to faulty electronic doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our focus areas are enterprise... and just continuing to grow at the premium, you know, higher-end of the market': AMD CEO plays down global memory shortage, says she expects PC market to shrink</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/our-focus-areas-are-enterprise-and-just-continuing-to-grow-at-the-premium-you-know-higher-end-of-the-market-amd-ceo-plays-down-global-memory-shortage-says-she-expects-pc-market-to-shrink</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">j6eCgxFLdC8JDWYKUyWcdk</guid>
      <description>AMD reports strong revenue growth while acknowledging rising RAM and SSD prices and predicting a shrinking PC market overall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyalty Is Dead in Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/model-behavior-loyalty-is-dead-in-silicon-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697d18dab8c7ce5e411f04be</guid>
      <description>Founders used to be wedded to their companies. Now, anyone can be lured away for the right price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A16z VC&#160;wants founders to stop stressing over insane ARR numbers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/a16z-vc-wants-founders-to-stop-stressing-over-insane-arr-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090068</guid>
      <description>A16z VC Jennifer Li&#8288;, who oversees some of the firm's fastest growing AI companies, warns founders not to believe every ARR claim made on X.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
