<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:28:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Jujutsu Kaisen Modulo&#8217; Is Better Than the OG Manga Series</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/jujutsu-kaisen-modulo-jjk-gege-akutami-yuji-iwasaki-manga-sequel-culling-game-shonen-jump-2000704291</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704291</guid>
      <description>Gege Akutami and Yuji Iwasaki's sequel manga remembered to make a worthwhile story the connective tissue of its sorcery fighting series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Football Bowl Games Free Streams: TV Channels, Schedule &amp; Preview for Cotton, Orange, Rose and Sugar Bowl</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/college-football-bowl-games-free-cotton-orange-rose-sugar</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">igxMYzxeS2busUq4HksBPR</guid>
      <description>As Cotton, Orange, Rose and Sugar will see eight teams become four, here's how to watch College Football Bowl games 2025/26 for free and from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hisense L9Q projector beams a bright, refined-looking picture and has incredible built-in sound</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/projectors/hisense-l9q-projector-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7CJSXPYD5vhpkmEB4pBGJm</guid>
      <description>The Hisense L9Q brings top-shelf projection and robust audio to a convenient ultra short throw footprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 8 most comfortable office chairs that saved our backs in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-8-most-comfortable-office-chairs-that-saved-our-backs-in-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XUzL6mKfkKxFeiKkTB8eoR</guid>
      <description>As TechRadar Pro's office furniture editor, I test office chairs for a living - and these are the most comfortable seats my team and I reviewed this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Samsung's "First Look" CES 2026 presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/how-to-watch-samsungs-first-look-ces-2026-presentation-190027604.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99e05139-49a3-486e-a22a-1ec128284043</guid>
      <description>NurPhoto via Getty Images
Samsung is arguably the 800-pound gorilla of CES, with a full spectrum of products that range from phones and computers to refrigerators to AI assistants and rolling robots. But for CES 2026, the company is shaking up the schedule a bit: Instead of its longtime midday Monday press conference position, the Korean giant will front-run the entire show with a Sunday night presentation.
Samsung has already given a few hints as to what's on the agenda, but what we're really hoping to see is an update on the Ballie robot &#8212; a star of previous CES presentations that ostensibly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are over 55 new Hulu movies arriving in January 2026 &#8212; these are the 3 I'd recommend streaming first</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/there-are-over-55-new-hulu-movies-arriving-in-january-2026-these-are-the-3-id-recommend-streaming-first</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TMXomKTScY7aQzrJvf9HuH</guid>
      <description>Catch new movies Hacksaw Ridge and Heat, as well as the second season of boxing drama A Thousand Blows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta buys Manus for $2 billion to power high-stakes AI agent race</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/meta-buys-manus-for-usd2-billion-to-power-high-stakes-ai-agent-race</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EYwT5w4Si4FZ2LVAJtcbcR</guid>
      <description>Meta&#8217;s $2 billion acquisition of Manus signals a major shift toward AI agents that can autonomously handle real work, not just generate responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this flu season is spiraling faster than anyone expected</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468046/why-this-flu-season-is-spiraling-faster-than-anyone-expected</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-31T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468046/why-this-flu-season-is-spiraling-faster-than-anyone-expected</guid>
      <description>A fast-moving strain, uneven vaccination rates, and early spread are colliding in this season&#8217;s outbreak.
Flu season is here and it&#8217;s shaping up to be a bad one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Sony Honda Afeela CES 2026 press conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/how-to-watch-the-sony-honda-afeela-ces-2026-press-conference-130048622.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55dc3f84-855b-40ed-9b3d-0dc382a60c59</guid>
      <description>
Sony's CES 2026 press conference is just days away, but this year has a twist: Instead of an overview of Sony's electronics, video game and Hollywood studio plans for the new year, the presser will apparently have a more narrow focus: electric vehicles. That's because the traditional end-of-press-day slot isn't just Sony, but rather Sony Honda Mobility &#8212; the joint venture responsible for the Afeela 1 electric car that has been showcased at CES for the better part of a decade. This year, however, we'll also apparently get to see a an all-new concept model at the event, too.&#160;
How to watch the S...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
