<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:25:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes minibus bill funding NASA, rejecting Trump's proposed cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/senate-passes-minibus-bill-funding-nasa-rejecting-trumps-proposed-cuts-231605536.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd421e48-bc53-4a4f-a1c2-3f92df7c2b2d</guid>
      <description>After a tumultuous 2025 that saw it lose around 4,000 employees, NASA finally has an operating budget for 2026, and one that largely preserves its scientific capabilities. On Thursday, the Senate passed an appropriations bill funding NASA, alongside the National Science Foundation and a handful of other federal agencies.&#160;Going into the appropriations process, the president called for a 24 percent year over year reduction to NASA's total operating budget. As part of that plan, the White House wanted to reduce the Science Mission Directorate's funding by nearly half, a move that would have force...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Ponies on TVNZ+ (it's *FREE*)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/how-to-watch-ponies-online-its-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sTaCeS8TgZ3uthWxUbakq4</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on how to watch Ponies online for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Filoni takes charge of Star Wars as new president of Lucasfilm</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/863065/dave-filoni-lucasfilm-president-star-wars</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T18:04:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863065</guid>
      <description>There's a new name in charge of stewarding Star Wars at Lucasfilm. The studio just announced that Dave Filoni - best-known for his work on The Mandalorian and The Clone Wars - will be taking over as president. Former president Kathleen Kennedy, whose departure had been rumored for some time, will be stepping down and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith's Disney+ series is full of world firsts &#8211; here&#8217;s how one explorer guided the actor through Earth&#8217;s harshest environment using cutting-edge tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/disney-plus/will-smiths-disney-series-is-full-of-world-firsts-heres-how-one-explorer-guided-the-actor-through-earths-harshest-environment-using-cutting-edge-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Qo7rxKYphGjc7xFcVRJPCL</guid>
      <description>Richard Parks, a world record-setting explorer, reveals the gadgets behind the first episode of National Geographic&#8217;s Pole to Pole with Will Smith expedition series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Cycles launches wristband to replace thermometers for its FDA-cleared birth control app</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863046/natural-cycles-wristband-digital-birth-control</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:46:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863046</guid>
      <description>Natural Cycles, the company behind a controversial FDA-cleared birth control app, is replacing its thermometer with a wristband that measures skin temperature, heart rate, and movement during sleep. The newly-launched wristband costs $129.99 and syncs with the Natural Cycles app, which uses an algorithm to determine a person's "daily fertility status." Users can already track [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators Postpone Crypto Market Bill as Coinbase Flexes Its Muscle in Washington</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/senators-postpone-crypto-market-bill-as-coinbase-flexes-its-muscle-in-washington-2000710816</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710816</guid>
      <description>Coinbase's CEO isn't happy. Senators pump the brakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s Layoffs Leave Supernatural Fitness Users in Mourning</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/metas-layoffs-supernatural-fitness-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967e3c32a35b050b1eec69d</guid>
      <description>Users of the VR fitness service are distraught that Supernatural has had its staff cut and won&#8217;t receive any more content updates. They&#8217;re also pissed at Meta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. is suspending immigrant visas from 75 countries. Here&#8217;s what it means for travelers</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475935/the-u-s-is-suspending-immigrant-visas-from-75-countries-heres-what-it-means-for-travelers</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T22:44:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475935/the-u-s-is-suspending-immigrant-visas-from-75-countries-heres-what-it-means-for-travelers</guid>
      <description>Popular travel destinations like Jamaica, the Bahamas, and Thailand are included in the new U.S. visa suspension.
Well, this could be awkward for Americans traveling abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $250 billion trade deal will see Taiwan bring more semiconductor production to the US</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/a-250-billion-trade-deal-will-see-taiwan-bring-more-semiconductor-production-to-the-us-224326501.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6deb066-b3a0-4071-b523-ac1b889baf53</guid>
      <description>The US and Taiwan have signed an agreement that will see a multi-billion dollar investment into domestic development of semiconductors and related infrastructure. The US Department of Commerce announced that Taiwanese businesses will make an upfront investment of at least $250 billion into their US production capacity, while Taiwan's government will provide credit guarantees of at least another $250 billion in support of the semiconductor industry and supply chain in the US.&#160;In exchange, Taiwan will receive a better deal on tariffs. Reciprocal tariffs will be limited to 15 percent, compared wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnets produced at room temperature using lasers could one day produce better HDDs, faster non-silicon processors &#8212; and at 20nm, they are so thin that they could be used almost anywhere, even in the human body</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/magnets-produced-at-room-temperature-using-lasers-could-one-day-produce-better-hdds-faster-non-silicon-processors-and-at-20nm-they-are-so-thin-that-they-could-be-used-almost-anywhere-even-in-the-human-body</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NcnQrzisYFkRD2d4uFZkaD</guid>
      <description>Magnets tuned with lasers at room temperature could lead to faster hard drives and a new generation of computer chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluesky's 'Live Now' badge is available to everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/blueskys-live-now-badge-is-available-to-everyone-223335221.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf34b1ed-389c-4f97-ab13-6d5b89858a2e</guid>
      <description>After testing the feature in a limited beta, Bluesky is making its "Live Now" badge for streamers available for everyone on the social network to try. Live Now is included as part of Bluesky's v1.114 update, alongside "cashtags," a separate type of hashtag for collecting conversations about publicly-traded companies.Bluesky first started testing its Live Now badge in May 2025 with a limited group of accounts, including the official NBA account. The feature lets Twitch streamers with Bluesky profiles append a Live Now badge to their profile picture that links directly to their livestream. Live ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Filoni Is Taking Over Lucasfilm From Kathleen Kennedy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dave-filoni-lucasfilm-kathleen-kennedy-2000706230</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706230</guid>
      <description>The 'Clone Wars' and 'Rebels' creator will share 'Star Wars' duties with Lynwen Brennan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley see double-digit profit jumps</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476028/goldman-sachs-morgan-stanley-double-digit-profit-stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T22:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476028/goldman-sachs-morgan-stanley-double-digit-profit-stock-market</guid>
      <description>Fourth-quarter investment fee revenues over at Goldman were up 25% year-over-year and Morgan Stanley saw a 47% jump in revenue in its investment banking division. 
A&#160;surging stock market&#160;and a flurry of deal-making padded the profits of Wall Street&#8217;s two big investment banks, which both saw a double-digit jump in profits in the fourth quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term mortgage rate drops to lowest point in more than 3 years</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476032/mortgage-rate-lowest-point-three-years</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T22:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476032/mortgage-rate-lowest-point-three-years</guid>
      <description>The last time the average rate was lower was Sept. 15, 2022, when it was at 6.02%.
The average long-term U.S. mortgage rate is now down to its lowest level in more than three years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon-carbon is just the start: these battery technologies could make your phone last even longer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/silicon-carbon-is-just-the-start-these-battery-technologies-could-make-your-phone-last-even-longer</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7jCxXvtpYVmja5rbEJFgyK</guid>
      <description>There are loads of exciting battery technologies under development, and one day some of them could make their way to phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can save over $1,500 on LG&#8217;s 65-inch C5 OLED TV</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/862989/lg-c5-oled-tv-ebay-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:23:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862989</guid>
      <description>LG might have just revealed its new C6 OLED TVs at CES 2026, but we still don&#8217;t know when they&#8217;ll actually hit stores. If you don&#8217;t want to wait &#8212; or spend a couple thousand dollars on a brand new model &#8212; the current-gen LG C5 OLED is a fantastic option now the 65-inch model [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best alternatives to Spotify for listening to music</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22910685/music-listening-service-spotify-apple-youtube-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:19:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22910685/music-listening-service-spotify-apple-youtube-amazon</guid>
      <description>Spotify is probably one of the most well-known music services available (if not the most popular) around - and it seems that the company it taking advantage of that. As of this month, Spotify announced that it was raising its prices, the third time since 2023. If that concerns you (especially if you're a current [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble&#8217;s Plans for Circular Smartwatches Could Bring Me Back to Wearables</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pebbles-plans-for-circular-smartwatches-could-bring-me-back-to-wearables-2000710823</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710823</guid>
      <description>The Pebble Round 2 and Index 01 are reminders of when tech didn't take itself 'too seriously.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 former NCAA players and fixers charged for rigging games</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475927/26-former-ncaa-players-fixers-charged-rigging-games</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T22:07:10</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475927/26-former-ncaa-players-fixers-charged-rigging-games</guid>
      <description>The varying charges against the 26 defendants, filed in federal court in Philadelphia, include bribery, wire fraud, and conspiracy.
An investigation into a sprawling betting scheme to rig&#160;NCAA&#160;and Chinese Basketball Association games ensnared 26 people, including more than a dozen college basketball players who tried to fix games as recently as last season, federal prosecutors said Thursday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus says it&amp;#8217;s dropping the RTX 5070 Ti as the memory shortage squeezes supply</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863000/asus-nvidia-rtx-5070-ti-5060-ti-supply-rumors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T17:06:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863000</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, Hardware Unboxed reported that Asus is winding down production of its RTX 5070 Ti, saying, Asus "explicitly told us this model is currently facing a supply shortage and, as such, they have placed the model into end-of-life status." They added that the same applies to Asus's 16GB RTX 5060 Ti, and mentioned how [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI lab revolving door spins ever faster</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/the-ai-lab-revolving-door-spins-ever-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083248</guid>
      <description>AI labs just can't get their employees to stay put. Yesterday&#8217;s big AI news was the abrupt and seemingly acrimonious departure of three top executives at Mira Murati&#8217;s Thinking Machines lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;All You Need Is Kill&#8217; Spins a Trippy, Heart&#8209;Flecked Loop That Only Partially Lands</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/all-you-need-is-kill-spins-a-trippy-heart%e2%80%91flecked-loop-that-only-partially-lands-2000707828</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707828</guid>
      <description>Studio 4&#176;C's anime film of Hiroshi Sakurazaka's beloved light novel, which also inspired the Tom Cruise adaptation 'Edge of Tomorrow,' hits theaters on January 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't be a doomer' - Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang says no one currently has 'any reasonable ability to create god AI', so we should all just relax</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dont-be-a-doomer-nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-says-no-one-currently-has-any-reasonable-ability-to-create-god-ai-so-we-should-all-just-relax</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LsqE5CEwyADJ9zxiySexrP</guid>
      <description>Jensen Huang dismisses god-level AI fears, stresses responsible use of AI tools to improve productivity and address real-world challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take an Extra $50 Off My Favorite Mattress With This Code</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/nolah-evolution-hybrid-mattress-sale-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69693f52053685ef2d2c1d7b</guid>
      <description>Nolah's Evolution is the mattress I personally sleep on as a certified sleep coach, and it's on sale pre-Presidents' Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Glasses for OnlyFans Live Streaming Have Arrived</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/smart-glasses-for-onlyfans-live-streaming-have-arrived-2000710780</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710780</guid>
      <description>It was only a matter of time, to be honest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump unveils a healthcare plan aimed at lowering costs</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475918/trump-great-health-care-plan-aca</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T21:34:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475918/trump-great-health-care-plan-aca</guid>
      <description>The cornerstone is his proposal to send money directly to Americans for health savings accounts so they can handle insurance and health costs as they see fit. 
President Donald Trump&#160;on Thursday announced the outlines of a health care plan he wants Congress to take up as&#160;Republicans have faced increasing pressure to address rising health costs&#160;after lawmakers let&#160;subsidies expire....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
