<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:30:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Discover Previously Unknown Species in Utah&#8217;s Great Salt Lake</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/researchers-discover-previously-unknown-species-in-utahs-great-salt-lake-2000709251</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709251</guid>
      <description>And they've proposed two "kind of crazy" ideas for how it got there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet&#8217;s Wing Adds 150 Walmart Stores to Drone Delivery Program</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alphabets-wing-adds-150-walmart-stores-to-drone-delivery-program-2000709294</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709294</guid>
      <description>Bzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bye Bye MLC: QLC and TLC to be dominant SSD technologies amidst AI's ravenous appetite for NAND &#8212; and PLC won't probably happen till the era of Petabyte SSDs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/bye-bye-mlc-qlc-and-tlc-to-be-dominant-ssd-technologies-amidst-ai-ravenous-appetite-for-nand-and-plc-wont-probably-happen-till-the-era-of-petabyte-ssds</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kv2WwK8VuiAfvkk3S7TXCH</guid>
      <description>TrendForce shows MLC NAND retreating while TLC and QLC dominate SSDs, driven by AI workloads, data growth, and supplier strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseus&#8217; retractable travel adapter is on sale for more than 50 percent off today</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/860791/baseus-enercore-cg11-6-in-1-universal-travel-adapter-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T15:04:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860791</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re planning on traveling at all this year, the Baseus EnerCore CG11 Universal Travel Adapter is worth a look. The adapter can power up to six devices at once, and now through the end of today, January 12th, it&#8217;s on sale for just $34.19 (about $36 off) at Amazon, matching the all-time low price [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK pushes up a law criminalizing deepfake nudes in response to Grok</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860881/uk-ai-x-grok-law-criminalizing-deepfake-nudes-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T15:03:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860881</guid>
      <description>The UK is bringing a law into force that makes creating non-consensual intimate deepfake images, like the ones that have proliferated on X because of the Grok AI chatbot, a criminal offense, as reported by the BBC. "The Data Act, passed last year, made it a criminal offence to create - or request the creation [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Is Going Full Borg to Try and Stop the Netflix-Warner Bros. Merger</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paramount-netflix-warner-bros-lawsuit-2000709200</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709200</guid>
      <description>Resistance is futile: Paramount isn't going to let Netflix grab ahold of Warner Bros. without a fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Research Exposes the Good and the Gross in Pompeii&#8217;s Baths</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-research-exposes-the-good-and-the-gross-in-pompeiis-baths-2000708925</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708925</guid>
      <description>Mount Vesuvius preserved the ancient city's water system, including evidence of filth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stranger Things behind-the-scenes doc is a lot more boring than a secret episode</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/860692/one-last-adventure-the-making-of-stranger-things-5-netflix-review</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860692</guid>
      <description>It's a weird time in the Stranger Things community. Following a monthslong lead-up to a finale that was so big it screened in theaters, the show's superfans have been spending their time dissecting the fifth season in order to prove that a hidden ninth episode is coming that represents the true ending of Stranger Things. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first Lego Pok&#233;mon sets have been announced, and of course the coolest is over $600</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/the-first-lego-pokemon-sets-have-been-announced-and-of-course-the-coolest-is-over-usd600</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dNNqBwWq63t7bntoc6J9</guid>
      <description>Want to be a master of Lego Pok&#233;mon? Get ready to pay up as the 8 Gym Badges are locked behind the most expensive set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Globes ignored this underrated body horror movie &#8212; but the Oscars didn&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/the-golden-globes-ignored-this-underrated-body-horror-movie-but-the-oscars-didnt</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66VUBb2nLjFvie4jLz6R2d</guid>
      <description>The Ugly Stepsister is a criminally underrated horror movie, but it is in with the chance of being Oscar-nominated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 robots were wild, silly, and sometimes disappointing but there was one that restored my faith in robotics</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/ces-2026-robots-were-wild-silly-and-sometimes-disappointing-but-there-was-one-that-restored-my-faith-in-robotics</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aGewotYVN8zKj35cbpsRGR</guid>
      <description>We take a look at the wide range of robots on display at CES 2026 and find that Altas is still the one to watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Just Built Its Own Time System for the Moon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/china-just-built-its-own-time-system-for-the-moon-2000708991</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708991</guid>
      <description>The Moon's weaker gravity results in slightly faster clocks than on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic wants you to use Claude to &amp;#8216;Cowork&amp;#8217; in latest AI agent push</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/860730/anthropic-cowork-feature-ai-agents-claude-code</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T14:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860730</guid>
      <description>Anthropic wants to expand Claude's AI agent capabilities and take advantage of the growing hype around Claude Code - and it's doing it with a brand-new feature released Monday, dubbed "Claude Cowork." "Cowork can take on many of the same tasks that Claude Code can handle, but in a more approachable form for non-coding tasks," [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic&#8217;s new Cowork tool offers Claude Code without the code</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/anthropics-new-cowork-tool-offers-claude-code-without-the-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081970</guid>
      <description>Built into the Claude Desktop app, Cowork lets users designate a specific folder where Claude can read or modify files, with further instructions given through the standard chat interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Lenovo monitor has six speakers and is the only Windows PC monitor with Dolby Atmos and Dolby Vision &#8212; it even has a 4K detachable webcam</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-lenovo-monitor-has-six-speakers-and-is-the-only-windows-pc-monitor-with-dolby-atmos-and-dolby-vision-and-it-even-has-a-4k-detachable-webcam</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VFW9tpSkKTEYJ9MbibdcXc</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s Yoga Pro 27UD-10 OLED monitor combines detachable 4K video, USB4 connectivity, Dolby audio, and laptop-focused color syncing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic made a version of its coding AI for regular people</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-made-a-version-of-its-coding-ai-for-regular-people-193000363.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e96f209-4988-475c-9ec3-ef79a87a6915</guid>
      <description>If you follow Anthropic, you're probably familiar with Claude Code. Since the fall of 2024, the company has been training its AI models to use and navigate computers like a human would, and the coding agent has been the most practical expression of that work, giving developers a way to automate rote programming tasks. Starting today, Anthropic is giving regular people a way to take advantage of those capabilities, with the release of a new preview feature called Claude Cowork.The company is billing Cowork as "a simpler way for anyone &#8212; not just developers &#8212; to work with Claude." After you give...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disney+ Hulu bundle is on sale for $10 for one month right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-disney-hulu-bundle-is-on-sale-for-10-for-one-month-right-now-192814784.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b6e8a2-981f-4fc9-b476-d49dcaeed4ba</guid>
      <description>The peak time for deals on streaming services &#8212; the holiday shopping season &#8212; has come and gone, but Disney is back with a fresh offer for the new year. New and eligible returning subscribers can get one month of the ad-supported Disney+ Hulu bundle for just $10. That's $3 off the usual monthly rate for the bundle, and more than 58 percent off if you consider the prices for each service individually (Disney+ at $12 per month and, separately, Hulu also at $12 per month).
We'd be remiss if we didn't mention that this isn't quite as good as the Black Friday deal we saw last year, which offered th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York wants to regulate Roblox</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/860727/new-york-governor-hochul-roblox-kids-online-safety</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T14:24:31-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860727</guid>
      <description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul is making kids' online safety a cornerstone of her administration, and she's eyeing a platform that has often flown under the radar: Roblox. As progress in Congress has stagnated, states have become the primary drivers of internet reforms meant to protect kids, including age verification laws and new requirements for [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s EPA plans to ignore health effects of air pollution</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/trumps-epa-plans-to-ignore-health-effects-of-air-pollution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081966</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration plans to stop assigning value to human life when analyzing the costs and benefits of air pollution controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg announces new 'Meta Compute' initiative for its data center and AI projects</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/mark-zuckerberg-announces-new-meta-compute-initiative-for-its-data-center-and-ai-projects-192100086.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1fcf9d8-ee66-4654-9d97-97fe34b6f480</guid>
      <description>On the heels of Mark Zuckerberg announcing that Meta's former board member, Dina Powell McCormick, would be formally joining the company as president and vice chairman, the CEO has shared new details about her purview at the company. The executive will play a key role overseeing Meta's sprawling infrastructure investments as part of a newly announced initiative called Meta Compute."Meta is planning to build tens of gigawatts this decade, and hundreds of gigawatts or more over time," Zuckerberg said in an update. "How we engineer, invest, and partner to build this infrastructure will become a s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon says 97% of its devices can support Alexa+</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/12/amazon-says-97-of-its-devices-can-support-alexa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081937</guid>
      <description>Amazon is counting on its Alexa footprint to help it gain traction in the consumer AI race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snag a Feature-Packed Gaming Headset for Under $100</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/corsair-void-wireless-v2-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696530da6954b8e16236c6e6</guid>
      <description>Corsair&#8217;s updated Void Wireless sports Dolby Atmos and a lightweight, breathable fit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's new tool will see ChatGPT try and help you find a new job</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/openais-new-tool-will-see-chatgpt-try-and-help-you-find-a-new-job</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CkTifzzc6QNoCCnGCVhc5k</guid>
      <description>OpenAI believed to be working on a new Jobs dashboard for job hunting, resume building, and upskilling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Administration Takes Stake in Major Critical Mineral Firm</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-administration-takes-stake-in-major-critical-mineral-firm-2000709109</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709109</guid>
      <description>The Pentagon is investing in Atlantic Alumina in a bid to boost U.S. gallium and alumina production and reduce reliance on China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-Wing Influencers Have Flooded Minneapolis</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/right-wing-influencers-have-flooded-minneapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69650e3b99c4d53ac57dbcac</guid>
      <description>Clips from creators in Minnesota have become primary evidence in attempts by the right wing to justify ICE&#8217;s surge on American cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hell Yeah, an Action Figure Wave of &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; Freaks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-wars-black-series-taun-we-watto-geonosian-price-release-date-2000709197</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709197</guid>
      <description>Dad, Taun We's here&#8212;as a 'Star Wars' Black Series action figure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are my favorite Switch 2 accessories</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/buying-guides/720160/best-switch-2-accessories</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=720160</guid>
      <description>The Nintendo Switch 2 can be enjoyed right out of the box, but it&#8217;s even better with the right accessories. Some of these add-ons are more crucial than others, especially if you&#8217;re deciding what to buy early on. For example, a case and a screen protector can keep your console safe from scuffs, scratches, and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of nurses go on strike at major New York City hospitals over contract disputes</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91473175/nurses-strike-new-york-city-hospitals-contracts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T18:49:11</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91473175/nurses-strike-new-york-city-hospitals-contracts</guid>
      <description>The strike could be a significant early test of Mayor Zohran Mamdani&#8217;s new administration.
Thousands of nurses in three hospital systems in New York City went on strike Monday after&#160;negotiations through the weekend&#160;failed to yield breakthroughs in their contract disputes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoFundMe Ignores Own Rules by Hosting a Legal-Defense Fund for the ICE Agent Who Killed Renee Good</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/gofundme-ice-jonathan-ross-renee-good-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69650ccc4975e7a7fa43a7b4</guid>
      <description>The fundraiser for the ICE agent in the Renee Good killing has stayed online in seeming breach of GoFundMe&#8217;s own terms of service, prompting questions about selective enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats should reject tech influence to win elections, Warren says</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860706/democrats-elections-big-tech-influence-senator-warren</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T13:44:21-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860706</guid>
      <description>The path forward for the Democratic party after its 2024 defeat includes less tech influence and more populist policies, according to Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA). Warren delivered this message in a speech at the National Press Club in Washington, DC on Monday, where she charted a vision for the future of a party that's still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Minisforum MS-02 Ultra : voici le PC le plus compact du monde avec une GeForce RTX 5060</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/test/2909463_test-du-minisforum-ms-02-ultra-voici-le-pc-le-plus-compact-du-monde-avec-une-geforce-rtx-5060</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/test/2909463_test-du-minisforum-ms-02-ultra-voici-le-pc-le-plus-compact-du-monde-avec-une-geforce-rtx-5060</guid>
      <description>
Testons le Minisforum MS-02 Ultra, le successeur spirituel du MS-01. La promesse ici est simple mais totalement d&#233;raisonnable : faire entrer un Core Ultra 9, 64 Go de RAM, une RTX 5060 et, tenez-vous bien, du r&#233;seau 25 GbE dans un ch&#226;ssis de moins de 5 litres.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientific breakthroughs are redefining what&#8217;s possible with asteroids, cancer research, and neurotech</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91448193/scientific-breakthroughs-are-redefining-whats-possible-with-asteroids-cancer-research-and-neurotech</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-12T18:31:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91448193/scientific-breakthroughs-are-redefining-whats-possible-with-asteroids-cancer-research-and-neurotech</guid>
      <description>At the WCI Summit in November, researchers shared some of the novel techniques that they are using to improve the human condition.
Technological advancements in various fields of science are shattering what some scientists once deemed impossible. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
