<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:23:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Was the Year the Vibes Were Off</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/2025-was-the-year-the-vibes-were-off-2000702368</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702368</guid>
      <description>We might have to start trying again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make your startup stand out in a crowded market, according to investors</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/29/vcs-spill-what-they-really-want-to-hear-in-a-founder-pitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078439</guid>
      <description>Investors on what they really want to hear in a founder's pitch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyson has just released a vacuum that doesn't make any sense &#8211; here are 6 baffling questions about the PencilVac, answered</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/dyson-just-released-a-vacuum-that-doesnt-make-any-sense-here-are-6-baffling-questions-about-the-pencilvac-answered</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cnpdVpy5Vpwaktt9o8gKKV</guid>
      <description>I've been using this vacuum for two weeks, and I've finally figured it all out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD Projekt Co-Founder Buys Steam Rival GOG</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cd-projekt-co-founder-buys-steam-rival-gog-2000704077</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704077</guid>
      <description>New owner, still DRM-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple AirTag four-packs are on sale for $65 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apple-airtag-four-packs-are-on-sale-for-65-right-now-202333053.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Apple keeps most of its product pricing on a tight leash, but we do see the company's AirTags go on sale pretty frequently. Another cost cut has come around for this item just in time for the new year. Amazon is currently selling a four-pack of AirTags for $65. At a third off the regular cost, that price is pretty close to the record low discount of $63 we've seen for these Bluetooth trackers.


AirTags can be useful for people who travel frequently, helping you to keep track of essentials like your passport as well as a way to keep tabs on luggage while you're on the go. If you do purchase so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opioid Abuse in Pregnancy Surged in Recent Decades, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/opioid-abuse-in-pregnancy-surged-in-recent-decades-study-finds-2000704027</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704027</guid>
      <description>Pregnant women who reported opioid use disorder were more likely to face serious health complications, as were their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's fastest mini PC doesn't run Windows 11 &#8212; $2,899 gets you a Core Ultra 9 CPU, 96GB of RAM, RTX 5090M, 2TB SSD, and yes, it is all about AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/worlds-fastest-mini-pc-doesnt-run-windows-11-usd2899-gets-you-a-core-ultra-9-cpu-96gb-of-ram-rtx-5090m-2tb-ssd-and-yes-it-is-all-about-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R4gfU8vbR599iQa4PAiyMW</guid>
      <description>The Olares One mini PC delivers desktop-grade components, substantial RAM, a high-end GPU, and SSD storage, emphasizing AI workloads and local processing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year's AI surprise: Fal releases its own version of Flux 2 image generator that's 10x cheaper and 6x more efficient</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/new-years-ai-surprise-fal-releases-its-own-version-of-flux-2-image-generator</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ex9vuxdBqKV469rO9Sczm</guid>
      <description>Hot on the heels of its new $140 million Series D fundraising round, the multi-modal enterprise AI media creation platform fal.ai, known simply as "fal" or "Fal" is back with a year-end surprise: a faster, more efficient, and cheaper version of the Flux.2 [dev] open source image model from Black Forest Labs.Fal's new model FLUX.2 [dev] Turbo is a distilled, ultra-fast image generation model that&#8217;s already outperforming many of its larger rivals on public benchmarks, and is available now on Hugging Face, though very importantly: under a custom Black Forest non-commercial license. It&#8217;s not a ful...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Beloved Hockey Homosexuals Are Dipping Their Toes Into Romantasy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/heated-rivalry-connor-storrie-hudson-williams-quinn-romantasy-2000704024</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704024</guid>
      <description>'Heated Rivalry' breakouts Connor Storrie and Hudson Williams star in an erotic audio tale in which they play fae princes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA finally has a leader, but its future is no more certain</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-finally-has-a-leader-but-its-future-is-no-more-certain-201109072.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07817bf3-9e80-4ca4-bce4-810a0aea5a02</guid>
      <description>After a rudderless year and an exodus of around 4,000 employees due to Trump administration cuts, NASA got what may be its first piece of good news recently. On December 17, the Senate confirmed billionaire Jared Isaacman as the agency's new administrator. He now holds the power to rehabilitate a battered engine of scientific research, or steer it towards even more disruption.&#160;Considering the caliber of President Trump's other appointees, Isaacman is probably the best candidate for the job. Outside of being a successful entrepreneur, he has flown fighter jets and been to space twice as part of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media follower counts have never mattered less, creator economy execs say</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/29/social-media-follower-counts-have-never-mattered-less-creator-economy-execs-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078997</guid>
      <description>&#8220;I think that 2025 was the year where the algorithm completely took over, so followings stopped mattering entirely,&#8221; LTK CEO Amber Venz Box said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s a 'secret' sleep timer hidden in your iPhone and iPad &#8211; here's how to unlock it for Netflix</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/ios/theres-a-secret-sleep-timer-hidden-in-your-iphone-and-ipad-heres-how-to-unlock-it-for-netflix</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BfZXkjh4JKZyz6hgz65R5Q</guid>
      <description>Some iOS and iPadOS apps like Netflix don't have built-in sleep timers, but fortunately this lesser-known feature lets you create your own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to give each state at least $147 million for rural health next year</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467598/trump-administration-rural-health-care-state-funding</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T19:55:40</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467598/trump-administration-rural-health-care-state-funding</guid>
      <description>The fund is intended to improve rural health outcomes that have worsened over decades.
The Trump administration will award each U.S. state between $147 million and $281 million in 2026 under a new rural health transformation program aimed at improving access to care and service quality, a senior White House aide said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch AMD Keynote at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/how-to-watch-ces-2026-amd-keynote</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02fv16IAPsfISTA22mAEM7h</guid>
      <description>AMD CEO Dr. Lisa Su will deliver a keynote address at CES, helping kick off the major tech event. You can watch the livestream on Monday, Jan. 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid robots are having a moment, but still face an uphill battle</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467593/humanoid-robots-summit-uphill-battle</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T19:38:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467593/humanoid-robots-summit-uphill-battle</guid>
      <description>About 50 companies around the world have raised at least $100 million to develop humanoids.
Robots have long been seen as a bad bet for Silicon Valley investors &#8212; too complicated, capital-intensive, and &#8220;boring, honestly,&#8221; says venture capitalist Modar Alaoui.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cameron Is Also Mad About the Opening of &#8216;Alien 3&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/james-cameron-alien-3-reaction-2000703999</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703999</guid>
      <description>The 'Aliens' director told friend and star Michael Biehn his feelings about how the franchise followed their sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Dev Loses His Mind Over AI Agent&#8217;s Unsolicited &#8216;Act of Kindness&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/legendary-dev-loses-his-mind-over-ai-agents-unsolicited-act-of-kindness-2000704001</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704001</guid>
      <description>Just fuck you. Fuck you all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers say they have stolen 40 million Cond&#233; Nast Records - here's how to stay safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-say-they-have-stolen-40-million-conde-nast-records-heres-how-to-stay-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ziNpUHyjTRPWpoaAtHFnkf</guid>
      <description>A hacker claims to have good intentions - but do they, really?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collecting Social Security? These 2026 changes could affect your money</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467502/collecting-social-security-these-2026-changes-could-affect-your-money</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T19:28:51</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467502/collecting-social-security-these-2026-changes-could-affect-your-money</guid>
      <description>A delayed cost-of-living adjustment grabbed headlines, but four other Social Security updates could affect retirees and future claimants alike.
Roughly 75 million Americans will receive a 2.8% boost to their income in 2026, thanks to the upcoming cost-of-living adjustment for Social Security benefits and Supplemental Security Income (SSI) payments. But other changes afoot to the program will affect people who are still working, without a glint of retirement yet in their eyes....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
