<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:42:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani is set to kill off New York's 'functionally unusable' business chatbot, which often gave out illegal advice</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/zohran-mamdani-is-set-to-kill-off-new-yorks-functionally-unusable-business-chatbot-which-often-gave-out-illegal-advice</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YfGDPUjeJ8zTEp5uxLjVS9</guid>
      <description>Mayor Zohran Mamdani plans to remove NYC business chatbot after repeated illegal advice, high costs, and inefficiencies exposed by testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big ChromeOS and Android Merger May Be Google&#8217;s Last Walled Garden</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-big-chromeos-and-android-merger-may-be-googles-last-walled-garden-2000717336</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717336</guid>
      <description>The Google-pilled ChromeOS may die so that &#8216;Aluminum&#8217; will live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Sneakily Brought Some More &#8216;Star Trek Online&#8217; Ships to TV</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-star-trek-online-klingon-ships-2000717306</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717306</guid>
      <description>After 'Picard' bolstered the Starfleet of the 25th century's fleets with some video game canonization, 'Starfleet Academy' lends a helping hand to the Klingons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get more screen space for less with this 16.1-inch Arzopa portable monitor &#8212; boasting a sharp 2.5K QHD display for only $140 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/get-more-screen-space-for-less-with-this-16-1-inch-arzopa-portable-monitor-boasting-a-sharp-2-5k-qhd-display-for-only-usd140-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i6DDpCicUi5ytVnVLDkAsW</guid>
      <description>The Arzopa 16.1-inch portable monitor with a 2.5K QHD display is $60 off at Amazon, now just $139.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft says it&#8217;s building an app store for AI content licensing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/873296/microsoft-publisher-content-marketplace-ai-licensing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873296</guid>
      <description>Microsoft says it is working on the Publisher Content Marketplace (PCM), an AI licensing hub that shows usage terms set by publishers. That way, AI companies can easily shop the terms and set up deals to use online content for "grounding" their AI models, while the content owners get usage-based reporting to help set prices. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple just made Xcode better for vibe coding</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/apple-just-made-xcode-better-for-vibe-coding-195653049.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">477d4d1b-ab12-4ec8-ac1f-ec11c985c0ae</guid>
      <description>Apple has just released Xcode 26.3, and it's a big step forward in terms of the company's support of coding agents. The new release expands on the AI features the company introduced with Xcode 26 at WWDC 2025 to give systems like Claude and ChatGPT more robust access to its in-house IDE.&#160;With the update, Apple says Claude and OpenAI's Codex "can search documentation, explore file structures, update project settings, and verify their work visually by capturing Xcode Previews and iterating through builds and fixes." This is in contrast to earlier releases of Xcode 26 where those same agents were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Infiltrated Moltbook, the AI-Only Social Network Where Humans Aren&#8217;t Allowed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/i-infiltrated-moltbook-ai-only-social-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69822a3b7c553e1f8e36ee8d</guid>
      <description>I went undercover on Moltbook and loved role-playing as a conscious bot. But rather than a novel breakthrough, the AI-only site is a crude rehashing of sci-fi fantasies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YC startups can now receive investment in stablecoin</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/yc-startups-can-now-recieve-investment-in-stablecoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089218</guid>
      <description>All startups accepted into YC will soon have the option to receive their seed checks via stablecoins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paramilitary ICE and CBP Units at the Center of Minnesota's Killings</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-cbp-srt-bortac-units-immigration-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697bda99eeb4ef697c02db68</guid>
      <description>Two agents involved in the shooting deaths of US citizens in Minneapolis are reportedly part of highly militarized DHS units whose extreme tactics are generally reserved for war zones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check Out 10 Weird and Wonderful Finalists for the &#8216;Pulitzer of the New Instrument World&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/check-out-10-weird-and-wonderful-finalists-for-the-pulitzer-of-the-new-instrument-world-2000717314</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717314</guid>
      <description>The finalists for Georgia Tech&#8217;s annual Guthman Musical Instrument Competition just dropped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road markers are a new target for hackers - experts find self-driving cars and autonomous drones can be misled by malicious instructions written on road signs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/not-even-road-markers-are-safe-from-hackers-experts-find-that-self-driving-cars-and-autonomous-drones-can-be-hacked-by-reading-malicious-instructions-written-on-road-signs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXZx9Ufv3YyPTfrFm8ByMh</guid>
      <description>Manipulated text in physical spaces can hijack autonomous systems, while existing cybersecurity tools offer no protection against this risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal replaces CEO Alex Chriss with HP&#8217;s Enrique Lores</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486201/paypal-hp-lores-chriss-venmo-dorman-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486201/paypal-hp-lores-chriss-venmo-dorman-ai</guid>
      <description>Lores will take over as PayPal CEO on March 1. 
PayPal is replacing CEO Alex Chriss with Enrique Lores, saying that the pace of change and execution at the company has not met board expectations over the past two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech faces new pressure for allowing ICE ads</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486019/big-tech-faces-new-pressure-for-allowing-ice-ads</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:35:30</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486019/big-tech-faces-new-pressure-for-allowing-ice-ads</guid>
      <description>Reps. Becca Balint and Pramila Jayapal are demanding answers from Google and Meta over recruitment posts they say mirror language used by extremist groups.
Amid nationwide outrage over the killings of Ren&#233;e Good and Alex Pretti, two House Democrats are pressing Google and Meta to answer for recruitment campaign posts that Immigration and Customs Enforcement has recently run on their platforms. The lawmakers, Reps. Becca Balint of Vermont and Pramila Jayapal of Washington, have accused the companies of being &#8220;complicit&#8221; with the Trump administration and enabling ICE&#8217;s efforts to promote slogans...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is your state making school zones more dangerous?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480894/is-your-state-making-school-zones-more-dangerous</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480894/is-your-state-making-school-zones-more-dangerous</guid>
      <description>Speed cameras save lives. Why are states seeking to ban them?
Ignaz Semmelweis was a physician working in a maternity ward in the 1840s. He noticed something disturbing: women giving birth in the ward staffed by doctors and medical students died from &#8220;childbed fever&#8221; at rates of 10-35%, while a nearby ward staffed by midwives had death rates under 4%....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox just made an unexpected move that Chrome would never copy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486070/this-new-firefox-setting-lets-you-block-ai-before-you-ever-see-it</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486070/this-new-firefox-setting-lets-you-block-ai-before-you-ever-see-it</guid>
      <description>AI tools are coming to the browser, but Mozilla is giving users full authority over whether they appear.
Firefox has a reputation as the browser of choice for power users who prefer to customize everything &#8211; and it just gave users one very important new option. While most other tech companies shove AI &#8220;enhancements&#8221; down their users&#8217; throats, Mozilla is introducing a way to disable Firefox&#8217;s AI features outright &#8211; a boon for anyone searching for a safe haven from the AI software onslaught....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsidian has no plans to make The Outer Worlds 3, likely due to poor sales</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/obsidian-has-no-plans-to-make-the-outer-worlds-3-likely-due-to-poor-sales-192756351.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88fa18a9-5188-470f-9a6f-e431ff796c13</guid>
      <description>Developer Obsidian recently announced that it currently has no plans to make The Outer Worlds 3, according to a report by Bloomberg. Company head Fergus Urquhart didn't give a reason as to why Obsidian won't be working on a sequel, but he did note that the performance of The Outer Worlds 2 was "disappointing" and that it needs to "think a lot about how much we put into the games, how much we spend on them and how long they take."
Urquhart also said that Avowed was something of a miss for the company, but that it remains committed to the franchise. Obsidian plans to "keep making games in the Av...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking back at the 5 biggest AI lessons of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485272/looking-back-at-the-5-biggest-ai-lessons-of-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:21:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485272/looking-back-at-the-5-biggest-ai-lessons-of-2025</guid>
      <description>And what they mean for 2026.
Lior Pozin had an epiphany about AI infrastructure in early 2025. As CEO of AutoDS, an AI-powered e-commerce automation platform, he had pushed his team to deploy AI features quickly, betting that speed would define success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While the World Waits for &#8216;Doctor Who&#8217; to Return, the BBC Is Selling Off Some Major Props</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/doctor-who-prop-auction-ncuti-gatwa-david-tennant-bbc-2000717284</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717284</guid>
      <description>Items from David Tennant's Tenth Doctor all the way through Fifteenth Doctor Ncuti Gatwa's final season are going on the block, with a portion of proceeds going to charity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft : malgr&#233; des investissements massifs, personne (ou presque) ne veut payer pour Copilot</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2965271_copilot-malgre-des-investissements-massifs-personne-ou-presque-ne-veut-payer-pour-lia-de-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2965271_copilot-malgre-des-investissements-massifs-personne-ou-presque-ne-veut-payer-pour-lia-de-microsoft</guid>
      <description>
Copilot n'aurait pas la rentabilit&#233; esp&#233;r&#233;e par Microsoft alors que la part d'utilisateurs payants de son IA reste encore tout &#224; fait minime.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Your Roku Before the Big Game</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/roku-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698233af8aac99dc2d60ad18</guid>
      <description>Roku is knocking down the price of all of its streaming devices ahead of football&#8217;s big game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP&#8217;s 15.6-inch Ultrabook with 16GB RAM and one-year Microsoft 365 Personal subscription is under $350 on Amazon - save $200 for a limited time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hps-15-6-inch-ultrabook-with-16gb-ram-and-one-year-microsoft-365-personal-subscription-is-under-usd350-on-amazon-save-usd200-for-a-limited-time</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5sZqTbBuxTLbjfoGBFsQLh</guid>
      <description>HP 15.6-inch Ultrabook with 16GB of RAM and a one-year Microsoft 365 Personal subscription is $200 off at Amazon, now just $349.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s Xcode adds OpenAI and Anthropic&#8217;s coding agents</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/873300/apple-xcode-openai-anthropic-ai-agentic-coding</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T14:04:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873300</guid>
      <description>Apple is building OpenAI and Anthropic's AI-powered coding agents directly into Xcode. New integrations in Xcode 26.3 will give developers the ability to call upon Anthropic's Claude Agent and OpenAI's Codex to write and edit code, update project settings, search documentation, and more. Xcode is the software developers can use to create and test apps [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France ditches Zoom and Teams as Europe seeks to cut digital ties to the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91485935/europe-digital-sovereignty-big-tech</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91485935/europe-digital-sovereignty-big-tech</guid>
      <description>The push for &#8216;digital sovereignty&#8217; is gaining attention as the Trump administration strikes an increasingly belligerent posture toward Europe. 
In France, civil servants will ditch Zoom and Teams for a homegrown video conference system. Soldiers in Austria are using open source office software to write reports after the military dropped Microsoft Office. Bureaucrats in a German state have also turned to free software for their administrative work....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 plans: What&#8217;s next for Startup Battlefield 200</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/looking-ahead-to-2026-whats-next-for-startup-battlefield-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083590</guid>
      <description>See what to expect for Startup Battlefield 200 in 2026, the ultimate startup pitch competition on the global stage at TechCrunch Disrupt. Join the mailing list to be the first to know when applications drop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;&#233;cran gaming incurv&#233; Samsung Odyssey G5 de 34 pouces revient &#224; moins de 245 &#8364; avec ce code promo</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2964797_lecran-gaming-incurve-samsung-odyssey-g5-de-34-pouces-revient-a-moins-de-245-e-avec-ce-code-promo</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2964797_lecran-gaming-incurve-samsung-odyssey-g5-de-34-pouces-revient-a-moins-de-245-e-avec-ce-code-promo</guid>
      <description>
Le Samsung Odyssey G5 se d&#233;marque avec une dalle incurv&#233;e de 34 pouces qui va vous proposer une toute nouvelle immersion dans vos jeux favoris. Chez Cdiscount, il tombe &#224; 244,99 euros avec un code promo.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
