<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 01:53:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A comprehensive list of 2025 tech layoffs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/12/tech-layoffs-2025-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=2607662</guid>
      <description>A complete list of all the known layoffs in tech, from Big Tech to startups, broken down by month throughout 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s 2025 holiday gift guide</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/809421/holiday-gift-guide-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-12T19:08:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=809421</guid>
      <description>The holidays have a way of sneaking up on us. One minute you're trick-or-treating with your kids, and the next you're panic shopping in a Buc-ee's gift aisle. But it doesn't have to be that way. With the right cheat sheet, you can keep the holiday spirit high and stress levels low. Fortunately, we did [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple releases OS updates, Edge Light tool. How to try macOS, iPadOS, and iOS 26.2.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/apple-launches-os-updates-macos-ipados-ios-26-2</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">039jgbRUu3AQbtSJ31K1HoW</guid>
      <description>The latest Apple OS updates started rolling out to users on Dec. 12. Users can now update to iOS 26.2, macOS 26.2, iPadOS 26.2, and watchOS 26.2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Saturday Night's Main Event: How to watch John Cena's final match for free</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/wwe-saturday-nights-main-event-how-to-watch-john-cenas-final-match-for-free-235537779.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">755ce920-9d91-43a0-aecd-1b1a56d18c42</guid>
      <description>John Cena began his WWE retirement tour back in January, and it's coming to an end this weekend when the wrestling legend headlines WWE Saturday Night's Main Event. For the last fight of his career, Cena has been matched up with "The Ring General" Gunther on the night's fight card, which also features matches between Cody Rhodes and Oba Femi, a tag team match featuring AJ Styles &amp; Dragon Lee vs. Je'Von Evans &amp; Leon Slater, and a women's matchup between Bayley and Sol Ruca. This show starts at 8 p.m. ET on Saturday and will stream with a subscription to Peacock, or grab a 7-day trial of Peacock...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
