<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:19:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Accused of Manipulating Streaming Play Counts With Bots in New Lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/drake-accused-of-manipulating-streaming-play-counts-with-bots-in-new-lawsuit-2000705004</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705004</guid>
      <description>A new class action claims the rapper helped promote an online casino and allegedly used the site to fund bot farms to boost music streaming numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Oysters Behind Salmonella Outbreak Sweeping Across the US, CDC Warns</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/raw-oysters-behind-salmonella-outbreak-sweeping-across-the-us-cdc-warns-2000704972</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704972</guid>
      <description>At least 64 cases in 22 states have been identified so far, though the true toll is "likely much higher," CDC health officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 88 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-88-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056445.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>Christmas may be over, but some holiday VPN deals are still going strong. The early days of January are a great time to grab a last-minute subscription for yourself or a loved one. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can stream TV shows and events from all over the world, protect your information from hackers and thwart  online trackers.
Although we strongly recommend using a VPN, jumping on the first deal that comes along might get you stuck with a substandard app. Beyond that, even otherwise respectable VPNs sometimes frame their prices in misleading ways, with advertised dea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physicists Turn Quantum Chaos Into Something Surprisingly Useful</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/physicists-turn-quantum-chaos-into-something-surprisingly-useful-2000704962</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704962</guid>
      <description>Long considered a serious technical challenge, superradiance could actually help quantum devices go even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Andor&#8217; Season 2&#8217;s Opening Remains One of Its Best Moments</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/andor-season-2-opening-scene-star-wars-2000704967</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704967</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the circle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America&#8217;s 15 richest billionaires got $1 trillion richer as the affordability crisis became a top concern in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468647/15-richest-billionaires-got-way-richer-during-the-affordability-crisis</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T20:17:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468647/15-richest-billionaires-got-way-richer-during-the-affordability-crisis</guid>
      <description>Rising costs and a worsening job market didn&#8217;t stop the super-wealthy from pulling even further ahead than everyone else last year.
For many Americans, 2025 wasn&#8217;t a great year financially. The affordability crisis and general economic concerns became defining themes of the year as people dealt with rising costs and a worsening job market.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entreprise d&#8217;Elon Musk | L&#8217;assistant IA de X utilis&#233; pour cr&#233;er du contenu p&#233;dopornographique</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-02/entreprise-d-elon-musk/l-assistant-ia-de-x-utilise-pour-creer-du-contenu-pedopornographique.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:16:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f752e1c5701d3c6d9fa75de51780f123</guid>
      <description>Grok, l&#8217;assistant d&#8217;intelligence artificielle (IA) du r&#233;seau social X, a reconnu vendredi l&#8217;existence de &#171;&#160;failles&#160;&#187; ayant permis &#224; des utilisateurs d&#8217;obtenir de lui des images &#224; caract&#232;re sexuel impliquant des mineurs ou des femmes, suscitant des protestations &#224; travers le monde et l&#8217;&#233;largissement d&#8217;une enqu&#234;te judiciaire en France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged PS5 Jailbreak Method Spikes Prices for Old Star Wars Game on eBay</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alleged-ps5-jailbreak-method-spikes-prices-for-old-star-wars-game-on-ebay-2000704980</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704980</guid>
      <description>'Star Wars Racer Revenge' is selling for hundreds of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 new horror movies on Prime Video, Shudder, HBO Max, and more in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/7-new-horror-movies-on-prime-video-shudder-hbo-max-and-more-in-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VcaSymNGvi6UKxv6qrWtXM</guid>
      <description>Looking to cure those January blues? There's some gripping horror movies waiting for you across the best streaming services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Samsung's "First Look" CES 2026 presentation on Sunday</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/how-to-watch-samsungs-first-look-ces-2026-presentation-on-sunday-190027889.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99e05139-49a3-486e-a22a-1ec128284043</guid>
      <description>NurPhoto via Getty Images
Samsung is arguably the 800-pound gorilla of CES, with a full spectrum of products that range from phones and computers to refrigerators, AI assistants and rolling robots. But for CES 2026, the company is switching things up a bit: Instead of its longtime midday Monday press conference, the Korean giant will take the lead of the show with a Sunday night presentation.
Over the past few weeks, Samsung has been dropping hints about what's on the agenda, but what we're really hoping to see is an update on the Ballie robot &#8212; a star of previous CES presentations that ostens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch NHL Winter Classic 2026: live stream New York Rangers vs Florida Panthers, TV channels, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/hockey/nhl-winter-classic-2026-live-stream-new-york-rangers-vs-florida-panthers</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2AzUNtapCpiqkRUy3dmTGQ</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch Rangers vs Panthers live streams online in the 2026 NHL Winter Classic, as the traditional New Year's game heads to Florida for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big changes are coming to national parks in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468435/big-changes-are-coming-to-national-parks-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468435/big-changes-are-coming-to-national-parks-in-2026</guid>
      <description>A slate of changes tied to America&#8217;s 250th anniversary will affect entry fees, passes, and who gets free access.
America&#8217;s National Parks offer some of the country&#8217;s most impressive vistas &#8211; and that fact draws hundreds of millions of people to the parks each year. But more changes are on the way for the National Parks in 2026 and visitors aren&#8217;t likely to be happy with all of them.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Scanned 3I/ATLAS for Alien Signals. Here&#8217;s What They Found</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-scanned-3i-atlas-for-alien-signals-heres-what-they-found-2000704975</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704975</guid>
      <description>As this interstellar object approached its closest point to Earth, a massive radio telescope attempted to sniff out a technosignature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok is undressing anyone, including minors</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/853191/grok-explicit-bikini-pictures-minors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T14:52:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853191</guid>
      <description>xAI's Grok is removing clothing from pictures of people without their consent following this week's rollout of a feature that allows X users to instantly edit any image using the bot without needing the original poster's permission. Not only does the original poster not get notified if their picture was edited, but Grok appears to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billion-dollar Bitcoin hacker Ilya Lichtenstein thanks Trump for early prison release</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/853160/ilya-lichtenstein-released-razzlekhan-bitcoin-hack</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T14:51:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853160</guid>
      <description>Just over a year after being sentenced to five years in prison for the theft of billions of dollars in Bitcoin, hacker Ilya Lichtenstein is free. Lichtenstein announced his release in a post on X, specifically crediting Trump: "Thanks to President Trump's First Step Act, I have been released from prison early. I remain committed [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are Engadget's CES 2025 winners now?</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/where-are-engadgets-ces-2025-winners-now-194500216.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">025a0611-285f-4f20-bd88-7a3ad88494da</guid>
      <description>With CES 2026 slated to officially start next week, the focus is understandably on all the new products that will be announced at this year's event. But before diving into what&#8217;s new, we thought it was a good idea to revisit our best of show winners from last year to see where they're at. After all, CES is synonymous with vaporware. The good news is the Engadget team has a keen sense for BS. Of the ones we awarded at CES 2025 that&#160;haven&#8217;t&#160;been released, most are coming this year. For the remaining few, we&#8217;ll be hunting them down this CES.ASUS Zenbook A14An Asus Zenbook A14 sits out a patio tab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE's new Smart Refrigerator automates grocery shopping with a barcode scanner and Instacart</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/ges-new-smart-refrigerator-automates-grocery-shopping-with-a-barcode-scanner-and-instacart-194326610.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde0a3bb-d76b-45b7-8d70-0ac9df5a8db1</guid>
      <description>Smart fridges are a dime a dozen at CES, and LG and Samsung have thoroughly explored what's possible when you connect your fridge to the internet or slap a touchscreen on the front. The new GE Profile Smart Refrigerator with Kitchen Assistant GE is announcing ahead of CES 2026 doesn't reinvent the wheel in that regard, but it does include a first: a built-in barcode scanner for adding items to your shopping list.GE's "Scan-to-List" feature uses the barcode scanner to quickly (and precisely) add items to a shareable shopping list in GE's SmartHQ app. You can refer to that list while you're shop...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Spent the Holidays Asking Grok to Generate Sexual Images of Children</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/people-spent-the-holidays-asking-grok-to-generate-sexual-images-of-children-2000704919</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704919</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's xAI has largely been silent on the matter, but some authorities have noticed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD is slowly turning into Intel of yesteryear as $501 32-thread Ryzen 9 7950X is just enough to beat 20-thread $270 Core Ultra 7 265KF &#8212; so what's going on?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amds-slowly-turning-into-intel-of-yesteryear-as-usd501-32-thread-ryzen-9-7950x-is-just-enough-to-beat-20-thread-usd270-core-ultra-7-265kf-so-whats-going-on</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JHLqAJsfVHKSj6c89wHUtU</guid>
      <description>Intel&#8217;s Core Ultra 7 pricing exposes how AMD&#8217;s high end desktop CPUs now offer smaller performance gains despite far higher prices and power requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the LG press conference at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-lg-press-conference-at-ces-2026-monday-190159561.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6eb7981-0913-4e7b-bd66-4bc9abdcb17b</guid>
      <description>LG
For years, LG has opened CES press day with the first event of the morning &#8212; and 2026 will be no exception. The Korea-based corporation is theming this year's presentation as "Innovation in Tune with You," and &#8212; if past shows are any indication &#8212; it will highlight both the consumer electronics and large appliance sides of its mammoth global businesses.
As with many tech-focused events nowadays, AI is expected to serve as the unifying thread of LG's CES 2026 presentation. That said, LG &#8212; much like Apple &#8212; has its own take on the acronym, referring to it as "Affectionate Intelligence." The co...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
