<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:27:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft, Meta, and Amazon are paying up for &#8216;enterprise&#8217; access to Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/microsoft-meta-and-amazon-are-paying-up-for-enterprise-access-to-wikipedia</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EDWPgWYUvbPNM4rSySmNa5</guid>
      <description>Wikipedia reminds us how important it is for AI training, which is why many tech firms pay for enterprise subscriptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite blocks creators from selling prize wheel spins</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863597/fortnite-creators-steal-the-brainrot-prize-wheel-spins-block</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T15:20:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863597</guid>
      <description>Epic Games is making a big change to the rules for Fortnite creators just days after allowing them to publish experiences with in-game transactions. Beginning January 20th, experiences - which Epic Games calls "islands" - will not be able to offer in-island transactions as "a 'spin' or 'increased luck' for a prize wheel," according to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From OpenAI&#8217;s offices to a deal with Eli Lilly &#8212; how Chai Discovery became one of the flashiest names in AI drug development</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/from-openais-offices-to-a-deal-with-eli-lilly-how-chai-discovery-became-one-of-the-flashiest-names-in-ai-drug-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076938</guid>
      <description>The startup has partnered with Eli Lilly and enjoys the backing of some of Silicon Valley's most influential VCs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada cuts tariff on Chinese EVs in exchange for lower tariffs on Canadian farm products</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476330/canada-cuts-tariff-on-chinese-evs-in-exchange-for-lower-tariffs-on-canadian-farm-products</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T20:09:23</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476330/canada-cuts-tariff-on-chinese-evs-in-exchange-for-lower-tariffs-on-canadian-farm-products</guid>
      <description>Xi told Carney in a meeting at the Great Hall of the People that he is willing to continue working to improve ties.
Breaking with the United States, Canada has agreed to cut its 100% tariff on Chinese electric cars in return for lower tariffs on Canadian farm products, Prime Minister Mark Carney said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the chief resource officer</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476709/meet-the-chief-resource-officer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T20:08:17</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476709/meet-the-chief-resource-officer</guid>
      <description>Here&#8217;s the next big job change driven by AI
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get up to 78 percent off ExpressVPN two-year plans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-up-to-78-percent-off-expressvpn-two-year-plans-180602525.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $101 for two years, plus four additional free months. That works out to $3.59 per month during the promotional period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hacker posted stolen government data on Instagram</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/supreme-court-hacker-posted-stolen-government-data-on-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083477</guid>
      <description>Nicholas Moore pleaded guilty to stealing victims&#8217; information from the Supreme Court and other federal government agencies, and then posting it on his Instagram @ihackthegovernment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Glasses Are Trying to Break Up With Your Phone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/smart-glasses-are-trying-to-break-up-with-your-phone-2000711064</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711064</guid>
      <description>It's not you, it's LTE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-end SSDs have gotten so pricey they're worth more than their weight in gold</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/storage-backup/top-end-ssds-have-gotten-so-pricey-theyre-worth-more-than-their-weight-in-gold</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TV3rJY9gavQYm7CRgovvwj</guid>
      <description>Is a high-end SSD worth more than its weight in gold? Yes, in some cases, as storage prices follow in the footsteps of RAM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberGhost VPN review: Despite its flaws, the value is hard to beat</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/cyberghost-vpn-review-despite-its-flaws-the-value-is-hard-to-beat-200000250.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39c4e470-0d47-4f79-ba84-4c4c09a987e7</guid>
      <description>CyberGhost is the middle child of the Kape Technologies VPN portfolio, but in quality, it's much closer to ExpressVPN than Private Internet Access. I mainly put it on my best VPN list because it's so cheap, but I wouldn't have done that if it didn't earn its place in other ways &#8212; affordable crap is still crap, after all.
My universal impression of CyberGhost is a VPN that's not perfect but is always genuinely working to make itself better. It makes decisions based on what will help its users, not to set itself apart in a crowded market. This makes it similar to a lot of other VPNs, but that's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT users are about to get hit with targeted ads</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/chatgpt-users-are-about-to-get-hit-with-targeted-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083430</guid>
      <description>OpenAI says that users impacted by the ads will have some control over what they see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucasfilm Tried to Make an Animated &#8216;Indiana Jones&#8217; Show</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lucasfilm-tried-to-make-an-animated-indiana-jones-show-2000711185</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711185</guid>
      <description>A new report says that Lucasfilm scrapped both an animated show and a live-action spinoff too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Go&#160;: l&#8217;abonnement &#224; 8&#160;&#8364; d&#8217;OpenAI arrive en France&#8230; avec de la publicit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/chatgpt-go-labonnement-a-8-e-dopenai-arrive-en-france-avec-de-la-publicite.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1320801</guid>
      <description>OpenAI lance une version moins ch&#232;re de ChatGPT en France et partout ailleurs dans le monde. Il s'agit de ChatGPT Go, une formule &#224; 8&#160;&#8364;&#160;par mois avec des avantages int&#233;ressants &#224; la cl&#233;. Un tarif abordable mais attention, qui sera financ&#233;e en partie par&#8230; la publicit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic opens up its Claude Cowork feature to anyone with a $20 subscription</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-opens-up-its-claude-cowork-feature-to-anyone-with-a-20-subscription-194000021.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75a1d7f4-4292-40c8-8897-118f80914963</guid>
      <description>Claude Cowork, Anthropic's AI assistant for taking care of simple tasks on your computer, is now available for anyone with a $20 per month Pro subscription to try. Anthropic launched Cowork as an exclusive feature for its Max subscribers, who pay a minimum of $100 per month for more uses of Claude's expensive reasoning models and early access to experimental features. Now Claude Cowork is available at a cheaper price, though Anthropic notes "Pro users may hit their usage limits earlier" than Max users do.Like other AI agents, the novelty of Claude Cowork is its ability to work on its own. If y...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration wants tech companies to buy $15B of power plants they may not use</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/16/trump-administration-wants-tech-companies-to-buy-15b-of-power-plants-they-may-not-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083434</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to alleviate rising electricity prices, the White House wants grid operator PJM to hold an auction for new generating capacity, and it wants tech companies to bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google brings its AI videomaker to Workspace users</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863570/google-flow-ai-video-generator-workspace</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T14:37:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863570</guid>
      <description>Google is expanding access to its AI videomaking tool. Launched last May, Flow was initially only available to Google AI Pro and AI Ultra subscribers, but now, those with Business, Enterprise, and Education Workspace plans can access it, too. Flow uses Google's AI video generation model Veo 3.1 to generate eight-second clips based on a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The era of AI hype is over - firms now want to see real returns</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-era-of-ai-hype-is-over-firms-now-want-to-see-real-returns</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sZ3WUncyMrmPg69naudCB7</guid>
      <description>Many businesses have already operationalized generative AI, and are looking at the future of agentic AI within their workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best n8n hosting</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/best-n8n-hosting</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HSrDbVFmbu2nbiseTibQMB</guid>
      <description>Want to self-host your AI-powered workflows on a VPS server to avoid n8n&#8217;s high per-usage costs? Here are the best services to pick from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic launches Claude Cowork, a version of its coding AI for regular people</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/anthropic-launches-claude-cowork-a-version-of-its-coding-ai-for-regular-people-193000849.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e96f209-4988-475c-9ec3-ef79a87a6915</guid>
      <description>If you follow Anthropic, you're probably familiar with Claude Code. Since the fall of 2024, the company has been training its AI models to use and navigate computers like a human would, and the coding agent has been the most practical expression of that work, giving developers a way to automate rote programming tasks. Starting today, Anthropic is giving regular people a way to take advantage of those capabilities, with the release of a new preview feature called Claude Cowork.The company is billing Cowork as "a simpler way for anyone &#8212; not just developers &#8212; to work with Claude." After you give...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM CEO Mary Barra says people aren&#8217;t plugging in their plug-in hybrids. That defeats their whole purpose</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476440/gm-ceo-mary-barra-says-people-arent-plugging-in-their-plug-in-hybrids-that-defeats-their-whole-purpose</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T19:29:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476440/gm-ceo-mary-barra-says-people-arent-plugging-in-their-plug-in-hybrids-that-defeats-their-whole-purpose</guid>
      <description>Plug-in hybrid vehicles might be even less fuel efficient than gas-only cars when owners don&#8217;t plug them in, and most owners apparently don&#8217;t.
If drivers want to switch away from a completely gas-powered car to something electric, they have a few options. Namely: battery electric vehicles, hybrids, or plug-in hybrids (PHEVs).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is bringing ads to ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-is-bringing-ads-to-chatgpt-192831449.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23288a39-c283-481a-a672-fd726808266e</guid>
      <description>OpenAI plans to start testing ads inside of ChatGPT "in the coming weeks." In a blog post published Friday, the company said adult users in the US of its free and Go tiers (more on the latter in a moment) would start seeing sponsored products and services appear below their conversations with its chatbot. "Ads will be clearly labeled and separated from the organic answer," OpenAI said, adding any sponsored spots would not influence the answers ChatGPT generates. "Answers are optimized based on what's most helpful to you."&#160;OpenAI says people won't see ads appear when they're talking to ChatGPT ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The two things AMD subtly revealed at CES that actually excite me</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/862861/amd-ces-2026-socketed-laptop-chips-strix-halo-price</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T14:25:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862861</guid>
      <description>As we predicted, the world's biggest consumer electronics show was a bit of a bust for gamers this year! CES 2026 brought us several neat gamepads, but barely any handhelds and no new desktop GPUs - not from Nvidia, not from Intel, and not from AMD. But if you dig deep, AMD said two things [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X is recovering after being down for most of the morning</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/x-is-recovering-after-being-down-for-most-of-the-morning-171843683.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">814237b9-63ca-4ae5-9c95-a454783a5e0b</guid>
      <description>X seems to be working again after struggling with an outage that took the service offline and made it slow to load for much of the morning. According to X&#8217;s developer platform page,  there is an ongoing incident related to streaming endpoints that&#8217;s caused increased errors. The incident started at 7:39AM PT, according to the page.That roughly coincides with a spike in reports at Down Detector. The issues seemed to be somewhat intermittent. At some points, X&#8217;s website loaded partially and only showed older posts. At other times, the app and website failed to load at all. As of 9:30AM PT, X&#8217;s Ex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mother of one of Elon Musk's children is suing xAI over nonconsensual deepfake images</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/the-mother-of-one-of-elon-musks-children-is-suing-xai-over-nonconsensual-deepfake-images-191451979.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6abfc3d7-f6bd-4d1e-85f9-358b68a74ceb</guid>
      <description>Although X removed Grok&#8217;s ability to create nonconsensual digitally undressed images on the social platform, the standalone Grok app is another story. It reportedly continues to produce &#8220;nudified&#8221; deepfakes of real people. And now, Ashley St. Clair, a conservative political strategist and mother of one of Elon Musk&#8217;s 14 children, has sued xAI for nonconsensual sexualized images of her that Grok allegedly produced.In the court filing, St. Clair accused xAI&#8217;s Grok chatbot of creating and disseminating deepfakes of her &#8220;as a child stripped down to a string bikini, and as an adult in sexually expl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover 2000-Year-Old Mummified Cheetah in an Unexpected Place</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-discover-2000-year-old-mummified-cheetah-in-an-unexpected-place-2000711079</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711079</guid>
      <description>The discovery marks the first time scientists have found mummified big cats in the Arabian Peninsula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's cut the nonsense: I've assessed and rated all the biggest iPhone 18 rumors so far</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/lets-cut-the-nonsense-ive-assessed-and-rated-all-the-biggest-iphone-18-rumors-so-far</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rZ5Ffra3nywX5cYDbscmLM</guid>
      <description>There are already loads of rumors about the iPhone 18 series, but some sound a lot more likely than others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Will Keep Warner Bros. Movies in Theaters for 45 Days</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/netflix-will-keep-warner-bros-movies-in-theaters-for-45-days-2000711122</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711122</guid>
      <description>Co-CEO Ted Sarandos committed to the theatrical window after looking at how much money could be made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia&#8217;s social media ban for children has already wiped out 4.7 million accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476324/australia-social-media-ban-children-wipes-out-accounts</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476324/australia-social-media-ban-children-wipes-out-accounts</guid>
      <description>Past estimates suggested 84% of 8- to 12-year-olds in Australia held social media accounts. 
Social media companies have revoked access to about 4.7 million accounts identified as belonging to children in Australia since&#160;the country banned use of the platforms&#160;by those under 16, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI healthcare gold rush is here</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/the-ai-healthcare-gold-rush-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3083413</guid>
      <description>AI companies are clustering around healthcare and fast.&#160; In just the past week, OpenAI&#160;bought health startup Torch, Anthropic launched&#160;Claude for healthcare, and Sam Altman-backed&#160;MergeLabs closed a $250 million seed round&#160;at an $850 million valuation. The money and products are pouring into health&#160;and voice AI, but so are concerns about hallucination risks, inaccurate medical information, and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman Is Tearing Apart His Former Colleague&#8217;s Startup</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altman-is-tearing-apart-his-former-colleagues-startup-2000711135</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711135</guid>
      <description>OpenAI just rehired former employees who previously left the company to work at Thinking Machines Lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego's latest educational kit seeks to teach AI as part of computer science, not to build a chatbot</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/legos-latest-educational-kit-seeks-to-teach-ai-as-part-of-computer-science-not-to-build-a-chatbot-184636741.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55b2488e-c460-4d49-99ec-60dfa20ede3f</guid>
      <description>Last week at CES, Lego introduced its new Smart Play system, with a tech-packed Smart Brick that can recognize and interact with sets and minifigures. It was unexpected and delightful to see Lego come up with a way to modernize its bricks without the need for apps, screens or AI.&#160;So I was a little surprised this week when the Lego Education group announced its latest initiative is the Computer Science and AI Learning Solution. After all, generative AI feels like the antithesis of Lego&#8217;s creative values. But Andrew Silwinski, Lego Education&#8217;s head of product experience, was quick to defend Lego...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frigidaire recall: 964,000 mini-fridges sold at Target pose a serious risk</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476527/frigidaire-recall-964000-minifridges-sold-at-target-pose-serious-risk</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476527/frigidaire-recall-964000-minifridges-sold-at-target-pose-serious-risk</guid>
      <description>Canada-based Curtis International is adding another 330,000 products to the unsafe list after reports that refrigerators caught fire. Here&#8217;s what to know.
Almost 1 million Frigidaire mini-fridges are being recalled because they pose the potential to catch fire, according to a notice&#160;from the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC) released on Thursday.&#160;The notice expands an earlier recall from 2024....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon-owned Visible is offering outage credits, too</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863554/visible-verizon-outage-credit-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T13:41:51-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863554</guid>
      <description>Customers of Visible Wireless, which is owned by Verizon, may be getting a $5 credit toward their next bill in response to a Verizon cell service outage earlier this week. Verizon customers were offered a $20 credit after the outage. As spotted by 9to5Google, a message sent to Visible customers explains: "Yesterday we let you [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about the botched launch of Eric Adams&#8217; new crypto token</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476321/what-to-know-about-the-botched-launch-of-eric-adams-new-crypto-token</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:32:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476321/what-to-know-about-the-botched-launch-of-eric-adams-new-crypto-token</guid>
      <description>Despite claims of transparency, Adams has so far declined to reveal his partners in the token.
For a moment, Eric Adams was riding high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructors at this boutique yoga studio may go on strike</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91471697/instructors-at-this-boutique-yoga-studio-may-go-on-strike</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91471697/instructors-at-this-boutique-yoga-studio-may-go-on-strike</guid>
      <description>Social media suggests that some yoga teachers at buzzy, trendy gyms make small wages after having paid large sums for training.
Rumors are circulating of potential strike action next month from CorePower Yoga instructors, who say they are paid less per hour than the cost of a single class drop-in fee.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is facing increasing demands to do more for Iranian protestors</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476162/apple-is-facing-increasing-demands-to-do-more-for-iranian-protestors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-16T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476162/apple-is-facing-increasing-demands-to-do-more-for-iranian-protestors</guid>
      <description>As Starlink becomes a lifeline to Iranian protestors, some are calling on Apple to expand access to satellite-based texting.
As protests in Iran intensify, satellite technology has become one of the only ways for people in the country to circumvent a total internet blackout and heavy restrictions on phone service. Now, as a number of people in the country turn to SpaceX&#8212;the company now providing free access to Starlink&#8212;there are growing calls for Apple to get involved, too....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel your inner Leon S Kennedy with this slick limited edition Resident Evil Requiem watch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/channel-your-inner-leon-s-kennedy-with-this-slick-limited-edition-resident-evil-requiem-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saXNZLieLyiL3VzMz7fAMn</guid>
      <description>$2,000+ might be a lot for a limited edition watch, but this Resi timepiece is pure quality with some great detail.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
