<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:46:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Un v&#233;ritable v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique SUV : on a test&#233; le Diamant Suvea Style, un VTC boost&#233; par Bosch et ultra bien &#233;quip&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2959555_un-veritable-velo-electrique-suv-on-a-teste-le-diamant-suvea-style-un-vtc-booste-par-bosch-et-ultra-bien-equipe</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/velo-electrique/2959555_un-veritable-velo-electrique-suv-on-a-teste-le-diamant-suvea-style-un-vtc-booste-par-bosch-et-ultra-bien-equipe</guid>
      <description>
S&#8217;il confirme un superbe agr&#233;ment de conduite et de belles performances lors de notre essai, le Diamant Suvea Style est un VTC &#233;lectrique tr&#232;s cher qui fait payer le GPS ou encore son astucieuse barre sup&#233;rieure amovible. Nous l'avons test&#233;, voici notre avis. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Florida Man&#8217;s Home&#8217; Is the Most Florida Thing Imaginable, and It Might Be Coming to Airbnb</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/florida-mans-home-is-the-most-florida-thing-imaginable-and-it-might-be-coming-to-airbnb-2000716056</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716056</guid>
      <description>Does YOUR house have a tribute to 'Jaws' out back?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT isn&#8217;t the only chatbot pulling answers from Elon Musk&#8217;s Grokipedia</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/870910/ai-chatbots-citing-grokipedia</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-31T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=870910</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is using Grokipedia as a source, and it's not the only AI tool to do so. Citations to Elon Musk's AI-generated encyclopedia are starting to appear in answers from Google's AI Overviews, AI Mode, and Gemini, too. Data suggests that's on the rise, heightening concerns about accuracy and misinformation as Musk seeks to reshape [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A nice upgrade for Apple&#8217;s simplest gadget</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/871493/apple-airtags-yahoo-scout-wonder-man-installer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-31T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=871493</guid>
      <description>Hi, friends! Welcome to Installer No. 114, your guide to the best and Verge-iest stuff in the world. (If you're new here, welcome, send Arc Raiders tips, and also you can read all the old editions at the Installer homepage.) This week, I've been reading about wind turbines and phishing scams and oboes, keeping organized [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does wireless charging kill your phone&#8217;s battery? Scientists explain the pros and cons of going cable-free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/does-wireless-charging-kill-your-phones-battery-scientists-explain-the-pros-and-cons-of-going-cable-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q4e8vFAespVcwDXTNfndVC</guid>
      <description>Wireless charging feels effortless, but some users worry it could damage their phone's battery. Experts explain how it works and if there&#8217;s any truth to the myth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeds vs Arsenal Free Streams: How to watch Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/leeds-vs-arsenal-premier-league-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">whqzWrZPGncL6AoGR5FBD5</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Leeds vs Arsenal live streams online and from anywhere, as the Gunners look to tighten their grip on top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to turn on hypertension alerts on Apple Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/how-to-turn-on-hypertension-alerts-on-apple-watch-130000090.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afa7ba47-4e1b-4d04-a7df-0958bca1d837</guid>
      <description>Apple has steadily expanded the Apple Watch&#8217;s health monitoring features over the years, moving beyond fitness tracking into areas that can offer early insight into potential medical concerns. One of the most recent additions is hypertension alerts, which are designed to notify users when their blood pressure trends are elevated over time. While Apple Watches cannot directly measure blood pressure, this feature can still play a useful role in highlighting patterns that may be worth discussing with your doctor. Here, we&#8217;ll explain what hypertension alerts do, how they work and how to enable and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cordless Stick Vacuum Throw Down: Bosch, Shark, Dyson (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/cordless-stick-vacuum-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a67853b7691dd83eb4526</guid>
      <description>Bosch&#8217;s Unlimited 10 combines key features from Dyson&#8217;s and Shark&#8217;s stick vacuums and packs some nice extras, but it can&#8217;t seem to keep debris inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 top tech items I'd buy to host the best Super Bowl party &#8212; TVs, soundbars, appliances, drinks dispensers, speakers, games, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/12-top-tech-items-id-buy-to-host-the-best-super-bowl-party-tvs-soundbars-appliances-drinks-dispensers-speakers-games-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3vhUec2Mi4FvzdUxsJdKYf</guid>
      <description>My guide to a selection of the top tech items worth buying if you're planning to host a Super Bowl party this year, including TVs, appliances, soundbars, games, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moins de 50 &#8364; en poche pour la fin des soldes ? Voici les 8 meilleurs deals sans se ruiner</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2961897_moins-de-50-e-en-poche-pour-la-fin-des-soldes-voici-les-8-meilleurs-deals-sans-se-ruiner</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2961897_moins-de-50-e-en-poche-pour-la-fin-des-soldes-voici-les-8-meilleurs-deals-sans-se-ruiner</guid>
      <description>
&#192; l&#8217;approche de la fin des soldes, les petits budgets ont encore la possibilit&#233; de se faire plaisir. Montres, &#233;couteurs sans fil, accessoires pour smartphone, ou encore objets connect&#233;s : nous avons r&#233;uni une s&#233;lection de bons plans Tech &#224; moins de 50 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Mirrorless Cameras (2026): Full-Frame, APS-C, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-mirrorless-cameras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">601ad3fbe39c63178eb2ffd3</guid>
      <description>Want the image quality of a DSLR without the bulk? These WIRED picks do more with less.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 24 Best Movies on Amazon Prime, WIRED's Picks (February 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-amazon-prime-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63c08a9ba218e1847e6e327b</guid>
      <description>Sinners, Wicked, and Die Hard are just a few of the movies you should be watching on Amazon Prime Video this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC 325 live stream: how to watch Volkanovski vs Lopes 2, start time, preview, full card</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/ufc-325-volkanovski-vs-lopes-2</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">htEMjpAPVNficyMAF8GK3J</guid>
      <description>Featherweight Championship bout headlines packed card Down Under &#8211; follow our guide to live stream UFC 325 online and watch Volkanovski vs Lopes 2 from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 new 4K Blu-rays from January 2026 to add to your collection</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/6-new-4k-blu-rays-from-january-2026-to-add-to-your-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">X9CDBAMnTfT8kE36MFczHZ</guid>
      <description>January 2026 has been a booming month for 4K Blu-ray, and we're looking at 6 new discs that you could add to your collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highguard, a hyperpop arena shooter and other new indie games worth checking out</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/highguard-a-hyperpop-arena-shooter-and-other-new-indie-games-worth-checking-out-120000874.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">462b5557-20ab-4878-be7c-f25feceae428</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our latest roundup of what's going on in the indie game space. There are tons of interesting games out this week. But first, there's been some discourse around the Nintendo Switch version of Dispatch, which arrived this week as well.On other platforms, there's an option to censor genitalia and other explicit content, but that's not present in the Switch version. Instead, such content is censored by default, with black rectangles covering up characters' bits and someone flipping the bird. Noises that suggest sexual pleasure are said to be toned down too."We worked with Nintendo to en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Tennessee proposal to ban sports betting on campus is too little, too late</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91483524/tennessee-ban-online-sports-betting-college-campuses</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-31T12:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91483524/tennessee-ban-online-sports-betting-college-campuses</guid>
      <description>States spent years rolling out the red carpet for online sportsbooks. Now lawmakers are attempting to cordon off an industry designed to be everywhere.
In the months after a 2018 Supreme Court decision opened the door for states to legalize sports betting within their borders, giddy lawmakers across the country couldn&#8217;t move quickly enough. No one wanted to miss out on the billions of dollars in tax revenue that the high court had suddenly placed within their reach&#8212;or, worse yet, to watch that easy money go to neighboring states whose leaders had the presence of mind to move first. Within a mo...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
