<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:29:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#8217;s GeForce Now is getting native Linux and Fire TV apps</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854688/nvidias-geforce-now-is-getting-native-linux-and-fire-tv-apps</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T00:22:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854688</guid>
      <description>Nvidia's RTX 5080 rollout for its GeForce Now cloud gaming service is now complete, so it's ready to announce some additional features for subscribers. In the coming months, Nvidia is planning to launch native GeForce Now apps for Linux and Amazon's Fire TV devices, alongside flight control support for its cloud gaming service. The native [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&#8217;s new G-Sync monitors automatically adjust brightness just like a laptop</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854662/nvidia-g-sync-pulsar-monitors-abmient-adaptive-technology-auto-brightness</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T00:12:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854662</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is bringing a new set of G-Sync Pulsar monitors to the market this week that will automatically adjust brightness and color based on the ambient lighting in a room. Much like a modern laptop, these new monitors have a built-in light sensor that measures the brightness and color temperature of an environment to enable [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia announces DLSS 4.5 with 6x Frame Generation and improved image quality</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854610/nvidia-dlss-4-5-announcement-multi-frame-generation-6x-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T00:04:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854610</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is announcing its next major update to its Deep Learning Super Sampling (DLSS) feature at CES today. DLSS 4.5 includes Nvidia's second-generation Super Resolution transformer model and a new 6x Multi Frame Generation mode for RTX 50-series GPUs that uses AI to generate up to five additional frames for every single rendered one. DLSS [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini le casse-t&#234;te des c&#226;bles : Ecovacs simplifie l&#8217;entretien des vitres avec le Winbot W3 Omni</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ecovacs/2929051_fini-le-casse-tete-des-cables-ecovacs-simplifie-lentretien-des-vitres-avec-le-winbot-w3-omni</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ecovacs/2929051_fini-le-casse-tete-des-cables-ecovacs-simplifie-lentretien-des-vitres-avec-le-winbot-w3-omni</guid>
      <description>
Parmi ses nombreuses annonces au CES 2026, Ecovacs a d&#233;voil&#233; la nouvelle g&#233;n&#233;ration de son robot laveur de vitres. Le Winbot W3 Omni se dote pour l'occasion d'une adh&#233;rence renforc&#233;e et d'un syst&#232;me de pulv&#233;risation plus large pour s'attaquer &#224; des vitres toujours plus complexes. On retrouve &#233;galement un nouveau syst&#232;me de propulsion antipatinage, et, surtout, l'arriv&#233;e d'un c&#226;ble 2-en-1 unique combinant alimentation et s&#233;curit&#233;.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerson&#8217;s SmartVoice devices follow verbal instructions without Wi-Fi or a hub</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/850919/smart-appliance-emerson-smartvoice-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T00:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850919</guid>
      <description>A new line of small appliances and devices from IAI Smart, billed as Emerson Smart products, are now available that will let you operate fans, heaters, smart plugs, and air fryers with your voice - with no apps, Wi-Fi, or smart home connection at all. Using the company's SmartVoice technology, the devices react to wake-up [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecovacs mise tout sur les rouleaux de lavage pour ses nouveaux robot aspirateurs laveur</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ecovacs/2928817_ecovacs-mise-tout-sur-les-rouleaux-de-lavage-pour-ses-nouveaux-robot-aspirateurs-laveur</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ecovacs/2928817_ecovacs-mise-tout-sur-les-rouleaux-de-lavage-pour-ses-nouveaux-robot-aspirateurs-laveur</guid>
      <description>
En marge du CES 2026, Ecovacs a lev&#233; le voile sur ses nouveaux fers de lance pour l'entretien de la maison. Avec les DEEBOT T90 PRO OMNI et la famille DEEBOT X12, le g&#233;ant chinois mise tout sur le rouleau laveur et la simplicit&#233; d'utilisation.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu le nouveau visage d&#8217;Alienware : fini les briques hors de prix, place &#224; la diversit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/pc-portables/2926251_jai-vu-le-nouveau-visage-dalienware-fini-les-briques-hors-de-prix-place-a-la-diversite</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/pc-portables/2926251_jai-vu-le-nouveau-visage-dalienware-fini-les-briques-hors-de-prix-place-a-la-diversite</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez toujours r&#234;v&#233; d'un Alienware sans devoir vendre un rein ? Votre v&#339;u est exauc&#233;. Dell profite du CES 2026 pour tuer sa distinction artificielle entre les &#171; gamers riches &#187; et les autres. La gamme G-Series dispara&#238;t pour laisser place &#224; de vrais Alienware d'entr&#233;e de gamme. Et rassurez-vous : pas question de vous refourguer des puces graphiques au rabais.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agibot's humanoid robots can give directions and learn your TikTok dances</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/agibots-humanoid-robots-can-give-directions-and-learn-your-tiktok-dances-045049798.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9007022-29ab-44c7-9868-b7c6533ab500</guid>
      <description>For better or worse, CES 2026 is already shaping up to be a big year for humanoid robots. Chinese company Agibot showed up with two: the roughly human-sized A2 and the slightly smaller X2, both of which were displaying their surprisingly impressive dancing abilities.&#160;We watched both robots walk around, wave at passersby and show off their best moves. The larger A2 mostly kept its legs still and danced mainly with its arms. The smaller X2 on the other hand is a bit more nimble &#8212; it has a larger set of "feet" to give it more stability &#8212; and those abilities were on full display.At the time we saw...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Handy 2 Pro is an 'overclockable' sex toy</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/the-handy-2-pro-is-an-overclockable-sex-toy-044456140.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c588cf9b-8dc8-4196-bef7-f7d499bc391e</guid>
      <description>The following article discusses adult themes.One surprising find at CES 2026 comes from OhDoki, the Norwegian makers of The Handy, a smart stroking device. It turned up to the desert with two new products, the Handy 2 and the Handy 2 Pro. Fundamentally, they&#8217;re the same device, but the Handy 2 Pro comes with a far bigger battery, taking the usable life from one hour on the standard model all the way to five. That extra power enables you to run the 2 Pro far faster and harder than the original once you set it into Turbo mode. In fact, I was told the hardware can essentially be &#8220;overclocked,&#8221; al...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony Honda Mobility&#8217;s Afeela Prototype 2026 puts an SUV spin on its too-familiar sedan at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/sony-honda-mobilitys-afeela-prototype-2026-puts-an-suv-spin-on-its-too-familiar-sedan-at-ces-043927882.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de1f5d5b-792e-4156-888b-e8880b53efc1</guid>
      <description>Last year in Las Vegas at CES 2025, Sony Honda Mobility displayed yet another revision of its now-familiar yet still-unreleased Afeela 1 sedan. With a starting price of $89,900 and a maximum range of 300 miles, it didn't seem like a great value proposition. 12 months later, the math still hasn't changed, but would-be buyers now have a slightly taller option to consider.Meet the Afeela Prototype 2026, a version of the Afeela 1 sedan that's been up-scaled to better suit American SUV proclivities. It offers a carbon copy of the smaller Afeela's understated styling, including the external, nose-mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Garmin had the nerve to launch a food-tracking feature in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/garmin-food-tracking-feature-connect-plus-ces-2026-043231948.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8d55c66-4e69-42f4-a7af-b213555618ef</guid>
      <description>Garmin&#8217;s big announcement for CES 2026 wasn&#8217;t another fitness watch. Instead, it revealed it is adding food (and calorie) tracking to its Connect app. It combines AI image recognition with a rich food database, so you can monitor your calorie and nutrient intake without leaving the app &#8212; and even log some food through its watches.
The food tracking works similarly to existing apps like MyFitnessPal, Noom, LifeSum and many others. Still, Garmin hopes to make its companion app the best place for tracking nutrition without having to leave its app &#8211; and tying it into your other fitness goals.
This...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missed out on Boxing Day sales? Don't stress, these 5 deals are still going strong</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/missed-the-boxing-day-sales-dont-stress-i-found-5-deals-still-going-strong</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3WM6RQ79qxxRKqfviUGJ7e</guid>
      <description>Score savings of up to AU$900 on robot vacuums, fitness trackers, ANC headphones and even a dirt-cheap mouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another look at OhSnap's MCON, a magnetic game controller for your phone</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/another-look-at-ohsnaps-mcon-a-magnetic-game-controller-for-your-phone-042424092.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a8b5dab-5609-411b-b8bb-822aff51eca5</guid>
      <description>OhSnap won our hearts (and a best of CES award) last year with the MCON, its tiny Bluetooth game pad that magnetically connects to your phone. At the time, we tried a pre-production unit, but in the year since the MCON has been finalized and went on sale last month. I just got a chance to try the final version here at CES, and just a quick demo was enough to convince me that OhSnap has made some solid refinements over the last year.Just as we saw last year, the MCON attaches magnetically to an iPhone or any compatible Android phone (the company also includes a magnetic ring in the box for Andr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffuser quatre sources simultan&#233;ment, voici pourquoi ces enceintes Bluetooth Fender Audio sont si sp&#233;ciales</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/2930025_diffuser-quatre-sources-simultanement-voici-pourquoi-ces-enceintes-bluetooth-fender-audio-sont-si-speciales</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/2930025_diffuser-quatre-sources-simultanement-voici-pourquoi-ces-enceintes-bluetooth-fender-audio-sont-si-speciales</guid>
      <description>
Au CES 2026, le fabricant de guitares Fender d&#233;voile sa gamme ELIE, des enceintes portables dot&#233;es d'une fonction in&#233;dite permettant de g&#233;rer quatre canaux audio en m&#234;me temps. Mais en a-t-on vraiment besoin&#160;?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cozyla showed off a 4K, 55-inch digital family calendar at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/cozyla-showed-off-a-4k-55-inch-digital-family-calendar-at-ces-040352802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0590e961-5cd0-4177-964e-95f4760e4597</guid>
      <description>New tech at CES often makes categorization hard. Is Cozyla&#8217;s latest device a digital family calendar, a TV or a smart home hub? After seeing it, I&#8217;d say the answer is, yes? Cozyla calls the Calendar + Max the &#8220;largest interactive hub in it&#8217;s category.&#8221; And indeed, it&#8217;s the size of a big flatscreen, but the main interface is just like any other Cozyla device, an Android-based family calendar and planner with shared schedules, notes, meal plans, and chores. It syncs with Google, Yahoo and Apple calendars as well as Outlook, and it will run apps from the Google Play store. (Yahoo owns Engadget, b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGIMI, best known for projectors, launches its own smart glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/xgimi-best-known-for-projectors-launches-its-own-smart-glasses-170000968.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54390b93-e1df-4254-8d11-df10a104845a</guid>
      <description>Projector maker XGIMI has turned up at CES to launch its own range of AR glasses, but don&#8217;t get the champagne out too soon. MemoMind is a new brand under which its AI-infused eyewear will be sold, with two distinct units arriving at some point in the near future. The company says it has leveraged its know-how in optics and engineering to produce glasses which are unobtrusively light, all the better for blending into your daily life. Fashionistas will even be overjoyed to learn the glasses&#8217; ship in eight different frame styles, five different temple designs and can be worn with prescription len...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai and Boston Dynamics May Have Just Stolen the Robot Factory Narrative Away from Tesla</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hyundai-and-boston-dynamics-may-have-just-stolen-the-robot-factory-narrative-away-from-tesla-2000705841</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705841</guid>
      <description>The key question isn't who you should root for. It's whose story do you find more plausible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD&#8217;s Latest Chips Are Betting Big on Gamers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amds-latest-chips-are-betting-big-on-gamers-2000705030</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705030</guid>
      <description>You&#8217;re going to be far more interested in AMD&#8217;s Ryzen Max than the Ryzen 400 series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware Upgrades Its Best Gaming Laptop So It Looks as Good as It Feels</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alienware-upgrades-its-best-gaming-laptop-so-it-looks-as-good-as-it-feels-2000703974</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703974</guid>
      <description>Also, for the first time in a long time, Alienware is finally making an 'ultra-slim' gaming laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware is working on new slim and cheaper gaming laptops</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851926/alienware-is-working-on-new-slim-and-cheaper-gaming-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851926</guid>
      <description>Dell-owned Alienware is looking to reach a wider swath of gamers, announcing at CES 2026 that it's working on two new laptops: one with a lower, entry-level price and one with an ultra-slim chassis. There aren't many details right now, as Alienware is only sharing some basic renders, and the behind-glass nonworking prototypes I saw [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP crammed an entire desktop computer into this keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/851965/hp-crammed-an-entire-desktop-computer-into-this-keyboard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851965</guid>
      <description>HP is announcing a new mini desktop computer at CES 2026, and the whole thing is housed in a compact keyboard. The Eliteboard G1a looks like a normal office keyboard with either a captive or detachable USB-C cable, but inside it is an AMD Ryzen AI 300-series chip, stereo speakers, RAM, storage, a fan, and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD&#8217;s new Ryzen 7 9850X3D makes the best gaming CPU even faster</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855188/amd-ryzen-7-9850x3d-processor-boost-clock-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855188</guid>
      <description>AMD is introducing an improved version of its popular Ryzen 7 9800X3D processor today at CES. The new Ryzen 7 9850X3D offers up the same 8-core / 16-thread CPU as the 9800X3D, running at even faster boost clocks. "We've fine-tuned our best gaming processor in the world and have increased the boost clocks to 5.6GHz," [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD Ryzen AI 400 official: Will these laptop chips maintain AMD&#8217;s lead?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855343/amd-ryzen-ai-400-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855343</guid>
      <description>We were rightly skeptical of AMD's Ryzen AI 300 "Strix Point" laptop chips in 2024. Now they're in some of the very best laptops you can buy, arguably hitting the sweet spot of price, performance, and battery life. Today at CES, AMD is announcing its successor, the Ryzen AI 400 line - but there's nothing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD heard you like powerful gaming portables &#8212; so here are new Strix Halo chips</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855463/amd-strix-halo-ai-max-plus-388-392-handheld-gaming</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T22:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855463</guid>
      <description>AMD's Strix Halo, aka "Ryzen AI Max," is a hugely expensive chip that includes some of the most powerful integrated graphics ever made. Though AMD initially marketed it more to AI workloads with its tremendous complement of up to 128GB of RAM, it's also inspired some unprecedented gaming designs - by far the most powerful [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD unveils new AI PC processors for general use and gaming at CES</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/amd-unveils-new-ai-pc-processors-for-general-use-and-gaming-at-ces/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080003</guid>
      <description>AMD announced the latest version of its AI-powered PC chips designed for a variety of tasks from gaming to content creation and multitasking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AMD Ryzen 7 9850X3D is only one of the chips Team Red announced at CES 2026&#8212;and the others might have Intel sweating</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/cpu/the-amd-ryzen-7-9850x3d-is-only-one-of-the-chips-team-red-announced-at-ces-2026-and-the-others-might-have-intel-sweating</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nPSVu9S6d3gdEYc8Nb2unB</guid>
      <description>AMD's next-gen gaming CPU looks powerful, but it might play second fiddle to the new round of Ryzen AI 400 chips in the long run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware teases 'covert' ultraslim gaming laptop line and a new budget-friendly option at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/alienware-teases-covert-ultraslim-gaming-laptop-line-and-a-new-budget-friendly-option-at-ces-2026-as-well-as-finally-offering-oled-on-its-area-51-models</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9F9kN7TzwprE94BWnLcEGJ</guid>
      <description>Alienware announced that it will be expanding its gaming laptop portfolio in 2026 with two new classes of product: an ultraslim 'covert' gaming laptop line, and a budget-oriented gaming laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware teases new super-slim and entry-level gaming laptops at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/alienware-teases-new-super-slim-and-entry-level-gaming-laptops-at-ces-2026-033000700.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413691de-1598-496f-a1c5-a36248195545</guid>
      <description>After relaunching its Area-51 brand with a new 16-inch laptop in 2025, Alienware is teasing two new laptops at CES 2026 in an attempt to reach an even larger audience. Dell's gaming brand plans to launch both entry-level and ultra-slim models later this year, and in the meantime, it's rolling out updates to its existing desktops and laptops to tide people over.Alienware isn't sharing all the details of its new laptops at CES, but we do have the highlights. The company's new "ultra-slim gaming laptop" will be around 17mm or 0.67 inches thin, and come in either 14-inch or 16-inch variants. While...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD's new Ryzen AI Max+ chips and Ryzen 7 9850X3D court desktop enthusiasts at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/amds-new-ryzen-ai-max-chips-and-ryzen-7-9850x3d-court-desktop-enthusiasts-at-ces-2026-033000587.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d93068a-302c-4cdc-8baa-6b213949a2e2</guid>
      <description>While it's nice to see desktop support in AMD's new Ryzen AI 400 chips, demanding gamers and enthusiasts will likely be more intrigued by the company's next batch of Ryzen AI Max+ chips, as well as the new Ryzen 7 9850X3D with 3D V-Cache. The former will make its way into small desktops and a handful of workhorse laptops, while the latter is another option for gamers who want the speed bump of 3D V-cache without shelling out for the $700 9950X3D.&#160; Last year, AMD debuted its Ryzen AI Max chips as a way to create a single piece of silicon with powerful CPU cores, GPU cores, NPUs and integrated m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD's Ryzen AI 400 chips are a big boost for laptops and desktops alike</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/amds-ryzen-ai-400-chips-are-a-big-boost-for-laptops-and-desktops-alike-033000635.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86a4c064-11c6-492e-8b50-df778285f612</guid>
      <description>The whole AI PC trend didn't exactly set the world on fire last year, but, like clockwork, AMD is still ready to deliver a new batch of AI chips at CES 2026. The Ryzen AI 400 processors will offer some slight speed upgrades over last year's chips, and notably, they also include AMD's first Copilot+ processors for desktops. Sure, the Copilot+ program didn't really go anywhere, but as I've argued, it at least served as a template for building capable AI PCs. Now we just need some genuinely useful AI features in Windows &#8212; Recall and Copilot's voice commands aren't really compelling enough on thei...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP's EliteBoard made me believe in keyboard computers again</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/hps-eliteboard-made-me-believe-in-keyboard-computers-again-033000955.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a465857-65de-4340-b8bf-15ecdc4b74e1</guid>
      <description>For as long as I can remember, I've always wanted to have a keyboard computer -- that is, a computer where the entire machine was stuffed inside of a keyboard. Maybe I caught a glimpse of the Commodore 64 at an impressionable age, but for whatever reason, the idea has always intrigued me. Now HP is bringing the concept back with its new EliteBoard G1a "Next Gen AI PC." It's an IT administrator's dream: It looks a typical desktop keyboard, but it has the full power of a Copilot+ AI PC inside. You can equip it with Ryzen 5 or 7 CPUs and their embedded Radeon 800 GPUs, up to 64GB of RAM and as mu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD officialise le Ryzen 7 9850X3D : ce qui change vraiment sur ce nouveau processeur de jeu</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2929153_amd-officialise-le-ryzen-7-9850x3d-ce-qui-change-vraiment-sur-ce-nouveau-processeur-de-jeu</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2929153_amd-officialise-le-ryzen-7-9850x3d-ce-qui-change-vraiment-sur-ce-nouveau-processeur-de-jeu</guid>
      <description>
Le Ryzen 7 9850X3D est officiel, mais le nouveau processeur de bureau d'AMD n'apporte finalement que tr&#232;s peu de choses par rapport au 9800X3D.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryzen AI 400 : tout savoir sur les nouvelles puces AMD qui vont booster vos prochains PC portables</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2928843_ryzen-ai-400-tout-savoir-sur-les-nouvelles-puces-amd-qui-vont-booster-vos-prochains-pc-portables</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amd/2928843_ryzen-ai-400-tout-savoir-sur-les-nouvelles-puces-amd-qui-vont-booster-vos-prochains-pc-portables</guid>
      <description>
AMD d&#233;voile au CES une nouvelle gamme de processeurs pour PC portables avec les puces Ryzen AI 400. Une &#233;volution &#224; petits pas de l'architecture actuelle avant l'arriv&#233;e de Zen 6.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
