<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:25:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT launches an app store, lets developers know it&#8217;s open for business</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/chatgpt-launches-an-app-store-lets-developers-know-its-open-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077506</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is looking to populate its flagship chatbot with a host of new user experiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Signs Executive Order Loosening Federal Cannabis Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trump-signs-executive-order-loosening-federal-cannabis-restrictions-2000701438</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701438</guid>
      <description>The order won't legalize cannabis at the federal level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto chip shortage: Honda will pause production in Japan and China</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/auto-chip-shortage-honda-will-pause-production-in-japan-and-china-200857591.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">965d4db1-6e2c-40e4-80bc-b331d9f5112c</guid>
      <description>The ripples of the auto industry's chip shortage are still being felt, as evidenced by Honda. Bloomberg reported on Wednesday that the automaker will suspend production in Japan on January 5 and 6. (Honda didn't specify the affected factories.) In addition, all three of the automaker's Guangqi Honda Automobile plants in China will shut down from December 29 to January 2.The halt is an outgrowth of a chip shortage stemming from a recent geopolitical proxy war in the Netherlands, of all places. In October, the Dutch government, bowing to pressure from the Trump administration, seized control of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickle Robot adds Tesla veteran as&#160;first&#160;CFO</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/pickle-robot-adds-tesla-veteran-as-first-cfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077498</guid>
      <description>Jeff Evanson recently joined Pickle Robot as the company's first CFO as the startup has allegedly expanded its partnership with UPS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Verge&#8217;s favorite holiday gifts under $100</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/800440/best-gifts-under-100-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=800440</guid>
      <description>Between all the new phones, smartwatches, and laptops we see throughout the year, it often feels like we're constantly being nudged toward shinier, more expensive gadgets. And I get it. As a self-professed gadget nerd, few things are more exciting than unboxing and setting up a new device. But the truth is, you can still [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why British politicians are flocking to American tech giants</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/why-british-politicians-are-flocking-to-american-tech-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077473</guid>
      <description>Former British Chancellor of the Exchequer George Osborne has joined OpenAI as managing director and head of OpenAI for Countries. He also will run Coinbase's internal advisory council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&#8217;s mobile app hits new milestone of $3B in consumer spending</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/chatgpts-mobile-app-hits-new-milestone-of-3b-in-consumer-spending/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077496</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT has reached $3B in lifetime mobile consumer spending in just 31 months, faster than TikTok and major streaming apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New &#8216;Odyssey&#8217; Poster Throws a Bone to All Those Armor Complaints</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-odyssey-poster-christopher-nolan-greek-armor-2000701416</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701416</guid>
      <description>And we mean that literally. Christopher Nolan directs the 2026 epic starring Matt Damon and Tom Holland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProPublica&#8217;s New Tool Provides Drug Info the FDA Won&#8217;t</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/propublicas-new-tool-provides-drug-info-the-fda-wont-2000701357</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701357</guid>
      <description>The first-of-its-kind app to help you find out where your generic drugs come from and see the track records of the factories that made them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Miss This Kindle Sale: Paperwhite, Colorsoft, and Accessories</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/last-minute-christmas-kindle-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6943426eb265e31526036e35</guid>
      <description>If your favorite reader is the one left on your Christmas list, good news: Several Kindles and Kindle accessories are on sale right now for your last-minute shopping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Displace Hub can make your normal TV wireless</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/the-displace-hub-can-make-your-normal-tv-wireless-193837460.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e068ce1-8e69-439b-9f53-8dcfb91c3471</guid>
      <description>Displace first tried its hand at reimagining the TV in 2023, with a wireless screen that suctions onto walls and features built-in rechargeable batteries. At CES 2026, the company is not only introducing new versions of its own TVs, it's also showing off the Displace Hub, an accessory that can make other TVs wireless.The Displace Hub is a wall-mounting system with some extra bells and whistles. It combines the "active-loop suction" of Displace&#8217;s TVs, with a rechargeable battery that can power whatever screen you mount on it and a built-in PC that runs Displace's "ambient computing platform." T...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anyone for a slice of record Pi? New landmark sees 314 trillion digits calculated as news site trounces Google Cloud - for now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/anyone-for-a-slice-of-record-pi-new-landmark-sees-314-trillion-digits-calculated-as-news-site-trounces-google-cloud-for-now</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">E4mQ7g4w4WhGHGavV2dce5</guid>
      <description>StorageReview computed 314 trillion digits of pi on one server, finishing faster and using far less energy than cloud-based records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple is bringing even more ads to the App Store</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/apple-is-bringing-even-more-ads-to-the-app-store-193416921.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">709ba0fe-6b15-42d9-9b65-7663171f276e</guid>
      <description>Apple just announced it will be integrating more ads into the App Store because our poor eyeballs must be assaulted at all times. The company plans on littering search results with advertisements beginning next year.
Currently, the App Store only has one ad spot. That's at the very top of search results. If you search for something like Instagram it's likely that top spot will be filled with an ad for a rival social media platform. The new ads will appear further down the actual search results.
Apple says that advertisers won't have to alter their campaigns, as the ads will "run in either the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Are U.S. Dams Holding Up? New Satellite Data Warns of Trouble</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-are-u-s-dams-holding-up-new-satellite-data-warns-of-trouble-2000701259</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701259</guid>
      <description>There's never been a giant dam failure in the US modern era, and a team of researchers is looking to keep it that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The age of next-gen RGB TVs is here &#8212; Samsung, LG, TCL and Hisense have all revealed models of the &#8216;OLED-beater&#8217; tech</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-age-of-next-gen-rgb-tvs-is-here-samsung-lg-tcl-and-hisense-have-all-revealed-models-of-the-oled-beater-tech</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2afbrjcPCkJyBSkU9c7Uwe</guid>
      <description>RGB LED TVs are the next big thing in home theater &#8211; and 'next' is coming very soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center will be renamed the Trump-Kennedy Center, White House says</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463026/kennedy-center-renamed-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T19:20:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463026/kennedy-center-renamed-trump</guid>
      <description>A name change won&#8217;t sit well with some Kennedy family members.
President Donald Trump&#8217;s&#160;handpicked board&#160;voted Thursday to rename Washington&#8217;s leading performing arts center as the Trump-Kennedy Center, the White House said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Mobile's T1 still doesn't exist, but the company is now selling refurbished phones</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/trump-mobiles-t1-still-doesnt-exist-but-the-company-is-now-selling-refurbished-phones-191740570.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1bee505-9a99-49cb-8933-595567fa579b</guid>
      <description>The T1 smartphone from Trump Mobile remains non-existent vaporware, but the company is still finding new ways to take people's money. Anyone who desperately wants to fund this sham can now buy a refurbished phone from the company. The business's website has listings for "Renewed" models of the Samsung S24 and S23 and the iPhone 15 and 14. Gizmodo noticed that Trump Mobile is selling these other brands' phones for the same cost, or sometimes more, than the same refurbs from other retailers.&#160;Seems pretty par for the course. NBC News opted to order one of the T1 phones in August to track its deve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Seeks Cyber Upgrade to Better Surveil and Investigate Its Employees</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-seeks-cyber-upgrade-to-better-surveil-and-investigate-its-employees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6944158f17f8230f56a84949</guid>
      <description>The agency plans to renew a sweeping cybersecurity contract that includes expanded employee monitoring as the government escalates leak investigations and casts internal dissent as a threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI vows to put teen safety first on ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/chatgpt-teen-safety-first-principles</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01Iw3xA7A6SVkRVn7vxFcS4</guid>
      <description>New update aims to provide a safe experience for teens between the ages of 13 and 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Image Shows 2 Protoplanets Smashing Into Each Other, Forming Giant Dust Cloud</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/unprecedented-image-shows-2-protoplanets-smashing-into-each-other-forming-giant-dust-cloud-2000701287</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701287</guid>
      <description>First it was an exoplanet. Then it became a dust cloud. Now it's bringing a cosmic revelation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising healthcare costs are testing small businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462725/rising-healthcare-costs-are-testing-small-businesses</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462725/rising-healthcare-costs-are-testing-small-businesses</guid>
      <description>As the backbone of the U.S. economy, these companies need more affordable healthcare options.
America&#8217;s small businesses are the backbone of our economy. They create two-thirds of new jobs, power innovation, and anchor communities across the country. But that backbone is under real strain. Rising healthcare costs dominate the headlines, but what&#8217;s missing from the conversation is how deeply they impact the small businesses that keep our economy running....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop waiting for perfect AI</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462888/stop-waiting-for-perfect-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462888/stop-waiting-for-perfect-ai</guid>
      <description>Builders aren&#8217;t waiting. They&#8217;re solving real problems with today&#8217;s imperfect AI. 
Experts have compressed their predictions for when artificial general intelligence (AGI)&#8212;the type of AI that can equal or exceed human intelligence&#8212;will arrive. When predictions were first made in 2023, AGI was expected to arrive in 50 years. Newer estimates say five years....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BP&#8217;s CEO shake-up signals the end of its green energy era</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462955/bps-ceo-shake-up-signals-the-end-of-its-green-energy-era</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462955/bps-ceo-shake-up-signals-the-end-of-its-green-energy-era</guid>
      <description>By appointing Woodside&#8217;s Meg O&#8217;Neill, BP is making clear that oil, gas, and LNG are back at the center of its strategy.
British oil giant BP just announced a new CEO, marking its fourth chief executive shake-up in the last six years alone.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term mortgage rate hits 6.22%, hovering near its low for the year</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462976/mortgage-rates-housing-financing-home</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462976/mortgage-rates-housing-financing-home</guid>
      <description>Economists generally forecast that the average rate on a 30-year mortgage will remain slightly above 6% next year.
The average rate on a 30-year U.S. mortgage edged higher this week, though it remains relatively near its low point so far this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 26.3 beta arrives: How to download it and 3 new features to try</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ios-26-3-beta-features-how-to-download</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06egynNGqK68rbhVH3Llxv6</guid>
      <description>The public beta for iOS 26.3 is here, bringing with it a few interesting new features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn&#8217;s profile verification push is accelerating &#8212; and India is leading the charge in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/18/linkedins-profile-verification-push-is-accelerating-and-india-is-leading-the-charge-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077445</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn profile verification adoption in India has risen about 80% in the past 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 great gift ideas that should arrive in time for Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/846378/best-last-minute-gifts-ideas-airpods-pro-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T13:42:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=846378</guid>
      <description>You don&#8217;t need to deal with long mall lines or crowded parking lots just to wrap up your holiday shopping, but you probably already knew this. Some of the best deals are online, and even though Christmas is now just a few days away, a lot of Verge-approved gifts should still arrive on time if [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation cooled in November, but data may be distorted</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462970/inflation-consumer-prices-november</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T18:40:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462970/inflation-consumer-prices-november</guid>
      <description>Thursday&#8217;s report gave investors, businesses, and policymakers their first look at CPI since the September numbers were released on Oct. 24.
At a time when Americans are frustrated and angry over the high cost of living, the government released a report Thursday showing that inflation had cooled unexpectedly in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Probe Instacart&#8217;s Al-Fueled Pricing Experiments on Groceries</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/feds-probe-instacarts-al-fueled-pricing-experiments-on-groceries-2000701379</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701379</guid>
      <description>The price is wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A massive new DDoS botnet has already snared 1.8 million devices - here's what we know about Kimwolf</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/a-massive-new-ddos-botnet-has-already-snared-1-8-million-devices-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CBcFwUGAxbxjPiYdt8BxqE</guid>
      <description>Researchers discovered a new botnet called Kimwolf, allegedly built by the same brain behind AISURU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was &#8216;The Force Awakens&#8217; the Savior of &#8216;Star Wars,&#8217; or a Sacrifice?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/was-the-force-awakens-the-savior-of-star-wars-or-a-sacrifice-2000699725</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699725</guid>
      <description>It's hard to separate 'The Force Awakens' from everything that happened in its wake.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
