<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:28:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Monday, January 19 (game #1456)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-19-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gbgUxciDrxUXjXk34GNQW3</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Monday, January 19 (game #953)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-19-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LZqpwBBwXqvzjTXcVTf6Pg</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Monday, January 19 (game #687)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-19-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">G2P5JqHUWuR297zubEtkri</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Revs Up a Speedy Gonzales Solo Movie</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/warner-bros-revs-up-a-speedy-gonzales-solo-movie-2000711426</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711426</guid>
      <description>'El Tigre' creator Jorge R. Guti&#233;rrez will give the popular 'Looney Tunes' character his time in the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Apple went in, Nvidia went in, a lot of smart people went in': Did Apple join Nvidia in investing in Intel? Trump seems to suggest so - or was it just a slip of the tongue?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/apple-went-in-nvidia-went-in-a-lot-of-smart-people-went-in-did-apple-join-nvidia-in-investing-in-intel-trump-seems-to-suggest-so-or-was-it-just-a-slip-of-the-tongue</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">knPt8HGoYCpxQjbSNwuoQJ</guid>
      <description>President Trump implies Apple may have joined Nvidia in investing in Intel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft issues emergency fix after a security update left some Windows 11 devices unable to shut down</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/microsoft-issues-emergency-fix-afer-a-security-update-left-some-windows-11-devices-unable-to-shut-down-192216734.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">298a8b9e-5869-47f4-bfb0-e7f160064f63</guid>
      <description>If you weren't able to shut down your Windows 11 device recently, Microsoft has rolled out an emergency fix addressing a couple of critical bugs that popped up with its latest January 2026 Windows security update. The latest "out-of-band" update repairs an issue for some Windows 11 devices that would only restart when users tried to shut down or hibernate. The same update restores the ability for Windows 10 and Windows 11 users to log into their devices via remote connection apps.
Microsoft said the inability to shut down or hibernate affected Windows 11 devices using Secure Launch, a security...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms &#8212; stream Game of Thrones prequel from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GLozMH7VryZoLUbQGJCSM5</guid>
      <description>Westeros returns with a smaller, character-driven tale. Here&#8217;s how you can watch A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms online and from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused work in a distracted world &#8212; my one secret weapon for staying on task</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/lola</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7p3wzraAwVoLfyrbZan2JR</guid>
      <description>Homescreen Heroes: Lola is a low-fidelity music solution to high-frequency distractions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop calling it 'The AI bubble': It's actually multiple bubbles, each with a different expiration date</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/infrastructure/stop-calling-it-the-ai-bubble-its-actually-multiple-bubbles-each-with-a</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5L3qWycOtIIPQZzNUek9oO</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s the question on everyone&#8217;s minds and lips: Are we in an AI bubble?It's the wrong question. The real question is: Which AI bubble are we in, and when will each one burst?The debate over whether AI represents a transformative technology or an economic time bomb has reached a fever pitch. Even tech leaders like Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg have acknowledged evidence of an unstable financial bubble forming around AI. OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates see clear bubble dynamics: overexcited investors, frothy valuations and plenty of doomed projects &#8212; but they still believe A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Fujifilm X-T30 III : un petit bo&#238;tier &#224; moins de 1000 &#8364; qui filme en 6K comme un grand</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fujifilm/2944897_test-du-fujifilm-x-t30-iii-un-petit-boitier-a-moins-de-1000-e-qui-filme-en-6k-comme-un-grand</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/fujifilm/2944897_test-du-fujifilm-x-t30-iii-un-petit-boitier-a-moins-de-1000-e-qui-filme-en-6k-comme-un-grand</guid>
      <description>
Le Fujifilm X-T30 III marque le retour d'une s&#233;rie qu'on croyait remplac&#233;e. Quatre ans apr&#232;s le X-T30 II et l'arriv&#233;e du X-T50 et son capteur de 40 MP, Fujifilm ressuscite sa ligne X-T30 avec un processeur X-Processor 5 et des capacit&#233;s vid&#233;o 6K. Un bo&#238;tier d'entr&#233;e de gamme qui tape au-dessus de sa cat&#233;gorie. Mais il y a des compromis.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face &#224; la crise, ce SSD NVMe M.2 4 To aux performances premium pour PC et PS5 est plus cher que d&#8217;habitude, mais &#231;a sera encore pire apr&#232;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944877_face-a-la-crise-ce-ssd-nvme-m-2-4-to-aux-performances-premium-pour-pc-et-ps5-est-plus-cher-que-dhabitude-mais-ca-sera-encore-pire-apres</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2944877_face-a-la-crise-ce-ssd-nvme-m-2-4-to-aux-performances-premium-pour-pc-et-ps5-est-plus-cher-que-dhabitude-mais-ca-sera-encore-pire-apres</guid>
      <description>
On le sait, c'est la crise de la m&#233;moire vive et du stockage : pour autant, Cdiscount propose le SSD WD_Black SN7100 4 To pour 399,99 euros au lieu de 799,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three months of Audible is on sale for $3 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/three-months-of-audible-is-on-sale-for-3-right-now-193859793.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d99938-0b9f-4c17-b1d6-b88b320bc1cc</guid>
      <description>Have a hankering for some audiobooks? Audible is holding one heck of a sale right now, giving users three months of access for $3. That's a dollar per month. This is something of a winter tradition for the Amazon-owned platform and the promotion ends on January 21.
An Audible subscription grants one audiobook per month to keep. This can be selected from a massive catalog of new releases and bestsellers. The collection here has just about everything. 


However, it's easy to plow through a single book in a month. Users also get streaming access to thousands of curated titles. Think of it like N...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
