<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:48:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 is tipped to get 2 smart camera upgrades &#8211; but the OnePlus 16 may show it up with an elite new telephoto sensor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/the-samsung-galaxy-s26-is-tipped-to-get-2-smart-camera-upgrades-but-the-oneplus-16-may-show-it-up-with-an-elite-new-telephoto-sensor</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KoWdNMYfchaGuKJmdePBSg</guid>
      <description>We have some fresh rumors around two of the most powerful smartphones expected to launch this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google's 'America-India Connect' is filling in the last gaps for a truly global subsea cable network</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/googles-america-india-connect-is-filling-in-the-last-gaps-for-a-truly-global-subsea-cable-network</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xHTozeuEnzkUaSnkyeXPcQ</guid>
      <description>Google&#8217;s America-India Connect strengthens subsea networks across continents and enables high-capacity AI infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a test&#233; ce casque v&#233;lo qui permet d&#8217;&#233;couter de la musique et de passer des appels : promesse tenue, mais des d&#233;fauts qui font t&#226;che</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tenways/2977097_on-a-teste-ce-casque-velo-qui-permet-decouter-de-la-musique-et-de-passer-des-appels-promesse-tenue-mais-des-defauts-qui-font-tache</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tenways/2977097_on-a-teste-ce-casque-velo-qui-permet-decouter-de-la-musique-et-de-passer-des-appels-promesse-tenue-mais-des-defauts-qui-font-tache</guid>
      <description>
Int&#233;grant des haut-parleurs pour la musique et les appels, ainsi qu&#8217;un &#233;clairage avec clignotant, le casque v&#233;lo Tenways EH20 est complet pour son prix de 159 euros. Mais il doit encore progresser pour vraiment convaincre. Voici notre test complet. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis is in a crisis of its own making</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/881987/stellantis-crisis-ev-loss-sales-regulations</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-21T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881987</guid>
      <description>Demand for EVs has gone glacial, and one automaker after another is running aground: General Motors threw $7.6 billion overboard. Ford washed $19.5 billion off its books. Leave it to Stellantis to face the most titanic charge yet, a $26.5 billion bill for its own misplaced bet on EVs. The Jeep, Dodge, and Chrysler parent [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I reviewed Philips' affordable Fidelio stereo speakers that look 'too good to be true' on the spec sheet &#8212; and they nearly pull it off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/philips-fidelio-fa3-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xmVbxummeTerkJuJaQhTv6</guid>
      <description>An active wireless speaker system with specification beyond the asking price, and an actually useful app &#8212; what&#8217;s the catch?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Wales vs Scotland: Free Streams, TV Channels &amp; Preview for Six Nations 2026 clash</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/rugby/wales-vs-scotland-six-nations-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">q5GHGXsUsf9UDTpMNUn6UQ</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Wales vs Scotland live streams online &#8211; including for FREE &#8211; in the 2026 Six Nations Round 3 clash at the Principality Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to know if an AirTag is tracking you</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/how-to-know-if-an-airtag-is-tracking-you-130000764.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ed2b124-dd5c-4928-9913-2e06174d4f2d</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s AirTag is designed to help people keep track of personal belongings like keys, bags and luggage. But because AirTags and other Bluetooth trackers are small and discreet, concerns about unwanted tracking are understandable. Apple has spent years building safeguards into the AirTag and the Find My network to reduce the risk of misuse and to alert people if a tracker they don&#8217;t own appears to be moving with them.If you&#8217;re worried about whether an AirTag or similar tracker might be following you, here&#8217;s how Apple&#8217;s unwanted tracking alerts work, what notifications to look for and what you ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget review recap: Sony WF-1000XM6, ASUS Zenbook Duo and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/engadget-review-recap-sony-wf-1000xm6-asus-zenbook-duo-and-more-130000298.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa1adb0c-47fe-452b-bf30-eeea543ed81e</guid>
      <description>Gather &#8216;round, it&#8217;s time to catch up on the latest batch of Engadget reviews. Whether you missed our in-depth testing of Sony&#8217;s latest flagship earbuds or a truly unique ASUS laptop, I&#8217;ve compiled our recent reviews so you can get up to speed quickly. Read on for the list that also includes a love letter to a tiny camera and another VPN option that worth considering. 
Sony WF-1000XM6


Sony&#8217;s 1000X earbuds have always been the top pick in our best wireless earbuds guide. With the M6 though, the company doesn&#8217;t do enough to clearly separate itself from the competition like it has in the past. &#8220;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aston Villa vs Leeds United Live Streams: How to watch Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/aston-villa-vs-leeds-united-premier-league-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FNsMTKsxzixHuUA9szQfzg</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Aston Villa vs Leeds United live streams online and from anywhere, as Unai Emery's side look to bolster their chances of a top-four finish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bon plan Intersport : le v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique Nakamura Crossover V chute &#224; 1499 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982459_bon-plan-intersport-le-velo-electrique-nakamura-crossover-v-chute-a-1499-e</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2982459_bon-plan-intersport-le-velo-electrique-nakamura-crossover-v-chute-a-1499-e</guid>
      <description>
Le Nakamura Crossover V est un v&#233;lo &#224; assistance &#233;lectrique polyvalent avec cadre ouvert et motorisation centrale puissante &#224; retrouver pour 1 499,99 euros sur Intersport au lieu de 1 699,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;The AI data centers of 2036 won&#8217;t be filled with GPUs&#8221;: FuriosaAI&#8217;s CEO on the future of silicon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-ai-data-centers-of-2036-wont-be-filled-with-gpus-furiosaais-ceo-on-the-future-of-silicon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HdZzQWmhgUKpe6TZmtb4qP</guid>
      <description>We talk AI hardware, data centers, Nvidia&#8217;s dominance, and the future of inference chips with June Paik, CEO and co-founder of FuriosaAI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Veteran Blood Donor&#8217;s Guide to Not Freaking Out Your First Time</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-veteran-blood-donors-guide-to-not-freaking-out-your-first-time-2000724609</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724609</guid>
      <description>Here are some simple tips on how to make your blood donation as smooth and faint-free as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Souvenirs From the 2026 Winter Olympics Are Being Resold for Big Bucks Online</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/gear-from-the-2026-winter-olympics-is-being-resold-for-big-bucks-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699894bb6dc08b373371fb51</guid>
      <description>From pins to mascots to Swatch watches, memorabilia from the Milano Cortina Games is showing up on sites like eBay and Vinted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Budget Monitors: I Found 3 Impressive Screens Under $200 (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-budget-monitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6984dc1c35de77580538259f</guid>
      <description>You might assume all monitors under $200 are terrible. But after trying some out, I found a few that defy expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Best Phones With Headphone Jacks (2026), Tested and Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-headphone-jack-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cdbf4fe2738a5050c0a82dd</guid>
      <description>Headphone jacks are endangered, but they&#8217;re not gone. Here are our favorite smartphones that still let you plug and play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I found all the best Google Pixel 10a cases &#8212; because your new phone deserves to look its best</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/google-pixel-phones/i-found-all-the-best-google-pixel-10a-cases-because-your-new-phone-deserves-to-look-its-best</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K6nKMtuTK5KPySHjLFw4d</guid>
      <description>These cases are perfect for showing off (and protecting) this stunning new device</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An old-school Zelda-like, Skate Bums and other new indie games worth checking out</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/an-old-school-zelda-like-skate-bums-and-other-new-indie-games-worth-checking-out-120000770.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca95510e-a218-4436-8d35-bec59f643ffa</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our latest roundup of what's going on in the indie game space. As a reminder, the latest edition of Steam Next Fest runs from February 23 until March 2, during which you'll be able to check out demos for hundreds of upcoming games. A bunch are available already, including one for Denshattack!, which I definitely recommend checking out. As it turns out, doing Tony Hawk Pro Skater-style tricks with a high-speed Japanese train absolutely rips.On Thursday, there were four showcases highlighting indie games all in a single day. It's not exactly feasible for me to recap them in full here,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burger King wants you to call its president to complain. No, really</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495887/burger-king-wants-you-to-call-its-president-to-complain-no-really</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-21T12:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495887/burger-king-wants-you-to-call-its-president-to-complain-no-really</guid>
      <description>Burger King has a new hotline that gives customers direct access to president Tom Curtis. In our Suspicion Economy, where everything&#8217;s a joke or a scam, BK is fighting cynicism with sincerity. And it just might work. 
I called Burger King president Tom Curtis a few times this week, but it went straight to voicemail. You can try too, his number is (305) 874-0520.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
