<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:34:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ce moniteur LG 4K de 32&#8243;, avec un bras articul&#233; et qui fait office de Smart TV co&#251;te pr&#232;s de 200 &#8364; de moins</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2924593_ce-moniteur-lg-4k-de-32-avec-un-bras-articule-et-qui-fait-office-de-smart-tv-coute-pres-de-200-e-de-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2924593_ce-moniteur-lg-4k-de-32-avec-un-bras-articule-et-qui-fait-office-de-smart-tv-coute-pres-de-200-e-de-moins</guid>
      <description>
Du haut de sa dalle de 32 pouces, ce moniteur LG peut s'utiliser dans tous les sens et pourra r&#233;pondre &#224; tous vos besoins. Sur le site de la marque, il tombe &#224; 823,99 euros et conna&#238;t une remise de 176 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the LG CES 2026 press conference</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-lg-ces-2026-press-conference-190159378.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6eb7981-0913-4e7b-bd66-4bc9abdcb17b</guid>
      <description>LG
For years, LG has opened CES press day with the first event of the morning. Though arch-rival Samsung getting the jump on its fellow Korean rival by giving its presentation the evening before, LG will be hitting the podium at breakfast time with the theme "Innovation in Tune with You."&#160;
As with many tech-focused events nowadays, AI is expected to serve as the unifying thread of LG's CES 2026 presentation. That said, LG &#8212; much like Apple &#8212; has its own take on the acronym, referring to it as "Affectionate Intelligence." The company will share "its vision for elevating daily life through Affec...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs t&#233;l&#233;viseurs 65 pouces 4K (Oled, QLED ou Full LED) en 2026 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/635033_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-tv-4k-et-hdr-de-65-pouces-et-plus-en-2019</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/635033_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-tv-4k-et-hdr-de-65-pouces-et-plus-en-2019</guid>
      <description>
Vous cherchez la meilleure TV 65 pouces ? Voyez les choses en grand avec notre s&#233;lection de t&#233;l&#233;viseurs grand format. Vous trouverez ici les meilleures TV de 65 pouces, qu'elles soient Oled, QLED ou LCD, des marques Samsung, LG, Philips ou encore Sony. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Brothers Keep Explaining Why Things Ended Like That</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-stranger-things-brothers-keep-explaining-why-things-ended-like-that-2000705129</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705129</guid>
      <description>The Duffers want 'Stranger Things' fans to draw their own conclusions, but did they lay the proper foundation to help with that?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La batterie &#233;lectrique au sel et au charbon, le plan d&#8217;EDF pour baisser le prix de l&#8217;electricit&#233; et la moins ch&#232;re des voitures &#233;lectriques chinoises &#8211; Le r&#233;cap&#8217; Survolt&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2926995_la-batterie-electrique-au-sel-et-au-charbon-le-plan-dedf-pour-baisser-le-prix-de-lelectricite-et-la-moins-chere-des-voitures-electriques-chinoises-le-recap-survoltes</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2926995_la-batterie-electrique-au-sel-et-au-charbon-le-plan-dedf-pour-baisser-le-prix-de-lelectricite-et-la-moins-chere-des-voitures-electriques-chinoises-le-recap-survoltes</guid>
      <description>
Cette semaine, l'actualit&#233; &#233;lectrique &#233;tait charg&#233;e, entre l&#8217;avanc&#233;e de l&#8217;Europe en mati&#232;re de batteries, la domination retrouv&#233;e de Renault sur l&#8217;&#233;lectrique, sans oublier les pol&#233;miques autour de Tesla et Xpeng.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE unveils smart fridge with barcode scanner linked to Instacart for delivery</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-ge-smart-fridge-with-barcode-scanner-linked-to-instacart</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07krVIMZxH8OwR9bHMVYkSr</guid>
      <description>GE's new Smart Refrigerator with Kitchen Assistant has a barcode scanner and a camera to check perishables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Belkin charging case for the Switch 2 has a screen for checking battery life</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/this-belkin-charging-case-for-the-switch-2-has-a-screen-for-checking-battery-life-170029450.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e64ca9d-4aa1-4b0b-a542-4f6b332e9944</guid>
      <description>Belkin just introduced the appropriately-named Charging Case Pro for Nintendo Switch 2 at CES. This is a high-end charging case specifically designed for Nintendo's latest console.
The 10,000mAh power bank delivers up to 30W of fast charging, which is a decent enough metric. I'm more excited, however, about the bells and whistles. The Charging Case Pro boasts an LCD screen on the exterior, making it easy to keep track of remaining battery life. It also doubles as a tabletop stand, which is always nice. The built-in Switch 2 stand is better than what we got with the first Switch, but it's still...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can charge the battery in Belkin&#8217;s new Switch 2 power case without opening it</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/849332/belkin-charging-case-pro-nintendo-switch-2-battery</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849332</guid>
      <description>Belkin has announced a new version of one of its first accessories for the Switch 2 at CES 2026. The Charging Case Pro for Nintendo Switch 2 carries forward the same 10,000mAh internal battery as the original, but it's been redesigned so you don't need to remove the battery to charge it, and you no [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belkin&#8217;s new 3-in-1 charging dock isn&#8217;t limited to the Apple Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/849759/belkin-ultracharge-modular-charging-dock-pro-power-bank-10-magnetic-ring-smartwatch</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849759</guid>
      <description>As convenient as 3-in-1 chargers can be, the vast majority of them work with a variety of smartphones and wireless earbuds, but only support one wearable: the Apple Watch. That's what sets the UltraCharge Modular Charging Dock that Belkin just announced at CES 2026 apart. Its design can accommodate different smartwatches, but you'll need to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belkin&#8217;s new HDMI adapter wirelessly connects to screens over 130 feet away</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/849948/belkin-connectair-wireless-hdmi-display-adapter-usb-c-plug-and-play</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=849948</guid>
      <description>Belkin has announced a new wireless display adapter that works without the need for a Wi-Fi network. The ConnectAir Wireless HDMI Display Adapter includes a USB-C transmitter you connect to devices like laptops, tablets, and phones, and an HDMI receiver that plugs into a display. You don't need to install drivers or stick to compatible [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plaud updates the NotePin with a button</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851393/plaud-notepin-s-desktop-app-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851393</guid>
      <description>Plaud has updated its compact NotePin AI recorder. The new NotePin S is almost identical to the original, except for one major difference: a button. It's joined by a new Plaud Desktop app for recording audio in online meetings, which is free to owners of any Plaud Note or NotePin. The NotePin S has the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are my 4 most anticipated new 4K Blu-ray releases from January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/here-are-my-4-most-anticipated-new-4k-blu-ray-releases-from-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FJJ7YrgqFNPqekGZWrdbVT</guid>
      <description>There are plenty of interesting 4K discs up for release in January 2026, but I've picked my 4 most anticipated ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plaud's latest AI wearable has a button for flagging key moments</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/plauds-latest-ai-wearable-has-a-button-for-flagging-key-moments-170000172.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86760f11-f770-4581-832b-b441e474a096</guid>
      <description>Plaud is back with another conversation-recording AI wearable. This one, the NotePin S, is only a minor iteration on the original NotePin. This model adds&#8230; a button.The recessed recording button replaces the squeeze-to-record mechanism on the 2024 original. A single long press starts recording. It also adds a new "press to highlight" feature. The idea is to flag what's most important in a conversation, helping the AI learn what to emphasize in its summary.Otherwise, you're getting the same package as in the first NotePin. The capsule-sized "S" model still has two microphones, weighs 0.6 ounces...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Webb : une &#233;nergie noire variable pour r&#233;soudre le myst&#232;re de certaines galaxies</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-james-webb-energie-noire-variable-resoudre-mystere-certaines-galaxies-w2t8-129723/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-james-webb-energie-noire-variable-resoudre-mystere-certaines-galaxies-w2t8-129723/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>L'&#233;nergie noire ne semblait influencer vraiment l'&#233;volution de l'Univers observable que depuis quelques milliards d'ann&#233;es, notamment en acc&#233;l&#233;rant son expansion. Mais si on suppose qu'elle &#233;volue elle aussi et qu'elle a influenc&#233; nettement pour cette raison l'Univers primitif, il devient...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oppo Find X9 Pro vs Google Pixel 10 Pro XL&#160;: comment choisir le meilleur smartphone&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/versus/2901663_oppo-find-x9-pro-vs-google-pixel-10-pro-xl-comment-choisir-le-meilleur-smartphone</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/versus/2901663_oppo-find-x9-pro-vs-google-pixel-10-pro-xl-comment-choisir-le-meilleur-smartphone</guid>
      <description>
Quand on a le budget, il est tout naturel d'h&#233;siter entre plusieurs r&#233;f&#233;rences ultra haut de gamme. Cette ann&#233;e, on est d'ailleurs bien servis avec les Oppo Find X9 Pro et le Google Pixel 10 Pro XL. Alors, comment bien d&#233;penser ses deniers pour son nouveau smartphone premium&#160;?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French and Malaysian authorities are investigating Grok for generating sexualized deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/04/french-and-malaysian-authorities-are-investigating-grok-for-generating-sexualized-deepfakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 16:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079528</guid>
      <description>France and Malaysia have joined India in condemning Grok for creating sexualized deepfakes of women and minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchBot says its humanoid household robot can do your laundry</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852741/switchbot-onero-h1-humanoid-household-robot-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852741</guid>
      <description>SwitchBot is bringing a new household robot to CES 2026. The smart home company is launching the Onero H1, which it calls "the most accessible AI household robot." The announcement follows last year's debut of its multitasking household bot - a robot vacuum mounted to a mobile platform. SwitchBot says the Onero is a general-use [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can unlock SwitchBot&#8217;s first deadbolt smart lock with your face</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852978/switchbot-lock-vision-deadbolt-facial-recognition</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852978</guid>
      <description>SwitchBot has announced a new deadbolt smart lock that can be unlocked with a glance. Like the Keypad Vision that SwitchBot launched last year, the new Lock Vision series unveiled at CES uses 3D facial recognition technology to enable "near-instant unlocking" after scanning your face. The Lock Vision is the first smart lock from SwitchBot [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchBot&#8217;s new E Ink display seems great for weather nerds</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/853042/switchbot-weather-station-e-ink-screen</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853042</guid>
      <description>One of SwitchBot's most interesting products announced at CES 2026 is one of its most basic. The Weather Station, as it's called, is a 7.5-inch framed E Ink screen that's packed with weather-related data. Its interface shows info including the date, time, weather, a six-day weather forecast, and when the sunrise and sunset will happen, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchBot&#8217;s AI audio recorder is a &#8216;second brain&#8217; for memories</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853109/switchbot-ai-mindclip-audio-recorder-ces-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853109</guid>
      <description>SwitchBot is joining the AI voice recorder bandwagon, introducing its own clip-on gadget that captures and organizes your every conversation. The SwitchBot AI MindClip announced at CES records spoken information from your daily life and work meetings and converts those conversations into summaries, to-do actions, and a personal audio memory database. This announcement follows competing [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchBot&#8217;s AI-powered desk light looks like a pixel-art snow globe</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853234/switchbot-obboto-ai-globe-desk-light-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T11:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853234</guid>
      <description>SwitchBot's new RGB desk light lets you put a teeny version of the Las Vegas Sphere in your home. The AI-powered Obboto lamp announced at CES is described by SwitchBot as an "expressive globe light companion" that can display preset animations and user-uploaded images and GIFs as pixel art, giving you a fun, customizable desktop [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola&#8217;s first book-style foldable leaks</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/854016/motorola-razr-fold-leak</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-04T11:36:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854016</guid>
      <description>The Motorola Razr Fold is reportedly coming soon, according to prolific leaker Evan Blass. Details are scant at the moment. All the info we have is based on a single slide from a marketing deck that talks up the Fold's camera system and displays, and squeezes in a mention of AI for good measure before [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
