<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:25:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit Played a Part in Nailing Jesse Plemons&#8217; Suspicious &#8216;Bugonia&#8217; Character</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/bugonia-jesse-plemons-reddit-2000708365</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708365</guid>
      <description>Screenwriter Will Tracy on how he shaped the conspiracy-obsessed Teddy in Yorgos Lanthimos' sci-fi thriller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is planning a Super Amazon-mart store near Chicago</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860058/amazon-chicago-supercenter-store-plans</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T18:18:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860058</guid>
      <description>Amazon could be taking another, even bigger swing at physical stores, this time with a Walmart-like supercenter. On Tuesday, the Orland Park Plan Commission in the Chicago suburb Orland Park, Illinois voted 6-1 to approve Amazon's proposal to develop 35 acres of land for a 229,000-square foot retail center, as reported by The Information. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic cracks down on unauthorized Claude usage by third-party harnesses and rivals</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/anthropic-cracks-down-on-unauthorized-claude-usage-by-third-party-harnesses</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4yqgGWkheba7NIePaBijR8</guid>
      <description>Anthropic has confirmed the implementation of strict new technical safeguards preventing third-party applications from spoofing its official coding client, Claude Code, in order to access the underlying Claude AI models for more favorably pricing and limits &#8212; a move that has disrupted workflows for users of popular open source coding agent OpenCode. Simultaneously but separately, it has restricted usage of its AI models by rival labs including xAI (through the integrated developer environment Cursor) to train competing systems to Claude Code. The former action was clarified on Friday by Thariq...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Automotive Tech at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/best-automotive-tech-ces-2026-2000708326</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708326</guid>
      <description>Robotaxis, concept cars, and a massive touchscreen were just some of the automotive highlights at CES 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scuf Envision Pro V2 has some of the best buttons and triggers I&#8217;ve ever used, but it&#8217;s massively let down by convoluted software</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/scuf-envision-pro-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">943Nw3DxiWhrFhuj7CfBt7</guid>
      <description>The Scuf Envision Pro V2 is a great PC controller that&#8217;s unfortunately hard to recommend to most. It feels brilliant to use, though most won&#8217;t need 90% of what the device offers in terms of customizability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;This is an unbelievable moment in the course of human history&#8217;: Sean Astin on how he&#8217;s fighting for humanity against an onslaught of AI actors</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/this-is-an-unbelievable-moment-in-the-course-of-human-history-sean-astin-on-how-hes-fighting-for-humanity-against-an-onslaught-of-ai-actors</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85kHG4PvLAPcezC8uDR9d3</guid>
      <description>We sat down with actor and SAG-AFTRA President Sean Astin to talk about AI and its impact on his industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X accuses music publishers of &amp;#8216;weaponizing&amp;#8217; DMCA takedowns</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/860013/x-nmpa-music-publishers-dmca-antitrust-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T17:59:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860013</guid>
      <description>X is suing music publishers and their trade group, the National Music Publishers' Association (NMPA), accusing them of attempted coercion in their ongoing battle over licensing, as reported earlier by The Hollywood Reporter. The Elon Musk-owned platform accuses music publishers of colluding with the NMPA to "coerce X into taking licenses to musical works from [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This company could help bring Auracast to an iPhone near you</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/860010/atitan-bluetooth-auracast-transceiver-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T17:56:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860010</guid>
      <description>One of the issues holding Auracast back from wider mainstream use is some companies' lack of support for the Bluetooth technology - Apple being a prime example. With iOS having 58 percent of the market share in North America and nearly 28 percent worldwide, a decision by Apple to enable native Auracast support would potentially [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is coming for collectibles next</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/859994/ai-collectibles-funko-pops-amiibo-buddyo-heymates-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T17:52:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859994</guid>
      <description>AI toys, companions, and robots have been everywhere at CES this year, but among the horde of waddling plushies and light-up emoji eyes, two stood out to me. HeyMates and Buddyo are each betting that the collectible figurine boom is going to come back with an AI-powered vengeance, letting us chat to sports stars and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: Everything revealed, from Nvidia&#8217;s debuts to AMD&#8217;s new chips to Razer&#8217;s AI oddities</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/09/ces-2026-everything-revealed-from-nvidias-debuts-to-amds-new-chips-to-razers-ai-oddities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080516</guid>
      <description>CES 2026&#160;is in full swing in Las Vegas, with the show floor open to the public after a packed couple of days&#160;occupied by&#160;press conferences from the likes of Nvidia, Sony, and AMD&#160;and previews from Sunday&#8217;s Unveiled event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The battle of the SuperPods: Nvidia challenges Huawei with Vera Rubin powered DGX cluster that can deliver 28.8 Exaflops with only 576 GPUs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-battle-of-the-superpods-nvidia-challenges-huawei-with-vera-rubin-powered-dgx-cluster-that-can-deliver-28-8-exaflops-with-only-576-gpus</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RoGTBRAyRg6cuVT84sZYr4</guid>
      <description>Nvidia&#8217;s Rubin DGX SuperPOD delivers 28.8 Exaflops using 576 GPUs, combining compute, memory, and software to rival Huawei&#8217;s SuperPOD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legacy of the &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Ending Debate Goes Back to &#8216;Mass Effect&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-conformity-gate-mass-effect-indoctrination-theory-2000708251</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708251</guid>
      <description>I remember when Conformity Gate was called the Indoctrination Theory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Watch Is Discounted on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-galaxy-watch8-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69613a804169e08c999c69d6</guid>
      <description>The Samsung Galaxy Watch8 gets marked down across a variety of colors, sizes, and feature sets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's time for Apple to reinstate ICEBlock</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/its-time-for-apple-to-reinstate-iceblock-220802356.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 22:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db1c945f-64db-4519-9c58-c6c65586ef02</guid>
      <description>In October, Apple caved to pressure from the Trump administration and removed ICEBlock &#8212; and similar apps which crowdsourced the location of Immigrations and Customs Enforcement activity &#8212; from its App Store. Apple's stated rationale? The apps could "be used to harm law enforcement officers."  But armed-to-the-teeth ICE officers don&#8217;t need protection from civilians. Apple had that exactly backward.That became impossible to ignore on Wednesday, when ICE agent Jonathon Ross killed 37-year-old Renee Nicole Good in cold blood. By now, you don't need me to recount her brutal last moments. But the f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alamo Drafthouse Moves to Mobile Food Ordering in the Movie Theater</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alamo-drafthouse-moves-to-mobile-food-ordering-in-the-movie-theater-2000708311</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708311</guid>
      <description>The small screen meets the big screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solawave Wand Fans: Don't Miss This Buy One, Get One Free Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/solawave-wand-fans-this-buy-one-get-one-free-deal-is-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6961636dc0c7d7edb18e6e76</guid>
      <description>Double up on LED therapy, because sharing is caring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character.AI settles lawsuits related to teen deaths</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/characterai-lawsuits-settled</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07vH37WNJ4sM7vo2rn9Ya13</guid>
      <description>The lawsuits alleged that Character.AI's chatbot product was defective and dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes Bets Its Credibility on New Polymarket Partnership</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/golden-globes-bets-its-credibility-on-new-polymarket-partnership-2000708316</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000708316</guid>
      <description>The awards show is teaming up with a controversial prediction marketplace that is facing growing scrutiny over insider trading concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is apparently planning a big box store in the Chicago suburbs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/amazon-is-apparently-planning-a-big-box-store-in-the-chicago-suburbs-213451978.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fa47371-d78c-4495-8719-c8823bf845ac</guid>
      <description>Amazon is making a return, of sorts, to physical retail via plans to build a big-box retail store in the Chicago suburbs, The Information reports. The 225,000-square foot retail space will open in Orland Park, Illinois, and give the company the opportunity to sell more than just groceries after it closed most of its physical bookstores and gift shops in 2022.The new store will offer in-store shopping, but also act as a fulfillment center for online orders, which could make it similar to competitors like Target and Walmart, and some of Amazon's existing Whole Foods and Amazon Fresh locations. "...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What NFL coaches could teach the wider business world</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91472276/what-nfl-coaches-could-teach-the-wider-business-world</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-09T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91472276/what-nfl-coaches-could-teach-the-wider-business-world</guid>
      <description>This week saw Black Monday, the NFL&#8217;s annual axing of low-performing coaches. Is this public, clear-cut accountability good . . . or bad?
The beginning of a new year ushers in an ominous day in the NFL: Black Monday, the day when coaches are (typically) most at risk of losing their jobs. Black Monday happens the day after the regular season ends, a time when an especially harsh backward review is cast over the wins, losses, and total misses.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
