<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:26:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>You Need to Check Your Wireless Headphones for Updates, Right Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-need-to-check-your-wireless-headphones-for-updates-right-now-2000710714</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710714</guid>
      <description>Hackers can abuse a loophole to spy on conversations and track your location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside OpenAI&#8217;s Raid on Thinking Machines Lab</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-openai-raid-on-thinking-machines-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6967d917aac0bb6ef1ecddf9</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is planning to bring over more researchers from Thinking Machines Lab after nabbing two cofounders, a source familiar with the situation says. Plus, the latest efforts to automate jobs with AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US claims it just strongarmed Taiwan into spending $250 billion on American chip manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862938/us-taiwan-chipmaking-deal-250-billion-investment-tsmc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T16:12:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862938</guid>
      <description>The US just lowered Taiwan's tariffs in exchange for a massive domestic chipmaking promise, the Commerce Department announced on Thursday. Under the deal, tariffs on goods from Taiwan will decrease from 20 to 15 percent, while Taiwanese technology companies will invest $250 billion into building and expanding chipmaking facilities in the US, supported by at [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Years Later, Has the MCU&#8217;s TV Excursion Worked?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/five-years-later-has-the-mcus-tv-excursion-worked-2000709110</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000709110</guid>
      <description>'WandaVision' put the MCU on a journey into television that took time for the megafranchise to fully adjust to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got a Nespresso machine? These 5 tricks and tips will help you make the most of it, and enjoy better-tasting coffee every morning</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/got-a-nespresso-machine-these-5-tricks-and-tips-will-help-you-make-the-most-of-it-and-enjoy-better-tasting-coffee-every-morning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">C2xdaxzpLPGrFfJKTqvVAV</guid>
      <description>Are you getting the best possible flavor from your Nespresso capsules? This quick guide will help ensure that you do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Help Ghouls Are Charging People Absurd Prices to Talk to Impersonator Chatbots</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/self-help-ghouls-are-charging-people-absurd-prices-to-talk-to-impersonator-chatbots-2000710744</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710744</guid>
      <description>Sure, it's exploitative, but it's also profitable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's New World: Aeternum MMO will go offline January 31, 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/amazons-new-world-aeternum-mmo-will-go-offline-january-31-2027-205449407.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">059941ce-c823-44f9-862e-c054624d3c17</guid>
      <description>Today, Amazon shared more details about the final chapter of its game New World: Aeternum. The company announced in October that it would wind down support for the MMO, with the Nighthaven season to be its last. New World will be delisted and no longer available for purchase starting today, but the game's servers will not be taken offline until January 31, 2027. People who own the game will be able to continue playing until that date. Nighthaven season will continue through to that end date.Players who had previously purchased New World: Aeternum will be able to re-download and continue playin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan to invest&#160;$250B in US semiconductor manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/taiwan-to-invest-250b-in-us-semiconductor-manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083221</guid>
      <description>The U.S. struck a trade deal with Taiwan as the country looks to help boost domestic semiconductor manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finally, Some Good News in the Fight Against Cancer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/finally-some-good-news-in-the-fight-against-cancer-2000710820</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710820</guid>
      <description>The American Cancer Society&#8217;s annual report found that 70% of patients now survive at least five years after diagnosis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krafton is trying to find its next PUBG</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862922/krafton-next-pubg-franchise</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T15:38:15-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862922</guid>
      <description>PUBG developer Krafton has 26 games in development, and in a recent town hall meeting, the company outlined a plan to "focus on its core gaming business while outlining a disciplined approach to building long-term Franchise IPs." "During the past year, KRAFTON has prepared for Franchise IP development by strengthening its creative leadership, as well [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the oldest phone you can still use in 2026?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/what-is-the-oldest-phone-you-can-still-use-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">paEMXJXmUa6LpDkb3az6jE</guid>
      <description>From iPhone to Galaxy to Google Pixel, these are the oldest phones you can still use day-to-day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our viewpoint is that we are trying to help consumers around the world': Micron finally breaks silence on claims it abandoned customers by dropping the Crucial memory brand</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/our-viewpoint-is-that-we-are-trying-to-help-consumers-around-the-world-micron-finally-breaks-silence-on-claims-it-abandoned-customers-by-dropping-the-crucial-memory-brand</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V66VKFTehydthjrQN98WXT</guid>
      <description>Micron confirms Crucial exit while emphasizing ongoing consumer support, highlighting enterprise DRAM growth and persistent shortages through at least 2028.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia inks new deals with AI companies to mark 25th anniversary</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475731/wikipedia-ai-deals-amazon-meta-microsoft-25th-anniversary</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:31:45</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475731/wikipedia-ai-deals-amazon-meta-microsoft-25th-anniversary</guid>
      <description>The new deals will help one of the world&#8217;s most popular websites monetize heavy traffic from AI companies.
Wikipedia unveiled new business deals with a slew of&#160;artificial intelligence&#160;companies on Thursday as it marked its 25th anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix's expanded Sony deal includes streaming rights to the Legend of Zelda movie</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/netflixs-expanded-sony-deal-includes-streaming-rights-to-the-legend-of-zelda-movie-203011384.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b09f0f28-9c05-4cb0-9720-961f235b1912</guid>
      <description>As part of a new agreement, films from Sony Pictures Entertainment will stream on Netflix first, the companies announced via a joint statement. The new deal expands on the exclusive rights Netflix had to Sony films in the US, and means the service will be the first place people will be able to stream upcoming projects like the live-action adaptation of The Legend of Zelda, and a quartet of biopics about The Beatles.Sony's films will stream worldwide on Netflix in what's called "Pay-1," the first window of availability after a movie's theatrical and VOD releases. As part of the deal, Netflix is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon is giving customers a $20 credit for the outage&#8212;but only if they claim it. Here&#8217;s how</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475876/verizon-outage-credit-for-customers-how-to-claim-redeem-on-app</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475876/verizon-outage-credit-for-customers-how-to-claim-redeem-on-app</guid>
      <description>The mobile giant experienced a massive nationwide service outage this week, and it&#8217;s offering a small refund that can be redeemed on the Verizon app.
If you are Verizon customer, like me, you&#8217;ve probably been scrambling to make phone calls, send texts, and get online since Wednesday, due to a massive, nationwide service outage. (I am writing this from my local food co-op outside Boston, where I am using the internet in their cafe.)...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digg Relaunches From the Grave With Some &#8216;AI Enhancements&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/digg-relaunches-from-the-grave-with-some-ai-enhancements-2000710736</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710736</guid>
      <description>For all the people who've abandoned or been kicked off Reddit, your Bluesky moment has arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Washington&#8217;s healthcare debate never really goes away</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475718/washingtons-health-care-debate-never-really-goes-away</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:13:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475718/washingtons-health-care-debate-never-really-goes-away</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the deliberations that never seem to end.
The president was barely a year into his administration when a health care debate began to consume Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some scientists say research on microplastics is flawed: What does it mean for our bodies?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475134/microplastics-research-flawed-what-does-it-mean-for-our-bodies</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:01:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475134/microplastics-research-flawed-what-does-it-mean-for-our-bodies</guid>
      <description>A recent story in the Guardian raised valid questions about an emerging field of study. It doesn&#8217;t mean we should write off equally valid concerns about health.
In recent years, there&#8217;s been a wave of studies reporting that humans are basically full of microplastics: They&#8217;ve been found in our brains, arteries, and even in placentas.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verizon Is Slipping Customers 20 Bucks to Pay for Yesterday&#8217;s Outage</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/verizon-is-slipping-customers-20-bucks-to-pay-for-yesterdays-outage-2000710778</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000710778</guid>
      <description>The carrier is offering a $20 credit to customers affected by a widespread and hours-long service outage on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the most interesting automotive tech I saw at CES &#8212; and the ones you should be watching in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/this-is-the-most-interesting-automotive-tech-i-saw-at-ces-and-the-ones-you-should-be-watching-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XoNLrP5EjmpTorwAobkiuG</guid>
      <description>From Qualcomm to Waymo, car companies and their partners are doing autos differently in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This TikTok lifehack could help you embrace rejection</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475295/this-tiktok-lifehack-could-help-you-embrace-rejection</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475295/this-tiktok-lifehack-could-help-you-embrace-rejection</guid>
      <description>Just be ready to settle in for the long haul.
Rejection stings. If you&#8217;re on the job hunt right now, it&#8217;s likely something you&#8217;ve grown accustomed to, if not entirely numb to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les astronomes pensent enfin savoir ce que sont les &#171; points rouges &#187; rep&#233;r&#233;s par le t&#233;lescope James-Webb</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/cosmologie-astronomes-pensent-enfin-savoir-ce-sont-points-rouges-reperes-telescope-james-webb-130212/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:59:31 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/cosmologie-astronomes-pensent-enfin-savoir-ce-sont-points-rouges-reperes-telescope-james-webb-130212/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Des &#171; petits points rouges &#187; dans les images renvoy&#233;es par le t&#233;lescope spatial James-Webb. Plusieurs mois que les astronomes s&#8217;y cassent les dents. Mais de nouvelles donn&#233;es pourraient enfin lever le voile. Ou laisser &#233;clore le papillon cosmique&#8201;?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s New World: Aeternum MMO will shut down next year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/862892/amazon-new-world-aeternum-mmo-servers-shut-down-delisted</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T14:52:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=862892</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced that the servers for New World: Aeternum, one of the company's MMOs, will be shut down on January 31st, 2027. The game will also be delisted and no longer available for purchase starting today, January 15th. Last year, Amazon announced that it would be pivoting away from MMOs to put more of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flaw in 17 Google Fast Pair audio devices could let hackers eavesdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/flaw-in-17-google-fast-pair-audio-devices-could-let-hackers-eavesdrop-194613456.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8404957d-0b0f-4df4-be02-abfa15084dd2</guid>
      <description>Now would be a good time to update all your Bluetooth audio devices. On Thursday, Wired reported on a security flaw in 17 headphone and speaker models that could allow hackers to access your devices, including their microphones. The vulnerability stems from a faulty implementation of Google's one-tap (Fast Pair) protocol.Security researchers at Belgium's KU Leuven University Computer Security and Industrial Cryptography group, who discovered the security hole, named the flaw WhisperPair. They say a hacker within Bluetooth range would only require the accessory's (easily attainable) device mode...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s Grok &#8216;Undressing&#8217; Problem Isn&#8217;t Fixed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musks-grok-undressing-problem-isnt-fixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6968fedb43f4ea26029fe444</guid>
      <description>X has placed more restrictions on Grok&#8217;s ability to generate explicit AI images, but tests show that the updates have created a patchwork of limitations that fail to fully address the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s an extreme step only Trump could take to crush anti-ICE protests. He&#8217;s threatening to do it</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91475679/anti-ice-protests-minneapolis-minnesota-insurrection-act-of-1807-trump-threat-explained</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91475679/anti-ice-protests-minneapolis-minnesota-insurrection-act-of-1807-trump-threat-explained</guid>
      <description>Rallies against Immigration and Customs Enforcement continue in Minneapolis, Minnesota. A crackdown from President Trump could end them.
President Donald Trump took to social media on Thursday threatening to crack down on protests in Minnesota, as federal Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) officers face off with protestors in the streets on Minneapolis following the death of Renee Nicole Good, who was fatally shot by an ICE agent....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI video startup, Higgsfield, founded by ex-Snap exec, lands $1.3B valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/15/ai-video-startup-higgsfield-founded-by-ex-snap-exec-lands-1-3b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083094</guid>
      <description>Higgsfield says it's on a $200 million annual revenue run rate. So it opened its previous Series A round back up and sold another $80 million in shares.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
