<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:30:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Marshals: A Yellowstone Story episode 1 on Paramount+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/marshals-a-yellowstone-story-episode-1-release-date-time-cbs</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gToLeiwnvX8P6RGso8RPV</guid>
      <description>Kayce Dutton is back for the ride of his life in a new Taylor Sheridan show, but when does Marshals: A Yellowstone Story episode 1 air on CBS and Paramount+?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix says it&#8217;s not buying Warner Bros. after all: &#8216;no longer financially attractive&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499776/netflix-warner-bros-merger-off-paramount-bid</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T01:22:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499776/netflix-warner-bros-merger-off-paramount-bid</guid>
      <description>In a stunning move, the streaming giant is walking away from the deal it struck in December after Paramount Skydance upped its bid. 
Netflix is declining to raise its offer to buy Warner Bros. Discovery&#8217;s studio and streaming business, in a stunning move that effectively puts Paramount in a position to take over its storied Hollywood rival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Latest Repair Battlefield Is the Iowa Farmlands&#8212;Again</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/latest-repair-battlefield-iowa-farmlands-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a0d40e17ebd66b4d3f05fb</guid>
      <description>A new bill that would give farmers in Iowa the right to repair is a big threat to tractor manufacturer John Deere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Awesome precision meets blisteringly fast connectivity&#8217; &#8211; I tested the Asus ROG Raikiri II Xbox Wireless and I&#8217;m never going back to my first-party controller</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-accessories/asus-rog-raikiri-ii-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jkTTAD99U8JCyLuhwAPTkB</guid>
      <description>Asus ROG&#8217;s innovative Raikiri II controller and its trailblazing TMR triggers have finally given me the edge I need in my favorite games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I called Soulja Boy&#8217;s new AI voice clone and had an uncanny chat</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/i-called-soulja-boys-new-ai-voice-clone-and-had-an-uncanny-chat</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qRj4zFseChUE5sdGd442mj</guid>
      <description>Soulja Boy teamed up with Bland AI to launch a phone-based voice clone fans can call, showcasing a playful but revealing example of how AI is reshaping celebrity interaction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Dorsey's Block cuts 40% of staff, 4,000+ people &#8212; and yes, it's because of AI efficiencies</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/orchestration/jack-dorseys-block-cuts-40-of-staff-4-000-people-and-yes-its-because-of-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4olNUVtj7Uf34LgZKcl7lm</guid>
      <description>Former Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey's new company Block &#8212; the parent of merchants payment system Square, mobile peer-to-peer payments Cash App, music streamer Tidal, and open source AI agentic system Goose &#8212; is sending shockwaves across the business world tonight after announcing a more than 40% headcount, cutting its workforce by more than 4,000 people out of a prior total of 10,000, despite its latest quarterly earnings statement released today showing $2.87 billion in gross profit up 24% year-over-year. The culprit? Newfound AI efficiencies. As Dorsey put it in a note shared on his own fo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Are Our Absolute Favorite Android Earbuds, and They're Below $200</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/pixel-buds-pro-2-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a083d2c8e5bf5aa70f7969</guid>
      <description>The Pixel Buds Pro 2 have great ANC and long battery life, and they&#8217;re marked down in several colors.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
