<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:48:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit expands access to its AI health coach</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876692/fitbit-ai-health-coach-public-preview-ios</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:42:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876692</guid>
      <description>Google announced on Tuesday that the public preview of Fitbit's AI personal health coach is rolling out to iOS users in the U.S. as well as both iOS and Android users in the UK, Canada, Australia, New Zealand, and Singapore. It initially launched in October, when it was only available in the U.S. on Android [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arm's owner and Intel say their Z-Angle Memory, HBM-rival, will hit the market in 2029 - but I hope it won't be another Optane/3D-Xpoint, which caused Micron to lose millions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/arms-owner-and-intel-say-their-z-angle-memory-hbm-rival-will-hit-the-market-in-2029-but-i-hope-it-wont-be-another-optane-3d-xpoint-one-that-caused-micron-to-lose-millions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PG4xgo5RyucDhdAtTqRPdg</guid>
      <description>Z-Angle Memory could rival HBM, yet previous failures like Optane show hundreds of millions in potential financial losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My most anticipated upcoming phone isn't this year's iPhone, it's a Chinese flagship filled with one-of-a-kind features</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/xiaomi-phones/my-most-anticipated-upcoming-phone-isnt-this-years-iphone-its-a-chinese-flagship-filled-with-one-of-a-kind-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ctCMzLQuj48dHNiDCDMziR</guid>
      <description>I'm not looking forward to the next iPhone, but this Chinese flagship has really caught my eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Now Lets Users Remove Explicit Images and Other Personal Info From Search Results</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-now-lets-users-remove-explicit-images-and-other-personal-info-from-search-results-2000720317</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720317</guid>
      <description>The search giant announced new tools aimed at giving people more control over how their information appears online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics CEO&#160;Robert Playter&#160;steps&#160;down after 30 years at the company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/boston-dynamics-ceo-robert-playter-steps-down-after-30-years-at-the-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091693</guid>
      <description>Robert Playter announcd he is leaving Boston Dynamics after 30 years at the company in various roles, including six years as CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VC Masha Bucher, Epstein associate and Day One founder, explains herself</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/vc-masha-bucher-epstein-associate-and-day-one-founder-explains-herself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091632</guid>
      <description>After numerous news reports documented Masha Bucher's close business and personal relationship with convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein, Bucher took to X to explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Phone Looks as Bad as It Sounds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-trump-phone-looks-as-bad-as-it-sounds-2000720184</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720184</guid>
      <description>The first real glimpse of the Trump phone confirms what we already suspected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F1 2026 Bahrain pre-season testing live streams: how to watch online from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/formula-one/f1-2026-bahrain-pre-season-testing-live-streams</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">p2ofJGp7wJjzCEyk6stP9B</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch the F1 2026 Bahrain pre-season testing. Stream all the live action from the two three-day tests at the Bahrain International Circuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayaneo&#8217;s new Windows handheld will cost up to $4,299 with maxed out specs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876521/ayaneo-next-2-windows-handheld-ryzen-ai-max-395-indiegogo-preorder</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:49:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876521</guid>
      <description>Ayaneo opened preorders for its next Windows 11 handheld and it looks like a powerhouse. The Ayaneo Next 2 is 13.45 inches wide, 10.3-inches tall, and weighs 3.14 pounds. That's more than twice as heavy as the original Ayaneo Next that launched back in 2022, and it easily outweighs the Steam Deck and Switch 2. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Figure Skaters Get Heat for Using AI-Generated Music</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/olympic-figure-skaters-get-heat-for-using-ai-generated-music-2000720192</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720192</guid>
      <description>"So you want the world to respect your art but don't give a shit about the art of music that helps you do it?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Physics Behind the Quadruple Axel, the Most Difficult Jump in Figure Skating</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/2026-winter-olympics-figure-skating-quadruple-axel-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698b3cd301ac8aa5897ea131</guid>
      <description>Are you speechless watching US figure skater Ilia Malinin on the ice? Science explains how it&#8217;s possible the Quad God can do more than four full rotations in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sent personal and financial information of student journalist to ICE</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/google-sent-personal-and-financial-information-of-student-journalist-to-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091670</guid>
      <description>The tech giant handed over the personal information of a journalist and student who attended a pro-Palestinian protest in 2024. This is the latest example of ICE using its controversial subpoena powers to target people critical of the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Trachtenberg&#8217;s Paramount Deal Doesn&#8217;t Kill His &#8216;Predator&#8217; Plans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dan-trachtenbergs-paramount-deal-doesnt-kill-his-predator-plans-2000720290</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720290</guid>
      <description>The director of 'Prey' and 'Predator: Badlands' spoke to io9 about his filmmaking future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of xAI&#8217;s founding team has now left the company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/nearly-half-of-xais-founding-team-has-now-left-the-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091548</guid>
      <description>Whatever the cause of the departures, the cumulative impact is alarming. There is a lot of work left to do at xAI, and an IPO will bring more scrutiny than the lab has ever faced before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Says Americans Need More Protein. His Grok-Powered Food Website Disagrees</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/rfk-jr-says-americans-need-more-protein-his-grok-powered-food-website-disagrees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6989ff959814f92797042bfb</guid>
      <description>The site Realfood.gov uses Elon Musk&#8217;s Grok chatbot to dispense nutrition information&#8212;some of which contradicts the government&#8217;s new guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favorite Switch 2 controller is 30 percent off for today only</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876544/easysmx-s10-switch-2-wireless-controller-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:27:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876544</guid>
      <description>The EasySMX S10 is a fantastic wireless controller for the Switch 2 that offers nearly as many features as Nintendo&#8217;s $90 gamepad. I ranked it as the best Switch 2 controller you can buy, thanks to its satisfying rumble sensation in games, support for motion controls as well as Nintendo&#8217;s amiibo NFC figures, plus the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Dictionary of English Slang Is Now Free Online to Help You Talk Like a Zoomer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/largest-dictionary-of-english-slang-is-now-free-online-to-help-you-talk-like-a-zoomer-2000720203</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720203</guid>
      <description>It'd probably help the New York Times, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'As adoption grows, confidence in safeguards must rise with it': Microsoft reveals new tool which can track backdoors in LLMs - and it's hoping this will restore trust in AI across the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/as-adoption-grows-confidence-in-safeguards-must-rise-with-it-microsoft-reveals-new-tool-which-can-track-backdoors-in-llms-and-its-hoping-this-will-restore-trust-in-ai-across-the-world</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JyJCCcHGCogw63uCopmyWG</guid>
      <description>Microsoft introduced a scanner that detects poisoned open-weight language models by analyzing attention behavior, memorization leaks, and trigger flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bumble quietly removes option for men to message first in Mexico and Australia</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/bumble-quietly-removes-option-for-men-to-message-first-mexico-australia</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ilEEjCC0MzTjHPgNDZLh3</guid>
      <description>Bumble removes Opening Moves in Mexico and Australia, amid legal threats in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord says &amp;#8216;vast majority&amp;#8217; of users won&amp;#8217;t see its new age verification setup</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876575/discord-age-verification-vast-majority-users-inference</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:17:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876575</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Discord released an update clarifying that the "vast majority of people can continue using Discord exactly as they do today," without needing to use a face scan or ID to verify their age so they can use the platform without restrictions. Discord states in the post that "age prediction" using information Discord already [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta AI can now animate your Facebook profile picture</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/facebook-ai-profile-picture-meta</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02lPJ7W1L6o1crmSeDqn0z3</guid>
      <description>Facebook will now let AI animate your profile picture. This one's for the Boomers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook is offering Meta AI-powered animations for profile photos</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/facebook-is-offering-meta-ai-powered-animations-for-profile-photos-201022506.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17919990-988c-428f-8773-4eb8806058e9</guid>
      <description>Meta has been going all in on AI, whether people want it or not, and now it's bringing more features in that vein to Facebook. The network's latest move is to let people use Meta AI to animate their profile photos. Because what better way to express your individuality than to use a pre-canned AI-generated animation on your own face?Meta AI is also coming for your Facebook Stories and Memories. The network's Restyle lets you use gen-AI to change up the aesthetic of your posts. You can once again use pre-canned stylings or give the AI assistant your own prompt.In the company's own words, the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get two years of Surfshark VPN for up to 87 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-two-years-of-surfshark-vpn-for-up-to-87-percent-off-123000309.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b286225-32f8-41dc-9bc9-bf699f554c51</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;ve been thinking about signing up for a VPN, Surfshark has solid deals on its two-year plans right now. Surfshark&#8217;s One plan is 87 percent off right now when you pay for two years upfront, plus you&#8217;ll get three extra months free. That comes out to a total of $62 for the first 27 months of access.
We&#8217;ve generally liked Surfshark as a straightforward, speedy service for everyday use, and it&#8217;s one of the picks in our guide to the best VPNs. In our Surfshark review, we found it delivered excellent speeds overall and reliably unblocked Netflix across most of our test servers, which makes thi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Einstein avait donn&#233; la cl&#233; de l'&#233;nigme des exoplan&#232;tes Tatooines de Star Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-einstein-avait-donne-cle-enigme-exoplanetes-tatooines-star-wars-130931/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:03:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-einstein-avait-donne-cle-enigme-exoplanetes-tatooines-star-wars-130931/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Quand on pense &#224; la th&#233;orie de la relativit&#233; g&#233;n&#233;rale d'Einstein, on pense imm&#233;diatement aux trous noirs, aux trous de ver, et bien s&#251;r aux ondes gravitationnelles et au Big Bang. Pourtant, la premi&#232;re application de la th&#233;orie d'Einstein a &#233;t&#233; en m&#233;canique c&#233;leste, avec le mouvement des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornhub traffic dipped during Bad Bunnys halftime show</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pornhub-traffic-dipped-during-bad-bunny-super-bowl-halftime</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">009ddBsPzaxk3tHgl0wTLx0</guid>
      <description>Pornhub traffic dropped below average during the Super Bowl halftime show, hinting that viewers watched Bad Bunny instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brendan Fraser-Rachel Weisz &#8216;Mummy&#8217; Reunion Is Coming in 2028</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mummy-4-release-date-brendan-fraser-rachel-weisz-2000720240</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720240</guid>
      <description>The much-anticipated fourth 'Mummy' film will be directed by Matt Bettinelli-Olpin and Tyler Gillett and now has a release date to look forward to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cure for the memory crisis? John Carmack envisions fiber cables replacing RAM for AI usage, which would mean a better future for us all</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/a-cure-for-the-memory-crisis-john-carmack-envisions-fiber-cables-replacing-ram-for-ai-usage-which-would-mean-a-better-future-for-us-all</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UjW4yFuQ8sp94CWcce8i9a</guid>
      <description>Fiber aside, there could be a nearer-term way of alleviating the memory crisis, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 bargain-priced soundbars that will instantly upgrade your TV's disappointing built-in sound &#8212; without breaking the bank</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/4-bargain-priced-soundbars-that-will-instantly-upgrade-your-tvs-disappointing-built-in-sound-without-breaking-the-bank</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dobCKMwWRiGya2zCUgX38K</guid>
      <description>Put more boom in your room with these cut-price soundbar deals, including Dolby Atmos options</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmarterTools network breached using auth-bypass attack against single unpatched virtual machine</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/smartertools-network-breached-using-auth-bypass-attack-against-single-unpatched-virtual-machine</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">U8r9evWkPHukY5LyxZuHGe</guid>
      <description>Just one neglected server was enough to suffer a ransomware infection but this time, the damage was minimal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target CEO shuffles leadership team as his first big move after taking over</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490437/target-michael-fiddelke-sales</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490437/target-michael-fiddelke-sales</guid>
      <description>It is the first substantial change under CEO Michael Fiddelke, a 20-year company veteran who took over for Brian Cornell this month. 
Target CEO Michael Fiddelke is reshuffling his leadership team and making other changes shortly after stepping into the top job at the retailer that has struggled operationally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir CEO Alex Karp Recorded a Video About ICE for His Employees</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/palantir-ceo-alex-karp-employee-questions-on-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6986287b89651d97f0bdbbac</guid>
      <description>In a video shared with Palantir employees, Alex Karp did not explain how ICE is utilizing the company&#8217;s products. Instead, workers were told they can sign NDAs if they want detailed information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount sweetens its bid for Warner Bros. Discovery with &#8216;additional benefits&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490430/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-hollywood</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T19:49:46</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490430/warner-bros-netflix-paramount-hollywood</guid>
      <description>The new March 2 deadline marks the third time Paramount has pushed back the expiration of its tender offer.
Paramount is again sweetening its&#160;hostile takeover bid&#160;for Warner Bros. Discovery, while again extending the deadline for its tender offer as it scrambles for more shareholder support.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
