<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:27:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Andor&#8217; Season 2&#8217;s Opening Remains One of Its Best Moments</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/andor-season-2-opening-scene-star-wars-2000704967</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704967</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the circle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entreprise d&#8217;Elon Musk | L&#8217;assistant IA de X utilis&#233; pour cr&#233;er du contenu p&#233;dopornographique</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-02/entreprise-d-elon-musk/l-assistant-ia-de-x-utilise-pour-creer-du-contenu-pedopornographique.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:16:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f752e1c5701d3c6d9fa75de51780f123</guid>
      <description>Grok, l&#8217;assistant d&#8217;intelligence artificielle (IA) du r&#233;seau social X, a reconnu vendredi l&#8217;existence de &#171;&#160;failles&#160;&#187; ayant permis &#224; des utilisateurs d&#8217;obtenir de lui des images &#224; caract&#232;re sexuel impliquant des mineurs ou des femmes, suscitant des protestations &#224; travers le monde et l&#8217;&#233;largissement d&#8217;une enqu&#234;te judiciaire en France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged PS5 Jailbreak Method Spikes Prices for Old Star Wars Game on eBay</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alleged-ps5-jailbreak-method-spikes-prices-for-old-star-wars-game-on-ebay-2000704980</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704980</guid>
      <description>'Star Wars Racer Revenge' is selling for hundreds of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 new horror movies on Prime Video, Shudder, HBO Max, and more in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/7-new-horror-movies-on-prime-video-shudder-hbo-max-and-more-in-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VcaSymNGvi6UKxv6qrWtXM</guid>
      <description>Looking to cure those January blues? There's some gripping horror movies waiting for you across the best streaming services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Samsung's "First Look" CES 2026 presentation on Sunday</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/how-to-watch-samsungs-first-look-ces-2026-presentation-on-sunday-190027889.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99e05139-49a3-486e-a22a-1ec128284043</guid>
      <description>NurPhoto via Getty Images
Samsung is arguably the 800-pound gorilla of CES, with a full spectrum of products that range from phones and computers to refrigerators, AI assistants and rolling robots. But for CES 2026, the company is switching things up a bit: Instead of its longtime midday Monday press conference, the Korean giant will take the lead of the show with a Sunday night presentation.
Over the past few weeks, Samsung has been dropping hints about what's on the agenda, but what we're really hoping to see is an update on the Ballie robot &#8212; a star of previous CES presentations that ostens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch NHL Winter Classic 2026: live stream New York Rangers vs Florida Panthers, TV channels, preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/hockey/nhl-winter-classic-2026-live-stream-new-york-rangers-vs-florida-panthers</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2AzUNtapCpiqkRUy3dmTGQ</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch Rangers vs Panthers live streams online in the 2026 NHL Winter Classic, as the traditional New Year's game heads to Florida for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big changes are coming to national parks in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468435/big-changes-are-coming-to-national-parks-in-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468435/big-changes-are-coming-to-national-parks-in-2026</guid>
      <description>A slate of changes tied to America&#8217;s 250th anniversary will affect entry fees, passes, and who gets free access.
America&#8217;s National Parks offer some of the country&#8217;s most impressive vistas &#8211; and that fact draws hundreds of millions of people to the parks each year. But more changes are on the way for the National Parks in 2026 and visitors aren&#8217;t likely to be happy with all of them.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Scanned 3I/ATLAS for Alien Signals. Here&#8217;s What They Found</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-scanned-3i-atlas-for-alien-signals-heres-what-they-found-2000704975</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704975</guid>
      <description>As this interstellar object approached its closest point to Earth, a massive radio telescope attempted to sniff out a technosignature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok is undressing anyone, including minors</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/853191/grok-explicit-bikini-pictures-minors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T14:52:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853191</guid>
      <description>xAI's Grok is removing clothing from pictures of people without their consent following this week's rollout of a feature that allows X users to instantly edit any image using the bot without needing the original poster's permission. Not only does the original poster not get notified if their picture was edited, but Grok appears to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billion-dollar Bitcoin hacker Ilya Lichtenstein thanks Trump for early prison release</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/853160/ilya-lichtenstein-released-razzlekhan-bitcoin-hack</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T14:51:18-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853160</guid>
      <description>Just over a year after being sentenced to five years in prison for the theft of billions of dollars in Bitcoin, hacker Ilya Lichtenstein is free. Lichtenstein announced his release in a post on X, specifically crediting Trump: "Thanks to President Trump's First Step Act, I have been released from prison early. I remain committed [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are Engadget's CES 2025 winners now?</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/where-are-engadgets-ces-2025-winners-now-194500216.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">025a0611-285f-4f20-bd88-7a3ad88494da</guid>
      <description>With CES 2026 slated to officially start next week, the focus is understandably on all the new products that will be announced at this year's event. But before diving into what&#8217;s new, we thought it was a good idea to revisit our best of show winners from last year to see where they're at. After all, CES is synonymous with vaporware. The good news is the Engadget team has a keen sense for BS. Of the ones we awarded at CES 2025 that&#160;haven&#8217;t&#160;been released, most are coming this year. For the remaining few, we&#8217;ll be hunting them down this CES.ASUS Zenbook A14An Asus Zenbook A14 sits out a patio tab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE's new Smart Refrigerator automates grocery shopping with a barcode scanner and Instacart</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/kitchen-tech/ges-new-smart-refrigerator-automates-grocery-shopping-with-a-barcode-scanner-and-instacart-194326610.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde0a3bb-d76b-45b7-8d70-0ac9df5a8db1</guid>
      <description>Smart fridges are a dime a dozen at CES, and LG and Samsung have thoroughly explored what's possible when you connect your fridge to the internet or slap a touchscreen on the front. The new GE Profile Smart Refrigerator with Kitchen Assistant GE is announcing ahead of CES 2026 doesn't reinvent the wheel in that regard, but it does include a first: a built-in barcode scanner for adding items to your shopping list.GE's "Scan-to-List" feature uses the barcode scanner to quickly (and precisely) add items to a shareable shopping list in GE's SmartHQ app. You can refer to that list while you're shop...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Spent the Holidays Asking Grok to Generate Sexual Images of Children</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/people-spent-the-holidays-asking-grok-to-generate-sexual-images-of-children-2000704919</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704919</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's xAI has largely been silent on the matter, but some authorities have noticed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD is slowly turning into Intel of yesteryear as $501 32-thread Ryzen 9 7950X is just enough to beat 20-thread $270 Core Ultra 7 265KF &#8212; so what's going on?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/amds-slowly-turning-into-intel-of-yesteryear-as-usd501-32-thread-ryzen-9-7950x-is-just-enough-to-beat-20-thread-usd270-core-ultra-7-265kf-so-whats-going-on</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JHLqAJsfVHKSj6c89wHUtU</guid>
      <description>Intel&#8217;s Core Ultra 7 pricing exposes how AMD&#8217;s high end desktop CPUs now offer smaller performance gains despite far higher prices and power requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the LG press conference at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/how-to-watch-the-lg-press-conference-at-ces-2026-monday-190159561.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6eb7981-0913-4e7b-bd66-4bc9abdcb17b</guid>
      <description>LG
For years, LG has opened CES press day with the first event of the morning &#8212; and 2026 will be no exception. The Korea-based corporation is theming this year's presentation as "Innovation in Tune with You," and &#8212; if past shows are any indication &#8212; it will highlight both the consumer electronics and large appliance sides of its mammoth global businesses.
As with many tech-focused events nowadays, AI is expected to serve as the unifying thread of LG's CES 2026 presentation. That said, LG &#8212; much like Apple &#8212; has its own take on the acronym, referring to it as "Affectionate Intelligence." The co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Duffer Brothers Took Inspiration From &#8216;Lord of the Rings&#8217; for the &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; End Credits</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-season-5-finale-end-credits-dnd-lord-of-the-rings-2000704937</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704937</guid>
      <description>'Dungeons &amp;Dragons' was the obvious reference, but Peter Jackson's fantasy trilogy also played a hand in how the Netflix series wrapped up its final episode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January 2026 full &#8216;wolf moon&#8217;: Look up tonight to see the dazzling first supermoon of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468562/full-wolf-moon-january-2026-see-first-supermoon-tonight</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T19:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468562/full-wolf-moon-january-2026-see-first-supermoon-tonight</guid>
      <description>Skywatchers are in for a treat this weekend as the winter supermoon will be easier to see than normal. Here&#8217;s what to know and when to see it.
This new year comes with a new moon. Skywatchers are in for a treat this weekend as 2026 rings in the first supermoon of the year, along with a Quadrantid meteor shower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordle today: Answer, hints for January 3, 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/wordle-today-answer-january-3-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00fd1CCabufeF6GEYGU2097</guid>
      <description>Here's the answer for "Wordle" #1658 on January 3 as well as a few hints, tips, and clues to help you solve it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the AMD CES 2026 keynote live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-amd-ces-2026-keynote-live-190012078.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c864a817-a6e7-423f-ab33-fb69dbcbdab4</guid>
      <description>AMD is kicking off CES 2026 on Monday, where it'll cover its latest AI developments and perhaps show off its newest Ryzen chips. The company will outline the full scope of its vision for AI implementations from across the full spectrum of consumer and enterprise applications. The presentation &#8212; which is the lead keynote for CES 2026 &#8212; will be led by CEO Dr. Lisa Su.
We'll tell you how to tune in to the livestream and what else you can expect to see.
How to watch AMD's keynote live
Dr. Su will deliver a keynote speech from the Palazzo Ballroom at the Venetian on Monday, January 5 at 9:30PM ET (...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Gian van Veen vs Gary Anderson: live stream 2026 PDC World Darts Championship semifinal online for *FREE*</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/gian-van-veen-vs-gary-anderson-2026-pdc-world-darts-championship-semifinal-free</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wmMzAy8JDptuVonhMfqedA</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch Gian van Veen take on Gary Anderson in the second World Darts Championship semifinal at Ally Pally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is planning to revamp the &#8216;president&#8217;s golf course&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468652/trump-presidents-golf-course-andrews</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468652/trump-presidents-golf-course-andrews</guid>
      <description>Trump has visited Andrews in the past, but the White House and military base have no record of him playing the courses.
President&#160;Donald Trump&#160;has spent much of his two-week vacation in Florida golfing. But when he gets back to the White House, there&#8217;s a military golf course that he&#8217;s never played that he&#8217;s eyeing for a&#160;major construction project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman wants to pay some lucky person $555,000 a year to look after OpenAI's AI - but obviously, all is not quite as it seems</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/sam-altman-wants-to-pay-some-lucky-person-usd555-000-a-year-to-look-after-openais-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5kr3bcXyCnTuLub7qdP9NL</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is hiring a new head to look after model abuse and safety for $555k plus equity, but it'll be high-stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's base Kindle is $20 off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/amazons-base-kindle-is-20-off-right-now-183302484.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9865d5d-82c0-47b4-858f-2d61df88bf8c</guid>
      <description>The latest entry-level Kindle ereader is on sale for $90 via Amazon. This is a nice discount of $20. It's not a record-low price, but it's certainly a budget-friendly way to keep that New Year's resolution to read more.
This made our list of the best ereaders, and for good reason. It's an iconic device that gets the job done. It doesn't have much by way of modern bells and whistles, but it ships with 16GB of storage and comes in two snazzy colorways. 


The build is compact and durable. It's also light, which makes it easy to pack and easy to hold up with one hand. It allows access to the vast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble Revives and Revamps Its Short-Lived Circular Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pebble-revives-and-revamps-its-short-lived-circular-smartwatch-2000704903</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704903</guid>
      <description>If you loved the old Pebble Time Round, the new Round 2 smartwatch is better in every way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pebble unveils Pebble Round 2 &#8212; and fixes all the original's major pitfalls</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/pebble-unveils-pebble-round-2-and-fixes-all-the-originals-major-pitfalls</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VdhzrXmL8ZpYF5P8ooWXvd</guid>
      <description>Pebble Round 2 is official &#8212; we can't believe we have to wait until May for this huge do-over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, new site: how to launch on a budget this weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-hosting/new-year-new-site-how-to-launch-on-a-budget-this-weekend</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">L3c2UzE2s6VcdVW8zQAbET</guid>
      <description>How to create a website on a budget before the end of the first weekend of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 million Americans started 2026 with a pay raise</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468496/8-3-million-americans-started-2026-with-a-pay-raise</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468496/8-3-million-americans-started-2026-with-a-pay-raise</guid>
      <description>Workers in states from California to New York saw minimum wage increases take effect Thursday.
A new year has brought a new pay rate for more than 8.3 million Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India orders Musk&#8217;s X to fix Grok over &#8216;obscene&#8217; AI content</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/02/india-orders-musks-x-to-fix-grok-over-obscene-ai-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079459</guid>
      <description>India's IT ministry has given X 72 hours to submit an action-taken report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickle AR Glasses seem to promise a real-life version of Jarvis. The internet is skeptical.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/pickle-ar-glasses-learn-how-you-live-ai-companion</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05uNRlVXEXjncZvhDBvTDTF</guid>
      <description>A startup claims its AI-powered AR glasses can see, remember, and anticipate your life, but skeptics aren't sure the technology is quite ready.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
