<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:48:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Cybercab Program Manager Exits, Brags About Pushing the Boundaries of Safety</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-cybercab-program-manager-exits-brags-about-pushing-the-boundaries-of-safety-2000727134</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727134</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's xAI has also seen a number of departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI-generated Resident Evil Requiem review briefly made it on Metacritic</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/an-ai-generated-resident-evil-requiem-review-briefly-made-it-on-metacritic-194414929.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a6afb98-195e-496a-9169-b0f47fa77c16</guid>
      <description>Review aggregator Metacritic has removed a review of Resident Evil Requiem because it was AI-generated, Kotaku reports. The review was published by UK gaming site VideoGamer, but appears to be "written" by a fake AI journalist rather than a real person.While it's unfortunately difficult to confirm with 100 percent accuracy whether a piece of text is AI-generated, you don't have to read VideoGamer's review for long to notice all the ways it feels off. The biggest giveaway, beyond heavy use of contrived metaphors, is a striking lack of detail beyond what you could glean from a trailer for the ga...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory shortage could cause the biggest smartphone shipments dip in over a decade</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/memory-shortage-could-cause-the-biggest-smartphone-shipments-dip-in-over-a-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097542</guid>
      <description>IDC says phone makers will ship only 1.12 billion smartphones as compared to 1.26 billion last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&amp;#8217;s F1 series Drive to Survive will stream on Apple TV, too</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/streaming/885538/netflix-f1-drive-to-survive-apple-tv-streaming</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:40:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885538</guid>
      <description>Netflix's sports docuseries obsession started a few years ago with F1: Drive to Survive, but when the eighth season premieres after midnight tonight, it will also be available on Apple TV. Now that Apple TV has a five-year deal to be the US streaming home for F1 races, subscribers in the US will be able [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsair is halting Drop sales after March 25th</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/884824/corsair-ending-drop-shopping-site</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:34:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884824</guid>
      <description>The Drop store, which was acquired by gaming gear giant Corsair in 2023, was a haven for mechanical keyboard enthusiasts and audiophiles to discover and buy hard-to-find gear - sometimes at surprisingly good prices. The company will cease sales after March 25th at 11:59PM PT, which is also the cut off to redeem Drop Rewards. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new $25 action game from the creator of Just Cause arrives on April 8</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/the-new-25-action-game-from-the-creator-of-just-cause-arrives-on-april-8-193058294.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a63981a4-05f8-4b38-abc3-1bd44d27344d</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re still waiting for releases dates for Remedy&#8217;s in-development Max Payne remakes, but if you&#8217;re in need of a noir fix sooner than that, keep an eye on Liquid Swords&#8217; Samson: A Tyndalston Story, which just got a release date of April 8.
The debut game from a new studio formed by Just Cause creator Christofer Sundberg, Samson looks like a tighter, more narrative-led experience than Avalanche&#8217;s proudly ridiculous open-world series, but no less packed with over-the-top action. You play as the eponymous Samson McRay, a man down on his luck and seriously in debt in the punishing city of Tyndalst...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple and Netflix are teaming up to share Formula 1 programming</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/apple-and-netflix-are-teaming-up-to-share-formula-1-programming-192829498.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5015a81-21b4-47ba-9443-43fa1411a455</guid>
      <description>Apple and Netflix have entered into a rather surprising partnership. The dynamic streaming duo will share Formula 1 programming, according to The Hollywood Reporter. The deal allows Netflix to stream the F1 Canadian Grand Prix in May, along with Apple TV. On the flipside, Apple TV and Netflix will both air season eight of the docuseries Drive to Survive.
The Netflix-created series spotlights various F1 drivers and their teams. The season premieres at midnight on both platforms. Eddy Cue, Apple&#8217;s senior VP of services, said that Netflix "has played a pivotal role in growing F1 since the launch ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prices of AMD's popular Ryzen 5 series doubled since February 1st to $400 &#8212; nobody knows why, but here's what may have happened</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/prices-of-amds-popular-ryzen-5-series-doubled-since-february-1st-to-usd400-nobody-knows-why-but-heres-what-may-have-happened</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Tt29QDT3A6LDXntdR39odM</guid>
      <description>AMD Ryzen 5 prices doubled to $400 in February 2026 amid memory shortages, wafer constraints, and thinning retail inventory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral AI inks a deal with global consulting giant Accenture</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/mistral-ai-inks-a-deal-with-global-consulting-giant-accenture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097539</guid>
      <description>Mistral AI lands a partnership with Accenture, the consultant that has also recently announced partnerships with rivals OpenAI and Anthropic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eBay will lay off 800 workers, or 6 percent of its staff</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/ebay-will-lay-off-800-workers-or-6-percent-of-its-staff-191500844.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c814602-aeaf-40c5-b434-6c35f816cfba</guid>
      <description>eBay announced that it is cutting about 800 jobs from its global staff. "We are taking steps to reinvest across our business and align our structure with our strategic priorities, which will affect certain roles across our workforce," the retailer said in a statement as reported by Bloomberg. This move will see about 6 percent of eBay's current full-time workers laid off. Bloomberg noted that eBay would continue hiring in "key areas" but did not specify what those fields are.The downsizing follows a week of business updates for eBay. On the same day it shared its latest financial results, the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO says iPhones are secure enough to handle classified data</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885516/nato-iphones-ipads-restricted-classified-information</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T14:08:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885516</guid>
      <description>The iPhone and iPad have been approved to hold NATO-restricted information, according to an announcement on Thursday. That means off-the-shelf devices running iOS 26 and iPadOS 26 can handle classified information "without requiring special software or settings," Apple says. The NATO-restricted designation is the lowest level of classified information, and it applies to information that [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le t&#233;lescope James-Webb r&#233;v&#232;le un &#171; cr&#226;ne &#187; cosmique dont on devine le cerveau !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-telescope-james-webb-revele-crane-cosmique-on-devine-cerveau-131713/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-telescope-james-webb-revele-crane-cosmique-on-devine-cerveau-131713/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>L'astre ressemblant &#224; un cerveau appel&#233; PMR 1 a &#233;t&#233; surnomm&#233; la n&#233;buleuse du &#171; Cr&#226;ne expos&#233; &#187; par les scientifiques de la d&#233;funte mission Spitzer, avec un t&#233;lescope spatial observant dans l'infrarouge. Cette n&#233;buleuse plan&#233;taire, situ&#233;e &#224; environ 5 000 ann&#233;es-lumi&#232;re dans la constellation des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about streaming F1 on Apple TV</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/everything-you-need-to-know-about-streaming-f1-on-apple-tv-190600771.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d802e22-feb0-438c-84ed-01e8df49578a</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;ve known Apple would follow up its blockbuster film F1: The Movie with live coverage of F1 races in 2026. Now that we&#8217;re approaching the first grand prix weekend of the year, the company has provided details on what fans can expect to see inside the Apple TV app and beyond. There&#8217;s already a dedicated F1 channel in the Apple TV app, which is where you&#8217;ll stream races live when the time comes. You can also watch practice sessions, sprint races and both pre- and post-race coverage. Apple offers a number of additional F1 videos there (I&#8217;d recommend watching the one on the new rules) and you&#8217;ll...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On &#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217;, the Theater Kids Are All Right</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-recap-episode-8-tilly-2000726815</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726815</guid>
      <description>And also returning 'Discovery' star Sylvia Tilly. But mostly the theater kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neanderthal Men and Human Women Were Most Likely to Hook Up, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/neanderthal-men-and-human-women-were-most-likely-to-hook-up-study-finds-2000726658</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726658</guid>
      <description>Geneticists have found an interesting pattern in how early humans and Neanderthals interbred&#8212;and it wasn't balanced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You &#8216;Agentic&#8217; Enough for the AI Era?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/silicon-valley-agentic-individuals-future-of-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699ca89387b4ddbea4d1c6a0</guid>
      <description>Silicon Valley built AI coding agents that can handle most of the grunt work. Now, the most valuable skill in tech is deciding what they should do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 prompts for Gemini 3.1 that really show off what it can do</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/gemini/5-prompts-for-gemini-3-1-that-really-show-off-what-it-can-do</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cMMGJkovvWQ74KcDKFSxD</guid>
      <description>Showcasing Gemini 3.1 Pro's most impressive features</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta sues advertisers in Brazil and China over 'celeb bait' scams</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-sues-advertisers-in-brazil-and-china-over-celeb-bait-scams-190000268.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88ee3eff-08ff-4e55-9039-e876ca0e4132</guid>
      <description>Meta has sued the people and groups behind three scam operations that used images and deepfakes of celebrities to lure users to scam websites. According to the company, the three entities were based in China and Brazil and targeted people in the US, Japan and other countries. The ads promoted fraudulent investment schemes and fake health products.Meta said that it had filed lawsuits against several people in Brazil who promoted fake or unapproved healthcare products and online courses promoting them. The company also sued a China-based entity it says used ads featuring celebrities "as part of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's still in our portfolio. We're not end of life [on] the product': Samsung exec on why the Galaxy S25 Edge is so important and here to stay</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/its-still-in-our-portfolio-were-not-end-of-life-the-product-samsung-exec-on-why-the-galaxy-s25-edge-is-so-important-and-here-to-stay</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aU2Cags5TnnuY8SPQ5cNBS</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S26 Edge was a no-show at Galaxy Unpacked, but there are a few very good reasons, and reasons for hope about an edgy future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambient Dreamie bedside companion review: The best sleep I've had in years</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/ambient-dreamie-bedside-companion-review-the-best-sleep-ive-had-in-years-184019430.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b13a64a6-5b23-4dab-9d51-06c398d7b5fe</guid>
      <description>How much would you pay for a good night's sleep? This is a question I've asked myself repeatedly over the last few weeks as I've been testing the Dreamie, a $250 alarm clock and "bedside companion" that I couldn't stop thinking about after I first encountered it at CES.
Ambient's Dreamie offers many of the conveniences of a smartphone-connected device &#8212; highly customizable alarm schedules, a library of soundscapes and noise masks, Bluetooth so you can connect earbuds and podcasts (soon). But it is phone-free every step of the way, with all controls and features built-in so you don't end up get...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security experts flag multiple issues in Claude Code, warning, 'As AI integration deepens, security controls must evolve to match the new trust boundaries'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/security-experts-flag-multiple-issues-in-claude-code-warning-as-ai-integration-deepens-security-controls-must-evolve-to-match-the-new-trust-boundaries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WDUMgbQSt7MXDCfTUPQWrR</guid>
      <description>An AI assistant can quickly turn into a malicious insider, so be careful with permissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide et automutilation | Instagram va avertir les parents si un jeune effectue des recherches &#224; r&#233;p&#233;tition</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-26/suicide-et-automutilation/instagram-va-avertir-les-parents-si-un-jeune-effectue-des-recherches-a-repetition.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:24:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecd2ba8b1ef7383cb7df96f1243570dc</guid>
      <description>Instagram va pr&#233;venir les parents ayant activ&#233; la supervision du compte de leur adolescent s&#8217;il effectue des recherches &#224; r&#233;p&#233;tition sur le suicide ou l&#8217;automutilation, a annonc&#233; jeudi le r&#233;seau social dans un communiqu&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts surpass AM/FM talk radio in U.S. for first time, Edison Research find</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499417/podcasts-surpass-am-fm-talk-radio-in-u-s-for-first-time-edison-research-find</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T18:16:56</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499417/podcasts-surpass-am-fm-talk-radio-in-u-s-for-first-time-edison-research-find</guid>
      <description>Podcasts now account for 40% of spoken-word listening, edging past radio&#8217;s 39% as video viewing surges.
For the first time in history, podcasts have overtaken talk radio as the most-listened-to medium for spoken-word audio in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eBay layoffs today: 6% of jobs cut days after buying Depop from Etsy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499335/ebay-layoffs-today-job-cuts-after-etsy-depop-acquisition-ai-investments</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T18:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499335/ebay-layoffs-today-job-cuts-after-etsy-depop-acquisition-ai-investments</guid>
      <description>The e-commerce retailer is downsizing its workforce by 800 employees as it shifts &#8216;strategic priorities,&#8217; and continues to invest in AI.
eBay is laying off about 800 employees, or 6% of its full-time workforce, saying the move is a push to align with its &#8220;strategic priorities.&#8221; It comes a week after the company announced it was acquiring second-hand clothing app Depop from rival Etsy for&#160;$1.2 billion....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazfit's affordable, 5-star Apple Watch rival just got a surprise sequel &#8212; and it promises 'meaningful progress' for runners</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/amazfits-affordable-5-star-apple-watch-rival-just-got-a-surprise-sequel-and-it-promises-meaningful-progress-for-runners</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gBZJ7ZEJ6yJCujdzkFmmYa</guid>
      <description>The Amazfit Active 3 Premium is here, and it looks as though you get a lot for your money once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The difference between conviction and guesswork</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91498679/the-difference-between-conviction-and-guesswork</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T18:02:54</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91498679/the-difference-between-conviction-and-guesswork</guid>
      <description>Product analytics tools, coupled with AI, work best when data foundations are consistent.
AI has not changed the importance of judgment in product leadership. What it has changed is the cost of getting it wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comment les panneaux solaires am&#233;liorent la laine des moutons</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2991961_comment-les-panneaux-solaires-ameliorent-la-laine-des-moutons</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/energie/batteries-et-panneaux-solaires/2991961_comment-les-panneaux-solaires-ameliorent-la-laine-des-moutons</guid>
      <description>
Certains &#233;leveurs ovins observent une am&#233;lioration de la qualit&#233; de la laine et une hausse de leurs recettes. Leur secret ? Des panneaux solaires install&#233;s sur leurs p&#226;turages, qui modifient les conditions d&#8217;&#233;levage.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Look at &#8216;Star City&#8217; Is Here, and Apple TV&#8217;s Spin-Off Era Has Officially Begun</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-city-apple-tv-for-all-mankind-spinoff-2000727121</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727121</guid>
      <description>Set in the world of 'For All Mankind,' the new space race thriller is told from the Soviet Union's point of view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. mortgage rate dips below 6% for the first time since 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91499454/mortgage-rates-housing-interest-financing-home-2</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91499454/mortgage-rates-housing-interest-financing-home-2</guid>
      <description>It could encourage prospective home shoppers who can afford to buy at current rates to shop for a home this spring.
The average long-term U.S. mortgage rate slipped this week below 6% for the first time since late 2022, good news for home shoppers as the spring homebuying season gets rolling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads is testing a shortcut to quickly start DM conversations</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/26/threads-is-testing-a-shortcut-to-quickly-start-dm-conversations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3097473</guid>
      <description>Users who are part of the test can type "DM me" or "Message me" in a post or reply to automatically generate a hyperlink that invites others to start a private conversation with them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at Samsung Unpacked: The Galaxy S26 Ultra, Galaxy Buds 4 and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/everything-announced-at-samsung-unpacked-the-galaxy-s26-ultra-galaxy-buds-4-and-more-180000530.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa960099-5089-40d9-a330-75f5056aaa69</guid>
      <description>Mobile World Congress is right around the corner, but Samsung got out ahead of many rivals that will be showing off new handsets at that event by running the latest edition of Unpacked on Wednesday. At its event in San Francisco&#8217;s Palace of Fine Arts, the company revealed the Galaxy S26 lineup, which includes the base S26, the S26+ and the S26 Ultra. We've got some hands-on time with all three handsets as well, and you can read about our in-person experience with the Galaxy S26 Ultra, as well as our S26 and S26+ impressions in those articles.In addition to those, Samsung announced the Galaxy B...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
