<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:28:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Physical Store Experiment Has Failed</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazons-physical-store-experiment-has-failed-2000714638</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714638</guid>
      <description>Amazon is taking its brick-and-mortar business and going home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive identity theft campaign targeting Okta single sign-on at over 100 top businesses - make sure your firm stays safe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/massive-identity-theft-campaign-targeting-okta-single-sign-on-at-over-100-top-businesses-make-sure-your-firm-stays-safe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UikTHs3LkLWfqoNoJa8AEZ</guid>
      <description>Scattered LAPSUS$ Hunters are targeting major firms with sophisticated voice phishing attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sennheiser debuts new models of wired headphones and earbuds</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/sennheiser-debuts-new-models-of-wired-headphones-and-earbuds-201245058.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7923fcd3-eae9-4c61-9d58-8bc236c4ce7d</guid>
      <description>Wireless audio has become the industry standard, but there are still options out there for people who prefer a wired connection. Two new choices joining the market come from Sennheiser, which has released the CX 80U wired earbuds and HD 400U wired over-ear headphones. These new takes on the company's previous models for wired listening have replaced the 3.5mm audio jack connector with a USB-C cable. Both sets support 24-bit, 96 kHz digital audio playback. They're compatible with a broad array of devices, including iOS, iPadOS, Android, ChromeOS, MacOS, Windows and SteamOS.&#160;Both of these items ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L'atmosph&#232;re vue comme jamais auparavant : comment ce nouveau satellite m&#233;t&#233;o change la donne</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/meteosat-atmosphere-vue-comme-jamais-auparavant-ce-nouveau-satellite-meteo-change-donne-130522/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:01:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/meteosat-atmosphere-vue-comme-jamais-auparavant-ce-nouveau-satellite-meteo-change-donne-130522/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Aujourd'hui, &#224; la Conf&#233;rence spatiale europ&#233;enne &#224; Bruxelles, les premi&#232;res images du sondeur m&#233;t&#233;orologique infrarouge europ&#233;en ont &#233;t&#233; d&#233;voil&#233;es, marquant une avanc&#233;e significative dans notre capacit&#233; &#224; surveiller les fluctuations atmosph&#233;riques avant et pendant les &#233;v&#233;nements m&#233;t&#233;orologiques...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Coogler Has Always Been the Guy to Root For</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ryan-coogler-has-always-been-the-guy-to-root-for-2000713781</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713781</guid>
      <description>Audiences have been wanting the 'Sinners' and 'Black Panther' director to get his day in the sun from the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 50 Best Shows on HBO Max, WIRED&#8217;s Picks (February 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/hbo-max-best-shows-to-stream-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">640802cca1c135ecdb12cf5f</guid>
      <description>A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms, The Pitt, and Industry are just a few of the shows you need to be watching on HBO Max this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornhub will become unavailable for many UK users as of February 2</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/pornhub-will-become-unavailable-for-many-uk-users-as-of-february-2-194622124.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64be2271-df01-4ecc-a6eb-e0827fced3ee</guid>
      <description>Pornhub will stop offering full access to new users in the UK on February 2, its parent company Aylo said Tuesday, citing the nation's Online Safety Act and its age-verification requirements. The company said users who already verified their ages before the cutoff will still be able to access the adult site through existing accounts.
The move follows the Online Safety Act&#8217;s Protection of Children Codes, which took effect last summer and require adult sites to use "highly effective" methods of age verification. Aylo claims the system is backfiring and shifting both adults and minors to noncompl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok joins Snap to settle social media addiction lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/27/tiktok-joins-snap-to-settle-social-media-addiction-lawsuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086707</guid>
      <description>Jury selection begins Tuesday as this case moves closer to trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer&#8217;s testing a new tool for customizing its keyboards in your browser</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/868843/razer-synapse-web-beta-browser-chromium-configure-settings</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T14:38:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868843</guid>
      <description>Razer has announced the beta release of a new online customization tool compatible with several versions of its Huntsman V3 Pro keyboards at launch. Razer Synapse Web isn't a full replacement for the company's Synapse 4 desktop app. It's instead designed to be a streamlined alternative accessible through a browser for situations where you're not [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom Is the First Casualty in France&#8217;s War on American Big Tech</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/zoom-is-the-first-casualty-in-frances-war-on-american-big-tech-2000714545</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714545</guid>
      <description>Homebrewed video conferencing may not be a moonshot, but you gotta start somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer confidence in the U.S. economy falls to lowest level since 2014</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481991/consumer-confidence-economy-spending-inflation-conference-board</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481991/consumer-confidence-economy-spending-inflation-conference-board</guid>
      <description>&#8216;The dramatic drop on confidence is a direct result of the hiring recession.&#8217;
U.S. consumer confidence declined sharply in January, hitting the lowest level since 2014 as Americans grow increasingly concerned about their financial prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple and Google reportedly still offer dozens of AI &#8216;nudify&#8217; apps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/apple-and-google-reportedly-still-offer-dozens-of-ai-nudify-apps-192712446.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3483249-cac8-4770-aa8a-036a5118cd6d</guid>
      <description>A recent investigation by an online advocacy organization called the Tech Transparency Project (TTP) found that the Apple App Store and Google Play Store are rife with so-called "nudify" apps. These are AI applications that create nonconsensual and sexualized images, which is a clear violation of both companies' store policies.
All told, the investigation found 55 of this type of app in the Google Play Store and 47 in the Apple App Store. Both platforms also still offer access to xAI's Grok, which is likely the most famous nonconsensual deepfake maker in the world.
"Apple and Google are suppos...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is closing its grocery stores. Here&#8217;s what it&#8217;s building instead</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481811/amazon-is-closing-its-grocery-stores-heres-what-its-building-instead</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T19:22:28</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481811/amazon-is-closing-its-grocery-stores-heres-what-its-building-instead</guid>
      <description>The company says customer behavior, not store performance, is driving a major shift toward online grocery and Whole Foods growth.
Amazon will double down on the Whole Foods brand, killing two of its own physical retail experiments in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon UK slashes the price of Blink, Ring, Fire TV, Kindle and Echo devices &#8212; here are the 12 best deals I'd buy from &#163;13.99 to upgrade my home</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/amazon-uk-slashes-the-price-of-blink-ring-fire-tv-kindle-and-echo-devices-here-are-the-12-best-deals-id-buy-from-gbp13-99-to-upgrade-my-home</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xo5fxg6rceYHuFCLBW3y2b</guid>
      <description>There's a big sale on Amazon Devices right now at Amazon UK, so I've gathered together 12 of the best deals on smart home tech and gadgets starting from &#163;13.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UpScrolled and Skylight rising: Users race to TikTok alternatives after U.S. takeover</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481890/upscrolled-skylight-tiktok-alternatives-surge-after-us-takeover-censorship-anti-ice-videos</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T19:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481890/upscrolled-skylight-tiktok-alternatives-surge-after-us-takeover-censorship-anti-ice-videos</guid>
      <description>Downloads of new short-form video apps are surging after TikTok&#8217;s ownership change, amid allegations the platform censored anti-Trump content.
Downloads of UpScrolled, a&#160;new&#160;short-form video app, are surging after TikTok&#8217;s recent change to U.S. ownership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Alexa+ Is Now Available to Everyone. Here&#8217;s How to Turn It Off (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/alexa-plus-early-access-rollout-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6971123a9ce7149baee42b25</guid>
      <description>Alexa+ has been rolling out to everyone with a Prime membership, even if you didn&#8217;t ask for it. Here&#8217;s how to change it back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is AI adoption at work flatlining? This major survey thinks so - but it's definitely not the end just yet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/is-ai-adoption-at-work-flatlining-this-major-survey-thinks-so-but-its-definitely-not-the-end-just-yet</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZBWeufrAsex8efX932CDt8</guid>
      <description>The number of people using AI might be flatlining, but it looks like we'll see more uses cases develop next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos introduces Amp Multi for complicated residential installs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/sonos-introduces-amp-multi-for-complicated-residential-installs-191000421.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61b9fdd2-95a6-4818-be19-8af52e686d49</guid>
      <description>Sonos has unveiled its first new product of 2026, the Amp Multi. This amplifier is a niche option for the owners of very large or complicated spaces, and it's being billed as professional grade option for residential audio installations. The Amp Multi has eight 125W outputs and four configurable zones, and each channel can support up to three Sonos Architectural speakers. In other words, that's a lot more audio than the average home needs. Even the Sonos Amp would probably be overkill for those of you living the apartment life.The Amp Multi will be available "in the coming months," according t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. population growth rate drops last year amid Trump&#8217;s immigration crackdown</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481986/census-bureau-immigration-trump-us-population</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T19:05:59</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481986/census-bureau-immigration-trump-us-population</guid>
      <description>The immigration drop dented growth in several states that traditionally have been immigrant magnets.
President Donald Trump&#8217;s&#160;crackdown on immigration&#160;contributed to a year-to-year drop in the nation&#8217;s growth rate as the U.S. population reached nearly 342 million people in 2025, according to population estimates released Tuesday by the U.S. Census Bureau....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#8216;Puppet Girl&#8217; of &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; on Doing a Performance Within a Performance</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-puppet-girl-of-a-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-on-doing-a-performance-within-a-performance-2000713659</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713659</guid>
      <description>Tanzyn Crawford plays Tanselle, a Dornish artist, in the new 'Game of Thrones' spin-off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting Against Elon Musk&#8217;s Predictions on Polymarket Might be the New Inverse Cramer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/betting-against-elon-musks-predictions-on-polymarket-might-be-the-new-inverse-cramer-2000714552</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714552</guid>
      <description>Easy money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA home office trends for 2026: freshen up your workspace with sage green and crisp white &#8212; from just $5</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/ikea-home-office-trends-for-2026-freshen-up-your-workspace-with-sage-green-and-crisp-white-from-just-usd5</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VMVMhBdb8z5fEK358dNxnC</guid>
      <description>IKEA's latest collection of office accessories, lighting, and furniture will bring a breath of spring to your working day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's no telescope this large ever built. It's not like we have a precedent for how to do these things,' Giant Magellan Telescope engineers on why they used the Unreal Engine to build an unprecedented telescope simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/inside-giant-magellan-telescopes-unreal-engine-based-bob-simulation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hou6mqdtLb7qJPWfafxCb3</guid>
      <description>The Giant Magellan Telescope under construction in Chile will help us find exoplanets &#8212; but before that, there's a complete, operating replica built in Unreal Engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon shutters all of its physical Go and Fresh stores</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/868800/amazon-go-and-fresh-stores-closed</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:55:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868800</guid>
      <description>Amazon Go and Fresh physical store locations will soon be no more, with Amazon announcing on Tuesday that it's closing up the majority of the stores and converting others into Whole Foods Market locations. Customers will still be able to order from Amazon Fresh online, but won't be able to shop at physical stores with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Feature-Packed Earbuds Are Less Than $50</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/anker-soundcore-a40-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6978fedb7a840e550e16b6df</guid>
      <description>Anker knocks almost half the cost off its already budget-friendly earbuds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cet &#233;cran PC gamer 34&#8243; MSI ultra-&#233;quip&#233; (QD-OLED, 240 Hz) ne d&#233;passe pas les 700 &#8364; pendant ces soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2956395_cet-ecran-pc-gamer-34-msi-ultra-equipe-qd-oled-240-hz-ne-depasse-pas-les-700-e-pendant-ces-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2956395_cet-ecran-pc-gamer-34-msi-ultra-equipe-qd-oled-240-hz-ne-depasse-pas-les-700-e-pendant-ces-soldes</guid>
      <description>
Pour profiter d'une exp&#233;rience de jeu bien fluide et r&#233;active, il n'y a pas de myst&#232;re : un moniteur gaming dot&#233; d'une configuration solide est indispensable. Le MSI MPG 341CQPX en est justement un, et pendant les soldes d'hiver 2026, vous le trouverez affich&#233; &#224; 699,99 euros au lieu de 999,99 euros chez Darty et Cdiscount.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The French government is ditching Zoom and Microsoft Teams for a home-grown alternative</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/the-french-government-is-ditching-zoom-and-microsoft-teams-for-a-home-grown-alternative-184747010.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcbd4ff3-d78b-43ce-93fe-c75bd8f27a1f</guid>
      <description>The French government is saying au revoir to Microsoft Teams and Zoom as it embraces a home-grown alternative. By next year, civil servants across all departments will have switched to French videoconference platform Visio, as EuroNews reports.As with Teams and Zoom, Visio has an AI-powered transcription tool. Visio runs on a French company's cloud infrastructure as well. The platform has around 40,000 users and it's been in testing for the last year. The government expects the switch to help reduce costs by as much as &#8364;1 million ($1.2 million) each year for every 100,000 users.The decision to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok settles to avoid major social media addiction lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/tiktok-settles-to-avoid-major-social-media-addiction-lawsuit-183943927.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abcc6c37-37ca-4e5e-8875-a91aaac1cd59</guid>
      <description>TikTok has reached a settlement in a closely-watched lawsuit over social media addiction, narrowly avoiding a trial that's scheduled to begin jury selection Tuesday. Terms of the deal, which was reported by The New York Times, weren't disclosed.&#160;TikTok's settlement comes about one week after Snap reached a settlement in the same case. The trial is expected to move forward in Los Angeles with Meta and YouTube as the only defendants. Mark Lanier, a lawyer for the plaintiff, said in a statement to NYT that they were "pleased" with the settlement and that it was "a good resolution." TikTok didn't ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State-Led Crackdown on Grok and xAI Has Begun</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-state-led-crackdown-on-grok-and-xai-has-begun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6965700bc9e9698ec20c258f</guid>
      <description>At least 37 attorneys general for US states and territories are taking action against xAI after Grok generated a flood of nonconsensual sexual images of women and minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;An issue that has gone unaddressed for too long': Major US city takes bold decision to ban single-use printer cartridges but will others follow suit?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/an-issue-that-has-gone-unaddressed-for-too-long-major-us-city-takes-bold-decision-to-ban-single-use-printer-cartridges-but-will-others-follow-suit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7PCKjmdvbXbe9hy4uz7vNH</guid>
      <description>A proposed ban on single-use ink cartridges in Los Angeles exposes the hidden environmental and financial cost of home printing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Data Shows Robotaxis Competing on Price&#8212;and Speed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-data-shows-robotaxis-competing-on-price-and-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977aa218ad4d08d0dc3c326</guid>
      <description>Research from the ride-hail aggregator Obi finds Waymo is starting to edge up on Uber and Lyft in San Francisco. Tesla, which operates a ride-hail service with human drivers, is winning the price wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A former Netflix game studio went indie to reach more players</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/868711/spry-fox-netflix-game-studio-indie-spirit-crossing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=868711</guid>
      <description>When Netflix first acquired cozy game developer Spry Fox in 2022, it made a lot of sense. The studio had been around for over a decade and had several hits with mobile games like Triple Town and Alphabear. That approachable style of puzzle game seemed like a good fit for Netflix's mobile-first strategy, and, as [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philip Glass cancels Kennedy Center symphony premiere to protest Trump&#8217;s leadership</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481979/philip-glass-kennedy-center-cancellations</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-27T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481979/philip-glass-kennedy-center-cancellations</guid>
      <description>Glass was a Kennedy Center honoree in 2018.
Prize-winning composer Philip Glass has called off a scheduled world premiere at the&#160;Kennedy Center&#160;of a symphony about Abraham Lincoln, the latest in a wave of cancellations since&#160;President Donald Trump&#160;ousted the previous leadership.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
