<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:40:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Prime members can play Alan Wake 2 for free on Luna</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/prime-members-can-play-alan-wake-2-for-free-on-luna-193509728.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9904cee3-d222-4aa5-9089-d48b73b5d73f</guid>
      <description>If you haven't yet played Alan Wake 2, here's your chance to immerse yourself in its terrors for free. Prime members can play it this month on Amazon's Luna cloud gaming service at no additional charge.The "fantastic" Alan Wake 2 oozes "psychedelic terror," as Engadget's Jessica Conditt put it in our review. The 2023 horror-survival game uses a dual-protagonist motif, alternating between the lost author Wake and the stoic FBI agent Saga Anderson. It "tells a twisted, serpentine story of paranormal murder, shifting realities and demonic possession, with two brooding investigators at its core." ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is giving its AI slop feed an app of its own</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/meta-is-giving-its-ai-slop-feed-an-app-of-its-own-192208200.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae196e01-d9e3-453b-9509-1b8bb7bb2e92</guid>
      <description>Meta is developing a standalone app for Vibes, its feed of AI-generated videos, according to reports from TechCrunch and Platformer. Vibes was introduced as a feature in the Meta AI app in September 2025. Similar to OpenAI's Sora app, Vibes lets users prompt Meta AI to create TikTok-style vertical videos."Following the strong early traction of Vibes within Meta AI, we are testing a standalone app to build on that momentum," Meta said in a statement. "We&#8217;ve seen that users are increasingly leaning into the format to create, discover, and share AI-generated video with friends. This standalone ap...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nintendo Switch 2 proved me wrong in several ways, and it's why I'd suggest buying it now before price hikes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nintendo/the-nintendo-switch-2-proved-me-wrong-in-several-ways-and-its-why-id-suggest-buying-it-now-before-price-hikes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jnMjn7X859gLHMFAdgiXe6</guid>
      <description>I've been surprised by the Nintendo Switch 2 after trying it, and since it could see a price hike soon, now's the best time to make a move for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Hail Mary is getting its own LEGO set</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/project-hail-mary-is-getting-its-own-lego-set-191106809.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c0a7c33-20d2-47bd-8cbe-d19f8121196c</guid>
      <description>The upcoming science fiction film Project Hail Mary is getting a LEGO set. This is fascinating because LEGO typically makes sets based on long-standing franchises like Star Wars and Harry Potter. Project Hail Mary doesn't even hit theaters until March 20.
It's not an entirely new IP. The movie is based on a 2021 book written by Andy Weir, the same author behind The Martian. It's cool to see a LEGO set based on something more contemporary than its usual fare. 
The 830-piece set looks pretty nifty. It includes a replica of The Hail Mary spaceship in all of its glory, complete with minifigures of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg considered changing how Meta studies social issues after research got it in trouble</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/874176/meta-zuckerberg-new-mexico-email-teen-girls-research</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T14:10:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874176</guid>
      <description>One day after The Wall Street Journal published a blockbuster story about Meta's own dismal findings about teen girls' mental health on Instagram, CEO Mark Zuckerberg wondered whether Meta should change how it studies its platforms' potential harms. "Recent events have made me consider whether we should change our approach to research and analytics around [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xikipedia Wants to Take the &#8216;Doom&#8217; Out of &#8216;Doomscrolling&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/xikipedia-wants-to-take-the-doom-out-of-doomscrolling-2000718582</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718582</guid>
      <description>An endless feed of random Wikipedia articles might be just what your soul needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laurence Fishburne Is the Latest Big Name to Join Mike Flanagan&#8217;s &#8216;The Exorcist&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/laurence-fishburne-is-the-latest-big-name-to-join-mike-flanagans-the-exorcist-2000718590</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718590</guid>
      <description>The 'Matrix' legend has joined the star-studded cast for Flanagan's all-new take on the horror classic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Great Deals on WIRED-Approved Valentine's Day Gifts (2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/valentines-day-deals-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6983b9aef9b07994b9bc156c</guid>
      <description>These swoon-worthy deals on WIRED-tested date night boxes, sex toys, and other gadgets will make your Valentine's Day extra sweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Europe&#8217;s largest universities knocked offline for days after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/one-of-europes-largest-universities-knocked-offline-for-days-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090016</guid>
      <description>An alleged ransomware attack has taken down the systems of the Sapienza University of Rome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Guess What Creature Won the Close-Up Photographer of the Year Competition?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/can-you-guess-what-creature-won-the-close-up-photographer-of-the-year-competition-2000718411</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718411</guid>
      <description>We'll give you a hint: It lives underwater, but it doesn't swim. At least, not as an adult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 'feature-stuffed pocket rocket' of a Garmin watch is at its lowest price ever &#8211; perfect timing for warmer spring runs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/this-feature-stuffed-pocket-rocket-of-a-garmin-watch-is-at-its-lowest-price-ever-perfect-timing-for-warmer-spring-runs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ummeGLVz8H3eq2RaoMdLoh</guid>
      <description>If you're a seasonal runner, the Garmin Vivoactive 6 is just what you need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk is getting serious about orbital data centers</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/elon-musk-is-getting-serious-about-orbital-data-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089928</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re starting to see the idea of Musk-owned orbital AI data clusters cohere into an actual plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La PlayStation 5 devrait &#233;chapper &#224; une nouvelle augmentation de prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2968103_la-playstation-5-devrait-echapper-a-une-nouvelle-augmentation-de-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2968103_la-playstation-5-devrait-echapper-a-une-nouvelle-augmentation-de-prix</guid>
      <description>
Enfin une bonne nouvelle concernant la p&#233;nurie de m&#233;moire vive et de stockage. Sony aurait suffisamment fait de stocks pour &#233;viter d'augmenter le prix de la PS5.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CIA stops publishing The World Factbook</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-cia-stops-publishing-the-world-factbook-184419024.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f201e526-d149-44ce-b629-22e2f55b2bf7</guid>
      <description>The US Central Intelligence Agency is ending one of its popular services, The World Factbook. Over the decades, this reference has provided readers with information about different countries and communities around the world. The post from the CIA announcing the news didn't provide any information about why it will stop offering The World Factbook. The agency was subject to the same buyouts and job cuts that decimated much of the federal workforce in 2025, so maybe this type of public-facing tool is no longer a priority.&#160;This reference guide was first published in 1962 as The National Basic Int...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How data centers provided power during Winter Storm Fern</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486037/how-data-centers-provided-power-during-winter-storm-fern</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:44:07</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486037/how-data-centers-provided-power-during-winter-storm-fern</guid>
      <description>Before Wright&#8217;s order, it was hard to say whether data centers would reduce the amount of electricity they take from the grid during storms or other emergencies.
As Winter Storm Fern swept across the United States in late January 2026, bringing ice, snow, and freezing temperatures, it left more than a million people without power, mostly in the Southeast....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2026 Winter Olympics Will Have a Major Impact on the Region&#8217;s Snow</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/winter-olympics-2026-impacts-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69754fb4162ea64cf574981d</guid>
      <description>A recent report found that carbon emissions caused by the Milano Cortina Olympics could lead to the loss of 5.5 square kilometers of snowpack and millions of metric tons of glacial ice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapt&#233; aux t&#226;ches bureautiques, ce Lenovo IdeaPad Slim 3 avec Windows 11 Mode S chute sous les 200 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967833_adapte-aux-taches-bureautiques-ce-lenovo-ideapad-slim-3-avec-windows-11-chute-sous-les-200-e</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2967833_adapte-aux-taches-bureautiques-ce-lenovo-ideapad-slim-3-avec-windows-11-chute-sous-les-200-e</guid>
      <description>
Le Lenovo IdeaPad Slim 3 est un laptop qui tend &#224; accomplir les principales t&#226;ches du quotidien gr&#226;ce &#224; son Windows 11 Mode S et son Intel Celeron. Chez Amazon, il perd 150 euros et tombe &#224; seulement 199,99 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch France vs. Ireland online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/france-ireland-six-nations-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05p67o3U0HrYju1dWDBsr8t</guid>
      <description>Watch the Six Nations for free. Live stream France vs. Ireland in the 2026 Six Nations for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof hosting providers renting cheap infrastructure to supply virtual machines to ransomware hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/bulletproof-hosting-providers-renting-cheap-infrastructure-to-supply-virtual-machines-to-ransomware-hackers</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K3FmWA2Eh9WJ8UwrwRTwTD</guid>
      <description>Most high-profile ransomware groups were using the same Russian-based infrastructure for years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla driver&#8217;s chilling 911 call transcript: &#8216;It&#8217;s on fire. Help please.&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/tesla-driver-911-call-transcript-on-fire</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03ZHQnUQFJCn5c2NIFnO5Qv</guid>
      <description>A new lawsuit includes a horrifying transcript of a 911 call made from inside a burning Tesla vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the best laptop power banks available is cheaper than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/874509/anker-laptop-power-bank-google-pixel-watch-4-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:34:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874509</guid>
      <description>If you often travel with your gadgets, a fast, reliable portable battery like Anker&#8217;s Laptop Power Bank is a worthwhile purchase. Right now, you can buy the silver model at its all-time low price of $87.99 ($47 off) from Anker via Newegg when you apply promo code ENCF232 at checkout. Alternatively, the black color scheme [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to stream the 2026 Super Bowl for free: Patriots vs. Seahawks time, where to watch and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-stream-the-2026-super-bowl-for-free-patriots-vs-seahawks-time-where-to-watch-and-more-124512202.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b2b14-4380-47f2-9cb8-bd2dfe744915</guid>
      <description>The 2026 Super Bowl between the New England Patriots and the Seattle Seahawks will air on NBC this Sunday, Feb. 8. The game will also stream on Peacock. If you don't have NBC over the air and don't subscribe to Peacock, there are still ways to watch Super Bowl LX &#8212; and Bad Bunny's history-making halftime show &#8212; for free. Here's how to tune in.&#160;
How to watch Super Bowl LX free:




Date: Sunday, Feb. 8
Time: 6:30 p.m. ET
Location: Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, Calif.
TV channel: NBC, Telemundo
Streaming: Peacock, DirecTV, NFL+ and more
2026 Super Bowl game channel
Super Bowl LX will air on NBC...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA astronauts can now bring their phones with them on their mission to the moon</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/nasa-astronauts-can-now-bring-their-phones-with-them-on-their-mission-to-the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089951</guid>
      <description>Get ready for some selfies that are out of this world. Crew-12 is expected to head to the International Space Station next week, while the highly anticipated Artemis II mission -- which will bring humans around the moon for the first time since the 1960s -- was delayed until March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of the World's Largest Gay Dating App</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-in-china-how-people-in-china-learn-what-they-can-say-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69836bf7cb78795d1881df66</guid>
      <description>The new book The Wall Dancers explores the uneasy relationship between Chinese internet users and a government that is always watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested several cases for the Switch 2 and these are the best</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/reviews/691319/best-switch-2-cases</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:19:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=691319</guid>
      <description>You might find it kind of sad to put your hard-earned Switch 2 into a protective case. To me, it&#8217;s freeing. Sure, it can take away from the slick design. But using a case relieves me of the worry that the console will accumulate tons of little scratches, or worse. I&#8217;ve tested several types of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl LX ads: all AI everything</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/874504/super-bowl-lx-ads-big-game</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:18:34-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=874504</guid>
      <description>Super Bowl LX is nearly here, with the Seattle Seahawks taking on the New England Patriots. While Bad Bunny will be the star of the halftime show, AI could be the star of the commercial breaks, much like crypto was a few years ago. Last year&#8217;s Super Bowl featured a Google Gemini ad that fumbled [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Notta Memo and ditched handwritten notes for searchable AI transcripts</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/notta-memo-ai-voice-recorder-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8UA4j56bH6bKReJeJkdgPT</guid>
      <description>The Notta Memo is a compact AI voice recorder that attaches to the back of your mobile phone, recording audio and using AI to transcribe, summarise, and translate with the aid of the companion app, making it a far superior option than a notepad for meetings, lectures, and everyday note-taking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer Wants to Sell You a $1,337 Gaming Mouse</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/razer-wants-to-sell-you-a-1337-gaming-mouse-2000718577</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718577</guid>
      <description>Remember the 1999 Boomslang mouse? Now, you can once again fondle one of a limited set of 1,337.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI launches&#160;a way for enterprises to build and&#160;manage AI agents</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/openai-launches-a-way-for-enterprises-to-build-and-manage-ai-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090000</guid>
      <description>OpenAI launched Frontier, a new platform designed for enterprises to build and deploy agents while treating them like human employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Latest Apple Watch Is $100 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/apple-watch-11-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6984cf92681463fce33e7294</guid>
      <description>Upgrade to a full day of battery life and new health features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Switch 2-exclusive co-op adventure Orbitals launches this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/the-switch-2-exclusive-co-op-adventure-orbitals-launches-this-summer-180657892.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbea459b-85e0-454c-a217-fba2e400e3e1</guid>
      <description>Nintendo capped off today&#8217;s partner-focused Nintendo Direct with a flurry of Bethesda-related announcements, but arguably the most interesting game of the showcase appeared right at the start.
First announced at the beginning of the year, Orbitals is a two-player puzzle adventure game in which you and your co-op partner play as the intergalactic explorers Maki and Omura, on a mission to save their home in the stars from an incoming cosmic storm. Gameplay-wise, Orbitals looks like it&#8217;s at least partly inspired by the likes of It Takes Two&#160;and Split Fiction, but really what really stands out her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Tried Drilling Into Antarctica&#8217;s &#8216;Doomsday Glacier,&#8217; But the Ice Had Other Plans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-tried-drilling-into-the-doomsday-glacier-but-the-ice-had-other-plans-2000718421</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718421</guid>
      <description>A project that has been years in the making came to an early halt about 3,000 feet deep in the ice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean energy jobs were soaring during the Biden era. Not anymore</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487088/clean-energy-jobs-were-soaring-during-the-biden-era-not-anymore</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487088/clean-energy-jobs-were-soaring-during-the-biden-era-not-anymore</guid>
      <description>Some 38,000 jobs, mostly in manufacturing, were erased from the sector last year, according to a new analysis. Some may never be recovered.
In 2024, the clean energy sector saw a job boom: The industry added nearly 100,000 new jobs throughout that year, meaning clean energy jobs grew more than three times faster than the rest of the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Director of &#8216;Masters of the Universe&#8217; Promises It&#8217;ll Be Silly</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-director-of-masters-of-the-universe-promises-itll-be-silly-2000718567</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718567</guid>
      <description>'Bumblebee' director Travis Knight knows that He-Man and friends are a little goofy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who&#8217;s who and what&#8217;s what in TVs in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/874138/tv-manufacturer-technology-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874138</guid>
      <description>Each TV company has its own distinct personality and direction. These change over the years, with new technological breakthroughs or at least new business deals. New aspirations shake up the natural order. This year, for example, nearly every company has decided to make and heavily promote RGB LED TVs. Some of them, like Hisense, seem [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude has been having a moment &#8212; can it keep it up?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/874308/anthropic-claude-code-opus-hype-moment</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874308</guid>
      <description>Boris Cherny gets recognized in public relatively often. At the bar, at the airport, and in generally any public space, people want to take selfies with the creator and head of Claude Code. For the last couple of months, Anthropic's Claude and its coding platform have been having a moment - on social media, in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic debuts new model with hopes to corner the market beyond coding</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/874440/anthropic-opus-4-6-new-model-claude</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874440</guid>
      <description>Anthropic's "smartest model" is getting a major boost, the company said in a blog post announcing Claude Opus 4.6. It called the new model a "direct upgrade" from its predecessor in a release, noting that it can better take on complex, multi-step tasks and get "much closer to production-ready quality on the first try than [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get two years of access to Proton VPN for 70 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/get-two-years-of-access-to-proton-vpn-for-70-percent-off-right-now-123000460.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dac4d6ed-e475-4c0c-80c0-7c390227395c</guid>
      <description>Proton VPN is offering a steep discount on its Proton VPN Plus subscription, with the two-year plan currently priced at $2.99 per month. You&#8217;ll pay $72 upfront for 24 months of service, which amounts to 70 percent off the usual monthly rate and brings the long-term cost well below what many premium VPNs typically charge.We&#8217;ve consistently been impressed by Proton VPN&#8217;s focus on privacy, its nonprofit ownership structure and the way it balances security features with strong real-world speeds. It&#8217;s a top pick in our best VPN guide, and this promotion also appears in our running list of the best ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s GPT-5.3-Codex drops as Anthropic upgrades Claude &#8212; AI coding wars heat up ahead of Super Bowl ads</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/openais-gpt-5-3-codex-drops-as-anthropic-upgrades-claude-ai-coding-wars-heat</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bMZILyIrXUF5kCTDaQkWY</guid>
      <description>OpenAI on Wednesday released GPT-5.3-Codex, which the company calls its most capable coding agent to date, in an announcement timed to land at the exact same moment Anthropic unveiled its own flagship model upgrade, Claude Opus 4.6. The synchronized launches mark the opening salvo in what industry observers are calling the AI coding wars &#8212; a high-stakes battle to capture the enterprise software development market.The dueling announcements came amid an already heated week between the two AI giants, who are also set to air competing Super Bowl advertisements on Sunday, and whose executives have ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Iger just left his Disney successor a disaster in the making</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486060/bob-iger-just-left-disney-successor-josh-damaro-disaster-in-the-making</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486060/bob-iger-just-left-disney-successor-josh-damaro-disaster-in-the-making</guid>
      <description>Iger doesn&#8217;t understand AI. That&#8217;s created a problem for new CEO Josh D&#8217;Amaro&#8212;and Disney itself.
Bob Iger doesn&#8217;t understand generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does your workplace look like this? If not, mothers may not want to work there</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487048/does-your-workplace-look-like-this-if-not-mothers-may-not-want-to-work-there</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487048/does-your-workplace-look-like-this-if-not-mothers-may-not-want-to-work-there</guid>
      <description>Even employers with generous parental leave benefits fail to fully address the unique transformation many working mothers are navigating when they return to work. 
In certain corners of corporate America, a generous parental leave policy has become a crucial tool for recruiting and retention. Many of the biggest tech employers have been leaders on this front, offering 16 to 20 weeks of leave, or even close to six months at companies like Google.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Novo Nordisk stock fell 7% after a telehealth startup&#8217;s announcement</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487685/why-novo-nordisk-stock-fell-7-after-a-telehealth-startups-announcement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487685/why-novo-nordisk-stock-fell-7-after-a-telehealth-startups-announcement</guid>
      <description>Hims &amp; Hers will sell a compounded version of the new Wegovy pill for a fraction of the price, claiming a legal workaround to U.S. patent protection.
Novo Nordisk&#8217;s stock dove 7% on Thursday just after an announcement from a key competitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings drop to lowest level since 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487805/job-openings-december-labor-economy-ai-layoffs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487805/job-openings-december-labor-economy-ai-layoffs</guid>
      <description>December job openings were lower than economists had forecast.
U.S. job openings fell to the lowest level in more than five years, another sign that the American labor market remains sluggish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's Super Bowl TV sale is offering some of the best prices I've seen &#8212; here are 11 deals that I'm recommending to family and friends</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/best-buys-super-bowl-tv-sale-is-offering-some-of-the-best-prices-ive-seen-here-are-11-deals-that-im-recommending-to-family-and-friends</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HELrDb4wDEYG4NBVJmocbE</guid>
      <description>Best Buy's Super Bowl TV sale is ending soon, and I'm rounding up my 13 favorite deals that I'm recommending to family and friends on best-rated 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's Presidents' Day appliance sale starts early &#8212; here are the deals I'd buy for a premium kitchen upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/best-buys-presidents-day-appliance-sale-starts-early-here-are-the-deals-id-buy-for-a-premium-kitchen-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6isMmhd4UxSJokBwKyzHcM</guid>
      <description>The Best Buy Presidents' Day appliances sale is now underway with savings of up to 40%, free gift cards and package discounts all up for grabs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic releases Opus 4.6 with new &#8216;agent teams&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/05/anthropic-releases-opus-4-6-with-new-agent-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089523</guid>
      <description>The newest version of Anthropic's model is designed to broaden its capabilities and appeal, allowing for a greater variety of uses and customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab&#8217;s comically large new headphones are actually wearable portable speakers &#8212; and theyre only $100</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jlab-blue-xl-speaker-headphones-where-to-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04sOpw2oMOgDPQNuhtBiDRf</guid>
      <description>The JLab Blue XL Speaker Headphones are wearable portable speakers that look like huge headphones. You can buy a pair for $100.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirDrop pour tous : Google veut ouvrir la fonction d&#8217;Apple &#224; d&#8217;autres smartphones Android</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2968025_airdrop-pour-tous-google-veut-ouvrir-la-fonction-dapple-a-dautres-smartphones-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2968025_airdrop-pour-tous-google-veut-ouvrir-la-fonction-dapple-a-dautres-smartphones-android</guid>
      <description>
Davantage de smartphones vont pouvoir go&#251;ter au partage de fichiers simplifi&#233; entre appareils gr&#226;ce &#224; Google.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLab's comically oversized headphones are not an April Fool's Prank</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/jlabs-comically-oversized-headphones-are-not-an-april-fools-prank-174338833.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9588dd3-a71c-488b-8286-7ec134078a90</guid>
      <description>JLab just released a gigantic pair of headphones that doubles as a Bluetooth speaker. The Blue XL headphones are ridiculously oversized, making them headphones in name only. I don't even think Andre the Giant could've comfortably worn these suckers.
Unless you have a mythically large head, these are basically "headphone speakers." The idea is to drape them around your neck and stream tunes for all to hear. Though you could also pop them on a table or something. I prefer my Bluetooth speakers to be speaker-shaped, but maybe that's just me.
JLab
As for the internals, they feature 30W of power an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snag the budget-friendly Nothing Ear (a) wireless earbuds for their lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-5-nothing-ear-a-wireless-earbuds-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01HlwHHNchgeKY3FjzUl4lH</guid>
      <description>As of Feb. 5, get the budget-priced Nothing Ear (a) wireless earbuds for their lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move over, Mac mini: Geekom A9 Max brings Ryzen AI power, 32GB RAM, and 2TB storage, all for under $1100</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/move-over-mac-mini-geekom-a9-max-brings-ryzen-ai-power-32gb-ram-and-2tb-storage-all-for-under-usd1100</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HD8LHTwV9PDzcJQNDA37uU</guid>
      <description>The Geekom A9 Max mini PC delivers serious AI-accelerated performance in a compact, upgradeable, office-ready design.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
