<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:33:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>India&#8217;s Varaha bags $20M to scale carbon removal from the Global South</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/indias-varaha-bags-20m-to-scale-carbon-removal-from-the-global-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089090</guid>
      <description>Varaha's fresh funding is part of a $45 million Series B round led by WestBridge Capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD hints Microsoft could launch its next-gen Xbox in 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/873490/microsoft-next-gen-xbox-console-2027-date-amd</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T18:22:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873490</guid>
      <description>Microsoft confirmed last year that it's working on a next-gen Xbox console in partnership with AMD. Now, AMD is hinting that the next Xbox console, which will use custom AMD chips, could be launching in 2027. "Development of Microsoft's next-gen Xbox, featuring an AMD semi-custom SoC, is progressing well to support a launch in 2027," [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is back up after an outage disrupted use this afternoon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/chatgpt-is-back-up-after-an-outage-disrupted-use-this-afternoon-210238686.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d88f72-a1b8-4f16-b13d-8dfe2dc59834</guid>
      <description>If you had trouble using ChatGPT today, you aren't alone. The AI chatbot experienced a partial outage for many users this afternoon, with Down Detector saw reports reaching more than 12,000 reports around the peak point of the issue today.. OpenAI issued a status update shortly after noting that "elevated error rates" were occurring for ChatGPT and Platform users. That problem was marked as resolved at 5:14PM ET.While the initial outage may be repaired, OpenAI does still have an active status alert up. It's only for the fine-tuning component of its API service. But the end may also be in sight...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scripts for David Lynch&#8217;s Never-Made Netflix Pitch May Soon Be Published</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-scripts-for-david-lynchs-never-made-netflix-pitch-may-soon-be-published-2000717427</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717427</guid>
      <description>The director's daughter, Jennifer Lynch, said the scripts for 'Unrecorded Night' could be made public soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve spent 15 hours in Highguard, but I'm not desperate to play any more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/highguard-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rpZMexG2dcN2Ez7MM4WWxg</guid>
      <description>Highguard feels fantastic to play, but it's a few major updates away from being the online shooter it wants to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen3-Coder-Next offers vibe coders a powerful open source, ultra-sparse model with 10x higher throughput for repo tasks</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/qwen3-coder-next-offers-vibe-coders-a-powerful-open-source-ultra-sparse</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ZoSefBKKEqtBvKTuSuh2I</guid>
      <description>Chinese e-commerce giant Alibaba's Qwen team of AI researchers has emerged in the last year as one of the global leaders of open source AI development, releasing a host of powerful large language models and specialized multimodal models that approach, and in some cases, surpass the performance of the proprietary U.S. leaders such as OpenAI, Anthropic, Google and xAI.Now the Qwen team is back again this week with a compelling release that matches the "vibe coding" frenzy that has arisen in recent months: Qwen3-Coder-Next, a specialized 80-billion-parameter model designed to deliver elite agenti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything we know about Chris Pratts Way of the Warrior Kid</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/way-of-the-warrior-kid-apple-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03czPWHx3rxFZ2pk6whMz3u</guid>
      <description>Chris Pratt stars in "Way of the Warrior Kid," about a Navy SEAL who teaches his nephew to defend himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Department of Justice appeals Google search monopoly ruling</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/873438/google-antitrust-case-doj-states-appeal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T17:40:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873438</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, the Department of Justice and the plaintiffs in the antitrust case against Google filed a cross-appeal, as the DOJ Antitrust Division announced in a post on X: "Today, the DOJ Antitrust Division filed notice that it will cross-appeal from the remedies decisions in its case against Google's unlawful monopolization of internet search and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take-Two hit pause on the Switch 2 port of Borderlands 4</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/take-two-hit-pause-on-the-switch-2-port-of-borderlands-4-222546776.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">581b52b5-c4e1-4610-b7ad-f2376a0f5006</guid>
      <description>2K owner Take-Two has paused development on Borderlands 4 for the Nintendo Switch 2, the company shared during its Q3 2026 earnings presentation. The Switch 2 port was originally planned to be released on October 3, 2025, a few weeks after the game's September 12 launch on all other platforms, but was indefinitely delayed on September 23."We made the difficult decision to pause development on that SKU," Take-Two told Variety. "Our focus continues to be delivering quality post-launch content for players on the ongoing improvements to optimize the game. We&#8217;re continuing to collaborate closely wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slopaganda goes West</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/873400/nick-shirley-somali-daycares-san-diego-california-youtube</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T17:23:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873400</guid>
      <description>After right-wing YouTuber Nick Shirley's viral video alleging fraud at Minnesota daycares he said were operated by Somali residents, Donald Trump's administration responded by flooding the state with federal immigration agents and freezing funding for childcare services. (A judge ruled that the federal government must continue funding childcare subsidies, at least temporarily.) Now Shirley is [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Minneapolis tech community holds strong during &#8216;tense and difficult time&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/minnesota-tech-community-founders-investors-ice-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089192</guid>
      <description>Founders and investors in the Minneapolis tech industry told TechCrunch they've put much of their work on hold to help out their community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Its official: The Switch is Nintendos highest-selling console ever</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nintendo-switch-best-selling-console-history-ds-ps2</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">012rold1ZnVkW9sxwCmu4bb</guid>
      <description>Nintendo's latest earnings report confirmed something we suspected: The original Switch is its most successful hardware ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Hill says his new Apple TV movie &#8216;uses fame as a metaphor for what we all go through on social media&#8217; &#8211; here&#8217;s what we know so far about Outcome</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/apple-tv-plus/jonah-hill-says-his-new-apple-tv-movie-uses-fame-as-a-metaphor-for-what-we-all-go-through-on-social-media-heres-what-we-know-so-far-about-outcome</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">E6WDKrVNMQZTepxvT8eB3j</guid>
      <description>Apple TV revealed that Jonah Hill&#8217;s new movie Outcome will premiere globally on April 10, 2026, and it&#8217;s gone straight to the top of my watchlist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Sanderson Reveals His Journey to Make a &#8216;Cosmere&#8217; Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/brandon-sanderson-reveals-his-journey-to-make-a-cosmere-adaptation-2000717505</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717505</guid>
      <description>The fantasy author opens up on pitching the 'Cosmere' universe to streamers and making the adaptations he wants to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain to Ban Under-16s on Social Media as the World Goes All in on Age Verification</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spain-to-ban-under-16s-on-social-media-as-the-world-goes-all-in-on-age-verification-2000717515</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717515</guid>
      <description>Spain, Australia, and other countries are pushing social media age crackdowns to protect kids from the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything we know about pickleball comedy The Dink</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/the-dink-apple-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07aayzOX5hbBqq7BYkfaonH</guid>
      <description>Jake Johnson and Mary Steenburgen play pickleball players in "The Dink," out July 24 on Apple TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s Quest 3 Has the First VR Keyboard That Doesn&#8217;t Totally Suck</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/metas-quest-3-has-the-first-vr-keyboard-that-doesnt-totally-suck-2000717467</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717467</guid>
      <description>A new experimental feature actually makes typing in XR feel doable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox browser to add AI off-switch, bucking industry trend</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/mozilla-announces-firefox-ai-controls</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">047RH0yYs7pvJ5kX39KWD4H</guid>
      <description>Mozilla will add a new AI control panel to Firefox &#8212; giving AI haters the option to turn off generative AI features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 3-Body Problem Just Got an Upgrade&#8212;and You Can Thank Einstein</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-3-body-problem-just-got-an-upgrade-and-you-can-thank-einstein-2000717348</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717348</guid>
      <description>A double sunset appears to be a true rarity in the cosmos, and general relativity explains why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8220;It&#8217;s nonsense&#8221;: Jensen Huang says reports of friction between Nvidia and OpenAI are false</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/its-nonsense-jensen-huang-says-reports-of-friction-between-nvidia-and-openai-are-as-strong-as-ever</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7WoAwaszbPEfexpuVDsr2i</guid>
      <description>Jensen Huang rejects reports of tension between his company and OpenAI, reiterating that Nvidia will invest heavily in the AI firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the JBL Boombox 4 and it's a wonderful party companion &#8212; but one minor flaw holds it back from audio perfection</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/jbl-boombox-4-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LGtnoKzBdv3FhzeKjbtW6F</guid>
      <description>The JBL Boombox 4 is a premium party speaker that delivers killer sound with punchy bass and superb battery life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borderlands 4 for Switch 2 is on &#8216;pause&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/873409/borderlands-4-nintendo-switch-2-development-pause</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T16:56:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873409</guid>
      <description>Development on the Nintendo Switch 2 version of Borderlands 4 is on "pause," according to a statement from a Take-Two spokesperson given to Variety. "We made the difficult decision to pause development on that SKU," Take-Two spokesperson Alan Lewis said in the statement published by Variety. "Our focus continues to be delivering quality post-launch content [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the Messy Drama Between OpenAI and Nvidia, Explained</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/all-the-messy-drama-between-openai-and-nvidia-explained-2000717226</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717226</guid>
      <description>The future of a $100 billion Nvidia-OpenAI agreement is looking murky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An &#8216;Intimacy Crisis&#8217; Is Driving the Dating Divide</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/justin-garcia-the-intimate-animal-sex-and-relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6977a6f98ad4d08d0dc3c324</guid>
      <description>In his book The Intimate Animal, sex and relationships researcher Justin Garcia says people have miscalculated their need for human intimacy, which is the real issue at the root of the loneliness epidemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melinda French Gates Appears to Confirm Divorce With Bill Was Related to Epstein</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/melinda-french-gates-appears-to-confirm-divorce-with-bill-was-related-to-epstein-2000717434</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717434</guid>
      <description>"I had to leave my marriage," Melinda Gates told NPR after being asked about the newly released emails.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
