<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:42:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos could have saved the Washington Post&#8217;s local news and sports reporters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/876834/bezos-washington-post-sports-local-reporters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T18:34:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/876834/this-town-2-0</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator, a newsletter for Verge subscribers about tech politicking in the age of Trump. If you're a subscriber, you are dominant and talented, like the Seattle Seahawks. If you're not a subscriber yet, it's time to get your act together, like the New England Patriots. (I'm from Boston and I'm allowed [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proc&#232;s de YouTube et Meta | Une psychiatre d&#233;crit les r&#233;seaux sociaux comme une &#171;&#160;drogue d&#8217;entr&#233;e&#160;&#187; pour les jeunes</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-02-10/proces-de-youtube-et-meta/une-psychiatre-decrit-les-reseaux-sociaux-comme-une-drogue-d-entree-pour-les-jeunes.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:34:16 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">975d22439dc9369ea292250c27d9c601</guid>
      <description>L&#8217;usage des r&#233;seaux sociaux constitue d&#233;sormais l&#8217;un des premiers comportements addictifs exp&#233;riment&#233;s par les jeunes, agissant comme une v&#233;ritable &#171;&#160;drogue d&#8217;entr&#233;e&#160;&#187; qui remod&#232;le leur cerveau au stade vuln&#233;rable du d&#233;veloppement, a t&#233;moign&#233; mardi une psychiatre am&#233;ricaine au proc&#232;s de YouTube et Meta &#224; Los&#160;Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon may launch a marketplace where media sites can sell their content to AI companies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/amazon-may-launch-a-marketplace-where-media-sites-can-sell-their-content-to-ai-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091683</guid>
      <description>A new report claims the e-commerce giant is looking to create a pipeline of licensable content between media publishers and AI companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NAACP is fighting back against AI data centers</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/naacp-data-centers</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">078r46P8PN9smcL3tgBzKIM</guid>
      <description>The infrastructure powering AI can cause severe environmental effects. Why should minority communities pay the price?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&#8217;s deep research tool adds a built-in document viewer so you can read its reports</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/876775/openai-deep-research-chatgpt-full-screen-report-viewer</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T18:02:32-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876775</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is updating ChatGPT's deep research tool with a full-screen viewer that you can use to scroll through and navigate to specific areas of its AI-generated reports. As shown in a video shared by OpenAI, the built-in viewer allows you to open ChatGPT's reports in a window separate from your chat, while showing a table [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Years Ago, &#8216;Deadpool&#8217; Made Wade Wilson the People&#8217;s Clown</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/10-years-ago-deadpool-made-wade-wilson-the-peoples-clown-2000715001</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715001</guid>
      <description>The R-rated superhero played by Ryan Reynolds made a splash in February 2016, and he's still a big part of pop culture today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s next Unpacked is confirmed for later this month</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876717/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-february-2026-s26</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876717</guid>
      <description>Samsung's annual Galaxy S-series reveal is later than usual this year, but we finally have a confirmed date to circle on the calendar: February 25th. And if you were hoping for major hardware upgrades from the company's flagship phones, you probably shouldn't hold your breath: an extensive leak published by WinFuture has seemingly confirmed that [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung just set the date for its first Galaxy Unpacked of 2026 &#8212; and all signs point to the Galaxy S26 with plenty of Galaxy AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/samsung-just-set-the-date-for-its-first-galaxy-unpacked-of-2026-and-all-signs-point-to-the-galaxy-s26-with-plenty-of-galaxy-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oW3WXNgrCnBHgG5oJHmfG7</guid>
      <description>Samsung has confirmed that its first Galaxy Unpacked event of 2026 will take place on February 25 in San Francisco, California, with the Galaxy S26 lineup expected to headline the show alongside a continued push around Galaxy AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's Galaxy S26 Unpacked event is on February 25</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsungs-galaxy-s26-unpacked-event-is-on-february-25-230000375.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13cdb2f5-5495-47f7-b38b-77296f22b89c</guid>
      <description>After kicking off CES 2026 with its "First Look" event, Samsung is ready to announce the first of what should be several new Galaxy smartphones this year. The company is officially hosting a Galaxy Unpacked event on February 25 at 1PM ET, where it'll introduce the Galaxy S26 series and updates to Galaxy AI.Leaks that have trickled out ahead of the event suggest that the Galaxy S26, S26+ and S26 Ultra will feature a new Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 5 chip, and could come with more RAM and storage. Only the Galaxy S26 Ultra is expected to include major hardware changes, though, with an updated camera ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung finally sets a date: Galaxy Unpacked is coming Feb. 25</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-galaxy-unpacked-february-2026-s26-announced</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036F6p0wsomLtbrygHXwGJp</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S26 lineup is almost here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple MacBook Air M4 is close to $150 off right now at Amazon &#8212; act fast to score this low price</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-10-13-inch-apple-macbook-air-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">050CuKLGR8P67AFOR8E7JB0</guid>
      <description>As of Feb. 10, the Apple 2025 13-inch MacBook Air (M4) is on sale at Amazon for $849.99, 15% off its list price of $999.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Microsoft Office 2021 and Windows 11 Pro bundle drops to under $50</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-10-the-ultimate-microsoft-office-professional-2021-for-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">004rnzOLY2S2RznNNxgTtke</guid>
      <description>Get Microsoft Office Professional 2021 and Windows 11 Pro with lifetime licenses for $44.97 for a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ice dance duo skated to AI music at the Olympics</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/olympics-czech-ice-dancers-duo-ai-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091561</guid>
      <description>Czech ice dancers Katerina Mrazkova and Daniel Mrazek are learning the hard way that LLMs sometimes spit out straight-up plagiarism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s new &#8216;Buy American&#8217; requirement for EV charging would dramatically curtail build-out</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/876703/trump-ev-charging-buy-american-nevi-funds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T17:30:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876703</guid>
      <description>It seems clear at this point to say that Donald Trump does not want to spend a single dime on EV charging. He tried to freeze $5 billion in funding for the National Electric Vehicle Infrastructure (NEVI) program, which was approved as part of the Bipartisan Infrastructure Law. And when a federal judge ordered the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Philips turntable with a CD player squirrelled away in its plinth and honestly, for this money it's hard to argue with the versatility</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/i-tested-the-philips-turntable-with-a-cd-player-squirrelled-away-in-its-plinth-and-honestly-for-this-money-its-hard-to-argue-with-the-versatility</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yPLwiaxiAqaK9ECcgbLwaB</guid>
      <description>In which Philips piles on the functionality without charging an arm and a leg &#8211;but is the Fidelio FT1 a music center for the 21st century?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Workers Circulate Open Letter Urging CEO Marc Benioff to Denounce ICE</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/letter-salesforce-employees-sent-after-marc-benioffs-ice-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698b9c4b3b8fbecbbb8fcffc</guid>
      <description>The letter comes after Benioff joked at a company event on Monday that ICE was monitoring international employees in attendance, sparking immediate backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barely any Microsoft 365 users are actually paying for Copilot - despite Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella claiming it is 'a true daily habit.'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/barely-any-microsoft-365-users-are-actually-paying-for-copilot-despite-microsoft-ceo-satya-nadella-claiming-it-is-a-true-daily-habit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Y5TMx3fRMD9qsjsteAzGYa</guid>
      <description>Microsoft claims rapid Copilot growth, yet only 3.3% of Microsoft 365 users pay, which raises questions over long-term AI investment returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checking in on Polymarket: Bets on Christ&#8217;s Return Jump on Bets That Bets on Christ&#8217;s Return Will Jump</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/checking-in-on-polymarket-bets-on-christs-return-jump-on-bets-that-bets-on-christs-return-will-jump-2000720298</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720298</guid>
      <description>Here's a prediction: this ends poorly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord will soon require age verification to access adult content</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/discord-will-soon-require-age-verification-to-access-adult-content-140000218.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16e72251-2944-4c39-8a63-dfa62eea200a</guid>
      <description>Discord is the latest company looking to bolster its child safety (again). Starting in March, all users will have a "teen-appropriate experience" by default. Unlocking adult content and age-gated spaces will require a (usually one-time) verification process. However, following blowback, the company appears to have pivoted. It now says its age prediction AI will verify the identities of &#8220;the majority of adult users&#8221; without requiring a manual age check.The platform's big safety update encompasses communication settings, restricted access to age-gated spaces and content filtering. Users who aren...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Founder&#8217;s Drone Startup Wins German Military Contracts</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spotify-favorite-drone-startup-wins-german-military-contracts-2000720249</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720249</guid>
      <description>A Peter Thiel-backed drone maker is also in the contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Is Using the &#8216;Game of Thrones&#8217; Theme Better Than &#8216;House of the Dragon&#8217; Ever Did</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-game-of-thrones-theme-2-2000720200</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720200</guid>
      <description>Even with the poop joke. Especially with the poop joke, even.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-Track Speed Skating at Winter Olympics 2026 Free Streams: TV Channels, Schedule, Preview</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/short-track-speed-skating-at-winter-olympics-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CCFeQ6bEbZPz2fFD3VDfVA</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Winter Olympics Short-Track Speed Skating 2026 live streams for FREE, with William Dandjinou and Arianna Fontana headlining the action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to get started with your spring clean? IKEA has the perfect sunny accessories to give you the motivation you need &#8211; from $2</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/struggling-to-get-started-with-your-spring-clean-ikea-has-the-perfect-sunny-accessories-to-give-you-the-motivation-you-need-from-usd2</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5tYsm89jWNgPiZzG4F5zZc</guid>
      <description>Kit yourself out with these colorful caddies, cloths and cleaners to get your home in ship shape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NLRB just gave up on SpaceX workers who claim they were illegally fired</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/the-nlrb-just-gave-up-on-spacex-workers-who-claim-they-were-illegally-fired-215332847.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73857ef4-b7ce-4232-8a6e-c99d0551893a</guid>
      <description>The National Labor Review Board (NLRB) has dropped a case accusing SpaceX of illegally firing eight employees who criticized the company's CEO Elon Musk, The New York Times. The employees were originally fired in 2022 after circulating a letter that referenced reports of Musk's sexual misconduct and called the executive "a frequent source of distraction and embarrassment." The NLRB filed a complaint claiming the firing was illegal in 2024.Originally, SpaceX's opposition to the NLRB's case was that the agency is unconstitutional, The New York Times writes. Complaints about the NLRB's independen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit&#8217;s AI health coach is now available on your iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876692/fitbit-ai-health-coach-public-preview-ios</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:42:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876692</guid>
      <description>Google announced on Tuesday that the public preview of Fitbit's AI personal health coach is rolling out to iOS users in the U.S. as well as both iOS and Android users in the UK, Canada, Australia, New Zealand, and Singapore. The update tests a major overhaul of Fitbit's app, introducing a conversational interface with a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
