<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:37:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit accuses ChatGPT of reinforcing delusions that led to a woman's death</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/lawsuit-accuses-chatgpt-of-reinforcing-delusions-that-led-to-a-womans-death-183141193.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63236523-f30e-4814-9f21-15cd0e5df80c</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has been hit with a wrongful death lawsuit after a man killed his mother and took his own life back in August, according to a report by The Verge. The suit names CEO Sam Altman and accuses ChatGPT of putting a "target" on the back of victim Suzanne Adams, an 83-year-old woman who was killed in her home.
The victim's estate claims the killer, 56-year-old Stein-Erik Soelberg, engaged in delusion-soaked conversations with ChatGPT in which the bot "validated and magnified" certain "paranoid beliefs." The suit goes on to suggest that the chatbot "eagerly accepted" delusional thoughts leading...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Launches 34,175-Mile AI Network That Acts Like One Massive Supercomputer</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/china-launches-34175-mile-ai-network-that-acts-like-one-massive-supercomputer-2000698474</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698474</guid>
      <description>If the system holds out long-term, it could significantly boost AI development in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoto&#8217;s new PixelDrive electric screwdriver is on sale for the first time</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/842687/hoto-pixeldrive-electric-screwdriver-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:18:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842687</guid>
      <description>Hoto&#8217;s PixelDrive electric screwdriver is designed to make everyday fixes a lot easier, and now it&#8217;s seeing its first discount. You can currently buy the sleek electric screwdriver for just $59.99 ($20 off) at Amazon. Despite its small size, the cordless PixelDrive delivers an adjustable 0.5&#8211;6Nm of torque, which is strong enough for assembling electronics, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's GPT-5.2 is here: what enterprises need to know</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-gpt-5-2-is-here-what-enterprises-need-to-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5AH2xqcQJzMolV09W5VM43</guid>
      <description>The rumors were true, and the "Code Red" is over: OpenAI today announced the release of its new frontier large language model (LLM) family: GPT-5.2.It comes at a pivotal moment for the AI pioneer, which has faced intensifying pressure since rival Google&#8217;s Gemini 3 LLM seized the top spot on major third-party performance leaderboards and many key benchmarks last month, though OpenAI leaders stressed in a press briefing that the timing of this release had been discussed and worked on well in advance of the release of Gemini 3.OpenAI describes GPT-5.2 as its "most capable model series yet for pro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is building an experimental new browser and a new kind of web app</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/842000/google-disco-browser-ai-experiment</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:10:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842000</guid>
      <description>The Chrome team at Google recently built a new browser. It takes a query or prompt, opens a bunch of related tabs for you, and then builds you a custom app for whatever you're trying to do. Ask it for travel tips and it'll build you a planner app; ask it for study help and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT&amp;#8217;s &#8216;adult mode&#8217; is expected to debut in Q1 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842657/openai-chatgpt-adult-mode-debut-q1-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:10:19-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842657</guid>
      <description>We've seen NSFW offerings from Grok and other chatbots, and OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has been teasing adult content within ChatGPT for a while. Now, we have a timeline. Fidji Simo, OpenAI's CEO of Applications, told reporters during a Thursday briefing about GPT-5.2 that she expects "adult mode" to debut within ChatGPT in the first [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s AI try-on feature for clothes now works with just a selfie</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/googles-ai-try-on-feature-for-clothes-now-works-with-just-a-selfie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075253</guid>
      <description>In the past, users had to upload a full-body picture of themselves to virtually try on a piece of clothing. Now, they can use a selfie and&#160;Nano Banana will generate a full body digital version of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Taiwan Made Cashless Payments Cute</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/icash-taiwan-payments-keychains-how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6936645f9a4c34f57fa814e9</guid>
      <description>Taiwan&#8217;s digital payment infrastructure is tactile, decentralized, and completely distinct from China&#8217;s QR code-dominated model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI fires back at Google with GPT-5.2 after &#8216;code red&#8217; memo</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/openai-fires-back-at-google-with-gpt-5-2-after-code-red-memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075273</guid>
      <description>OpenAI just launched GPT-5.2, a frontier model aimed at developers and professionals, pushing reasoning and coding benchmarks as it races Google&#8217;s Gemini 3 while grappling with compute costs and no generator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hideaki Anno Bids a Final Farewell to Original &#8216;Evangelion&#8217; Studio Gainax</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hideaki-anno-gainax-bankruptcy-neon-genesis-evangelion-studio-khara-2000698488</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698488</guid>
      <description>A year after the animation studio filed for bankruptcy, Gainax has shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Launches GPT-5.2 as It Navigates &#8216;Code Red&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-gpt-launch-gemini-code-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6939fab6adb3c84b25e0f697</guid>
      <description>The ChatGPT-maker is releasing its &#8220;best model yet&#8221; as it faces new pressures from Google and other AI competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comcast cable boxes are getting Amazon Luna cloud gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842201/amazon-luna-comcast-xfinity-rogers-cable-boxes</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842201</guid>
      <description>Amazon's Luna cloud gaming service is coming to cable boxes from Comcast and Rogers. The Luna app is already available via web browsers, Fire TV devices, Fire tablets, and many smart TVs from Samsung and LG, and this new expansion will bring the service to "millions" more devices, according to Amazon. Starting Thursday, Luna will [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5.2 is OpenAI&amp;#8217;s latest move in the agentic AI battle</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/842529/openai-gpt-5-2-new-model-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842529</guid>
      <description>GPT-5.2 is here, and with it, OpenAI wants "to unlock even more economic value for people," Fidji Simo, the company's CEO of Applications, told reporters in a Thursday briefing. She said it's been in the works for "many, many months." The company calls GPT-5.2 its "best model yet for everyday professional use" in a release, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google debuts &#8216;Disco,&#8217; a Gemini-powered tool for making web apps from browser tabs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/google-debuts-disco-a-gemini-powered-tool-for-making-web-apps-from-browser-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075205</guid>
      <description>Google Labs is testing a product that will work with your browser tabs to make web apps for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission: Impossible &#8211; The Final Reckoning is massive, messy, and a must-see action movie on Paramount+</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/paramount-plus/mission-impossible-the-final-reckoning-is-massive-messy-and-a-must-see-action-movie-on-paramount</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fDiZxogPZFVmhsV32DBBXL</guid>
      <description>Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is to watch the eight Mission Impossible film on Paramount's streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Disco is an experimental web browser that builds AI widgets based on your tabs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/google-disco-is-an-experimental-web-browser-that-builds-ai-widgets-based-on-your-tabs-180000701.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">929ad3ca-1a30-4fd5-83ff-e995c848163d</guid>
      <description>The latest experiment emerging out of Google Labs is Disco, which is the company's AI-driven approach to web browsing. The first feature for Disco is called GenTabs, built on Google's Gemini 3 model.&#160;GenTabs are interactive widgets created from a mix of user prompts, open tabs and chat history. The preview examples demonstrate how GenTabs can create a model to demonstrate entropy as a study aid, or collect trip ideas into one screen for building an itinerary. The GenTab can be further refined with natural language requests, and it will also offer contextual suggestions for additions that may b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian&#8217;s AI&#160;assistant&#160;is&#160;coming to its EVs in early 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/rivians-ai-assistant-is-coming-to-its-evs-in-early-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075197</guid>
      <description>And when it does, the AI assistant will roll out to every existing&#160;EV in its lineup, not just the next-generation versions of its R1T truck and R1S SUV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le tout r&#233;cent robot aspirateur de Roborock, not&#233; 9/10 par nos soins, perd d&#233;j&#224; 300 &#8364; de son prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2906817_le-tout-recent-robot-aspirateur-de-roborock-note-9-10-par-nos-soins-perd-deja-300-e-de-son-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2906817_le-tout-recent-robot-aspirateur-de-roborock-note-9-10-par-nos-soins-perd-deja-300-e-de-son-prix</guid>
      <description>
Avec le lavage &#224; 100 &#186;C, le retrait automatique des serpilli&#232;res, ou encore le capteur LiDAR pour se rep&#233;rer,&#160;le Roborock Qrevo Curv 2 ProX est un aspirateur robot qui assure un nettoyage complet. Cet appareil est on&#233;reux, mais Boulanger adoucit son prix avec 300 euros de remise. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Cops Are Now Using AI-Generated &#8216;Mugshots&#8217; to Sketch Crime Suspects</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/arizona-cops-are-now-using-ai-generated-mugshots-to-sketch-crime-suspects-2000698072</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698072</guid>
      <description>A police department in a suburb of Phoenix has used ChatGPT twice this year to generate images of crime suspects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Nothing Phone (4a) pointent le bout de leur nez dans une fuite&#160;: encore un rapport qualit&#233; prix du tonnerre &#224; venir&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/les-nothing-phone-4a-pointent-le-bout-de-leur-nez-dans-une-fuite-encore-un-rapport-qualite-prix-du-tonnerre-a-venir.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315082</guid>
      <description>Nothing poursuit sa mue vers le milieu de gamme. Apr&#232;s le succ&#232;s du Phone (3a), la marque londonienne pr&#233;parerait d&#233;j&#224; les Nothing Phone (4a) et (4a) Pro, misant sur des sp&#233;cifications solides et un tarif contenu autour de 500&#8239;dollars. Une fuite &#233;voque &#233;galement un casque Nothing Headphone (a), version plus accessible du mod&#232;le phare, qui viendrait compl&#233;ter cette nouvelle offensive sur le march&#233;....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The People Behind &#8216;Supergirl&#8217; Are Ready to Share Their Imperfect Hero</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-people-behind-supergirl-are-ready-to-share-their-imperfect-hero-2000698165</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698165</guid>
      <description>Producer James Gunn, director Craig Gillespie, and star Milly Alcock talked about the DC Studios film coming June 26, 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eli Lilly&#8217;s Weight Loss Superdrug Worked So Well During Trials, Some Quit Over Losing Too Much</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/eli-lillys-weight-loss-superdrug-worked-so-well-during-trials-some-quit-over-losing-too-much-2000698424</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698424</guid>
      <description>Step aside, semaglutide&#8212;retatrutide is showing the most impressive weight loss results of any obesity drug to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamoru Hosoda explains why Hamlet is everywhere this year</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/842346/mamoru-hosoda-interview-scarlet</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842346</guid>
      <description>Hamlet is having something of a renaissance in 2025. This year's edition of the Toronto International Film Festival featured three different takes on the idea, including Chlo&#233; Zhao's adaptation of the play's inspiration and Aneil Karia's rendition set in modern-day London. But the most out-there version came from Belle director Mamoru Hosoda, who transformed Shakespeare's [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Crypto king&#8217; Do Kwon faces sentencing for misleading Terraform Labs&#8217; investors</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458731/do-kwon-sentenced-terraform-labs-cryptocurrency</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458731/do-kwon-sentenced-terraform-labs-cryptocurrency</guid>
      <description>Investors worldwide lost billions in the downfall of the Singapore crypto firm, which Kwon co-founded in 2018. 
Cryptocurrency mogul Do Kwon is scheduled to be sentenced Thursday for misleading investors who lost billions when his company&#8217;s crypto ecosystem&#160;collapsed in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry, Smart Glasses Will Not Save You From Your Phone</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sorry-smart-glasses-will-not-save-you-from-your-phone-2000698420</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698420</guid>
      <description>Say "distraction-free" one more time, I dare you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian goes big on autonomy, with custom silicon, lidar, and a hint at robotaxis</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/rivian-goes-big-on-autonomy-with-custom-silicon-lidar-and-a-hint-at-robotaxis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075170</guid>
      <description>CEO RJ Scaringe laid out his plan for how Rivian's vehicles will increasingly drive themselves, in a bid to match or exceed the capabilities of rival automakers and AV companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian goes all in on 'universal hands-free' driving at its first Autonomy and AI day</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/rivian-goes-all-in-on-universal-hands-free-driving-at-its-first-autonomy-and-ai-day-172004733.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94590970-c2fc-4f70-aefd-2f4732696276</guid>
      <description>EV automaker Rivian just held its inaugural Autonomy and AI day which, unsurprisingly, focused extensively on hands-free driving. An upcoming software update promises the introduction of "universal hands-free" driving. The company says its vehicles will be able to autonomously navigate more than 3.5 million miles of roads in North America, "covering the vast majority of marked roads in the US."
This is coming to the R2 line of EVs, but also Gen 2 R1 vehicles like the recently-released Rivian R1S. The service will be locked behind a subscription for something called Autonomy+ that includes self...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian is building its own powerful AI chips for autonomous driving</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842213/rivian-ai-autonomous-chip-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T12:20:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842213</guid>
      <description>Rivian announced that it was designing its own AI chips for fully autonomous driving, in a bold - if belated - move to catch up with Tesla and other automakers that have working on the technology for far longer. At an "AI and Autonomy" event at the company's office in Silicon Valley on Thursday, Rivian [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland will revise proposed law change after backlash from tech industry</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/switzerland-will-revise-proposed-law-change-after-backlash-from-tech-industry</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Ceqv8baMYTvPzkQJLFEm9h</guid>
      <description>The Swiss tech industry joined forces and managed to make the government reconsider the amendment to widen surveillance obligations. Yet, the fight for privacy isn't over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Int&#233;gration de personnages &#224; Sora | Disney investit 1&#160;milliard&#8239;US dans OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-11/integration-de-personnages-a-sora/disney-investit-1-milliard-us-dans-openai.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 12:13:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58000122a36e3f0c90c7fc4609db297e</guid>
      <description>Disney investit 1&#160;milliard&#8239;US dans OpenAI et int&#233;grera des personnages tels que Mickey Mouse, Cendrillon et Luke Skywalker &#224; Sora, l&#8217;outil de g&#233;n&#233;ration vid&#233;o de la soci&#233;t&#233; d&#8217;intelligence artificielle (IA), dans le cadre d&#8217;un accord de licence annonc&#233; jeudi par les deux entreprises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney and OpenAI are set to open the vault to Sora &#8212; yet an AI Mickey feels like magic lost</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/disney-and-openai-are-set-to-open-the-vault-to-sora-yet-an-ai-mickey-feels-like-magic-lost</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AroKBrDKz5j9xcE3zUBpMC</guid>
      <description>Some imagination, huh?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AirPods Pro 3 just dropped below $200 for the first time</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/842551/apple-airpods-pro-3-wireless-earbuds-deal-sale-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T12:10:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842551</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s latest gadgets have gotten some notable discounts lately &#8212; including the recently released Apple Watch Series 11, which is still on sale for $100 off at Amazon. Now, we&#8217;re seeing the AirPods Pro 3 drop down to their lowest price to date, with the noise-canceling earbuds going for just $199 ($50 off) at Amazon [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supergirl&#8217;s first trailer introduces the Woman of Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/842392/supergirl-trailer-warner-bros-dc-studios-james-gunn-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T12:05:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842392</guid>
      <description>The first trailer for DC Studios' Supergirl feature is finally here to give us a look at what the Woman of Tomorrow is made of. Though Superman's (technically) older cousin Kara Zor-El (Millie Alcock) was kind of a mess when we first met her, she's trying to pull it together in Supergirl's new trailer. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia develops new software to help track chips following smuggling discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/nvidia-develops-new-software-to-help-track-chips-following-smuggling-discovery</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">L2A83CMwZU8Piy9nJpG46f</guid>
      <description>Nvidia has open-sourced new GPU monitoring software, but it's not for geolocation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix-Warner-Paramount : vous n&#8217;avez rien suivi ? Voici notre foire aux questions sur le deal qui chamboule le cin&#233;ma et la SVoD</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/services/svod/2901563_netflix-warner-vous-navez-rien-suivi-voici-notre-foire-aux-questions-sur-le-deal-qui-chamboule-le-cinema-et-la-svod</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/services/svod/2901563_netflix-warner-vous-navez-rien-suivi-voici-notre-foire-aux-questions-sur-le-deal-qui-chamboule-le-cinema-et-la-svod</guid>
      <description>
S'il y a des personnes qui ont pass&#233; la derni&#232;re semaine sous un rocher, ou qui se sont simplement coup&#233;es de l'actualit&#233;, sachez que Netflix a annonc&#233; l'acquisition de Warner Bros. Cette fusion de deux titans de l'audiovisuel pose beaucoup de questions auxquelles nous apportons les r&#233;ponses ici.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite colleges are prioritizing economic diversity in admissions after affirmative action ban</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458727/elite-colleges-economic-diversity-admissions-affirmative-action-students</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:02:52</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458727/elite-colleges-economic-diversity-admissions-affirmative-action-students</guid>
      <description>At 17 highly selective colleges that have released new data, almost all saw increases in Pell-eligible students between 2023 and this year.
Some of the country&#8217;s most prestigious colleges are enrolling record numbers of low-income students &#8212; a growing admissions priority in the absence of&#160;affirmative action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney accuses Google of &#8216;massive&#8217; copyright infringement following deal with OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842573/disney-google-copyright-infringement-cease-and-desist</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T12:02:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842573</guid>
      <description>Disney has accused Google of engaging in copyright infringement on a "massive scale," claiming its AI models have generated content resembling characters from Frozen, Deadpool, Star Wars, and others, according to reports from Variety and Deadline. In a cease-and-desist letter sent on Wednesday, Disney demands that Google stop allegedly infringing on its copyrighted works. Disney [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runway releases its first world model, adds native audio to latest video model</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/11/runway-releases-its-first-world-model-adds-native-audio-to-latest-video-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075161</guid>
      <description>Runway debuts a physics-aware world model that simulates reality to train agents and power video, robotics and avatar applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye June review: New Netflix movie is a near flawless directorial debut for Kate Winslet &#8212; but you&#8217;ll cry your eyes out</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/goodbye-june-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kxPSo4W5rpzLJeQ2P67LAC</guid>
      <description>Did I have Helen Mirren being fictionally killed off on my Christmas bingo card? No &#8211; but I'm so glad she agreed to star in new Netflix movie Goodbye June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Nvidia&#8217;s White House &#8216;coup,&#8217; China may not be buying</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458277/china-nvidia-h200-chips-meta-bezos-data-center</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458277/china-nvidia-h200-chips-meta-bezos-data-center</guid>
      <description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang appeared to have scored big on Monday when the White House approved sales of his company&#8217;s H200 chips to China. But China may prefer Chinese-made chips&#8212;or smuggled ones.
Welcome to AI Decoded, Fast Company&#8217;s weekly newsletter that breaks down the most important news in the world of AI. I&#8217;m Mark Sullivan, a senior writer at Fast Company,covering emerging tech, AI, and tech policy....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le meilleur vid&#233;oprojecteur ultra courte focale de l&#8217;ann&#233;e &#8211; Frandroid Awards 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2897781_voici-le-meilleur-videoprojecteur-ultra-courte-focale-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2897781_voici-le-meilleur-videoprojecteur-ultra-courte-focale-de-lannee-frandroid-awards-2025</guid>
      <description>
Le meilleur vid&#233;oprojecteur &#224; ultra courte focale test&#233; par Frandroid est le Hisense PX3-Pro. D&#233;couvrez pourquoi ce produit a re&#231;u le Frandroid Awards avec Delos de sa cat&#233;gorie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Trailer for &#8216;Supergirl&#8217; Welcomes Superman&#8217;s Mighty Mess of a Cousin</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-first-trailer-for-supergirl-welcomes-supermans-mighty-mess-of-a-cousin-2000696001</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000696001</guid>
      <description>Milly Alcock goes punk rock as Kara Zor-El in the next DC Studios movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulies OP180 office chair review: Surprisingly comfortable and built for the workplace</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/boulies-op180-office-chair-review</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xnrgBfjx9GPk4S8fnNnrbM</guid>
      <description>The OP180 sits neatly in Boulies' Office Professional line-up ideal for office spaces with multiple users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chantage sur Android&#160;: ce nouveau virus peut effacer toutes vos donn&#233;es et exiger une ran&#231;on</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/chantage-android-nouveau-virus-peut-effacer-toutes-donnees-exiger-rancon.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315083</guid>
      <description>Un nouveau malware cherche &#224; ran&#231;onner les utilisateurs d'un smartphone Android. Cach&#233; dans de fausses applications, le virus menace en effet d'effacer toutes les donn&#233;es enregistr&#233;es sur le t&#233;l&#233;phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open AI and Microsoft are facing a lawsuit over ChatGPT&#8217;s alleged role in this murder-suicide</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458719/open-ai-microsoft-facing-lawsuit-over-chatgpts-alleged-role-murder-suicide</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T16:53:28</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458719/open-ai-microsoft-facing-lawsuit-over-chatgpts-alleged-role-murder-suicide</guid>
      <description>The heirs of an 83-year-old Connecticut woman allege ChatGPT intensified her son&#8217;s &#8216;paranoid delusions,&#8217; playing a key role in her death.
The heirs of an 83-year-old Connecticut woman are suing ChatGPT maker OpenAI and its business partner Microsoft for wrongful death, alleging that the artificial intelligence chatbot intensified her son&#8217;s &#8220;paranoid delusions&#8221; and helped direct them at his mother before he killed her.Police said Stein-Erik Soelberg, 56, a former tech industry worker, fatally beat and strangled his mother, Suzanne Adams, and killed himself in early August at the home where they...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quels sont les meilleurs TV Samsung en 2025 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-tv/1173005_quelle-est-la-meilleure-tv-samsung-a-acheter</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-tv/1173005_quelle-est-la-meilleure-tv-samsung-a-acheter</guid>
      <description>
Sur le march&#233; des t&#233;l&#233;viseurs, Samsung est un acteur majeur au sein d'une concurrence bien install&#233;e. D&#233;couvrez notre s&#233;lection des meilleurs TV Samsung cette ann&#233;e.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Amazon Is Morphing Into a &#8216;Hypertropical&#8217; Climate&#8212;and It&#8217;s as Apocalyptic as It Sounds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-amazon-is-morphing-into-a-hypertropical-climate-and-its-as-apocalyptic-as-it-sounds-2000698491</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698491</guid>
      <description>A new study predicts that by 2100, the Amazon rainforest could experience up to 150 days of hot drought conditions each year, causing mass tree die-offs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disney-OpenAI Deal Redefines the AI Copyright War</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/disney-and-openais-deal-is-a-major-turning-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693aebfb97f8ad30748d1249</guid>
      <description>Disney is hedging against the future. OpenAI is clearing a path for Sora. And together they&#8217;ve made a blueprint for how AI and Hollywood can move forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les capteurs photo du Galaxy S26 pourraient en d&#233;cevoir plus d&#8217;un, voici pourquoi</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2906741_les-capteurs-photo-du-galaxy-s26-pourraient-en-decevoir-plus-dun-voici-pourquoi</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2906741_les-capteurs-photo-du-galaxy-s26-pourraient-en-decevoir-plus-dun-voici-pourquoi</guid>
      <description>
D'apr&#232;s une source bien inform&#233;e, Samsung aurait pris une d&#233;cision &#233;tonnante pour les capteurs photo du futur Galaxy S26 standard.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon just slashed the Bose QuietComfort Earbuds to a record-low price - now $129</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/amazon-just-slashed-the-bose-quietcomfort-earbuds-to-a-record-low-price-now-usd129</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5JJRZHohtbi8rNA7Vfwqsf</guid>
      <description>The Bose QuietComfort Earbuds are an excellent pair of budget-friendly noise-cancelling buds, and you can now get them for a record-low price on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonos Ace : le meilleur casque audio de 2024 est presque &#224; moiti&#233; prix gr&#226;ce &#224; cette offre de No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2880295_sonos-ace-le-meilleur-casque-audio-de-2024-est-presque-a-moitie-prix-grace-a-cette-offre-de-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2880295_sonos-ace-le-meilleur-casque-audio-de-2024-est-presque-a-moitie-prix-grace-a-cette-offre-de-noel</guid>
      <description>
Pour sa premi&#232;re incursion dans le monde des casques audio Bluetooth, Sonos a frapp&#233; fort avec son Ace hyper abouti, &#233;quilibr&#233; et bourr&#233; de technologies. Celui qu'on a qualifi&#233; de meilleur mod&#232;le l'an dernier est affich&#233; &#224; 270 euros au lieu de 499 euros &#224; son lancement.  
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney has accused Google of copyright infringement on a 'massive scale'</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/disney-has-accused-google-of-copyright-infringement-on-a-massive-scale-163737642.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0137d09-1211-498e-a9f8-b853b5fbbc4f</guid>
      <description>Disney has accused Google of copyright infringement on a "massive scale," alleging that the tech giant is training its AI tools on protected materials as well as allowing those tools to generate infringing images and videos. Variety reports that Disney attorneys sent a cease-and-desist letter to Google on Wednesday.
&#8220;Google is infringing Disney&#8217;s copyrights on a massive scale, by copying a large corpus of Disney&#8217;s copyrighted works without authorization to train and develop generative artificial intelligence (&#8216;AI&#8217;) models and services, and by using AI models and services to commercially exploi...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
