<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:20:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Darabont Reveals the Real Story Behind Why He Didn&#8217;t Take on &#8216;The Dark Tower&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/frank-darabont-reveals-the-real-story-behind-why-he-didnt-take-on-the-dark-tower-2000701920</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701920</guid>
      <description>The director of 'The Shawshank Redemption,' 'The Green Mile,' and 'The Mist' talks about the Stephen King project that got away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#8217;s Stargate Data Center Approved in Michigan as American Anger Starts to Boil</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openais-stargate-data-center-approved-in-michigan-as-american-anger-starts-to-boil-2000701890</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701890</guid>
      <description>The data center backlash has begun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPad deals this week include the iPad mini for $100 off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-ipad-deals-this-week-include-the-ipad-mini-for-100-off-150020342.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c2b9c33-9a87-45ff-b978-e41b8f7a90a2</guid>
      <description>The iPad, of course, isn't the only tablet computer out there &#8212; it wasn't even the first &#8212; but Apple's version redefined the category. In our opinion, it's the best tablet you can buy and these slates consistently earn high scores in our reviews. That doesn't mean you should have to pay full price for your next iPad. We are continually on the hunt for good deals on iPads (and other Apple gear while we're at it) and each week, we round them up right there.Current discounts include the iPad mini and the 11-inch iPad Pro, each for $100 off the list price. Beyond iPads, are a few other Apple deals...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Blacklyte Atlas Lite and it's an ultra-cool standing desk for work and play</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/blacklyte-atlas-lite-standing-desk-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36FpKU3HAXP6YissCUgcam</guid>
      <description>The Blacklyte Atlas Lite is a standing desk with hints of the gamer aesthetic and functionality well-suited for business professionals - and it meets those needs with ease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman&#8217;s New Brain Venture, Merge Labs, Will Spin Out of a Nonprofit</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/sam-altman-brain-computer-interface-merge-labs-spin-out-nonprofit-forest-neurotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69431180bc07478ec08f559c</guid>
      <description>Merge Labs, a brain-computer interface startup that seeks to read brain activity using ultrasound, is being spun out of Forest Neurotech, a Los Angeles nonprofit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Reddit Post Helped Find the Brown University Shooting Suspect</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-a-reddit-post-helped-find-the-brown-university-shooting-suspect-2000701854</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701854</guid>
      <description>"The police need to look into a grey Nissan with Florida plates, possibly a rental."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new music player is like a hi-res iPod nano, but with microSD storage &#8212; and you won&#8217;t believe how cheap it is</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/portable-media-players/this-new-music-player-is-like-a-hi-res-ipod-nano-but-with-microsd-storage-and-you-wont-believe-how-cheap-it-is</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qyBJS7Y7KRKbwiGHsMaMAV</guid>
      <description>A very tempting new option from our favorite budget audiophile brand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg's nonprofit cuts ties with the immigration advocacy group he co-founded</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/mark-zuckerbergs-nonprofit-cuts-ties-with-the-immigration-advocacy-group-he-co-founded-183447900.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6527912-d56a-43d8-ab07-30a9ebbe2f23</guid>
      <description>Behold Mark Zuckerberg: man of principle. Witness the Meta CEO's dedication to the most high-minded of causes: "currying favor with whoever's in charge." In 2013, when Barack Obama was president, Zuckerberg co-founded FWD.us, a pro-immigration advocacy group. For years, he vocally supported providing paths to citizenship for "the most talented and hardest-working people, no matter where they were born." Now, in 2025, with Donald Trump back in power and pushing draconian immigration policies, Zuckerberg's philanthropy organization has officially cut ties with the group. Who says Big Tech execut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used an ATM since 2007? Visa and Mastercard may owe you cash</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463788/used-an-atm-since-2007-visa-and-mastercard-may-owe-you-cash</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463788/used-an-atm-since-2007-visa-and-mastercard-may-owe-you-cash</guid>
      <description>The money would go to customers charged unreimbursed fees at non-bank ATMs nationwide.
Visa and Mastercard have agreed to pay $167.5 million to settle a long-running class action lawsuit. The suit, which was first filed&#160; back in Oct. 2011, accused the two major credit card companies of conspiring to keep ATM fees artificially high.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford recalls over 270,000 electric and hybrid cars due to parking function issue</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463906/ford-recall-electric-hybrid-mustang-maverick-parking</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463906/ford-recall-electric-hybrid-mustang-maverick-parking</guid>
      <description>Ford said that it will implement a park module software update for free.
Ford is recalling more than 270,000 electric and hybrid vehicles in the U.S. because of a parking function problem that could lead to them rolling away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;On s&#8217;est fait avoir&#160;&#187; : comment iRobot a perdu la guerre des aspirateurs robots et pourquoi la Chine est son seul salut</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/irobot/2917283_on-sest-fait-avoir-comment-irobot-a-perdu-la-guerre-des-aspirateurs-robots-et-pourquoi-la-chine-est-son-seul-salut</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/irobot/2917283_on-sest-fait-avoir-comment-irobot-a-perdu-la-guerre-des-aspirateurs-robots-et-pourquoi-la-chine-est-son-seul-salut</guid>
      <description>
C'est rare. Tr&#232;s rare. Un CEO qui vous regarde dans les yeux et vous dit : "On s'est plant&#233;s." C'est pourtant ce que vient de faire Gary Cohen. Alors qu'iRobot passe sous pavillon chinois pour &#233;viter la faillite, le patron de la marque embl&#233;matique ne cherche pas d'excuses. Retards technologiques, arrogance, prix d&#233;connect&#233;s... iRobot nous explique tout.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Suction-Based Wall Mount Is Here to Clean Up Your Hideous TV Cord Spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-suction-based-wall-mount-is-here-to-clean-up-your-hideous-tv-cord-spaghetti-2000701816</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701816</guid>
      <description>Displace is back with a hub that makes your regular TV "cordless."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix is betting on podcasts to become the new daytime talk show</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/netflix-is-betting-on-podcasts-to-become-the-new-daytime-talk-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077619</guid>
      <description>Netflix is making exclusive deals with podcast studios to compete with YouTube, but podcasters have mixed feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix is acquiring an avatar company as it moves into party games</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/848252/netflix-avatar-company-ready-player-me-acquisition</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T13:12:33-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848252</guid>
      <description>As Netflix continues to build out its gaming strategy, which has recently included a new era of TV party games, it's going to let people build avatars - with the help of a new acquisition. The company is acquiring avatar company Ready Player Me and its "cross-game avatar tech" to let players "carry their identities [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#8217;t expect Trump Media&#8217;s nuclear fusion power plant to generate electricity soon</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/848205/nuclear-fusion-energy-trump-media-tae</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T13:04:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848205</guid>
      <description>Trump Media - yup, the parent company of Truth Social - is the latest entrant in the near century-long race to develop a nuclear fusion power plant. It announced a merger agreement with fusion company TAE Technologies on Thursday and a bold plan to break ground on the first utility-scale fusion plant some time in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217;s&#8217; New Power Couple Discuss Their Trippy Seduction</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avatar-fire-and-ash-trippy-seduction-2000701835</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701835</guid>
      <description>Oona Chaplin and Stephen Lang talked to io9 about Varang and Quaritch's intimate scene, in theaters now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Christmas gifts for gamers and movie lovers</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/780850/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=780850</guid>
      <description>Most of us in the Northern Hemisphere spend the holidays indoors, but you can only watch so many TikToks about cute cats and cooking hacks before the need for something a little more substantive kicks in. Choosing the right game or movie to gift is tough, though, especially if you don't have an exact read [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home sales rose in November, but are down from last year</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463893/home-sales-november-down-annually</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463893/home-sales-november-down-annually</guid>
      <description>Through the first 11 months of this year, home sales are down 0.5% compared to the same period last year.
Sales of previously occupied U.S. homes rose in November from the previous month, but slowed compared to a year earlier for the first time since May despite average long-term mortgage rates holding near their low point for the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FrandroidOffreMoi une trottinette UrbanGlide 100 EVO</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/trottinette-electrique/2915705_frandroidoffremoi-une-trottinette-urbanglide-100-evo</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/trottinette-electrique/2915705_frandroidoffremoi-une-trottinette-urbanglide-100-evo</guid>
      <description>
On a r&#233;ussi &#224; cacher une trottinette &#233;lectrique dans la 19e case de notre calendrier de l'Avent. Voici comment gagner l'UrbanGlide 100 EVO avec le concours #FrandroidOffreMoi.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's USB-C Magic Mouse is back on sale for $68</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/apples-usb-c-magic-mouse-is-back-on-sale-for-68-175424709.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd8fc096-303c-44be-a905-b9c4f8c2af08</guid>
      <description>Amazon is selling Apple's USB-C Magic Mouse for $68, which is a discount of 14 percent. This isn't a record-low price, but it's darned close. The mouse typically sells for $79, though today's sale only applies to the white model.
It's rare for official Apple accessories to go on sale, and the USB-C Magic Mouse is pretty much a must-have for those working on desktop computers. It's also fairly handy when combined with a laptop, letting folks avoid the trackpad. 


As the name suggests, this mouse charges via USB-C. Apple stuck with replaceable AA batteries for way too long, so this change was m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton VPN climbs to third in our updated VPN rankings</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-services/proton-vpn-climbs-to-third-in-our-updated-vpn-rankings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KftW9SrV2zia7HsWyyW8i7</guid>
      <description>We've fully retested our recommended VPNs and the results are in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI adds new teen safety rules to ChatGPT as lawmakers weigh AI standards for minors</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/openai-adds-new-teen-safety-rules-to-models-as-lawmakers-weigh-ai-standards-for-minors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077799</guid>
      <description>OpenAI updated its guidelines for how its AI models should behave with users under 18, and published new AI literacy resources for teens and parents. Still, questions remain about how well policies translate into practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Shocked to Discover Microbes &#8216;Colonizing&#8217; Lava Within Hours of Solidifying</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-shocked-to-discover-microbes-colonizing-lava-within-hours-of-solidifying-2000701834</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701834</guid>
      <description>Not even the strongest microbes can survive volcanic eruptions, but they are capable of returning surprisingly quickly, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai pris en main le Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold : trois fois plus de plaisir et trois fois plus de questions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2915097_jai-pris-en-main-le-samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-trois-fois-plus-de-plaisir-et-trois-fois-plus-de-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2915097_jai-pris-en-main-le-samsung-galaxy-z-trifold-trois-fois-plus-de-plaisir-et-trois-fois-plus-de-questions</guid>
      <description>
J'ai eu l'occasion de prendre en main le Samsung Galaxy Z TriFold. Voici mes premiers ressentis sur le smartphone tri-pliable, les bons comme les moins bons.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce pack Asus Vivobook 14 sous Snapdragon X accompagn&#233; d&#8217;un sac et d&#8217;une souris sans fil est &#224; un super prix chez Fnac et Darty</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2916277_ce-pack-asus-vivobook-14-sous-snapdragon-x-accompagne-dun-sac-et-dune-souris-sans-fil-est-a-un-super-prix-chez-fnac-et-darty</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2916277_ce-pack-asus-vivobook-14-sous-snapdragon-x-accompagne-dun-sac-et-dune-souris-sans-fil-est-a-un-super-prix-chez-fnac-et-darty</guid>
      <description>
Si vous pr&#233;f&#233;rez tout avoir d&#8217;un coup, il existe des packs pr&#234;ts &#224; l&#8217;emploi avec l&#8217;essentiel pour d&#233;marrer sans friction. C&#8217;est le cas de ce bundle autour du PC portable Asus Vivobook 14 sous ARM, accompagn&#233; d&#8217;un sac et d&#8217;une souris sans fil. L&#8217;ensemble est affich&#233; &#224; 649,99 euros au lieu de 699,99 euros chez Darty et &#224; la Fnac, avec l'aide d'un code qui se termine le 21 d&#233;cembre 2025.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make any TV wireless and battery powered with this add-on that also means you can wall-mount anywhere instantly without drilling</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/make-any-tv-wireless-and-battery-powered-with-this-add-on-that-also-means-you-can-wall-mount-anywhere-instantly-without-drilling</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zEMRF2q4yUqQw8bQoQckcm</guid>
      <description>The Displace Hub enables you to wall-mount your TV without drilling, and even to move it &#8211;and it's got a PC inside it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No storefront needed &#8212; get paid via DMs and QR codes with Squarespace&#8217;s new tool</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/website-building/no-storefront-needed-get-paid-via-dms-and-qr-codes-with-squarespaces-new-tool</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ivUFDuvt2JAm2kcdveLsaN</guid>
      <description>Generate dedicated URLs for payment with Pay Links.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers stole data in UK government cyberattack, minister confirms</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-stole-data-in-uk-government-cyberattack-minister-confirms</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BTcMK5oEaa4CAcAibSEZpP</guid>
      <description>The attack seems to have happened in October but the risk towards citizens is minimal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known uses voice AI to help you go on more in-person dates</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/known-uses-voice-ai-to-help-you-go-on-more-in-person-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076939</guid>
      <description>In its test phase in San Francisco, Known said it observed 80% of its introductions led to physical dates, which is much higher than swipe-based dating apps.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
