<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:35:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>South Park Writer Snagged &#8216;Trump-Kennedy Center&#8217; Web Domains Months Ago</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/south-park-writer-snagged-trump-kennedy-center-web-domains-months-ago-2000703562</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703562</guid>
      <description>The writer has made a habit of acquiring official-sounding domains for satirical purposes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About the &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Upside Down Was in Place Back in Season 1</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-upside-down-origin-truth-2000703523</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703523</guid>
      <description>However, viewers were kept in the dark until season five's second batch of episodes, now streaming on Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework announces another memory price hike &#8212; and it likely won&#8217;t be its last</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850376/framework-ram-memory-ddr5-price-hikes</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T13:13:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850376</guid>
      <description>The modular PC company Framework is adjusting the price of its DDR5 RAM modules once again as the cost of memory continues to surge. In an update on Wednesday, Framework said it will charge $10 per GB for 8GB, 16GB, and 32GB, with "slightly higher" prices for the 48GB and up. Framework first announced a [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#8217;s ahead for startups and VCs in 2026? Investors weigh in</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/26/whats-ahead-for-startups-and-vcs-in-2026-investors-weigh-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078787</guid>
      <description>VCs share their thoughts on what next year could bring to the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluffy rice and melt-in-your-mouth meats make the Ninja Foodi PossibleCooker my new favorite kitchen appliance</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/multi-cookers/ninja-foodi-possiblecooker-review</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cMEr6teKC9LwRdnwcTKHSL</guid>
      <description>A rice cooker, slow cooker, stove, and steamer in one, this is the perfect multi-purpose kitchen appliance for any household.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headed home after Christmas? A snowstorm could ground your flight</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467150/headed-home-after-christmas-a-snowstorm-could-ground-your-flight</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T17:52:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467150/headed-home-after-christmas-a-snowstorm-could-ground-your-flight</guid>
      <description>As winter weather alerts stretch from Pennsylvania to Connecticut, airports across the Northeast brace for possible delays and dangerous runway conditions.
A number of airlines are waiving change fees ahead of what is expected to be a major winter storm forecast to hit the Northeast on Friday afternoon, affecting millions of people traveling after Christmas, during one of the busiest times of the year....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi 17, 17 Pro, 17 Pro Max, 17 Ultra&#8230; Combien de smartphones va lancer Xiaomi en France ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2813437_xiaomi-17-17-pro-17-pro-max-17-ultra-combien-de-smartphones-va-lancer-xiaomi-en-france</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/xiaomi/2813437_xiaomi-17-17-pro-17-pro-max-17-ultra-combien-de-smartphones-va-lancer-xiaomi-en-france</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s la pr&#233;sentation des Xiaomi 17, Xiaomi 17 Pro et 17 Pro Max puis du Xiaomi 17 Ultra, on peut se demander s'ils seront tous lanc&#233;s en France.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Smart Glasses Make Posting Straight to TikTok Less Annoying</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/these-smart-glasses-make-posting-straight-to-tiktok-less-annoying-2000703463</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703463</guid>
      <description>Rokid is giving its new smart glasses more camera aspect ratio options so you won't have to crop for social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why high-speed rail may not work the best in the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91452449/high-speed-rail-us-adoption</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T17:34:11</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91452449/high-speed-rail-us-adoption</guid>
      <description>Not many U.S. cities have enough travel between them and are at the correct distance to support an investment in high-speed rail.
High-speed rail systems are found all over the globe. Japan&#8217;s bullet train began operating in 1964. China will have 31,000 miles (50,000 kilometers) of high-speed track by the end of 2025. The fastest train in Europe goes almost 200 mph (320 kph). Yet high-speed rail remains absent from most of the U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Creative, Inspiring People We Lost in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-creative-inspiring-people-we-lost-in-2025-2000702157</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702157</guid>
      <description>io9 remembers the sci-fi, fantasy, and horror standouts we sadly said goodbye to this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple won't make an iPhone Fold until foldables are perfect, so I don't think we'll ever see a foldable iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/apple-wont-make-an-iphone-fold-until-foldables-are-perfect-so-i-dont-think-well-ever-see-a-foldable-iphone</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4gWm4C2BrTy2XvLYy7hHod</guid>
      <description>Why play a flawed game when it can win without playing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Death in Paradise 2025 Christmas Special online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/tv-shows/watch-the-death-in-paradise-2025-christmas-special-online-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">qVVpVLQkutmR7Zcq8EFsG6</guid>
      <description>When four friends wake after Christmas, a shocking murder changes everything. Here's how to watch the Death in Paradise 2025 Christmas special online from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Refuses to Give Up on Glasses-Free 3D Gaming Monitors</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/samsung-refuses-to-give-up-on-glasses-free-3d-gaming-monitors-2000703471</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000703471</guid>
      <description>Samsung's got a whole family of new Odyssey gaming monitors, including a 32-inch 6K Odyssey 3D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese demonstration shows how dangerous commercial robot hacks can be</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/chinese-robot-hack-voice-command-spread-network</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00146nNkjVFLG19z6UKsOtO</guid>
      <description>Chinese researchers showed off how a hacked humanoid robot could infect others nearby, creating potential dangers for owners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From OpenAI to Nvidia, here&#8217;s a list of recent multibillion-dollar AI deals</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91467080/openai-nvidia-heres-list-recent-multi-billion-dollar-ai-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-26T17:02:52</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91467080/openai-nvidia-heres-list-recent-multi-billion-dollar-ai-deals</guid>
      <description>In the race for AI dominance, companies including Google, SoftBank, and Amazon have signed deals worth billions.
Nvidia has agreed to license technology from AI startup Groq for use in some of its artificial intelligence chips, marking the chipmaker&#8217;s largest deal and underscoring its push to strengthen competitiveness amid surging demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avec l&#8217;IA, les sites Web qui proposent de faux m&#233;dicaments contre l&#8217;ob&#233;sit&#233; se multiplient</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/avec-lia-les-sites-web-qui-proposent-de-faux-medicaments-contre-lobesite-se-multiplient.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317316</guid>
      <description>Des deepfakes pour de faux t&#233;moignages, des faux logos d'une autorit&#233; de sant&#233; destin&#233;e &#224; &#171; certifier &#187; telle vente... Avec l'intelligence artificielle, les sites proposant des produits pr&#233;sent&#233;s comme des &#233;quivalents aux Ozempic, Wegovy, Mounjaro, ces m&#233;dicaments prescrits comme l'ob&#233;sit&#233; et pl&#233;biscit&#233;s sur les r&#233;seaux sociaux comme coupe-faims miracles, se multiplient. Le mois dernier, l'ANSM, l'Agence nationale de s&#233;curit&#233; du m&#233;dicament et des produits de sant&#233;, avait d&#233;j&#224; tir&#233; la sonnette d'alarme....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPad accessories for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/best-ipad-accessories-130018595.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94f7e0a4-2c37-37fd-9879-739177ccbf4c</guid>
      <description>The best iPad accessories can make an aging tablet feel like new again, or give you additional ways to use that new slab you just bought. Whether it's a slim folio case, an Apple Pencil, a docking station or a paper-like screen protector, there are so many iPad accessories out there that can transform how you use your tablet on a regular basis &#8212; and make your iPad last longer, too. We've tested a plethora of accessories over the years, and these are the best iPad accessories you can get right now.
Table of contents

Which iPad generation do you own?
iPad cases
iPad stands and docks
iPad keyboa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naware&#8217;s chemical-free weed killer tech could change how we treat lawns</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/26/nawares-chemical-free-weed-killer-tech-could-change-how-we-treat-lawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3062417</guid>
      <description>A classic hardware startup, Naware's founders set out with a problem -- kill weeds without chemicals -- and relentlessly tinkered until they found a solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mario Kart World vs Kirby Air Riders: which Nintendo Switch 2 racer is better?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/mario-kart-world-vs-kirby-air-riders</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Z6jnLk5JcZGg4DJjThUAzN</guid>
      <description>I love both Mario Kart World and Kirby Air Riders, and here I'm breaking down the differences between the two in a head-to-head battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchester United vs Newcastle live streams: How to watch Premier League 2025-26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/manchester-united-vs-newcastle-live-streams-how-to-watch-premier-league-2025-26-from-anywhere-in-the-world</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ojLTvvmJrqYmZNFGFHaUbh</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Manchester United vs Newcastle live streams online and from anywhere in the only Premier League fixture on Boxing Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You may soon be able to change your Gmail address</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/you-may-soon-be-able-to-change-your-gmail-address-165633905.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7826f190-7502-418e-917f-ea696c8b9f0d</guid>
      <description>A Google support page in Hindi says the ability to change your Gmail address is on the way. The feature would allow you to replace your current @gmail.com address with another. Your old address would remain active as an alias on the account, and all your data would stick around, unaffected.The support page (translated) says that "the ability to change your Google Account email address is gradually rolling out to all users." The change was first spotted on a Google Pixel forum on Telegram and was first reported in the press by 9to5Google.Google hasn't made a formal announcement about the change...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG announces line of premium gaming monitors that offer 5K visuals</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/accessories/lg-announces-line-of-premium-gaming-monitors-that-offer-5k-visuals-165224945.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2145f63f-e95d-4f36-82de-658cb8eb94a8</guid>
      <description>LG has revealed a new lineup of gaming monitors just ahead of CES. The UltraGear evo displays offer 5K visuals. Many incorporate on-device AI upscaling, taking some of the burden away from the GPU.&#160;
LG says the tech will let consumers skip out on some card upgrades. This could end up being extremely beneficial because the AI boom has been impacting GPU prices.
LG
There are three displays in the lineup so far, with more to come down the line. There's a 39-inch OLED (39GX950B) that includes the aforementioned AI upscaling to 5K, but also algorithms for scene optimization and sound. The company s...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
