<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:25:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Page loosens business ties to CA amid state&#8217;s proposed wealth tax, report</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/larry-page-loosens-business-ties-to-ca-amid-states-proposed-wealth-tax-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3081006</guid>
      <description>Larry Page is reportedly moving assets out of California over concern the state will vote in a tax on billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traces of Leonardo da Vinci's DNA May Have Been Discovered on a Red Chalk Drawing Called 'Holy Child'</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/traces-of-leonardo-da-vincis-dna-may-have-been-discovered-on-a-red-chalk-drawing-called-holy-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695ea94e6b73533153d0c7a4</guid>
      <description>Researchers suggest that they have recovered sequences from ancient works and letters that may belong to the Renaissance genius.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Your New Favorite &#8216;Game of Thrones&#8217; Character in This &#8216;Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Featurette</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meet-your-new-favorite-game-of-thrones-character-in-this-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-featurette-2000707042</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707042</guid>
      <description>Peter Claffey's very endearing hedge knight, Ser Duncan the Tall, is coming to HBO on January 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetti now charges power stations at up to 1200W in your car</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/842308/bluetti-now-charges-power-stations-at-up-to-1200w-in-your-car</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842308</guid>
      <description>Bluetti's latest car charger can quickly charge power stations at a very fast 1200W - about 10 times faster than plugging it into the 12V cigarette lighter outlet. The Charger 2, as it's called, can also reverse the flow of electrons to jump-start your vehicle or maintain its starter battery when used with a Bluetti [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetti's Charger 2 uses solar and engine power to charge your portable battery</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/bluettis-charger-2-uses-solar-and-engine-power-to-charge-your-portable-battery-230000270.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e96525eb-d1f7-4683-9156-0b924d2dfe3b</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re off-roading, it&#8217;s a neat idea to use your engine to top up your battery, which prompted Bluetti to launch the Charger. You could hook it to your alternator and draw off energy as you drove to make sure you turned up to your campsite with full batteries. But if you&#8217;re also toting around solar panels on your roof, then it&#8217;s a shame you can&#8217;t also use that power to top up. This omission is what prompted Bluetti to turn up to CES 2026 with the Charger 2, which will take power from your engine and your solar panels at the same time.
Bluetti says the Charger 2&#8217;s dual-input architecture wil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best deals on MacBooks right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T17:59:01-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals</guid>
      <description>Apple currently sells MacBooks equipped with its own M-series processors in a wide range of sizes and price points, all of which run the company&#8217;s newest operating system, macOS 26. Purchasing a new MacBook can be complicated if you&#8217;re trying to figure out what specs you need, but finding a deal on a relatively speedy [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the perfect robovac for klutzes &#8212; it'll help you figure out where you dropped your wallet</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/this-is-the-perfect-robovac-for-klutzes-itll-help-you-figure-out-where-you-dropped-your-wallet</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Yp5N2ehBZzjPVMeLBctrJ7</guid>
      <description>Narwal's latest robot vacuum has a whole range of tricks up its metaphorical robo-sleeve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rokid&#8217;s new AI glasses are lighter, cheaper, and ready to challenge Meta&#8217;s Ray-Bans</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/rokids-new-ai-glasses-are-lighter-cheaper-and-ready-to-challenge-metas-ray-bans</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pfv7tmCWaaNcZZJP22RgF5</guid>
      <description>Rokid&#8217;s new screenless AI glasses undercut Meta on price and weight, offering a glimpse of a voice-first, post-screen future for wearable tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character.AI and Google settle teen suicide and self-harm suits</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/858102/characterai-google-teen-suicide-settlement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T17:30:22-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858102</guid>
      <description>Character.AI and Google have reached settlements with several families whose teens harmed themselves or died by suicide after interacting with Character.AI's chatbots, according to new court filings. The details of the settlements are still unknown. The parties notified a federal court in Florida that they had reached a "mediated settlement in principle to resolve all [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple AirPods Pro 3 Are $50 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/apple-airpods-pro-3-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695e9ae04e793bb818c7d36c</guid>
      <description>Snag a relatively rare discount on Apple&#8217;s finest earbuds at Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engadget Podcast: CES 2026 and the rocky year ahead for the PC industry</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/engadget-podcast-ces-2026-and-the-rocky-year-ahead-for-the-pc-industry-221500019.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18e5fc2c-eb4a-471c-ad66-982d59bd2ee0</guid>
      <description>CES 2026: A rocky year ahead of the PC industryWe're halfway through CES 2026, and it&#8217;s clear that it's going to be a rough year for the PC industry. In this episode, Devindra chats with Engadget's Dan Cooper about Intel, AMD, NVIDIA and the sad state of the PC industry. We've got some new CPUs, but the volatile RAM market will likely make everything expensive this year. Also, they dive into Dell's revival of the XPS brand, as well as iPolish's smart nails and Subtle's AI-powered VoiceBuds.Subscribe!iTunesSpotifyPocket CastsStitcherGoogle PodcastsTopicsThe state of the PC industry in 2026 -- 0...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, LinkedIn banned AI agent startup Artisan, but now it&#8217;s back</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/yes-linkedin-banned-ai-agent-startup-artisan-but-now-its-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080944</guid>
      <description>Several viral posts noticed that Artisan was banned. But the CEO tells us it wasn't for the reasons many thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Display at CES 2026: Playful demos and mysterious prototypes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/samsung-display-ces-2026-playful-demos-and-mysterious-prototypes-220407696.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01743a0a-5f8c-4b31-957f-73ae08c4b1a6</guid>
      <description>Samsung Display is the part of its giant parent company that makes OLEDs, LCDs and other screens for both Samsung devices and anyone else that can afford them. This year, it&#8217;s going all-in on OLEDs of the future. And that meant things like foldable displays with invisible creases, robots hurling basketballs at supertough OLED panels, and OLED screens packed into baffling form factors for no good reason.
Creases
Samsung Display
The &#8220;seamless&#8221; foldable display that might be a part of a future foldable iPhone disappeared from the booth during our tour, reappearing when it was time to leave. (This...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Launches ChatGPT Health, Wants Access to Your Medical Records</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/openai-launches-chatgpt-health-wants-access-to-your-medical-records-2000707024</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707024</guid>
      <description>OpenAI's biggest play into the burgeoning health AI market is here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#8217;s Live-Action &#8216;Tangled&#8217; Has Found Its Leads</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/disney-live-action-tangled-casting-rapunzel-2000707051</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707051</guid>
      <description>Relative newcomers Teagan Croft and Milo Manheim will play Rapunzel and Flynn Rider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI enters the connected health space with ChatGPT Health</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91470872/openai-connected-health-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-07T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91470872/openai-connected-health-chatgpt</guid>
      <description>Health is already a popular topic area on ChatGPT. OpenAI is now adding physician expertise, and plugins for health apps and records.
OpenAI has launched ChatGPT Health, a product that allows users to connect their medical records and wellness apps to the AI chatbot and get personalized health guidance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the Keurig K-Express for $69.99 at Amazon for a limited time</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-7-keurig-k-express-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04W1rVn7dlBlwnV5NJkk6sJ</guid>
      <description>Get the Keurig K-Express Single Serve Coffee Maker for just $69.99 at Amazon. Features a 42oz reservoir and a Strong Brew option.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scan, organize, and conquer your clutter with SwiftScan right on your phone for 80% off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-7-swiftscan-lifetime-subscription</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05Gr7UOFLbNtKQ1nHNp5r2n</guid>
      <description>SwiftScan VIP makes scanning, organizing, and storing all your documents effortless &#8212; get lifetime access for $39.97 with code SCAN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok Is Generating Sexual Content Far More Graphic Than What's on X</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/grok-is-generating-sexual-content-far-more-graphic-than-whats-on-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695d7fbcdbe489ef91435a3f</guid>
      <description>A WIRED review of outputs hosted on Grok&#8217;s official website shows it&#8217;s being used to create violent sexual images and videos, as well as content that includes apparent minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dominATE Experience trailer proves Stray Kids were built for the big screen</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/stray-kids-the-dominate-experience-concert-film-trailer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07mxlHyDVMzYu2cOfbgzeio</guid>
      <description>'Stray Kids: The dominATE Experience' trailer previews the upcoming concert film, filmed at SoFi Stadium and releasing in theaters worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This haptic wristband pairs with Meta smart glasses to decode facial expressions</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/this-haptic-wristband-pairs-with-meta-smart-glasses-to-decode-facial-expressions-214305431.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc006348-e94a-4af9-91ae-7418b1334036</guid>
      <description>It's only been a few months since Meta announced that it would open its smart glasses platform to third-party developers. But one startup at CES is already showing off how the glasses can help power an intriguing set of accessibility features.Hapware has created Aleye, a haptic wristband that, when paired with Ray-Ban Meta smart glasses, can help people understand the facial expressions and other nonverbal cues of the people they are talking to. The company says the device could help people who are blind, low vision or neurodivergent unlock a type of communication that otherwise wouldn't be av...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 7% of Americans Want Their Next Car to Be Electric, Survey Finds</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/only-7-of-americans-want-their-next-car-to-be-electric-survey-finds-2000707031</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000707031</guid>
      <description>A new Deloitte survey finds price, driving range, and charging concerns are slowing EV adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roku&#8217;s $3 streaming service Howdy will be coming to other platforms, CEO says</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/07/rokus-3-streaming-service-howdy-will-be-coming-to-other-platforms-ceo-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3080966</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Anthony Wood, Roku's founder, chairman, and CEO, offered a hint about the future of the company's newest streaming channel, Howdy, and its ambition to become a broader competitor in the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Motorola Razr Fold could open up a new era for folding phones &#8211; if the price is right</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/motorola-phones/the-motorola-razr-fold-could-open-up-a-new-era-for-folding-phones-if-the-price-is-right</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YMTqm95HVmY2bGrpWrrite</guid>
      <description>Motorola could be the one to lead the charge on mid-range foldables by adding the Razr Fold to its lineup of existing flip phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is RAM the new Bitcoin? DDR4 memory prices are rising so fast, some tracker graphs are running out of space - and I fear 2026 could well see a 10x price rise</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/is-ram-the-new-bitcoin-ddr4-memory-prices-are-rising-so-fast-some-tracker-graphs-are-running-out-of-space-and-i-fear-2026-could-well-see-a-10x-price-rise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5t7sDDso9v3rsigjMXEHm</guid>
      <description>Is RAM the new Bitcoin? DDR4 prices jump from under $100 to several hundred dollars in a matter of months and the worrying trend shows no signs of slowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning 25-Year Timelapse Shows a Supernova Tearing Through Deep Space</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stunning-25-year-timelapse-shows-a-supernova-tearing-through-deep-space-2000706993</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706993</guid>
      <description>Decades in the making, NASA's X-ray timelapse shows a stellar explosion expanding into space at up to 2% the speed of light.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
