<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:29:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#8217;s Fire TV Stick 4K Plus is on sale for just $18 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/865230/amazon-fire-tv-stick-4k-plus-iphone-air-magsafe-battery-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:28:52-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865230</guid>
      <description>In February, Amazon plans to roll out a much-needed revamp of Fire TV OS, one that seemingly takes a cue from Google&#8217;s TV platform. The forthcoming UI redesign will introduce better organization, support for Alexa Plus, and quicker performance to the aging OS, the latter of which has been a crux of the platform&#8217;s issues [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk just told Davos that Tesla will sell humanoid robots next year, really, he swears</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/elon-musk-just-told-davos-that-tesla-will-sell-humanoid-robots-next-year-really-he-swears-192515568.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94dc5929-855e-4d3b-9085-d49bc6d27ffe</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk just took the stage at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland and announced that Tesla's Optimus humanoid robot will be sold to the public by the end of next year. Musk is the master of unrealistic timetables, but this may be the nuttiest one yet. These are humanoid robots that are supposed to be able to do just about any task a human can do.
Musk, as usual, gave himself an out if the robots don't start rolling off the assembly line in 2027, saying that they'll only be released when Tesla is "confident that it&#8217;s very high reliability, very high safety and the range of functio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans&amp; thinks coordination is the next frontier for AI, and they&#8217;re building a model to prove it</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/humans-thinks-coordination-is-the-next-frontier-for-ai-and-theyre-building-a-model-to-prove-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085222</guid>
      <description>Humans&amp;, a new startup founded by alumni of Anthropic, Meta, OpenAI, xAI, and Google DeepMind, is building the next generation of foundation models for collaboration, not chat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out - this devious new Android malware clicks on hidden browser ads to put you at risk</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/watch-out-this-devious-new-android-malware-clicks-on-hidden-browser-ads-to-put-you-at-risk</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iNbFeqptBx5FNV3TJ97KyF</guid>
      <description>Malware uses AI to mimic authentic human behavior and trick traditional defenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fable is coming to PS5 when it finally launches this fall</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865305/fable-xbox-playground-games-developer-direct-2026-ps5-pc</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:04:27-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865305</guid>
      <description>Xbox showed off new footage of its Fable reboot during its Developer Direct on Thursday and announced that the game is set to launch this autumn for Xbox, PC, and PS5. The new Fable is an open-world action RPG. In addition to letting you customize your character and your combat skills, you can also do [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mario Kart World adds a team option in Knockout Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/mario-kart-world-adds-a-team-option-in-knockout-tour-190348248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8831619d-2a03-427a-ae4c-f54ddb841377</guid>
      <description>Mario Kart World received a free update today that brings a team option to its Knockout Tour mode. Initially, the Knockout races in this Nintendo Switch 2 launch title were only for solo drivers, challenging players to finish ahead of enough other competitors or get eliminated from the series. It was one of the highlights of the game in our review, and this new wrinkle should bring plenty more fun chaos to the racetrack.In the team mode, players compete either in two teams of twelve, three teams of eight or four teams of six. If you don't have enough people to fill out a team CPU drivers will ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Cobra Kai&#8217; Is Getting the Dream Physical Release It Deserves</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/cobra-kai-is-getting-the-dream-physical-release-it-deserves-2000713011</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713011</guid>
      <description>All six seasons of the hit Netflix show are coming to Blu-ray, with a few new commentaries to boot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Claude Code Is Reshaping Software&#8212;and Anthropic</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/claude-code-success-anthropic-business-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697129ce8c25eb9b6d63a92c</guid>
      <description>WIRED spoke with Boris Cherny, head of Claude Code, about how the viral coding tool is changing the way Anthropic works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Disinformation Swarms Are Coming for Democracy</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-powered-disinformation-swarms-are-coming-for-democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696fae551d9eb7b4565d30e5</guid>
      <description>Advances in artificial intelligence are creating a perfect storm for those seeking to spread disinformation at unprecedented speed and scale. And it&#8217;s virtually impossible to detect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best laptops you can get</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21250695/best-laptops</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21250695/best-laptops</guid>
      <description>Buying the right laptop can be stressful. It&#8217;s likely one of the pricier tech purchases you&#8217;ll make, and there are a ludicrous number of models, sizes, form factors, and configurations to pick from. We review a wide swath of them here at The Verge, and we&#8217;re constantly considering what&#8217;s best and who it&#8217;s best for. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA lighting trends for 2026: give your home a lift with lamps and smart lights from just $3</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-lights/ikea-lighting-trends-for-2026-give-your-home-a-lift-with-lamps-and-smart-lights-from-just-usd3</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nNsGzCCRaP3obrGyKzfDiY</guid>
      <description>Bold and beautiful lighting to give your space the ultimate glow-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substack launches a TV app</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/substack-launches-a-tv-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085113</guid>
      <description>The move comes as Substack has been investing more heavily in video and livestreaming, as it looks to compete with platforms like YouTube and Patreon for both creators and viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nioh 3 : voici les configurations sur PC, &#224; quoi s&#8217;attendre ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2951711_nioh-3-voici-les-configurations-sur-pc-a-quoi-sattendre</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2951711_nioh-3-voici-les-configurations-sur-pc-a-quoi-sattendre</guid>
      <description>
Le troisi&#232;me opus de la s&#233;rie de jeux Nioh sort tr&#232;s bient&#244;t. Quelles sont les configurations attendues pour pouvoir en profiter ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Our Favorite Smart Plugs for Apple Users Is $15 Off</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/meross-smart-plug-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69725f1e904332ad78632c84</guid>
      <description>The Meross smart plug mini boasts excellent compatibility and slim construction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this the end of Epic and Google&#8217;s feud?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/865178/epic-v-google-settlement-before-judge</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T13:55:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865178</guid>
      <description>Today, I am sitting in the courtroom that may decide the fate of Android. Epic CEO Tim Sweeney is here. Google Android boss Sameer Samat is here. Together, they'll try to convince Judge James Donato that they're no longer enemies - that Google's illegal monopoly on Android app stores can be resolved with a mutual [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s a new look at Beast of Reincarnation, from the team behind Pok&#233;mon</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/865588/beast-of-reincarnation-trailer-date-pokemon-game-freak</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T13:55:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865588</guid>
      <description>It's been a bit of a wait, but a big new game from Pok&#233;mon developer Game Freak is almost here. During the Xbox Developer Direct showcase, the studio showed off more gameplay for its action RPG Beast of Incarnation, and confirmed that it will be launching in the summer of 2026 on the PS5, Xbox, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla launches robotaxi rides in Austin with no human safety driver</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/tesla-launches-robotaxi-rides-in-austin-with-no-human-safety-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085158</guid>
      <description>Not all of Tesla's fleet in Austin will be fully driverless. Per Tesla's AI lead Ashok Elluswamy, the company will be "starting with a few unsupervised vehicles mixed in with the broader robotaxi fleet with safety monitors, and the ratio will increase over time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Seekers Want to Know What the Hell Is Going on With AI-Based Hiring Decisions: Lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/job-seekers-want-to-know-what-the-hell-is-going-on-with-ai-based-hiring-decisions-lawsuit-2000712967</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712967</guid>
      <description>Eightfold, an AI company that makes human resources software, is being sued over one of its hiring tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Unpacked rumors: When it is, what devices well see</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/samsung-unpacked-2026-date-rumors</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05j2FQG07QPzUeZjBoI8J3D</guid>
      <description>Samsung has to show off its next batch of Galaxy phones soon, but when exactly will that be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Actually Need the Best Gaming CPU?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/do-you-actually-need-the-best-gaming-cpu-2000713038</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713038</guid>
      <description>AMD&#8217;s new Ryzen 7 9850X3D seems powerful, though it's not a massive leap over what we already have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta seeks to limit evidence in child safety case</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/meta-seeks-to-limit-evidence-in-child-safety-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085084</guid>
      <description>Meta is set to go on trial in New Mexico for allegedly failing to protect minors. The company is requesting a broad swath of information not be allowed to be presented in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rare, Deadly Fungus Is Making People Sick in Tennessee</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-rare-deadly-fungus-is-making-people-sick-in-tennessee-2000712977</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712977</guid>
      <description>At least 36 cases of histoplasmosis and possibly one death have been reported in the state since last fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Bezos and Blue Origin want to help provide high-speed satellite internet across the globe</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/jeff-bezos-and-blue-origin-want-to-help-provide-high-speed-satellite-internet-across-the-globe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gpAshKjDifBSkLd2Wh45UQ</guid>
      <description>Blue Origin will offer a LEO/MEO satellite internet network for enterprises and governments, but not consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After settling lawsuit, Snapchat adds new parental controls for teens</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/snapchat-time-limits-friend-list-parent-lawsuit</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03ic8rvZO3L6TaLLcnkRMlH</guid>
      <description>Snap adds new monitoring tools for parents to its Family Center, including ways to monitor a teen's app use and contacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dacia Spring &#224; 5 900 euros : voici comment ce pays casse le prix de la voiture &#233;lectrique</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2952607_dacia-spring-a-5-900-euros-voici-comment-ce-pays-casse-le-prix-de-la-voiture-electrique</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/dacia/2952607_dacia-spring-a-5-900-euros-voici-comment-ce-pays-casse-le-prix-de-la-voiture-electrique</guid>
      <description>
5 900 euros pour une voiture &#233;lectrique neuve. C'est le tarif affich&#233; par la Dacia Spring en Allemagne gr&#226;ce &#224; un alignement des plan&#232;tes assez unique.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forza Horizon 6 will hit Xbox Series X/S and PC on May 19</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/xbox/forza-horizon-6-will-hit-xbox-series-xs-and-pc-on-may-19-183242726.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc2b9c5f-3523-41bd-a810-fee126209886</guid>
      <description>Forza Horizon 6 is taking the racing series to Japan for the first time, and now we know exactly when you&#8217;ll be able to hit the virtual streets of Tokyo. The game will arrive on Xbox Series X/S, PC and Xbox Cloud on May 19, with an early access period commencing on May 15. That lines up with earlier reports about the release date(s) after an in-game ad supposedly appeared in Forza Horizon 5. The upcoming title will hit PS5 later this year.The standard edition of Forza Horizon 6 is expected to cost $70, though it will be on Xbox Game Pass Ultimate and PC Game Pass. To jump in a few days early, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is AI&#8217;s core architectural flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91476391/this-is-ais-core-architectural-flaw</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T18:30:44</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91476391/this-is-ais-core-architectural-flaw</guid>
      <description>Why large language models are stuck in Plato&#8217;s cave (and what comes next).
Large language models feel intelligent because they speak fluently, confidently, and at scale. But fluency is not understanding, and confidence is not perception. To grasp the real limitation of today&#8217;s AI systems, it helps to revisit an idea that is more than two thousand years old....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Valentino: How the fashion icon shaped the runway and red carpet for 60&#160;years</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478610/valentino-fashion-icon-shaped-the-runway-red-carpet-60-years</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478610/valentino-fashion-icon-shaped-the-runway-red-carpet-60-years</guid>
      <description>Valentino will leave a lasting legacy as the Italian designer who managed to break through the noise of the French haute couture elite and make a name for himself.
Valentino, who died on Monday at 93, leaves a lasting legacy full of celebrities, glamour and, in his words, knowing what women want: &#8220;to be beautiful&#8221;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI pin is beneath Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/an-ai-pin-is-beneath-apple-182744647.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a9c4806-23e0-4b7e-8496-a6afa6f6c483</guid>
      <description>So it's come to this: Apple is reportedly working on a wearable AI pin. According to The Information, it is going to be a small device with "multiple cameras, a speaker, microphones and wireless charging." It sounds like the perfect gadget to pair with the long-awaited AI-powered Siri update, which will also reportedly work as a chatbot. But while many Apple rumors conjure up an air of excitement, the notion of an Apple AI pin sounds downright baffling. Worse, it just seems desperate.&#160;Apple, the company known for taking its time to jump into new categories with more thoughtful solutions than i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google now offers free SAT practice exams, powered by Gemini</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/google-now-offers-free-sat-practice-exams-powered-by-gemini/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085134</guid>
      <description>Students can prompt Gemini by typing "I want to take a practice SAT test,&#8221; and the AI will provide them with a free practice exam. Gemini then analyzes the results, highlighting strengths and identifying areas that need further review. It also offers detailed explanations for any incorrect answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurosky et W Social : tout savoir sur les deux alternatives europ&#233;ennes &#224; X et Threads</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2952595_eurosky-et-w-social-tout-savoir-sur-les-deux-alternatives-europeennes-a-x-et-threads</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/culture-tech/web/2952595_eurosky-et-w-social-tout-savoir-sur-les-deux-alternatives-europeennes-a-x-et-threads</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu passer cette lettre ouverte &#224; Ursula von der Leyen ? L'Europe ne veut plus d&#233;pendre des caprices d'Elon Musk. Pour remplacer la plateforme am&#233;ricaine, deux projets sortent du bois : Eurosky et W Social. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forza Horizon 6 launches in May</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865355/forza-horizon-6-xbox-developer-direct-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T13:18:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865355</guid>
      <description>Forza Horizon 6 will launch on Xbox Series X / S and PC on May 19th, Xbox and developer Playground Games announced during Thursday's Developer Direct showcase. If you preorder the Premium Edition, you can play starting May 15th. The game will come to PS5 later this year. The game has the largest map in [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici ce que le &#171;&#160;Starlink&#160;&#187; de Jeff Bezos promet : un d&#233;bit de 6 TBit/s partout sur Terre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/2952579_voici-ce-que-le-starlink-de-jeff-bezos-promet-un-debit-de-6-tbit-s-partout-sur-terre</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/telecom/2952579_voici-ce-que-le-starlink-de-jeff-bezos-promet-un-debit-de-6-tbit-s-partout-sur-terre</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que la guerre des &#233;toiles se jouait uniquement entre Starlink et Kuiper ?Jeff Bezos vient de sortir une nouvelle carte de sa manche : TeraWave. Un r&#233;seau de 5 408 satellites pens&#233; pour les entreprises, avec des technologies optiques qui laissent les experts perplexes. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump&#8217;s Greenland strategy is really about outmaneuvering China</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478597/trumps-greenland-strategy-is-really-about-outmaneuvering-china</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T18:10:03</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478597/trumps-greenland-strategy-is-really-about-outmaneuvering-china</guid>
      <description>China seeks to establish mining interests in Greenland and the Arctic as part of its Polar Silk Road initiative. 
In 2019, during his first term, U.S. President Donald Trump expressed a desire to buy Greenland, which has been a part of Denmark for some 300 years. Danes and Greenlanders quickly rebuffed the offer at the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korg's new experimental synthesizer combines acoustic sounds with electronic control</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/korgs-new-experimental-synthesizer-combines-acoustic-sounds-with-electronic-control-180809332.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0de8a06-753c-4133-976c-dbea7e7fb5b0</guid>
      <description>Korg just officially unveiled the Phase8 synthesizer, after years of tinkering by a team led by legendary engineer Tatsuya Takahashi. This is a highly experimental synthesizer, but it's not a concept unit. It'll be available for purchase in April.
The Phase8 uses a new form of "acoustic synthesis" that combines acoustic sound generation with electronic control. Takahashi says the synthesizer is "beyond analog vs. digital" and "beyond electronics" altogether. It features chromatically tuned steel resonators, which creates an acoustic sound similar to that of a kalimba. These signals can be mani...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like an Avalanche: Wild Video Captures the Violent Trigger Behind Solar Flares</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/like-an-avalanche-wild-video-captures-the-violent-trigger-behind-solar-flares-2000712926</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712926</guid>
      <description>Solar Orbiter captured the most detailed view of a solar flare, observing the build-up of events that lead to the explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy has slashed $100 off the Asus ROG Xbox Ally 3 &#8212; and get three-months free Xbox Game Pass Premium</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-pcs/best-buy-has-slashed-usd100-off-the-asus-rog-xbox-ally</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ut3DdxYACjBvVkdEAAMsS4</guid>
      <description>The ASUS ROG Ally hits near record-low price, making it a better proposition compared to the Steam Deck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Makes a Prank War Out of One of the Oldest Debates in &#8216;Star Trek&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-episode-3-recap-2000712640</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712640</guid>
      <description>'Vitus Reflux' pushes the show's balance between 'Star Trek' ideas and its youthful vibe to a fun, if fruitless, stretching point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CEO of celeb fav gym Dogpound launches $5M fund to back wellness companies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/former-ceo-of-celeb-fav-gym-dogpound-launches-5m-fund-to-back-wellness-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084701</guid>
      <description>Jenny Liu is a solo first-time GP looking to back underrepresented wellness founders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk layoffs today: Software company cuts 7% of jobs in latest tech downsizing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91479393/autodesk-layoffs-today-software-company-1000-jobs-cut-in-latest-tech-downsizing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91479393/autodesk-layoffs-today-software-company-1000-jobs-cut-in-latest-tech-downsizing</guid>
      <description>The cuts, part of a multi-phase restructuring plan, will affect about 1,000 employees.
Autodesk, Inc. announced Thursday it plans to lay off about 1,000 employees, largely in sales roles. The announcement comes just a week after another tech company, Meta, announced it would eliminate up to 1,500 positions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok generated an estimated 3 million sexualized images&#160;&#8212; including 23,000 of children &#8212;&#160;over 11 days</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/grok-generated-an-estimated-3-million-sexualized-images--including-23000-of-children--over-11-days-175053250.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98f36b3d-e1cf-4748-9f68-adf54b55e798</guid>
      <description>We already knew xAI's Grok was barraging X with nonconsensual sexual images of real people. But now there are some numbers to put things in perspective. Over an 11-day period, Grok generated an estimated 3 million sexualized images &#8212; including an estimated 23,000 of children.Put another way, Grok generated an estimated 190 sexualized images per minute during that 11-day period. Among those, it made a sexualized image of children once every 41 seconds.On Thursday, the Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH) published its findings. The British nonprofit based its findings on a random sample of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Developer Direct 2026: the biggest games and announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/865573/xbox-developer-direct-2026-the-biggest-games-and-announcements</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T12:50:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?post_type=vm_stream&amp;p=865573</guid>
      <description>In a now-annual tradition, Microsoft is kicking off the year with a showcase of some of its biggest upcoming games. Last year&#8217;s edition of the Xbox Developer Direct had some big names, like Doom: The Dark Ages and a little game called Clair Obscur: Expedition 33. And we already know the three main titles that [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If there's one TV I recommend watching the Super Bowl on, it's LG's 65-inch C5 OLED TV &#8212; $1,300 off at Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/if-theres-one-tv-i-recommend-watching-the-super-bowl-on-its-lgs-65-inch-c5-oled-tv-usd1-300-off-at-best-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Q99S87ANrVAnLPmpsrSwS3</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the upcoming Super Bowl, LG's stunning 65-inch C5 OLED, our best-rated TV, is on sale for a massive $1,300 discount at Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Agents Are &#8216;Doxing&#8217; Themselves</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-agents-are-doxing-themselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696f977f81397433db57a96c</guid>
      <description>The alleged risks of being publicly identified have not stopped DHS&#160; and ICE employees from creating profiles on LinkedIn, even as Kristi Noem threatens to treat revealing agents' identities as a crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;They are starting to realize no one wants Horizon integration&#8217; &#8212; Meta announces a major Quest 3 change, but is it a blessing or a curse in disguise?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/they-are-starting-to-realize-no-one-wants-horizon-integration-meta-announces-a-major-quest-3-change-but-is-it-a-blessing-or-a-curse-in-disguise</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">R6dUfA9rgMBLbvmhrch6Gn</guid>
      <description>Your Meta Quest 3 is getting a big Horizon-related change in update v85.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shop the best Samsung deals this week: monitors, smartphones, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-22-best-samsung-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06lVNp3Nm6qFKbsh2tHaFHQ</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 22, shop discounted Samsung monitors, smartphones, and more for the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl: TV channel, where to stream and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-tv-channel-where-to-stream-and-more-173222003.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>We might still be in the midst of the playoffs, but that doesn't mean we can't plan ahead for Super Bowl LX. For those of you who just can't with Roman numerals, thats Super Bowl 60, and it's taking place this year at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA, on February 8, starting at 6:30 p.m. ET.&#160;
Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the championship game will be broadcast on Super Bowl Sunday on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. And it's not just the game that we're excited for, either. This year's halftime performer is singer and rapper Bad Bunny, and there will be pre-gam...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Invincible&#8217; Season 4 Brings the War Home in March</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/invincible-season-4-trailer-amazon-2000712828</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712828</guid>
      <description>Dinosaurs, dads, and demons all threaten to give Mark a hard time when 'Invincible' returns in two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This group of workers is winning the AI adoption race</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478672/this-group-of-workers-is-winning-the-ai-adoption-race</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478672/this-group-of-workers-is-winning-the-ai-adoption-race</guid>
      <description>With fewer practical constraints and more direct benefits, independently employed professionals are leveraging the technology at higher rates
After spending much of his career in marketing, Daniel Hebert pivoted into Software as a Service (SaaS) sales for a high-growth startup in 2018. But what started out as a dream job soon turned into a nightmare....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
