<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 23:23:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Too busy even for Santa? Japanese PC maker forced to stop sales due to deluge of orders</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/too-busy-even-for-santa-japanese-pc-maker-forced-to-stop-sales-due-to-deluge-of-orders</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KmiM2mmzBhiMehReuAXfum</guid>
      <description>Mouse Computer halts all PC product sales due to massive order surge, component shortages, and disrupted New Year promotional plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's two new speakers will deliver crisp audio while blending into your decor</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/samsungs-two-new-speakers-will-deliver-crisp-audio-while-blending-into-your-decor-230053770.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 23:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1371f83b-c3e9-452b-a7d9-d78aa20e5608</guid>
      <description>Samsung is adding two brand new speakers to its audio lineup, along with updated soundbars boosted with AI features. While not as inconspicuous as the Samsung Frame, the new WiFi speakers, called the Music Studio 5 and 7, were designed to blend into your living room's atmosphere with their minimalist design. However, if you're looking for a more convenient option, Samsung also updated its flagship HW-Q990H soundbar, while also introducing the more affordable choice of the HW-QS90H.
Samsung built the Music Studio 5 with a four-inch woofer and dual tweeters, pairing them with a built-in waveguid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two new wireless Samsung speakers for 2026 lean into aesthetics</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850481/two-new-wireless-samsung-speakers-for-2026-lean-into-aesthetics</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-27T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850481</guid>
      <description>For years, Samsung has made products that try to camouflage what they are by displaying works of art. The Frame TV is the most famous example, but the company also released the Music Frame, a speaker disguised as a picture frame, at last year's CES. Now, instead of hiding a speaker with a piece of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the cheapest OCuLink mini PC you can buy right now &#8212; NucBox K15 costs just $360 barebone and supports up to 24TB SSD</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-is-the-cheapest-oculink-mini-pc-you-can-buy-right-now-nucbox-k15-costs-just-usd360-barebone-and-supports-up-to-24tb-ssd</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yskWJSknNEjkLYbWEs6sod</guid>
      <description>The NucBox K15 is a $360 mini PC supporting extensive SSD storage, quad display outputs, and hybrid Intel CPU performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is hiring a new Head of Preparedness to try to predict and mitigate AI's harms</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/openai-is-hiring-a-new-head-of-preparedness-to-try-to-predict-and-mitigate-ais-harms-220330486.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 22:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f08d742-f952-4b3f-a1b5-13ad710de592</guid>
      <description>OpenAI is looking for a new Head of Preparedness who can help it anticipate the potential harms of its models and how they can be abused, in order to guide the company's safety strategy. It comes at the end of a year that's seen OpenAI hit with numerous accusations about ChatGPT's impacts on users' mental health, including a few wrongful death lawsuits. In a post on X about the position, OpenAI CEO Sam Altman acknowledged that the "potential impact of models on mental health was something we saw a preview of in 2025," along with other "real challenges" that have arisen alongside models' capabi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That's a crossover we never saw coming - Facebook borrows the Linux scheduler from the Steam Deck to help run its data centers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/thats-a-crossover-we-never-saw-coming-facebook-borrows-the-linux-scheduler-from-the-steam-deck-to-help-run-its-data-centers</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kU56KPzcwAjQiw7azdu369</guid>
      <description>Meta is testing a Steam Deck Linux scheduler on servers, betting that latency-driven design scales beyond gaming into production infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
