<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:45:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Akai's MPC XL groovebox is the most powerful device the company has ever made</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/akais-mpc-xl-groovebox-is-the-most-powerful-device-the-company-has-ever-made-183952483.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37d85553-27e5-46c0-86d2-789438fed154</guid>
      <description>Akai just revealed its most powerful standalone groovebox, the MPC XL. For the uninitiated, the MPC has been around since the 1980s and pretty much defined hip hop from that era. The line has continuously iterated to keep up with the times and the XL looks to be the baddest of them all.
First of all, it offers four times the processing power of previous MPCs, which is enough to load up to 32 virtual instruments at the same time. This is assisted by a full 16GB of RAM, which is a whole lot in this era of AI tomfoolery. The XL can handle 16 audio tracks simultaneously. In my experience with prev...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung&#8217;s discounted microSD Express card more than doubles your Switch 2 storage</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/864404/samsung-p9-microsd-express-card-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T13:36:47-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864404</guid>
      <description>If you buy digital games for the Nintendo Switch 2, Samsung&#8217;s P9 microSD Express card offers an easier way to expand your storage without constantly deleting games to make room. It&#8217;s cheaper than other microSD cards, and it&#8217;s even better value right now, with the 512GB version priced at $79.99 ($40 off) &#8212; just $5 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X open sources its algorithm: 5 ways businesses can benefit</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/x-open-sources-its-algorithm-5-ways-businesses-can-benefit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1qFuWHbkIXTB3z7RR1q4zV</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's social network X (formerly known as Twitter) last night released some of the code and architecture of its overhauled social recommendation algorithm under a permissive, enterprise-friendly open source license (Apache 2.0) on Github, allowing for commercial usage and modification. This is the algorithm that decides which X posts and accounts to show to which users on the social network.The new X algorithm, as opposed toto the manual heuristic rules and legacy models in the past, is based on a "Transformer" architecture powered by its parent company, xAI&#8217;s, Grok AI language model. Th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life is Strange will bring the Max and Chloe story to an end in new game</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/864438/life-is-strange-reunion-release-date-max-chloe</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T13:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864438</guid>
      <description>A little over a decade ago, Life is Strange burst onto the scene with a unique blend of teen drama and interactive storytelling. That first game told the story of Max Caulfield, who had the supernatural ability to reverse time, and her best friend Chloe Price. Now developer Deck Nine Games is finally bringing their [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life is Strange: Reunion has been revealed and is the 'emotional conclusion' of Max and Chloe's story</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/life-is-strange-reunion-has-been-revealed-and-is-the-emotional-conclusion-of-max-and-chloes-story</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FTEcVjZUd8jdSYs7APp84J</guid>
      <description>Square Enix has revealed Life is Strange: Reunion, the next entry in the Life is Strange series, with the fan-favorite Chloe set to return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The memory price hike crisis could get even worse, as US threatens 100% tariffs &#8211; this is how it could affect you</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/the-memory-price-hike-crisis-could-get-even-worse-as-us-threatens-100-percent-tariffs-this-is-how-it-could-affect-you</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">z7W8uHN558vWNffYELa7ih</guid>
      <description>Consumers in the US now face an additional danger in terms of factors that could seriously hike the price of laptops and PCs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth&#8217;s Getting Blasted by the Largest Solar Radiation Storm in Over 20 Years</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/earths-getting-blasted-by-the-largest-solar-radiation-storm-in-over-20-years-2000711972</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711972</guid>
      <description>Storms of this severity can impact satellites, astronauts, and some commercial flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth is having some issues, so let's enjoy the Webb telescope's new nebula image</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/earth-is-having-some-issues-so-lets-enjoy-the-webb-telescopes-new-nebula-image-181049901.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aa9c0fd-3ffb-4b17-874c-cf10daccfa2e</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, you just need to give your mind a little vacation. And these days, outer space sounds like as good a destination as any. Thankfully, the James Webb Space Telescope (JWST) is here to give us a dazzling new image of the Helix Nebula.Discovered in the early 19th century, the Helix Nebula resides in the constellation Aquarius. (Cue The 5th Dimension.) At about 655 light-years away, it's one of Earth's closest planetary nebulae. When zoomed farther out, it's easy to see why it's been nicknamed the Eye of God or Eye of Sauron. This 2004 image from the Hubble telescope illustrates that.A w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#160;: le S&#233;nat am&#233;ricain rejette les coupes massives voulues par Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/nasa-le-senat-americain-rejette-les-coupes-massives-voulues-par-trump.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321197</guid>
      <description>C'est un ouf de soulagement pour l'agence spatiale am&#233;ricaine. Le S&#233;nat vient d'adopter un budget qui maintient les capacit&#233;s de la NASA &#224; flot, rejetant fermement le plan de la Maison Blanche qui visait &#224; amputer l'agence d'un quart de ses financements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huawei Mate X7 : le pliable qui veut enterrer les reflex est disponible &#224; prix d&#8217;or</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/huawei/2949461_huawei-mate-x7-le-pliable-qui-veut-enterrer-les-reflex-est-disponible-a-prix-dor</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/huawei/2949461_huawei-mate-x7-le-pliable-qui-veut-enterrer-les-reflex-est-disponible-a-prix-dor</guid>
      <description>
Ce 20 janvier 2026, Huawei lance officiellement le Mate X7 dans l'Hexagone. Au menu : une prouesse d'ing&#233;nierie qui fait tenir un setup photo tr&#232;s complet dans un ch&#226;ssis ultra-fin.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE becomes one of the most-blocked accounts on Bluesky after its verification</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/ice-becomes-one-of-the-most-blocked-accounts-on-bluesky-after-its-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083840</guid>
      <description>ICE has been verified on Bluesky, and quickly becomes one of the top most-blocked accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail startup Another raises a $2.5M seed to help sell excess inventory</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/20/retail-startup-another-raises-a-2-5m-seed-to-help-sell-excess-inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3083775</guid>
      <description>Another raises a $2.5 million seed round led by Anthemis FIL and Westbound to help retailers with off-channel inventory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laika&#8217;s Next Film Hits Theaters in October, but Not in the Way You&#8217;d Expect</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/laikas-next-film-hits-theaters-in-october-but-not-in-the-way-youd-expect-2000712001</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712001</guid>
      <description>'Wildwood,' directed by Travis Knight, will be distributed by Fathom Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;A new era of e-bike use&#8217; or &#8216;the dumbest ebike law ever&#8217;? E-bike restrictions are hitting New Jersey, and I&#8217;m worried it&#8217;s just the beginning</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/bikes/a-new-era-of-e-bike-use-or-the-dumbest-ebike-law-ever-e-bike-restrictions-are-hitting-new-jersey-and-im-worried-its-just-the-beginning</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jAoFqbsXhkeKBt84jgz6cg</guid>
      <description>New Jersey has entered &#8216;A new era of e-bike use,&#8217; but many hope its overly restrictive rules won&#8217;t spread &#8211;I worry they will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest camera store reveals its surprising best-selling cameras and lenses for 2025 &#8212; and it was a great year for compacts and zoom lenses</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-lenses/worlds-largest-camera-store-reveals-its-surprising-best-selling-cameras-and-lenses-for-2025-and-it-was-a-great-year-for-compacts-and-zooms</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ywTpXFJCfNDKRowCKvpttS</guid>
      <description>Yodobashi Camera, Japan's largest camera store, has revealed its best-selling cameras and lenses for 2025, and the 20 product-strong shortlists show some surprising trends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best iPad deals you can get right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21280354/best-ipad-deals-apple</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T12:57:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21280354/best-ipad-deals-apple</guid>
      <description>While the best iPad deals usually land during major sale events like Black Friday,&#160;many great iPad deals are available outside of those times. The day-to-day discounts come and go like changing winds, so there&#8217;s often some amount to be saved, particularly on Apple&#8217;s most affordable iPad, the iPad Mini, and the latest iPad Air. Hell, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chute des ventes et fermeture de bureaux : OnePlus est en train de dispara&#238;tre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/oneplus/2949621_chute-des-ventes-et-fermeture-de-bureaux-oneplus-est-en-train-de-disparaitre</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/oneplus/2949621_chute-des-ventes-et-fermeture-de-bureaux-oneplus-est-en-train-de-disparaitre</guid>
      <description>
Une enqu&#234;te explosive vient de confirmer ce que nous sentions tous depuis des mois : OnePlus est en train d'&#234;tre d&#233;mantel&#233;. Bureaux ferm&#233;s, &#233;quipes licenci&#233;es, ventes en chute libre... La marque qui voulait &#171; ne jamais se contenter &#187; est doucement mise sous assistance respiratoire par Oppo.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozempic Brings Back the &#8216;Mac vs PC&#8217; Ads for the GLP-1 Era</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ozempic-brings-back-the-mac-vs-pc-ads-for-the-glp-1-era-2000711982</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711982</guid>
      <description>Novo Nordisk is worried about competition and wants to be seen as the cool kid... by using a 20-year-old ad format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi les voitures prot&#232;gent moins bien les femmes que les hommes, et pourquoi &#231;a va changer</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2948127_pourquoi-les-voitures-protegent-moins-bien-les-femmes-que-les-hommes-et-pourquoi-ca-va-changer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2948127_pourquoi-les-voitures-protegent-moins-bien-les-femmes-que-les-hommes-et-pourquoi-ca-va-changer</guid>
      <description>
Si les constructeurs aiment toujours communiquer sur la s&#233;curit&#233; de leurs voitures, il aura fallu attendre 2026 pour qu'un mannequin f&#233;minin de crash-test soit officiellement pr&#233;sent&#233;. De quoi augurer d'une s&#233;curit&#233; accrue, et ce pour l'int&#233;gralit&#233; de la population.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The coating is sprayed onto each smartwatch, then baked to help cure the coating' &#8212; Garmin's new Cerakote Edition of its tactix 8 outdoor watch offers 'long-lasting durability' compared to the standard polymer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/the-coating-is-sprayed-onto-each-smartwatch-then-baked-to-help-cure-the-coating-garmins-new-cerakote-edition-of-its-tactix-8-outdoor-watch-offers-long-lasting-durability-compared-to-the-standard-polymer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SVMFmCgtBAtvawcJsu65aA</guid>
      <description>Garmin tactix 8 gets an ultra-tough Cerakote coating for enhanced durability in the field, plus new Garmin golf equipment drops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Inter vs. Arsenal online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/inter-milan-arsenal-2026-champions-league-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07xn6sy2jENlLfobDPFdeGv</guid>
      <description>How to watch the Champions League for free. Watch Inter Milan vs. Arsenal in the Champions League for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy's massive Super Bowl sale is live &#8212; here are 15 deals I'd buy on big-screen TVs, air fryers, soundbars, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/best-buys-massive-super-bowl-sale-is-live-here-are-15-deals-id-buy-on-big-screen-tvs-air-fryers-soundbars-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7joppB7FmUMmSvi8gSwUvQ</guid>
      <description>Best Buy has launched a huge Super Bowl sale, and I'm rounding up today's 15 best deals, including up to 55% off big-screen TVs, soundbars, air fryers, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang claims it hacked into Hyatt systems, says it has stolen data for sale</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/ransomware-gang-claims-it-hacked-into-hyatt-systems-says-it-has-stolen-data-for-sale</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbc2mTAxLDYRFvu9D6qP55</guid>
      <description>NightSpire claims to have stolen almost 50GB of Hyatt files, including login credentials for CMS systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;Apple Watch Ultra 3 n&#8217;&#233;chappe pas aux soldes d&#8217;hiver et voit son prix passer sous les 700 &#8364;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949375_lapple-watch-ultra-3-nechappe-pas-aux-soldes-dhiver-et-voit-son-prix-passer-sous-les-700-e</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2949375_lapple-watch-ultra-3-nechappe-pas-aux-soldes-dhiver-et-voit-son-prix-passer-sous-les-700-e</guid>
      <description>
D&#233;voil&#233;e en septembre dernier, l'Apple Watch Ultra 3 est l'actuelle repr&#233;sentante de la s&#233;rie de tocantes connect&#233;es haut de gamme de la marque &#224; la Pomme. Pendant les soldes d'hiver, Rakuten l'affiche &#224; 669,99 euros au lieu de 899 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s Star Search will let you vote to decide who wins</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/864424/netflix-star-search-live-voting</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T12:19:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864424</guid>
      <description>Though Netflix's upcoming Star Search reboot will feature a panel of celebrity judges, viewers are going to have a hand in choosing which contestants win the competition. Ahead of Star Search's premiere tonight, Netflix has announced that it is launching a new real-time voting functionality that will give you the ability to tell the streamer [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The giant 55-inch Samsung Odyssey Ark curved gaming monitor is on sale for $1,500 off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-20-samsung-odyssey-ark-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">006krgGkGVAWiHkKBXZoomJ</guid>
      <description>The 55-inch Samsung Odyssey Ark curved gaming monitor is on sale at Woot for $1,199.99, down from the list price of $2,699.99. That's a 56% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN deal: Two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-deal-two-year-plans-are-up-to-78-percent-off-right-now-180602610.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to up your privacy game on the internet in the new year, you can do so for a little less than usual thanks to ExpressVPN's latest deal. Its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now: the Advanced tier is on sale for $101 for two years, plus four additional free months. That works out to $3.59 per month during the promotional period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pivoting to Smart Glasses Is Getting Out of Hand</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/pivoting-to-smart-glasses-is-getting-out-of-hand-2000711938</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711938</guid>
      <description>Going all-in on smart glasses is either going to be a really smart decision or a really dumb one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tottenham vs Borussia Dortmund Free Streams: How to watch Champions League 2025/26 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/tottenham-vs-borussia-dortmund-champions-league-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mpA2XvCH6R4SVACMWLCMSM</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Tottenham vs Borussia Dortmund live streams from anywhere, with both Thomas Frank and Niko Kovac under pressure ahead of this UCL tie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 : quelles sont les offres &#224; saisir en ce mardi 20 janvier ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-quelles-sont-les-offres-a-saisir-en-ce-mardi-20-janvier</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941853_soldes-dhiver-2026-quelles-sont-les-offres-a-saisir-en-ce-mardi-20-janvier</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver suivent leur chemin et nous arrivons d&#233;j&#224; presque &#224; la troisi&#232;me d&#233;marque ! Au programme : toujours plus d'offres Tech &#224; prix cass&#233;s, que ce soient les smartphones, les tablettes, les t&#233;l&#233;viseurs 4K, et surtout les ordinateurs portables, gaming ou de bureautique. M&#234;me le gaming s'invite de plus en plus dans la danse des promotions.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firehound ranks apps that leak your data. These are the 10 worst.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/apps-leak-data-worst-firehound-rankings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06wfMbnbNVsQYEOgSOK8SEw</guid>
      <description>Firehound ranked the apps that leak the most data. Make sure to check your apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Box 5G vs Bbox 5G WiFi 7 : qui propose la meilleure offre en France ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2949477_free-box-5g-vs-bbox-5g-wifi-7-qui-propose-la-meilleure-offre-en-france</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2949477_free-box-5g-vs-bbox-5g-wifi-7-qui-propose-la-meilleure-offre-en-france</guid>
      <description>
Bouygues Telecom a d&#233;voil&#233; sa nouvelle box 5G et pour la premi&#232;re fois, il s'agit d'une v&#233;ritable Bbox. Que vaut cette nouvelle offre face &#224; la box 5G de Free ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Pok&#233;mon TCG deals to shop this week</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-20-best-pokemon-tcg-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00kivX63KRYZDmLhuLXHLRg</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 20, these are some of the best Pok&#233;mon TCG deals to shop this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Research Debunks Trump and RFK Jr.&#8217;s Claims Linking Tylenol to Autism</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/new-research-debunks-trump-and-rfk-jr-s-claims-linking-tylenol-to-autism-2000711954</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711954</guid>
      <description>It's the latest research to find no clear link between maternal acetaminophen use and a higher autism risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You should buy an electric car now, UK government says &#8211; while ignoring 5 massive roadblocks that affect millions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/you-should-buy-an-electric-car-now-uk-government-says-while-ignoring-5-massive-roadblocks-that-affect-millions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">T8TCjxoHd56JrHRG5MSZ9n</guid>
      <description>The UK government says there's "never been a better time to switch" to an EV, but five big roadblocks are still standing in the way of many.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guerre en Ukraine&#160;: les donn&#233;es du front, nouvel or noir de l&#8217;IA</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/guerre-en-ukraine-les-donnees-du-front-nouvel-or-noir-de-lia.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321334</guid>
      <description>L'Ukraine va partager les donn&#233;es enregistr&#233;es sur le front avec ses alli&#233;s afin d'entra&#238;ner leurs mod&#232;les d'intelligence artificielle. Un atout strat&#233;gique de poids, &#224; la crois&#233;e des enjeux militaires, technologiques et diplomatiques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meilleur Google Pixel (2026) : le guide d&#8217;achat complet</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2043088_quel-smartphone-google-pixel-choisir</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2043088_quel-smartphone-google-pixel-choisir</guid>
      <description>
Google propose ses propres smartphones, nomm&#233;s "Pixel". Chez Frandroid, nous les testons tous : on vous explique ici la gamme Pixel ainsi que le mod&#232;le qu'il vous faut.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to balance intuition and strategic thinking</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468675/how-to-balance-intuition-and-strategic-thinking</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T17:01:01</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468675/how-to-balance-intuition-and-strategic-thinking</guid>
      <description>Why your gut and dashboard need each other.
Balancing gut feelings with hard data isn&#8217;t a soft skill.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Jones&#8217; Comeback Was Never Going to Be Easy</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/indiana-jones-future-lucasfilm-kathleen-kennedy-2000711931</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711931</guid>
      <description>After 'Dial of Destiny' and 'The Great Circle', charting a path for Lucasfilm's *other* big franchise to return will take work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix has introduced a new live vote feature that'll let you decide the outcome of some shows &#8212; but not everyone will be able to use it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/netflix-has-introduced-a-new-live-vote-feature-thatll-let-you-decide-the-outcome-of-some-shows-but-not-everyone-will-be-able-to-use-it</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RLdANuLktarQr4RnN4XBuH</guid>
      <description>Netflix's new star-based live voting feature sounds great in practice, but is it a novelty that'll eventually lose its shine?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2026 Serpentine Pavilion is a clever, curvaceous trick</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91477703/the-2026-serpentine-pavilion-is-a-clever-curvaceous-trick</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-20T17:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91477703/the-2026-serpentine-pavilion-is-a-clever-curvaceous-trick</guid>
      <description>See one of the most prestigious installations of the year.
Curving walls of clay brick and the dappled light of a forest canopy make up the design of the 2026 Serpentine Pavilion, the annual architectural installation that has become one of the field&#8217;s most prestigious commissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C&#8217;est la grande braderie des soldes chez Samsung, avec des prix bas sur les Galaxy Z Fold, Galaxy S, Galaxy Book&#8230;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2939747_galaxy-z-fold-6-galaxy-s25-les-16-meilleures-offres-samsung-lors-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2939747_galaxy-z-fold-6-galaxy-s25-les-16-meilleures-offres-samsung-lors-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
La 3e d&#233;marque des soldes approche &#224; grands pas et les offres restent toujours attractives, notamment du c&#244;t&#233; des produits Samsung. Entre smartphones pliant &#224; -50 %, TV OLED en r&#233;duction et &#233;crans Ultra Wide OLED, il y en a pour tous les go&#251;ts.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shop the best Apple deals this week: iPad Pro, MacBook Air, and more</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-20-best-apple-deals</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02Tg3dUp6LMh4OnHRcM0cB3</guid>
      <description>The best Apple deals this week include the M4 MacBook Air, M5 iPad Pro, Apple Watch Ultra 2, and more. Save up to $250.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suri's eco-friendly electric toothbrush that offers 'sustainability and performance at its absolute best' just got a big price cut on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/oral-health/suris-eco-friendly-electric-toothbrush-that-offers-sustainability-and-performance-at-its-absolute-best-just-got-a-big-price-cut-on-amazon</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PUk5gk2rsEfBBjMiT2XJcZ</guid>
      <description>The Suri 2.0 Sonic Electric Toothbrush is a fantastic alternative to plastic options from Oral-B and Philips &#8211; and it just dropped to its lowest price since Black Friday on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes d&#8217;hiver : passer l&#8217;aspirateur et laver les sols devient un plaisir avec ces mod&#232;les en promotion. Le top 10 des offres</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941951_soldes-dhiver-passer-laspirateur-et-laver-les-sols-devient-un-plaisir-avec-ces-modeles-en-promotion-le-top-10-des-offres</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2941951_soldes-dhiver-passer-laspirateur-et-laver-les-sols-devient-un-plaisir-avec-ces-modeles-en-promotion-le-top-10-des-offres</guid>
      <description>
Aspirer, nettoyer, laver... Les aspirateurs-robots sont un v&#233;ritable gain de temps dans nos quotidiens bien remplis, mais ils ont un co&#251;t. M&#234;me chose pour les aspirateurs-balais qui sont de v&#233;ritables prouesses de technologie. Pour ces soldes d'hiver, voici notre top des meilleures offres.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
