<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:23:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Massive data breach sees credit card details of over 5.6 million victims leaked - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/massive-data-breach-sees-credit-card-details-of-over-5-6-million-victims-leaked-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">APHXKQuV9Tqizg6PS8J9sV</guid>
      <description>Affected 700Credit customers are being offered free credit monitoring and reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s &#8216;dark web report&#8217; feature will no longer be available starting in February</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/googles-dark-web-report-feature-will-no-longer-be-available-starting-in-february/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076072</guid>
      <description>Google has revealed that its &#8220;dark web report&#8221; feature will be discontinued starting February 16, 2026. Launched initially about a year and a half ago, this tool aimed to help users monitor their personal information on the dark web For some users, the dark web report seemed like a valuable tool, scanning various data breach [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is recruiting Big Tech workers for the government</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844804/trump-tech-force-usds-apple-google-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T14:18:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844804</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump will recruit workers from Amazon, Apple, Google, Meta, Microsoft, and other tech giants to form the US Tech Force, a new program that aims to "modernize the federal government," according to an announcement on Monday. Under the new program, Trump plans to hire around 1,000 technology specialists to work across federal agencies [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU prepares ground for wider data retention &#8211; and VPN providers are among the targets</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/the-eu-prepares-ground-for-wider-data-retention-and-vpn-providers-are-among-the-targets</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vcYNnAcMnPBwGxa7RCi6UQ</guid>
      <description>With the Chat Control bill entering its final stage, the EU Council has been busy thinking about what a new data retention framework could look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Fitbits for your fitness and health</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22982833/best-fitbit-watch-fitness-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:59:38-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22982833/best-fitbit-watch-fitness-tracker</guid>
      <description>In 2025, you might wonder if Fitbit is still relevant. Despite being acquired by Google, Fitbit remains one of the most recognizable names in the industry. Fitbit trackers aren&#8217;t meant for the most hardcore of athletes, but they&#8217;re still excellent devices for tracking overall activity as well as monitoring certain health and wellness metrics, like [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook prend une d&#233;cision incompr&#233;hensible : fin de Messenger sur Windows et Mac</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2911001_facebook-prend-une-decision-incomprehensible-fin-de-messenger-sur-windows-et-mac</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/windows/2911001_facebook-prend-une-decision-incomprehensible-fin-de-messenger-sur-windows-et-mac</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez vu ce pop-up en ouvrant Messenger sur votre Mac ce matin ? Ce n'est pas un bug. Meta tue officiellement ses applications de bureau pour Windows et macOS. Alors que WhatsApp gagne en fonctionnalit&#233;s natives, Messenger fait un bond de dix ans en arri&#232;re. La logique m'&#233;chappe.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Best Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and Horror TV Shows of 2025</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-12-best-sci-fi-fantasy-and-horror-tv-shows-of-2025-2000698626</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698626</guid>
      <description>In a year full of standout shows, io9 picks the very best genre stories to hit the small screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Things season 5, volume 2's trailer teases a character's death and I'm already terrified</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/stranger-things-season-5-volume-2s-trailer-teases-a-characters-death-and-im-already-terrified</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xn7otaiTyYZdCgwRoTL9Sa</guid>
      <description>The Stranger Things season 5, volume 2 trailer is here and you won't be able to take your eyes off it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie&amp;#8217;s delayed shooter Marathon launches in March</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844780/bungie-marathon-march-launch-delay</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:42:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844780</guid>
      <description>Bungie's Marathon, its upcoming extraction shooter that it delayed from a planned September release, will now launch in March 2026. The studio is "targeting" a price of $39.99, and "purchasing Marathon will give you full access to the game, including a roadmap of free gameplay updates as the year progresses," according to a blog post. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift guide: TechCrunch&#8217;s favorite things</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/gift-guide-techcrunchs-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075952</guid>
      <description>As tech journalists we have a lot of opinions. So if we really like something, it's probably good!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon sells MOBA March of Giants to Ubisoft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/amazon-sells-moba-march-of-giants-to-ubisoft-183948291.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3db79d71-d375-4ff8-8b02-f502e57de22c</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft is moving deeper into MOBAs after buying March of Giants  from Amazon and acquiring the team that made the game. As part of the agreement, Amazon will help promote March of Giants on Twitch. The deal is expected to close on December 16There&#8217;s no release date as yet for March of Giants. Amazon announced the free-to-play game back in August and there was a closed alpha playtest the following month. The next playtest will take place in 2026.  The next major update for March of Giants will include &#8220;new giants, expanded competitive modes and foundational systems designed to support long-ter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We filled the internet with garbage, and now Slop is the word of the year &#8212; nice going, AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/we-filled-the-internet-with-garbage-and-now-slop-is-the-word-of-the-year-nice-going-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7uCp4rDG2KVMuLJD4wGZ7h</guid>
      <description>Merriam-Webster has named "Slop" as its word of the year. Here's why this is all about AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messaging app Freedom Chat exposes user phone numbers and more - here's what we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/messaging-app-freedom-chat-exposes-user-phone-numbers-and-more-heres-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yx6hTuQg7pxzQyTNrmiHsN</guid>
      <description>A patch was released to fix the bugs and users were forced to update their PIN codes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lidar-maker Luminar files for bankruptcy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844755/luminar-lidar-chapter-11-bankruptcy</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:32:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844755</guid>
      <description>Luminar, the lidar manufacturer that rode a wave of self-driving car hype to land deals with major automakers like Volvo and Mercedes-Benz, filed for bankruptcy Monday. The company has been mired in a legal fight with its founder and former CEO, Austin Russell, who was ousted earlier this year following an ethics inquiry. As part [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok is rebranding ice-hockey rinks as &#8216;boy aquariums&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460524/tiktok-ice-hockey-boys-aquarium</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460524/tiktok-ice-hockey-boys-aquarium</guid>
      <description>While it&#8217;s a tongue-in-cheek joke, the trend risks playing into harmful stereotypes of female sports fans. 
&#8220;There are boy aquariums all over the United States,&#8221; a TikTok creator explains in a recent post.&#160;&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How &#8216;slop&#8217; became the defining word of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460529/how-slop-became-the-defining-word-of-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T18:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460529/how-slop-became-the-defining-word-of-2025</guid>
      <description>AI spam, fake videos, and junk content turned a centuries-old word into the perfect label for today&#8217;s internet.
It&#8217;s official: 2025 was the year of slop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test du Ecovacs Deebot mini : le mini robot aspirateur qui a tout d&#8217;un grand</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/test/2860197_test-du-ecovacs-deebot-mini-le-mini-robot-aspirateur-qui-a-tout-dun-grand</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/test/2860197_test-du-ecovacs-deebot-mini-le-mini-robot-aspirateur-qui-a-tout-dun-grand</guid>
      <description>
L&#8217;Ecovacs Deebot Mini est l&#8217;un des rares mini-robots aspirateurs du march&#233;. Pens&#233; pour les petits int&#233;rieurs, il se veut aussi efficace que s&#233;duisant gr&#226;ce &#224; son format compact. Alors que la concurrence reste assez minimaliste, Ecovacs propose un v&#233;ritable robot aspirateur-laveur, aussi complet que les mod&#232;les classiques, avec une base capable d&#8217;autovidange et de nettoyer la vadrouille. Sur le papier, c&#8217;est tr&#232;s s&#233;duisant. Mais cela se v&#233;rifie-t-il au quotidien ?
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Slop' is Merriam-Webster's word of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/slop-is-merriam-websters-word-of-the-year-181903322.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d58b26b1-424e-4b08-82ea-53e6e099ce84</guid>
      <description>Merriam-Webster has selected "slop" for the dictionary company's 2025 word of the year. The leading lexicographers define slop as "digital content of low quality that is produced usually in quantity by means of artificial intelligence." We've seen an absolute deluge of AI slop this year, from fake movie trailers on YouTube to AI-generated bands on Spotify. Not even food delivery like Uber Eats could escape the onslaught of AI-generated garbage that no one asked for.
It's gotten to the point that half the videos my well-meaning parents send me on social media are AI-generated videos of dogs. Th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Is Testing Robotaxis Without Safety Drivers &#8212; or Riders</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tesla-is-testing-robotaxis-without-safety-drivers-or-riders-2000699814</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699814</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk confirmed that Tesla is testing its robotaxis without any safety monitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best white elephant gifts worth fighting over for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/the-10-best-white-elephant-gifts-worth-fighting-over-for-2025-150516281.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">167b1092-71dd-42b0-b152-e8240159f089</guid>
      <description>If you have a white elephant gift exchange at work this year or with friends and family, there&#8217;s a good chance you&#8217;re scrambling right now to find a good gift &#8212; or decipher what even makes a good white elephant gift. The possible origins of the term &#8220;white elephant&#8221; provide one way of looking at it: According to legend, the King of Siam would give a white elephant to courtiers who had upset them. It was a far more devious punishment than simply having them executed. The recipient had no choice but to simply thank the king for such an opulent gift, knowing that they likely could not afford the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With New &#8216;Ask this Book&#8217; Kindle Feature, Amazon Wants Lost Readers to Ask AI for Help</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kindle-ask-this-book-ai-2000699503</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699503</guid>
      <description>There used to be this thing called &#8220;flipping back a few pages.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Michael Cera Return to Edgar Wright&#8217;s World In New &#8216;Running Man&#8217; Clip</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/michael-cera-edgar-wright-running-man-2000699737</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699737</guid>
      <description>Glen Powell stars in the adaptation of the Stephen King novel, which hits digital December 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cadillac and Chevy are getting native Apple Music</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/844697/gm-cadillac-chevy-apple-music-native</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T13:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844697</guid>
      <description>General Motors is adding native Apple Music to the infotainment systems of select 2025 model year Cadillac and Chevrolet vehicles, the company announced today. The news comes as the automaker is racing to add more native app experiences to some of its vehicles to make up for the absence of popular phone mirroring services like [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads adds new communities, tests badges for highly engaged members</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/threads-adds-new-communities-tests-badges-for-highly-engaged-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075839</guid>
      <description>Threads, which has more than 150 million daily active users, adds more communities to its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP price takes another hit today as digital asset slide continues. What&#8217;s happening with the crypto market?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460560/xrp-price-update-today-crypto-down-again-why-falling</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T18:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460560/xrp-price-update-today-crypto-down-again-why-falling</guid>
      <description>The native token of the XRP ledger launched by Ripple Labs has struggled to stay above a key psychological threshold over the last several days.
The value of cryptocurrency XRP continues to slide, dipping as low as $1.92 as of Monday morning. XRP&#8212;the native crypto token of the XRP Ledger, created by Ripple Labs&#8212;has seen its value hover around the $2 mark for roughly a month, and has been on a downward trend since late July, when values peaked at more than $3.50.&#160;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin just leaked its Vivosmart 6 tracker &#8211; and it might come with one major upgrade over its predecessor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/fitness-trackers/garmin-just-leaked-its-vivosmart-6-tracker-and-it-might-come-with-one-major-upgrade-over-its-predecessor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54X4c9oXZPzpKzYbZNmxFQ</guid>
      <description>Garmin&#8217;s Vivosmart 6 fitness tracker just leaked out with a tempting new feature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Season 2 Is Opening Up the Vault a Little Early</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-season-2-early-release-date-amazon-2000699757</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699757</guid>
      <description>Want to return to the wasteland a little earlier than Amazon planned? Okie dokie!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone, MacBook&#160;: pr&#233;parez-vous &#224; une flamb&#233;e des prix en 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/iphone-macbook-preparez-vous-a-une-flambee-des-prix-en-2026.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315470</guid>
      <description>M&#234;me les g&#233;ants ont leurs faiblesses. Apple s'appr&#234;te &#224; ren&#233;gocier des contrats cruciaux pour la m&#233;moire de ses appareils, et la facture risque d'&#234;tre sal&#233;e. Une augmentation des co&#251;ts de production qui pourrait bien finir par se r&#233;percuter sur le ticket de caisse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C&#8217;est une premi&#232;re historique : la marque chinoise Chery veut s&#8217;attaquer officiellement aux 24 Heures du Mans</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/chery/2910869_cest-une-premiere-historique-la-marque-chinoise-chery-veut-sattaquer-officiellement-aux-24-heures-du-mans</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/chery/2910869_cest-une-premiere-historique-la-marque-chinoise-chery-veut-sattaquer-officiellement-aux-24-heures-du-mans</guid>
      <description>
Le constructeur chinois Chery, via sa marque premium Exeed, vient d'annoncer son intention de participer aux mythiques 24 Heures du Mans d'ici cinq ans.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Time to Give MP3 Players a Second Chance</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/its-time-to-give-mp3-players-a-second-chance-2000699677</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699677</guid>
      <description>Spotify ain't what it used to be, and we may have the perfect antidote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging &#8216;Super Flu&#8217; Strain Is Spreading Fast. Here&#8217;s What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/emerging-super-flu-strain-is-spreading-fast-heres-what-you-need-to-know-2000699701</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699701</guid>
      <description>The UK is facing a surge of hospitalizations fueled by the novel variant subclade K. And the U.S. is likely next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lidar-maker Luminar files for bankruptcy</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/15/lidar-maker-luminar-files-for-bankruptcy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3075970</guid>
      <description>The filing marks the end of a tumultuous year full of layoffs, executive departures, and piling debts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon fait un super prix ce SSD externe ultra&#8209;rapide de 2 To avant la flamb&#233;e des prix du stockage</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2910611_amazon-fait-un-super-prix-ce-ssd-externe-ultra%e2%80%91rapide-de-2-to-avant-la-flambee-des-prix-du-stockage</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2910611_amazon-fait-un-super-prix-ce-ssd-externe-ultra%e2%80%91rapide-de-2-to-avant-la-flambee-des-prix-du-stockage</guid>
      <description>
&#192; l&#8217;heure o&#249; les prix de la m&#233;moire vive s&#8217;envolent et que la p&#233;nurie menace les composants, le Crucial X10 Pro se pr&#233;sente comme une solution de stockage rapide, robuste et abordable. Actuellement en promotion dans sa version 2 To, ce SSD externe devient un alli&#233; pr&#233;cieux.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurry &#8212;&#160;its your last chance to get HBO Max for free via DashPass</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-15-hbo-max-dashpass-last-chance-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">009Nbi9omqBKYFngmDLBNNE</guid>
      <description>You can still get HBO Max for free with an annual DashPass plan for one more day. Secure the streaming deal by Dec. 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This home security cam monitors your property 24/7 with 'unlimited' battery life &#8211; and it costs less than you might expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-home/this-home-security-cam-monitors-your-property-24-7-with-unlimited-battery-life-and-it-costs-less-than-you-might-expect</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HakdBXxgqcFZrCCtcptYyD</guid>
      <description>IMOU's latest point-and-tilt camera uses a solar panel, high-capacity battery, and power-efficient recording for constant surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&amp;#8217;s turning off its dark web monitoring service that scoured data breaches for your info</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/844700/google-dark-web-reports-shut-down</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-15T12:30:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844700</guid>
      <description>Google notified users in an email today that, beginning next month, it will stop sending its dark web reports, an opt-in feature that alerted users when Google detected their personal information on the dark web, as reported by 9to5Google. On January 15th, Google will stop scanning for that data, like contact info and home addresses, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the Sony Inzone M9 II 27-inch 4K gaming monitor for $250 less at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-15-sony-inzone-monitor-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01nycDSIkXuSqip7JHfLPyq</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 15, you can get the Sony Inzone M9 II 27-inch 4K gaming monitor for $698, down from $949.99, at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traveling this holiday? Save $30 on a four-pack of Apple AirTags before you take off.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-15-apple-airtags-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03ihNNADU6RseXXlyLIDQBF</guid>
      <description>A four-pack of Apple AirTags is on sale at Amazon for $69.99, down from the normal price of $99. That's a 29% discount.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
