<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:36:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Has a New Estimate for Europa&#8217;s Ice Shell, and Whoa Is It Ever Thick</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/nasa-has-a-new-estimate-for-europas-ice-shell-and-whoa-is-it-ever-thick-2000715015</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715015</guid>
      <description>Jupiter's fourth-largest moon is a main character in our search for other life-friendly places in our solar system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny startup Arcee AI built a 400B open source LLM from scratch to best Meta&#8217;s Llama</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/tiny-startup-arcee-ai-built-a-400b-open-source-llm-from-scratch-to-best-metas-llama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086608</guid>
      <description>30-person startup Arcee AI has released a 400B model called Trinity, which it says is one of the biggest open source foundation models from a US company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve been using iPhones for years, and I always turn off this major iOS feature</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/ive-been-using-iphones-for-years-and-i-always-turn-off-this-major-ios-feature</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ex9AgESpirp9xydNf8xT5U</guid>
      <description>The iPhone's always-on display feature is potentially useful, but it also drains battery, and if you have an Apple Watch you probably don't need it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to cancel Windscribe and get your money back</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-cancel-windscribe-and-get-your-money-back-173000785.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9111484-53a9-4d3d-9f79-ec1f666bcb09</guid>
      <description>Windscribe isn't a VPN for everybody, and it's not trying to be. Despite its high-achieving free plan, it didn't quite make my list of the best VPNs, largely due to alienating interface choices and swingy download speeds. Its iconoclastic approach to everything from design to pricing to its online knowledge base will likely win some customers for life and turn others off.For those in the latter camp, I've written up this guide for cancelling Windscribe. Follow the instructions below to stop Windscribe from auto-renewing, cancel third-party subscriptions, delete your account altogether and get ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I write about TV deals for a living &#8212; here&#8217;s what I&#8217;d buy to watch the Super Bowl LX</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/i-write-about-tv-deals-for-a-living-heres-what-id-buy-to-watch-the-super-bowl-lx</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CGpMwMPyQw2a5p2QBG6fdH</guid>
      <description>As TechRadar's TV deals expert, I'm listing my top 10 recommendations for watching the Super Bowl, including record-low prices on 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Should Probably Buy Wired Headphones Now</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-should-probably-buy-wired-headphones-now-2000714991</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714991</guid>
      <description>Sennheiser's new HD400U are cheap; they're cool; they're hi-fi. What more could you ask for?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus en f&#233;vrier 2026 : voici les non pas trois, mais quatre jeux offerts aux abonn&#233;s du service !</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2958813_ps-plus-en-fevrier-2026-voici-les-non-pas-trois-mais-quatre-jeux-offerts-aux-abonnes-du-service</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2958813_ps-plus-en-fevrier-2026-voici-les-non-pas-trois-mais-quatre-jeux-offerts-aux-abonnes-du-service</guid>
      <description>
PlayStation vient de d&#233;voiler les quatre jeux qui seront offerts ce mois-ci aux abonn&#233;s du PS Plus. Au programme : de la boxe, de la plong&#233;e, un cousin de Metroid et des avions de chasse !
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures cartes graphiques en 2026 ? Tests et s&#233;lection</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/815386_meilleures-cartes-graphiques</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/guides-dachat-gaming/815386_meilleures-cartes-graphiques</guid>
      <description>
La carte graphique (GPU) est un &#233;l&#233;ment essentiel de tout bon PC gamer. Face &#224; un march&#233; en perp&#233;tuelle &#233;volution, avec des g&#233;n&#233;rations de GPU qui s&#8217;encha&#238;nent et des technologies qui progressent sans cesse, il peut &#234;tre difficile de s&#8217;y retrouver. Bienvenue sur notre guide s&#233;lectif qui vous aidera &#224; choisir la carte graphique la plus pertinente selon votre budget.
...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN two-year plans are up to 78 percent off</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/expressvpn-two-year-plans-are-up-to-78-percent-off-180602104.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6bc22c-2c6b-4ec4-832c-d6d9af119838</guid>
      <description>ExpressVPN is back on sale again, and its two-year plans are up to 78 percent off right now. You can get the Advanced tier for $101 for 28 months. This is marked down from the $392 that this time frame normally costs. On a per-month basis, it works out to roughly $3.59 for the promo period.
We&#8217;ve consistently liked ExpressVPN because it&#8217;s fast, easy to use and widely available across a large global server network. In fact, it's our current pick for best premium VPN. One of the biggest drawbacks has always been its high cost, and this deal temporarily solves that issue. 


In our review we were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There Can Only Be One First Look at the &#8216;Highlander&#8217; Reboot</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/there-can-only-be-one-first-look-at-the-highlander-reboot-2000715039</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715039</guid>
      <description>Henry Cavill is the new Connor MacLeod in Chad Stahelski and Amazon MGM's fresh take on the fantasy adventure film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napoli vs Chelsea Free Streams: How to watch Champions League 2025/26 online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/napoli-vs-chelsea-free-streams-how-to-watch-champions-league-2025-26-online-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2WEs5LsFCJdHK9bQBZtbWN</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Napoli vs Chelsea in the 2025/26 Champions League with both sides in desperate need of three points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk reportedly wants a June SpaceX IPO to align with his birthday, the planets</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/elon-musk-reportedly-wants-a-june-spacex-ipo-to-align-with-his-birthday-the-planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087205</guid>
      <description>SpaceX eyes June for IPO to align with Musk's birthday and the planets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Not just censorship, it&#8217;s digital isolation:" Iran plans to cut ties with the global internet &#8212; and VPNs may not help this time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/not-just-censorship-its-digital-isolation-iran-plans-to-cut-ties-with-the-global-internet-and-vpns-may-not-help-this-time</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eyndRRX85amx5wGxGW3q3</guid>
      <description>After enforcing "one of the most severe blackouts in history," Iran is moving towards a permanent whitelisting system to better police the internet. Here's what is at stake for people in Iran, and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple lance aujourd&#8217;hui Creator Studio, pour cr&#233;er sur abonnement</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/apple-lance-aujourdhui-creator-studio-pour-creer-sur-abonnement.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323041</guid>
      <description>Les cr&#233;ateurs de tout poil ont d&#233;sormais &#224; leur disposition un nouvel abonnement pour couvrir tous leurs besoins ou presque. Le Creator Studio d'Apple regroupe sous une m&#234;me banni&#232;re tous les logiciels pro et bureautiques du constructeur, accompagn&#233;s de fonctions in&#233;dites g&#233;n&#233;r&#233;es par IA. Premi&#232;re d&#233;couverte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN service for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/best-vpn-130004396.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad91508b-bbe1-44e8-a716-02724cbca3ac</guid>
      <description>As frustrating as it is that governments and businesses are running roughshod over our online freedoms, at least we have plenty of good VPNs to keep us protected online. There are so many fast, intelligently designed, full-featured and affordable services on the market that the biggest problem is picking one. For any use case, you can bet at least two providers will be neck-and-neck for first place.
On the other hand, the VPN world is still the Wild West in some ways. It's easy enough to slap a cheap VPN together that the market is flooded with low-quality apps that put more money into adverti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer made a web app version of Synapse</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/razer-made-a-web-app-version-of-synapse-170715465.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09f81cc0-4cbf-49e0-8726-482006b2a3b2</guid>
      <description>Gaming peripheral company Razer has announced the beta release of Synapse Web, a browser-based version of its desktop software. The web app is intended for quick adjustments when away from home, such as LANs or tournaments, where downloading the full desktop version may not be possible or practical.
At launch, Synapse Web will only support the Razer Huntsman V3 Pro keyboards, though Razer says more devices will be added down the line. Using any Chromium-based browser, users can make quick changes to key settings, apply Chroma RGB quick effects and manage on-board profiles. These profiles can t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One UI 8.5 (Android 16) : Samsung ajoute enfin une fonctionnalit&#233; cl&#233; &#224; la Now Bar</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/one-ui-8-5-android-16-samsung-ajoute-enfin-une-fonctionnalite-cle-a-la-now-bar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1323031</guid>
      <description>Introduite avec One UI 7 et les Galaxy S25, la Now Bar devait incarner la nouvelle mani&#232;re d&#8217;interagir avec son smartphone Samsung. Un an plus tard, elle s&#8217;enrichit enfin d&#8217;une fonction aussi simple qu&#8217;attendue : l&#8217;affichage des appels manqu&#233;s. Une &#233;volution modeste, mais symbolique, alors que la firme cor&#233;enne pr&#233;pare d&#233;j&#224; One UI 8.5 et les Galaxy S26, dans un contexte concurrentiel plus tendu que jamais....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Apple&#8217;s new Creator Studio Pro, AI is a tool to aid creation, not replace it</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/with-apples-new-creator-studio-pro-ai-is-a-tool-to-aid-creation-not-replace-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087197</guid>
      <description>Apple&#8217;s Creator Studio Pro leverages AI to help creators with tedious tasks&#8212;like finding clips or building slides&#8212;without trying to do the work for them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best OLED TVs for all budgets, as reviewed by our experts.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-best-oled-tvs-for-all-budgets-as-reviewed-by-our-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vijPiUytHBa6yjCCwsa7Fh</guid>
      <description>With infinite contrast and phenomenal picture quality, the best OLED TVs will change how you experience your favorite movies and shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Police Department investigating Zoox collision with a parked car</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/san-francisco-police-department-investigating-zoox-collision-with-a-parked-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3086198</guid>
      <description>The investigation is looking into a January 17 crash where a Zoox robotaxi hit the driver's side door of a parked car, which Zoox said was "suddenly opened."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best projectors for all budgets, including portable and 4K projectors, all real-world tested by home theater experts.</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/projectors/the-best-projectors-for-all-budgets-including-portable-and-4k-projectors-all-real-world-tested-by-home-theater-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7mSCGippZ9HUtm6JGtjF94</guid>
      <description>From long throw to ultra short throw and portable models, our guide will give you the big picture on the best 4K projectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's second-generation AirTag offers greater range but still doesn't have a keyring hole</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/apples-second-generation-airtag-offers-greater-range-but-still-doesnt-have-a-keyring-hole-150540407.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a69a787-277c-4401-8e22-7cb791d6eb0d</guid>
      <description>Apple has launched its next-generation AirTag for $29 and brought a slew of new features along with it. But, first, it's important to get this out of the way: The new AirTag still doesn't have a keyring hole, so you'll still need accessories like a case, holder or secure pocket.Once you get over that, the new Apple AirTag does offer some nice improvements. For starters, it's now powered by Apple's second-generation Ultra Wideband chip &#8212; the same one used in the iPhone 17 lineup and for the Apple Watch Ultra 3. It also uses Precision Finding to reach items up to 50 percent further away than the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAFTA vs the Oscars &#8211; I&#8217;m a serial movie-watcher, and there's a clear winner in these nominations lists</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/bafta-vs-the-oscars-im-a-serial-movie-watcher-and-theres-a-clear-winner-in-these-nominations-lists</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dGhQM7o96RXHukMH58nPGE</guid>
      <description>Chase Inifiniti and Odessa A'zion were snubbed at the Oscars, but their BAFTA nominations show which ceremony has better taste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roku just made a major tweak to its home screen &#8211; and not everyone is happy about it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/streaming-devices/roku-just-made-a-major-tweak-to-its-home-screen-and-not-everyone-is-happy-about-it</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">WzNQnR9Adrz5fZm72P2Q6U</guid>
      <description>A new Subscriptions tab has appeared on the Roku home screen, letting you pick up where you left off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech needs less than a month to pay off over $7 billion in 2025 fines, Proton warns</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/big-tech-could-need-only-one-month-to-pay-off-over-usd7-billion-in-2025-fines-proton-warns</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vDqWFgbnUGGBbB8dYBRMc7</guid>
      <description>Big Tech was slapped with $7.8 billion in fines in 2025, but Proton found this massive sum represents less than a month of free cash flow. Is it time for regulators to find new teeth?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voici le PC de l&#8217;ind&#233;cence : une configuration ultime mais un prix ind&#233;cent</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2958861_voici-le-pc-de-lindecence-une-configuration-ultime-mais-un-prix-indecent</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2958861_voici-le-pc-de-lindecence-une-configuration-ultime-mais-un-prix-indecent</guid>
      <description>
Vous pensiez que votre config de gaming &#233;tait solide ? Attendez de voir ce que vient de sortir Optimum.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best VPN deals: Up to 87 percent off ProtonVPN, Surfshark, ExpressVPN, NordVPN and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-best-vpn-deals-up-to-87-percent-off-protonvpn-surfshark-expressvpn-nordvpn-and-more-120056484.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3820f07f-0c5e-4a96-baba-d6d9ea0510c3</guid>
      <description>If one of your New Year's resolutions was to improve your cybersecurity, it's not too late. Most of the holiday deals are over by now, but plenty of services are still offering excellent prices. With access to a virtual private network (VPN), you can keep your activity hidden from your ISP and any advertisers it may sell that data to &#8212; all while streaming sporting events and TV dramas from all across the globe.
We strongly recommend using a VPN, but if you jump on the very first deal you see, you might get stuck with a substandard app. It's also easy to mistakenly end up paying more than you w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vintage NASA Jet Skids to a Fiery Stop in Dramatic &#8216;Wheels-Up&#8217; Landing</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/vintage-nasa-jet-skids-to-a-fiery-stop-in-dramatic-wheels-up-landing-2000714975</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714975</guid>
      <description>A suspected mechanical issue forced the two-person crew to land the aging aircraft on its belly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British speaker great Ruark has made two stunning 'radiograms' for its 40th anniversary &#8212; beautiful modern wireless speakers that double as a sideboard</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-bluetooth-speakers/british-speaker-great-ruark-has-made-two-stunning-radiograms-for-its-40th-anniversary-beautiful-modern-wireless-speakers-that-double-as-a-sideboard</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ourCmPML4S3yfQ8yLxnGfP</guid>
      <description>Ruark celebrates its 40th with two exquisite and extremely limited edition statement pieces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C&#8217;est historique : deux trous noirs viennent d&#8217;&#234;tre photographi&#233;s ensemble pour la premi&#232;re fois</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cest-historique-deux-trous-noirs-viennent-etre-photographies-ensemble-premiere-fois-w2t8-130496/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-cest-historique-deux-trous-noirs-viennent-etre-photographies-ensemble-premiere-fois-w2t8-130496/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Pour la premi&#232;re fois, des astronomes ont r&#233;ussi &#224; capturer une image radio montrant deux trous noirs en orbite l'un autour de l'autre. Jusqu'&#224; pr&#233;sent, les astronomes n'avaient r&#233;ussi &#224; photographier que des trous noirs individuels. Mais il y a plusieurs ann&#233;es, ils ont pu disposer d'un...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Watch : cette nouvelle option va enfin vous aider &#224; ne plus jamais perdre vos cl&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2957575_avec-les-nouveaux-airtags-votre-apple-watch-devient-encore-plus-pratique-pour-trouver-vos-objets-perdus</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/apple/2957575_avec-les-nouveaux-airtags-votre-apple-watch-devient-encore-plus-pratique-pour-trouver-vos-objets-perdus</guid>
      <description>
Avec la sortie des nouveaux AirTags de deuxi&#232;me g&#233;n&#233;ration, les montres connect&#233;es d'Apple s'enrichissent d'une fonction bien pratique pour retrouver vos objets &#233;gar&#233;s. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulanger met le paquet pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes avec de belles promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-met-le-paquet-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-avec-de-belles-promotions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2931541_boulanger-met-le-paquet-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-avec-de-belles-promotions</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d'hiver touchent bient&#244;t &#224; leur fin ! Pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque, Boulanger ne l&#233;sine pas sur les offres : enceinte bluetooth, &#233;cran gaming g&#233;ant de 40", nouveau Redmi Note 15 en promo... Il y a de quoi se faire plaisir, mais plus pour longtemps. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valve is facing a lawsuit over 'monopoly' claims on Steam &#8211; and I'm scratching my head at this one</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/pc-gaming/valve-is-facing-a-lawsuit-over-monopoly-claims-on-steam-and-im-scratching-my-head-at-this-one</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dy8Wf2Ejz5NKhZ5ikDAepA</guid>
      <description>Valve's Steam storefront is favoured by a large majority of PC gamers, with generous discounts and pricing, but a lawsuit has called that into question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fnac et Darty multiplient les bonnes affaires avec ces derni&#232;res offres &#224; saisir avant la fin des soldes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-multiplient-les-bonnes-affaires-avec-ces-dernieres-offres-a-saisir-avant-la-fin-des-soldes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2930751_fnac-et-darty-multiplient-les-bonnes-affaires-avec-ces-dernieres-offres-a-saisir-avant-la-fin-des-soldes</guid>
      <description>
C'est l'heure de la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque ! Il reste encore quelques jours pour profiter des soldes d'hiver, et les enseignes Fnac et Darty n'ont pas dit leur dernier mot. On trouve tout un tas d'offres Tech int&#233;ressantes sur les 2 sites : voici celles qui ont retenu notre attention. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI&#8217;s refreshed Prestige series laptops are now available to buy</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/msis-refreshed-prestige-series-laptops-are-now-available-to-buy-165234479.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d7666b-0ca5-41ba-b997-3d8422da27d4</guid>
      <description>The latest lineup of MSI's Prestige laptops is now available to buy. The company unveiled its next-generation business laptop at CES earlier this month, all of them powered by the latest Intel Core Ultra Series 3 processors.
Available in configurations that include up to the Intel Core Ultra 9, the updated Prestige series are equipped with chunky 91Wh batteries and, depending on the model, offer over 30 hours of 1080p video playback. In more real-world terms, if you&#8217;re on a work trip and know you won&#8217;t always have a power supply to hand, you can trust one of these to get you through a day of h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les meilleures offres tombent pour la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver : le TOP 50 des deals &#224; ne pas louper</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_les-meilleures-offres-tombent-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-voici-le-top-25</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2957561_les-meilleures-offres-tombent-pour-la-derniere-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver-voici-le-top-25</guid>
      <description>
Il ne faut pas se le cacher, la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes est souvent le moment o&#249; l'on trouve les meilleures offres, car les e-commer&#231;ants comme Amazon, Fnac, Darty ou encore Boulanger veulent &#233;couler les derniers stocks. Avec cet article, vous serez s&#251;rs de ne manquer aucun deal Tech int&#233;ressant. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I scavenged 33 pieces of Fallout "loot" that will turn your home office into a Vault-Tec shelter</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/i-scavenged-33-pieces-of-fallout-loot-that-will-turn-your-home-office-into-a-vault-tec-shelter</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZXGvQCwbpnVZA7U5uJaZrX</guid>
      <description>Overseer-approved home office gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allbirds is closing its last brick-and-mortar store in San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/28/allbirds-closing-last-store-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3087194</guid>
      <description>Once symbolic of a mid-2010s San Francisco tech bro, Allbirds is cutting costs to "support the long-term health of the business."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSG vs Newcastle Free Streams: How to watch Champions League 2025/26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/psg-vs-newcastle-champions-league-2025-26-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nvVAkCW777MDEaSktSw9Pj</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch PSG vs Newcastle live streams from anywhere and for free, with both sides looking to secure a place in the Champions League Round of 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Months later, the Supreme Court still hasn&#8217;t decided on Trump&#8217;s emergency tariffs. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482439/months-later-supreme-court-still-hasnt-decided-trumps-emergency-tariffs-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:44:56</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482439/months-later-supreme-court-still-hasnt-decided-trumps-emergency-tariffs-heres-why</guid>
      <description>Back in November, many of the court&#8217;s nine justices expressed doubts about the legality of Trump&#8217;s tariffs.
When the Supreme Court granted an unusually quick hearing over President Donald Trump&#8217;s tariffs, a similarly rapid resolution seemed possible.After all, Trump&#8217;s lawyers told the court that speed was of the essence on an issue central to the Republican president&#8217;s economic agenda. They pointed to a statement from Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent warning that the &#8220;longer a final ruling is delayed, the greater the risk of economic disruption.&#8221;But nearly three months have elapsed since argum...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Laying Off 16,000 as It Increases &#8216;Ownership&#8217; and Removes &#8216;Bureaucracy&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazon-laying-off-16000-as-it-increases-ownership-and-removes-bureaucracy-2000715027</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715027</guid>
      <description>A blog post by the company&#8217;s head of HR hinted that more layoffs could be on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La puissante Ugreen 200 W profite des soldes d&#8217;hiver pour perdre 31 % de son prix et passer sous les 90 euros</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2958607_la-puissante-ugreen-200-w-profite-des-soldes-dhiver-pour-perdre-31-de-son-prix-et-passer-sous-les-90-euros</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/2958607_la-puissante-ugreen-200-w-profite-des-soldes-dhiver-pour-perdre-31-de-son-prix-et-passer-sous-les-90-euros</guid>
      <description>
Entre sa puissance de 200 W, ses trois ports de charge ou encore ses treize protections par&#233;es &#224; toutes les &#233;ventualit&#233;s, cette batterie externe de Ugreen est un super alli&#233; pour vos voyages. Chez Amazon, elle passe de 129,99 euros &#224; 89,99 euros pendant les soldes d'hiver.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The UK war on VPNs is an embarrassment' &#8211; backlash grows over proposed VPN age-checks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/the-uk-war-on-vpns-is-an-embarrassment-backlash-grows-over-proposed-vpn-age-checks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Fh7yW3WE2JCeCX9B2i7U39</guid>
      <description>Critics are warning against proposals to restrict VPN access &#8212; but will the plans actually become law?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecast Map Reveals Which East Coast States Should Brace for More Snow This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/forecast-map-reveals-which-east-coast-states-should-brace-for-more-snow-this-weekend-2000715018</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715018</guid>
      <description>Meteorologists are tracking another major storm system that could exacerbate lingering impacts from last weekend&#8217;s Winter Storm Fern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Star Trek&#8217; Legend Robert Picardo on Why the &#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Cadets Talk Like Modern Kids</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/star-trek-starfleet-academy-robert-picardo-modern-speaking-2000715030</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000715030</guid>
      <description>The latest episode of 'Starfleet Academy' will give its young cadets a lesson in diction from the good Doctor himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google, Apple hosted dozens of deepfake nudify apps, investigation reveals</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/google-apple-app-stores-hosted-nudify-apps-investigation-reveals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04HMavEWK1NCrEw2PAftIYD</guid>
      <description>App stores reportedly hosted so-called nudify apps (deepfake tools that use AI) despite such apps violating the companies' rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrinking Season 3, episode 1s emotional ending, explained</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/shrinking-season-3-episode-1-ending-explained</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06eBWF6pIoTOcqPyzpZfMU1</guid>
      <description>"Shrinking" Season 3, episode 1 has a poignant ending that shows how Paul's Parkinson's is progressing. What happens, and what does it mean?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les PC portables gaming et bureautiques ont jusqu&#8217;&#224; 1 000 &#8364; de r&#233;duction pendant l&#8217;ultime d&#233;marque des soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935325_les-pc-portables-gaming-et-bureautiques-ont-jusqua-1-000-de-reduction-pendant-lultime-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935325_les-pc-portables-gaming-et-bureautiques-ont-jusqua-1-000-de-reduction-pendant-lultime-demarque-des-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Configuration gaming, bureautique, avec carte graphique Nvidia ou non, processeur AMD, Intel ou Qualcomm, &#233;cran IPS ou OLED... Nombre de PC portables sont en promotion lors de la derni&#232;re d&#233;marque des soldes d'hiver mais seuls quelques-uns m&#233;ritent vraiment de figurer dans cette s&#233;lection.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La nouvelle MG4 &#233;lectrique abordable est enfin en Europe : voici les premiers chiffres</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mg/2958635_la-nouvelle-mg4-electrique-abordable-est-enfin-en-europe-voici-les-premiers-chiffres</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/mg/2958635_la-nouvelle-mg4-electrique-abordable-est-enfin-en-europe-voici-les-premiers-chiffres</guid>
      <description>
Promise de longue date, la nouvelle MG4 Urban vient d'arriver au Royaume-Uni. Cette voiture &#233;lectrique venue de Chine se place sous la MG4 qu'on conna&#238;t d&#233;j&#224;, notamment en termes de prix. La version actuelle gagne un nouvel int&#233;rieur et ne garde que ses grandes batteries.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be prepared for anything with the Oupes Guardian 6000 power station for its lowest price yet</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-oupes-guardian-6000-power-station-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06pdKT5iXc5iKQeXhfnBwrX</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 28, get the Oupes Guardian 6000 power station for its lowest price yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK government could ban VPNs for children</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/uk-government-ban-vpns-for-children</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">075vu1RfqgImOsVz3SAuD3J</guid>
      <description>The UK House of Lords voted to allow an amendment to ban VPNs for children in the Children's Wellbeing and Schools Bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is your hit product a &#8216;gateway product&#8217;?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482093/is-your-hit-product-a-gateway-product</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:11:05</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482093/is-your-hit-product-a-gateway-product</guid>
      <description>The challenge is to figure out what its shelf life is. Here are the questions to ask.
Remember the Flip video recorder? In 2009, it was a sensation&#8212;a dead-simple, pocket-size recorder that let ordinary people capture and share moments without lugging around a camcorder or figuring out complicated settings. Cisco acquired Flip&#8217;s maker, Pure Digital Technologies, for $590 million in stock. Two years later, Cisco shut Flip down entirely....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You shouldn't worry as much about AI taking your job as you should worry about someone who's very good using AI taking your job': Cisco CEO says effects of AI will cause "carnage" in the jobs market</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/you-shouldnt-worry-as-much-about-ai-taking-your-job-as-you-should-worry-about-someone-whos-very-good-using-ai-taking-your-job-cisco-ceo-says-effects-of-ai-will-cause-carnage-in-the-jobs-market</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">n8EXomcvcihTo7C43Atvf3</guid>
      <description>Cisco CEO says "carnage" will hit future labor markets, IMF MD likens AI to a "tsunami" that will change how we see work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DJI Mic Mini is back at its lowest-ever price &#8212; save $90 at Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-dji-mic-mini-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06LCHAEIHPHRgi28gsA4A4t</guid>
      <description>The DJI Mic Mini is on sale at Amazon for $79, down from the list price of $169. That's a 53% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last chance to score the DJI Power 1000 V2 portable power station for under $430</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-dji-power-1000-v2-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05cNGlrxgudfkRMYJyJmibC</guid>
      <description>The DJI Power 1000 V2 is on sale at Amazon for $429 with the on-page coupon, down from the list price of $699. That's a 39% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon to cut 16,000 jobs as it shifts resources to AI</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/amazon-16000-layoffs-ai-amazon-go-amazon-fresh-closing</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05RGUKYt06HpLDVZrWK57u3</guid>
      <description>Amazon is laying off thousands of workers and closing its Amazon Go and Amazon Fresh stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apple Watch Ultra 2 is now $250 off on Amazon. Thats $50 better than its Black Friday deal.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-apple-watch-ultra-2-gps-cellular-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06zZU8EIiNl33y0U9r71cHo</guid>
      <description>Amazon has the Apple Watch Ultra 2 on sale for $549 as of Jan. 28. That's 31% off its $799 MSRP, its biggest discount ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackle all your home DIY projects with $80 off the Dewalt 20V MAX Cordless Drill Driver Set</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-28-dewalt-cordless-drill-driver-set-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03rUKCwBVQHOkhkqY4zJgje</guid>
      <description>As of Jan. 28, Save $80 on the Dewalt 20V MAX Cordless Drill Driver Set at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Pilgrim EX will hit PC and consoles on March 3</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/scott-pilgrim-ex-will-hit-pc-and-consoles-on-march-3-160427832.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10701ac9-10f6-4e06-a589-e693b719aae5</guid>
      <description>Fans of co-op beat-&#8216;em-ups and fictional bass players who kind of suck as human beings might want to mark March 3 on their calendars. That&#8217;s when Scott Pilgrim EX is set to hit PS4, PS5, Xbox Series X/S, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch and Steam.&#160;Developer and publisher Tribute Games announced the release date in a new trailer, which also revealed two more playable characters: Matthew Patel (a member of the League of Evil Exes) and Robot-01, a creation of the Katayanagi Twins. One more fighter will be unveiled in the coming weeks.&#160;Tribute worked with Scott Pilgrim creator Bryan Lee O&#8217;Malley on an or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Harvard-affiliated study on night owls reveals surprising heart health findings</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482442/this-harvard-affiliated-study-night-owls-reveals-surprising-heart-health-findings</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:00:30</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482442/this-harvard-affiliated-study-night-owls-reveals-surprising-heart-health-findings</guid>
      <description>The large study found that night owls have worse heart health than the average person.
Being a night owl can be bad for your heart.That may sound surprising but a large study found people who are more active late at night &#8212; when most of the population is winding down or already asleep &#8212; have poorer overall heart health than the average person.&#8220;It is not like, that, night owls are doomed,&#8221; said research fellow Sina Kianersi of Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital and Harvard Medical School, who led the study. &#8220;The challenge is the mismatch between your internal clock and typical daily schedules&#8221; that m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alienware 16X Aurora</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/alienware-16x-aurora</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xjuvSE5CqNVdyiQPFAeLE4</guid>
      <description>Weighing under six pounds, alongside being less than an inch thick when closed, the Alienware 16X features an Intel Core Ultra 9, Nvidia GeForce RTX 5070 GPU, 32GB DDR5 RAM, and 1TB SSD. These specs are matched with a 16-inch display featuring a 2560 x 1600 resolution with a 240Hz refresh rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepMind&#8217;s New AI Can Read a Million DNA Letters at Once&#8212;and Actually Understand Them</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/deepminds-new-ai-can-read-a-million-dna-letters-at-once-and-actually-understand-them-2000714798</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000714798</guid>
      <description>AlphaGenome is reportedly the most comprehensive and accurate DNA sequence model developed to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Denier Tina Peters Was &#8216;Pardoned&#8217; by Trump. She&#8217;s Still in Prison</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/donald-trump-wants-to-force-colorado-to-free-an-imprisoned-election-denier-its-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69739dc60b6f61693b8dafc3</guid>
      <description>Former election clerk Tina Peters is a hero to conspiracy theorists, and even received an empty &#8220;pardon&#8221; from the president. Colorado's governor has held firm against commuting her sentence&#8212;so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2026 TV deals: The best sales ahead of kickoff</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/super-bowl-2026-tv-deals-the-best-sales-ahead-of-kickoff-160000725.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19a8ed95-5057-4f9e-952b-502d925814e1</guid>
      <description>The big game is one of the few instances now in the US where most people gather around the TV to watch the live event together. While the teams playing in Super Bowl 2026 are the true stars of the show (and Bad Bunny, of course), your TV is a pretty important part of the puzzle of putting together an excellent Super Bowl party. Maybe you&#8217;ve been thinking about replacing an aging set, or you&#8217;re itching for a full refresh of your home theater setup &#8212; either way, you&#8217;ll want to try to get a good deal on a new TV. Thankfully, the weeks leading up to the Super Bowl can be a great time to shop for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From unemployed to self-employed: Why the switch is more common than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481987/the-unemployed-to-self-employed-pipeline-is-stronger-than-ever-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481987/the-unemployed-to-self-employed-pipeline-is-stronger-than-ever-heres-why</guid>
      <description>More people are finding success as solopreneurs, even if they were forced into it by layoffs or other unsavory circumstances.
When Mikala Mahoney was laid off from her marketing job last summer, first she was shocked. Then the anxiety flooded in.&#160;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers go &#8216;Back to Starbucks&#8217; as company posts first U.S. growth in 2 years</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482601/starbucks-earnings-first-us-growth-in-2-years</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482601/starbucks-earnings-first-us-growth-in-2-years</guid>
      <description>Global and U.S. sales are up as Brian Niccol&#8217;s grand strategy shows signs of life.
Since Brian Niccol took over as Starbucks Chairman and CEO in 2024, he&#8217;s promised a grand turnaround for the coffee giant by going back to its roots in lovingly designed, customer-centric stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Liverpool vs. Qarabag online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/liverpool-qarabag-champions-league-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">020uXrRExcRm6Zc4v38lUVv</guid>
      <description>How to watch Champions League for free. Live stream Liverpool vs. Qarabag in the Champions League for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette vid&#233;o virale est bluffante&#8230; jusqu&#8217;&#224; ce que vous d&#233;couvriez ce qui s&#8217;y passe vraiment</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/meteorites-cette-video-virale-bluffante-jusqua-ce-vous-decouvriez-ce-y-passe-vraiment-130620/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:57:44 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/meteorites-cette-video-virale-bluffante-jusqua-ce-vous-decouvriez-ce-y-passe-vraiment-130620/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Imaginez deux m&#233;t&#233;ores dont le chemin se croise juste au-dessus d&#8217;un volcan japonais. La vid&#233;o est fascinante. Mais derri&#232;re les apparences se joue un ph&#233;nom&#232;ne physique inattendu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26 : voici &#224; quoi ressemble le chargeur sans fil nouvelle g&#233;n&#233;ration pour rattraper Apple et Google</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2958629_samsung-galaxy-s26-voici-a-quoi-ressemble-le-chargeur-sans-fil-nouvelle-generation-pour-rattraper-apple-et-google</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2958629_samsung-galaxy-s26-voici-a-quoi-ressemble-le-chargeur-sans-fil-nouvelle-generation-pour-rattraper-apple-et-google</guid>
      <description>
Voici des photos montrant le chargeur sans fil magn&#233;tique (Qi2) officiel que pr&#233;pare Samsung pour les Galaxy S26, S26 Plus et S26 Ultra.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donn&#233;es sensibles&#160;: l&#8217;Europe ne veut pas exclure les g&#233;ants du Cloud am&#233;ricains</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/donnees-sensibles-leurope-ne-veut-pas-exclure-les-geants-du-cloud-americains.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322905</guid>
      <description>Un sujet autant technique que g&#233;opolitique : apr&#232;s des ann&#233;es de n&#233;gociation, Bruxelles a tranch&#233; : elle n'inclut pas des crit&#232;res de souverainet&#233; dans l'EUCS, le futur label de cybers&#233;curit&#233; europ&#233;en, mais elle n'interdit pas aux 27 de le faire, pays par pays. La mesure, d&#233;fendue par Paris et des d&#233;fenseurs d'une souverainet&#233; europ&#233;enne, aurait emp&#234;ch&#233; les leaders am&#233;ricains du march&#233; du cloud (Amazon, Microsoft et Google) d'h&#233;berger nos donn&#233;es les plus sensibles....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of our favorite budgeting apps is only $50 for the year for new users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apps/one-of-our-favorite-budgeting-apps-is-only-50-for-the-year-for-new-users-204507183.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764214b-3509-4628-8631-8692fa12e904</guid>
      <description>A new year is the perfect time to get your spending in order, and if you're not trying to build your own spreadsheet, budgeting apps are one of the best ways to do it. To save yourself some money in the process, you can pick up a year-long subscription to Monarch Money, one of Engadget's favorite budgeting apps, for just $50 if you use code NEWYEAR2026 at checkout and you're a new subscriber. That's a 50 percent discount on the service's normal $100 price.
Monarch Money makes for a capable and detailed budgeting companion. You can use the service via apps for iOS, Android, iPadOS or the web, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why &#8216;nihilist penguin&#8217; is the mood of the moment</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91481875/nihilist-penguin-meme-why-its-the-mood-of-the-moment-internet-obsessed</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T15:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91481875/nihilist-penguin-meme-why-its-the-mood-of-the-moment-internet-obsessed</guid>
      <description>Amid an overwhelming week of bad news, the internet is obsessed with one rather dark meme.
Need a break from the news? We thought so. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to remember before Bridgerton Season 4</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/bridgerton-season-3-recap</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">044a5ksD3FjSZcOzmBaLZzu</guid>
      <description>Who married whom in "Bridgerton" Season 3? What went down at that ball? And where's Lady Whistledown at?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes franchisee closes 17 restaurants in bankruptcy. See the full list of doomed locations</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91482422/popeyes-closing-restaurants-full-list-doomed-locations-franchisee</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-28T15:40:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91482422/popeyes-closing-restaurants-full-list-doomed-locations-franchisee</guid>
      <description>Sailormen Inc., which recently sought Chapter 11 protection, has just shuttered more than a dozen locations of the beloved fried chicken chain.
Fans of Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen will be sad to learn that more than a dozen locations have shuttered this month across two Southeastern states. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyson's ridiculously compact new vacuum is going to change the market forever &#8211; here's why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/dysons-ridiculously-compact-new-vacuum-is-going-to-change-the-market-forever-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">JcSeQZjhvzAdtG9aocMMEe</guid>
      <description>The PencilVac prioritizes lightness over outright power, and that's a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen s&#8217;est fait doubler : Ford lance la nouvelle batterie LFP tant attendue avant m&#234;me les ID.4</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2958539_volkswagen-sest-fait-doubler-ford-lance-la-nouvelle-batterie-lfp-tant-attendue-avant-meme-les-id-4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/actualites-generales/2958539_volkswagen-sest-fait-doubler-ford-lance-la-nouvelle-batterie-lfp-tant-attendue-avant-meme-les-id-4</guid>
      <description>
La nouvelle batterie LFP de Volkswagen arrive enfin ! Mais chez Ford en premier. Le constructeur vient de mettre &#224; jour ses deux SUV &#233;lectriques phares en Europe, l'Explorer et le Capri. De quoi faire grimper l'autonomie sans toucher au prix, et envisager l'arriv&#233;e de cette batterie dans les prochaines semaines chez Volkswagen.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Samsung Galaxy A37 risque de concurrencer le Galaxy S26 sur ce point bien pr&#233;cis</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-samsung-galaxy-a37-risque-de-concurrencer-le-galaxy-s26.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1322987</guid>
      <description>Deux visuels du Galaxy A37 sortent du bois. Le futur smartphone devrait &#234;tre commercialis&#233; autour de 400 euros et int&#232;grerait une charge de 45 W.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Windows 11 25H2 edges ahead of Windows 10 in gaming performance': testing proves newer OS is faster &#8212; but there's an elephant-sized BSOD in the room</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/windows-11-25h2-edges-ahead-of-windows-10-in-gaming-performance-testing-proves-newer-os-is-faster-but-theres-an-elephant-sized-bsod-in-the-room</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EegyH7QuRumogXbirFVGkF</guid>
      <description>Think Windows 10 is faster than Windows 11 for gaming? You're dead wrong, based on a new test &#8212; but I'm betting this won't sway Windows 10 holdouts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
