<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:21:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump could introduce &#8216;mandatory&#8217; social media reviews for travelers</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842129/trump-admin-us-cbp-social-media-history-travelers</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T18:21:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842129</guid>
      <description>The Trump administration could soon require tourists from dozens of nations to hand over their social media handles before entering the country. Under a proposal from US Customs and Border Protection, the agency would make social media history from the past five years a "mandatory" part of the screening process, as reported earlier by The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Up &#8216;Fallout: The Ghoul Log&#8217; and Irradiate Your Holidays</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fire-up-fallout-the-ghoul-log-and-irradiate-your-holidays-2000698035</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698035</guid>
      <description>Prime Video has released a festive video ahead of 'Fallout' season two, but be warned: that's not a log burning in the fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I abandon my iPhone for a return to Android? Tell me what to do</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/should-i-abandon-my-iphone-for-a-return-to-android-tell-me-what-to-do</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eQCxCdNfoTELhxCkZDLwTc</guid>
      <description>Tell me whether I should abandon my iPhone for a return to Android. Or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 70% factuality ceiling: why Google&#8217;s new &#8216;FACTS&#8217; benchmark is a wake-up call for enterprise AI</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-70-factuality-ceiling-why-googles-new-facts-benchmark-is-a-wake-up-call</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">M3mgoBJoOEtdpvWd9JF58</guid>
      <description>There's no shortage of generative AI benchmarks designed to measure the performance and accuracy of a given model on completing various helpful enterprise tasks &#8212; from coding to instruction following to agentic web browsing and tool use. But many of these benchmarks have one major shortcoming: they measure the AI's ability to complete specific problems and requests, not how factual the model is in its outputs &#8212; how well it generates objectively correct information tied to real-world data &#8212; especially when dealing with information contained in imagery or graphics.For industries where accuracy i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beelink promises a 4-liter, 4-drive NAS that could put 120TB in the palm of your hand</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/beelink-promises-a-4-liter-4-drive-nas-that-could-hold-120tb-in-the-palm-of-your-hand</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eoctB7zyNs9e4XnJnS4CYj</guid>
      <description>Beelink&#8217;s ME Pro NAS compresses four drives into four liters, offering 120TB potential, but core specs remain unannounced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle of the pivot tables: Diarmuid &#8216;The LeBron James of Excel&#8217; Early defeats three-time champion Andrew Ngai to claim the 2025 Excel World Championship and a $5,000 cash prize</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/battle-of-the-pivot-tables-diarmuid-the-lebron-james-of-excel-defeats-three-time-champion-andrew-ngai-to-claim-the-2025-title-and-usd5-000-cash-prize</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6hi6RTzocW44ZVG7MnRVMC</guid>
      <description>Diarmuid Early won the 2025 Excel World Championship in Las Vegas, completing intense pivot table challenges and securing cash and a trophy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify&amp;#8217;s Prompted Playlists use AI to control your algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/842053/spotify-ai-prompted-playlists</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T17:11:57-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=842053</guid>
      <description>A new beta feature on Spotify takes the idea behind the Discover Weekly playlist and puts the control in users' hands through AI prompts. Prompted Playlists, which are initially launching in New Zealand on Thursday, let users type out exactly what they want to listen to, with as much or little detail as they like. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NES game Jaws is getting a retro physical re-release on Switch and PS5</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-nes-game-jaws-is-getting-a-retro-physical-re-release-on-switch-and-ps5-221052996.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de931d2-037d-48f0-b595-ecc32a925c93</guid>
      <description>The year is 1987. Beverly Hills Cop II is the highest-grossing movie. "Walk Like an Egyptian" is the hottest song. The Iran-Contra scandal dominates American political headlines, while Konami&#8217;s Contra sucks up coins in arcades. But towering above them all is the watershed moment of Jaws arriving on the NES. ("This time there's no escape!", warned the box art.) Now, 38 years later, the 8-bit game is returning as a Limited Run Games physical re-release.The retro release coincides with the Spielberg movie's 50th anniversary. From December 19 to January 18, you can pre-order a physical copy for Sw...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV and Apple Music were down for some users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/apple-tv-and-apple-music-were-down-for-some-users-214425802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26f8cfe4-c1e9-4ebf-97ba-995a63248b54</guid>
      <description>Apple Music and Apple TV were briefly down during outage, according to Apple&#8217;s System Status page. The outage was logged on Apple&#8217;s own system at around 2:53PM ET and affected both of the company&#8217;s streaming services, along with Apple TV&#8217;s Channels feature, until the company resolved the issue around 4:31PM ET. On DownDetector, reports of issues with Apple TV and Apple Music first appeared right around 2:33PM ET, a little before Apple officially confirmed the outage on its own site. Only &#8220;some&#8221; users were affected by the outage, according to Apple, and anecdotally, multiple members of Engadget...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia is&#160;reportedly testing&#160;tracking software as chip-smuggling&#160;rumors swirl</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/nvidia-is-reportedly-testing-tracking-software-as-chip-smuggling-rumors-swirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074807</guid>
      <description>A new software option could make it possible to see the approximate location of some of Nvidia's AI chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of the Cuts of the Original &#8216;Star Wars&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/every-change-to-star-wars-a-new-hope-ever-made-2000697419</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000697419</guid>
      <description>The original theatrical cut of 'Star Wars: A New Hope' is returning to theaters for its 50th anniversary. But what does 'original' actually mean?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan On Alert for &#8216;Megaquake&#8217; After Magnitude 7.6 Shakes the Nation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/japan-on-alert-for-megaquake-after-magnitude-7-6-shakes-the-nation-2000698091</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000698091</guid>
      <description>"Please stay prepared to evacuate immediately if you feel any shaking, while continuing your socioeconomic activities.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald&#8217;s pulls AI-generated Christmas ad after backlash over 'soulless' visuals and holiday chaos</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/mcdonalds-pulls-ai-generated-christmas-ad-after-backlash-over-soulless-visuals-and-holiday-chaos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5XmNRvMEiNDyQZfRq2B3N5</guid>
      <description>McDonald&#8217;s removed an AI-made Christmas commercial after intense public backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A brief history of Calibri, the &#8216;woke&#8217; font the Trump administration is replacing</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458062/brief-history-of-calibri-the-woke-font-trump-is-replacing</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T22:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458062/brief-history-of-calibri-the-woke-font-trump-is-replacing</guid>
      <description>The type designer behind Calibri says the decision to replace his font with Times New Roman as the official U.S. State Department typeface is &#8216;hilarious and regrettable.&#8217; 
Calibri and Times New Roman have been at war for years. And now the two fonts are once again pitted against each other after the U.S. State Department declared it will be swapping its current official typeface, Calibri, for Times New Roman. It&#8217;s a full circle moment, considering the State Department ditched Times New Roman for Calibri in just 2023....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is reportedly working on a new AI model called 'Avocado' and it might not be open source</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/meta-is-reportedly-working-on-a-new-ai-model-called-avocado-and-it-might-not-be-open-source-215426778.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1069db79-3fad-434a-99de-f83d17d34bb3</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg has for months publicly hinted that he is backing away from open-source AI models. Now, Meta's latest AI pivot is starting to come into focus. The company is reportedly working on a new model, known inside of Meta as "Avocado," which could mark a major shift away from its previous open-source approach to AI development.&#160;Both CNBC and Bloomberg have reported on Meta's plans surrounding "Avocado," with both outlets saying the model "could" be proprietary rather than open-source. Avocado, which is due out sometime in 2026, is being worked on inside of "TBD," a smaller group within...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now share live video with emergency services on Android</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/10/you-can-now-share-live-video-with-emergency-services-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074909</guid>
      <description>This feature could help give emergency dispatchers context in circumstances like car accidents, fires, or medical crises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Bluebird wants to reclaim Twitter&#8217;s &#8216;abandoned&#8217; trademarks for a new social network</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/841994/operation-bluebird-twitter-trademarks-petition</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T16:31:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=841994</guid>
      <description>A startup called Operation Bluebird is trying to reclaim Twitter's branding, as reported earlier by Ars Technica and Reuters. Last week, Operation Bluebird filed a petition that asks the US Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) to cancel X Corp.'s ownership of the "Twitter" and "Tweet" trademarks, claiming they've been "abandoned" by the Elon Musk-owned company. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best budget robot vacuums</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/23846479/best-budget-robot-vacuum-robot-mop</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-10T16:31:06-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/23846479/best-budget-robot-vacuum-robot-mop</guid>
      <description>Today&#8217;s robot vacuums are becoming a bit like cars: with all the features, upgrades, and fancy trimmings available these days, it&#8217;s easy to forget that they can just be simple machines that get us from point A to point B. Yes, some bots blow hot air on their bums (mop pads), deftly navigate dog poop, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
