<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:33:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of creatives warn against an AI slop future</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/864951/human-artistry-campaign-ai-licensing-artists</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T00:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864951</guid>
      <description>Around 800 artists, writers, actors, and musicians signed on to a new campaign against what they call "theft at a grand scale" by AI companies. The signatories of the campaign - called "Stealing Isn't Innovation" - include authors George Saunders and Jodi Picoult, actors Cate Blanchett and Scarlett Johansson, and musicians like the band R.E.M., [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X is also launching Bluesky-like starter packs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/x-is-also-launching-bluesky-like-starter-packs-050057033.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad338ed5-10f1-4280-adf6-abecc993c6b4</guid>
      <description>X is rolling out a new feature called &#8220;Starterpacks&#8221; to all users in the coming weeks, the company&#8217;s head of product has announced. It&#8217;s made up of compilations of accounts new users can follow based on their interests. If that sounds familiar, it&#8217;s because Bluesky launched a very similar feature that&#8217;s also called &#8220;starter packs&#8221; back in 2024. Bluesky allows ordinary users to curate their own packs as long as each one doesn&#8217;t exceed 50 accounts. They can then share those lists broadly on the platform or directly with new users via QR code. X, on the other hand, compiled and curated its own li...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka vs England ODI Live Streams: How to watch cricket online from anywhere, TV channels, schedule</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/cricket/sri-lanka-vs-england</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zHTDuMJwuQt3BPUzVhbhUi</guid>
      <description>How to watch 2026 Sri Lanka vs England live streams online, with the cricket series getting underway with a trio of ODIs at R. Premadasa Stadium in Colombo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero Dubai Desert Classic 2026 live stream: how to watch DP World Tour golf online, TV channels, preview, Round 1 tee times</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/golf/hero-dubai-desert-classic-2026-dp-world-tour-golf-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MsK648Zwgd7A9MFb4Wzq7B</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Hero Dubai Desert Classic 2026 live streams online from anywhere, as Rory McIlroy, Tommy Fleetwood &amp; Co. start the new golf season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft CEO urges AI developers &#8220;to get to a point where we are using this to do something useful,&#8221; or &#8220;lose even the social permission...to generate these tokens&#8221;</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/microsoft-ceo-urges-ai-developers-to-get-to-a-point-where-we-are-using-this-to-do-something-useful-or-lose-even-the-social-permission-to-generate-these-tokens</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ybVd8gCLAhyTUonFZeAqR</guid>
      <description>Satya Nadella used his Davos platform to warn that AI&#8217;s future hinges on proving real-world utility.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
