<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:56:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#171; Ubisoft tel qu&#8217;on le connait n&#8217;existe plus &#187; : 6 jeux annul&#233;s, studios ferm&#233;s, restructuration &#8211; Ubisoft fait son grand reboot</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2951251_ubisoft-tel-quon-le-connait-nexiste-plus-jeux-annules-studios-fermes-fin-du-teletravail-ubisoft-fait-un-grand-reboot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2951251_ubisoft-tel-quon-le-connait-nexiste-plus-jeux-annules-studios-fermes-fin-du-teletravail-ubisoft-fait-un-grand-reboot</guid>
      <description>
C'est le grand chamboulement pour Ubisoft. La firme annonce une immense restructuration. Plusieurs jeux sont annul&#233;s, des studios ferment et les employ&#233;s n'auront plus le droit au t&#233;l&#233;travail.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annulations et reports de jeux, fermetures de studio, r&#233;organisation&#160;: l&#8217;&#233;lectrochoc Ubisoft</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/annulations-et-reports-de-jeux-fermetures-de-studio-reorganisation-lelectrochoc-ubisoft.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321700</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft, le g&#233;ant fran&#231;ais du jeu vid&#233;o, op&#232;re une r&#233;organisation majeure et s'appr&#234;te &#224; vivre quelques mois difficiles, entre fermetures de studios, reports et annulations de jeux. Une transformation en profondeur n&#233;cessaire, selon la direction, pour &#171; reprendre son leadership cr&#233;atif &#187; et provoquer un rebond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is expanding ads to all users globally</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-is-expanding-ads-to-all-users-globally-183900439.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e35048f8-f484-499f-87d1-adea38ca7b5c</guid>
      <description>Threads has grown enough for Meta to fully integrate it into its advertising machine. On Wednesday, the company said that, with the platform now hosting 400 million monthly active users, ads are expanding globally to all users. The inevitable move follows a test in 30 countries early last year.Ads on Threads are powered by Meta's AI-powered advertising system. They'll use the "same level of personalization" (i.e., tracking and profiling) as Facebook and Instagram. Image, video and carousel ad formats will all appear natively in Threads feeds.Meta said the ad expansion will begin next week, but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Origin&#8217;s satellite internet network TeraWave will move data at 6Tbps</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/21/blue-origins-satellite-internet-network-terawave-will-move-data-at-6tbps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084588</guid>
      <description>The network will be designed for enterprise, data center, and government customers and could offer an alternative to SpaceX's Starlink service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers have finally made sophisticated AI generated malware &#8211; this AI virus was functional in a matter of days and mimicked the work of a three dev teams working 50 hours a week</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-have-finally-made-sophisticated-ai-generated-malware-this-ai-virus-was-functional-in-a-matter-of-days-and-mimicked-the-work-of-a-three-dev-teams-working-50-hours-a-week</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kovszpcNePJbXjVMTpBXoV</guid>
      <description>VoidLink malware was created by a single developer using an AI agent to do the work of three development teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zipline charts drone delivery expansion with $600M in new funding</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/21/zipline-charts-drone-delivery-expansion-with-600m-in-new-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084562</guid>
      <description>The startup plans to expand to at least four new U.S. states in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For All Mankind returns on March 27 for a fifth season</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/for-all-mankind-returns-on-march-27-for-a-fifth-season-183212860.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">870143af-89dd-46a8-84c5-50a4ab938082</guid>
      <description>Apple TV+ has become one of the best streaming services for sci-fi, with hits like Pluribus, Severance, Foundation and many more. There are so many shows that it's easy to forget the one that started it all. For All Mankind was the platform's very first attempt at sci-fi and it's finally coming back after two years for season five on March 27.
The next season will run for ten episodes on a weekly basis. It concludes on May 29, with new installments dropping each Friday.

What follows are some slight spoilers for the show, so read with caution. The streamer dropped a short teaser to announce th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#8217;s Time for Nvidia to Prove It Can Do More Than Graphics Cards for PCs</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/its-time-for-nvidia-to-prove-it-can-do-more-than-graphics-cards-for-pcs-2000712552</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712552</guid>
      <description>This may be the moment when ARM really takes off on PCs, though it couldn't come at a worse time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL Knocks $1,000 off One of Our Favorite Mid-Range TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/tcl-qm8k-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6971084c58f6cbc40178c43f</guid>
      <description>The 65-inch QM8K sees a massive discount, with equally generous markdowns on larger models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Adorable Good Boy Just Got Rare, Life-Saving Brain Surgery</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-adorable-good-boy-just-got-rare-life-saving-brain-surgery-2000712485</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712485</guid>
      <description>Six-year-old Woody has recovered well enough to take his daily walks again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26 battery pack leak points to Qi2 charging support</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865083/samsung-galaxy-s26-battery-pack-qi2-support</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T13:11:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865083</guid>
      <description>It looks like Samsung is preparing to launch a new Qi2 battery pack for the upcoming Galaxy S26, which is rumored to support the upgraded charging standard. A report from Winfuture shows off leaked images of what appears to be the new accessory, outfitted with a magnetic Qi2 charging ring that delivers up to 15W [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFOs are now getting their own 'vibe coding' moment thanks to Datarails</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/cfos-are-now-getting-their-own-vibe-coding-moment-thanks-to-datarails</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eeM5IG6PRP1alu4DeZtBG</guid>
      <description>For the modern CFO, the hardest part of the job often isn't the math&#8212;it's the storytelling. After the books are closed and the variances calculated, finance teams spend days, sometimes weeks, manually copy-pasting charts into PowerPoint slides to explain why the numbers moved.Today, 11-year-old Israeli fintech company Datarails announced a set of new generative AI tools designed to automate that "last mile" of financial reporting, effectively allowing finance leaders to "vibe code" their way to a board deck.Launching today to accompany the firm's newly announced $70 million Series C funding ro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is adding AI-powered assistant to One Medical</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/amazon-is-adding-ai-powered-assistant-to-one-medical-180803368.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30303e1d-df8b-4867-ac8b-bc94095b4e43</guid>
      <description>Amazon is introducing an AI-powered assistant to One Medical, the tech-forward primary care provider it acquired in 2023. Dubbed 'Health AI,' Amazon says the tool "provides 24/7 personalized health guidance based on your medical records."
The company says Health AI can explain lab results, help manage medications, and book appointments for patients. Amazon also says it can "analyze images" but doesn't specify whether this means medical imaging or user uploaded photos. While the company specifically says the tool "complements, but does not replace," a patient's healthcare provider, it also vagu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance and ICE Are Driving Patients Away From Medical Care, Report Warns</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/surveillance-and-ice-are-driving-patients-away-from-medical-care-report-warns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6970de66f85422ea0213ff44</guid>
      <description>A new EPIC report says data brokers, ad-tech surveillance, and ICE enforcement are among the factors leading to a &#8220;health privacy crisis&#8221; that is eroding trust and deterring people from seeking care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenEvidence hits $12B valuation, with new round led by Thrive, DST</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/21/openevidence-hits-12b-valuation-with-new-round-led-by-thrive-dst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3084544</guid>
      <description>The medical info database has doubled in valuation since last raise in October, despite encroachment from model makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Just Made All Your James Bond Dreams Come True</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/netflix-just-made-all-your-james-bond-dreams-come-true-2000712556</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712556</guid>
      <description>Basically every Bond film, from 'Dr. No' to 'No Time to Die,' is now on the streamer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've seen most of 2026's new robot vacuums, and these are the 2 models I can't wait to try</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/ive-seen-most-of-2026s-new-robot-vacuums-and-these-are-the-2-models-i-cant-wait-to-try</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MZpcAfKVjw3zgiYV6Qbzoh</guid>
      <description>These are my hot tips for the best robot vacuums of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time remake among six games canceled by Ubisoft</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/the-prince-of-persia-the-sands-of-time-remake-among-six-games-canceled-by-ubisoft-175801132.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d800f9a1-485d-49a3-b1b1-23475c703acc</guid>
      <description>Two high-profile upcoming Ubisoft games have been starting to look more and more like vaporware with each passing year. One of them is Beyond Good &amp; Evil 2, which we were assured is still in development last year. The other is the Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time remake, which is now officially canceled, along with five other games on Ubisoft&#8217;s release slate.
The news came in a media briefing attended virtually by VGC, in which the French company also announced delays to seven other games as part of a major restructuring. As reported by VGC, the only canceled game currently named by Ubisoft...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon has launched a massive sale ahead of Presidents' Day &#8212;here are 21 deals I'd buy now, including 50% off appliances, TVs, heaters, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/amazon-has-launched-a-massive-sale-ahead-of-presidents-day-here-are-21-deals-id-buy-now-including-50-percent-off-appliances-tvs-heaters-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rRNWERtXmM6NGBUpvooN8W</guid>
      <description>Amazon has launched a huge sale ahead of Presidents' Day, and I'm rounding up my 21 favorite deals to buy now, including TVs, appliances, heaters, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving theory test cheats are using Bluetooth earpieces and hidden phones to pass &#8212; and after my recent nightmare, I&#8217;m not surprised</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/driving-theory-test-cheats-are-using-bluetooth-earpieces-and-hidden-phones-to-pass-and-after-my-recent-nightmare-im-not-surprised</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BeCmZePeBaguTM3YwkMs3Y</guid>
      <description>The number of learner drivers caught cheating in their driving tests has skyrocketed in the UK as candidates face long waiting times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D&#233;pendance aux r&#233;seaux sociaux | Snapchat conclut un accord avec une plaignante am&#233;ricaine</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-21/dependance-aux-reseaux-sociaux/snapchat-conclut-un-accord-avec-une-plaignante-americaine.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:35:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09946cb4de21395b8112ef70d55fe6ec</guid>
      <description>Snapchat a conclu un accord pour clore des poursuites qui devaient le voir compara&#238;tre fin janvier aux c&#244;t&#233;s d&#8217;Instagram, TikTok et YouTube, dans le premier d&#8217;une s&#233;rie de proc&#232;s aux &#201;tats-Unis sur l&#8217;impact des r&#233;seaux sociaux sur la sant&#233; mentale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo EX60 vs Audi Q6 e-tron et Tesla Model Y vs BMW iX3 : qui est le meilleur aujourd&#8217;hui ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2949915_volvo-ex60-vs-audi-q6-e-tron-et-tesla-model-y-vs-bmw-ix3-qui-peut-le-meilleur-aujourdhui</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2949915_volvo-ex60-vs-audi-q6-e-tron-et-tesla-model-y-vs-bmw-ix3-qui-peut-le-meilleur-aujourdhui</guid>
      <description>
66 500 &#8364;. C'est le ticket d'entr&#233;e du nouveau Volvo EX60. &#192; ce tarif, et jusqu'&#224; plus de 82 000 &#8364; pour la version int&#233;ressante. Volvo ne cherche pas &#224; d&#233;mocratiser l'&#233;lectrique. La marque vise la gorge des premiums allemands. Et avec 810 km d'autonomie, elle a les crocs.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The company Americans say is the best place to work in 2026 isn&#8217;t who you think</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478569/the-company-americans-say-is-the-best-place-to-work-in-2026-isnt-who-you-think</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T17:30:52</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478569/the-company-americans-say-is-the-best-place-to-work-in-2026-isnt-who-you-think</guid>
      <description>Workers praised flexibility, growth, and culture at a company far removed from Silicon Valley.
For as much as we heard about AI in the past year, the top two best places to work in the U.S. are decidedly AI-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo&#8217;s EX60 Promises 400-mile Range in a More Competitive EV Climate</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/volvos-ex60-promises-400-mile-range-in-a-more-competitive-ev-climate-2000712520</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712520</guid>
      <description>HugInCore, integrated AI, and Nvidia-powered infotainment are some of the features in Volvo's new electric SUV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo EX60 Electric SUV: Range, Specs, Availability, and Price</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/volvo-ex60-electric-suv-range-specs-availability-price/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696feb12e00c6fae963751a3</guid>
      <description>The Swedish brand&#8217;s latest computer-packed EV hopes to take on and beat the BMW iX3. But we&#8217;re more excited about the new seat belt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo aims for an EV reset with the new EX60 crossover</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864561/volvo-ex60-range-price-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T12:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864561</guid>
      <description>Volvo's EX60, with fast-charging capabilities and a brand-new electric architecture, made its official debut today, with the Swedish automaker positioning the crossover EV as a new direction for its battery-powered lineup. With up to 400 miles of estimated range and an 800-volt architecture for ultra-fast charging, the EX60 feels like a concerted effort by Volvo [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic's official Git MCP server had some worrying security flaws - this is what happened next</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/anthropics-official-git-mcp-server-had-some-worrying-security-flaws-this-is-what-happened-next</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7vE2rkzC8dbWNQ9UBN8woL</guid>
      <description>Bugs could be chained for devastating effect, but Anthropic stepped up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo EX60 SUV preview: 400-mile range, 670 hp and Google Gemini onboard</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/volvo-ex60-suv-preview-400-mile-range-670-hp-and-google-gemini-onboard-173000033.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3556f3d6-dcf7-45df-999f-4b79db63f4ee</guid>
      <description>Volvo hasn't exactly had a great run of EVs lately. The rollout of its flagship EX90 was stymied out of the gate by a bevy of software glitches. The EX30, meanwhile, was too expensive when it launched &#8212; the promised $35,000 model was incompatible with the currently chaotic global tariff situation.Now, it's time for a new generation of EV from Volvo, one that's radically different at its core with a gigacast frame, a much higher-density battery and enough digital and literal horsepower to impress the most jaded of automotive enthusiasts. Mix in high-performance chipsets from both NVIDIA and Qua...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 reasons why cutting back on alcohol is so hard</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91478171/5-reasons-why-cutting-back-on-alcohol-is-so-hard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T17:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91478171/5-reasons-why-cutting-back-on-alcohol-is-so-hard</guid>
      <description>Anyone reviewing their relationship with alcohol should look at what I call the three Cs: consumption, consequences, and control.
Below, Charles Knowles shares five key insights from his new book,&#160;Why We Drink Too Much: The Impact of Alcohol on Our Bodies and Culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo EX60&#160;: 800 km d&#8217;autonomie et une ceinture de s&#233;curit&#233; next gen qui peut tout changer&#160;?</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/volvo-ex60-presentation-avis.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1321581</guid>
      <description>Volvo lance l&#8217;EX60 : 800 km d&#8217;autonomie, vitesse de recharge record, ceinture de s&#233;curit&#233; miracle. Le nouveau SUV &#233;lectrique semble disposer de nombreux atouts. On a d&#233;cid&#233; d&#8217;aller le voir en vrai pour le v&#233;rifier. D&#233;couverte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo d&#233;voile l&#8217;EX60 : prix, date et fiche technique du nouveau rival du Model Y et des Allemands</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/volvo/2949789_volvo-devoile-lex60-prix-date-et-fiche-technique-du-nouveau-rival-du-model-y-et-des-allemands</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/volvo/2949789_volvo-devoile-lex60-prix-date-et-fiche-technique-du-nouveau-rival-du-model-y-et-des-allemands</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s un EX30 imparfait et un EX90 retard&#233;, Volvo joue sa carte ma&#238;tresse : l'EX60. C'est le rempla&#231;ant spirituel du XC60, le best-seller de la marque.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RetroBox is a new TV/VCR combo &#8212; yes, really &#8212; with a classic design and modern tech including HDMI ports</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/the-retrobox-is-a-new-tv-vcr-combo-yes-really-with-a-classic-design-and-modern-tech-including-hdmi-ports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">XdGuJcTMLkBJn6w7Gu3pdZ</guid>
      <description>Who needs 4K when you can watch a grainy old VHS instead?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cet &#233;metteur et r&#233;cepteur Ugreen permet de projeter votre PC sur un t&#233;l&#233;viseur et perd 14 % de son prix chez Amazon pour les soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2951049_cet-emetteur-et-recepteur-ugreen-permet-de-projeter-votre-pc-sur-un-televiseur-et-perd-14-de-son-prix-chez-amazon-pour-les-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2951049_cet-emetteur-et-recepteur-ugreen-permet-de-projeter-votre-pc-sur-un-televiseur-et-perd-14-de-son-prix-chez-amazon-pour-les-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Gr&#226;ce &#224; un signal projet&#233; sur 50 m et une compatibilit&#233; avec la 5G pour &#233;viter les soucis de connexion, cet &#233;metteur et r&#233;cepteur de Ugreen s'affiche comme un excellent moyen de projeter votre ordinateur sur un plus grand &#233;cran. Amazon profite des soldes d'hiver pour retirer 14 % de son prix et il tombe &#224; 58,58 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft cancels Prince of Persia remake as part of major reorganization</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865060/ubisoft-prince-of-persia-sands-of-time-remake-canceled-reorganization</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T12:23:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865060</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft is announcing a major reorganization, and with the changes, it's refocusing its portfolio and canceling some games, including the beleaguered remake of Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time. With the reorganization, Ubisoft will focus its efforts on big open worlds and live service games and is making "accelerated investments" in "player-facing Generative AI." [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configurations PC pour Marathon : tout ce qu&#8217;il faut pour le faire tourner</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2950301_configurations-pc-pour-marathon-tout-ce-quil-faut-pour-le-faire-tourner</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/2950301_configurations-pc-pour-marathon-tout-ce-quil-faut-pour-le-faire-tourner</guid>
      <description>
Le fameux shooter d'extraction fa&#231;on Bungie a enfin une date de sortie, heureusement toute proche. Les joueurs PC ont aussi appris &#224; quelle sauce ils seront mang&#233;s pour le faire tourner sur leur machine...
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk is reportedly trying to take SpaceX public</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/elon-musk-is-reportedly-trying-to-take-spacex-public-170337053.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3ae18b2-a078-40b2-9224-edbcf2ac2b1e</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is reportedly looking to finally take SpaceX public after years of resistance, according to sources who spoke to The&#160;Wall Street Journal. The company has long said it wouldn't choose an IPO until it had established a presence on Mars. That isn't happening anytime soon.
So why now? Company insiders have suggested it's because Musk wants to build AI data centers in space. Google recently announced it was looking into putting a data center in space, with test launches scheduled for 2027. Musk reportedly wants to beat his rival to the punch, but SpaceX would need the billions of dollars ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Pratt&#8217;s Sci-Fi Movies, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chris-pratts-sci-fi-movies-ranked-2000712057</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000712057</guid>
      <description>The 'Guardians of the Galaxy' and 'Jurassic World' star has been in a lot of sci-fi beyond 'Mercy,' out this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElevenLabs made an AI album to plug its music generator</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/864843/elevenlabs-ai-music-eleven-album-release</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-21T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=864843</guid>
      <description>ElevenLabs has released an album of AI-generated songs in its latest attempt to separate itself from the ethical concerns surrounding AI music. The Eleven Album aims to showcase "how artists can use AI to expand their creative range while maintaining full authorship and commercial rights," according to ElevenLabs. ElevenLabs is using the album to market [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercy review: Chris Pratt's new AI sci-fi thriller is so haphazard, you'll wonder if ChatGPT could do a better job of writing it</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/mercy-review</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RkKSjF8FRZkmGDz8ijN3VX</guid>
      <description>AI is taking over the world, but what if it swallowed the entire legal system too? Chris Pratt finds out in Mercy, but watching this film is more punishment than any generated court could dole out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix says a big mobile app redesign is coming &#8211; and subscribers are bracing themselves for another UI nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/netflix/netflix-says-a-big-mobile-app-redesign-is-coming-and-subscribers-are-bracing-themselves-for-another-ui-nightmare</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85k72nLzXm4PVRMMYECfDh</guid>
      <description>There's a new Netflix update coming to mobile, and it's bringing a new vertical feed to your account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Et si tout venait&#8230; d&#8217;un second Big Bang ? Une th&#233;orie sid&#233;rante pour expliquer la mati&#232;re noire</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-si-tout-venait-second-big-bang-theorie-siderante-expliquer-matiere-noire-w2t8-130191/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-si-tout-venait-second-big-bang-theorie-siderante-expliquer-matiere-noire-w2t8-130191/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Le rayonnement fossile prouve que le Big Bang quelques secondes apr&#232;s son d&#233;but avait produit un plasma incroyablement chaud de protons, neutrons et photons, sans oublier des &#233;lectrons et des neutrinos. Le mod&#232;le cosmologique standard repose aussi sur l'hypoth&#232;se que ce plasma contenait des...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldes PC portables : le top 10 des offres sur les configurations gaming et bureautiques est ici !</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935325_les-pc-portables-bureautiques-et-gaming-sont-vendus-au-rabais-lors-des-soldes-le-top-10-des-offres</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2935325_les-pc-portables-bureautiques-et-gaming-sont-vendus-au-rabais-lors-des-soldes-le-top-10-des-offres</guid>
      <description>
Les soldes d&#8217;hiver 2026 battent encore leur plein avec la troisi&#232;me d&#233;marque. Si vous pensiez que les meilleures affaires &#233;taient d&#233;j&#224; pass&#233;es, d&#233;trompez-vous : plusieurs restent disponibles, notamment sur les laptops gaming et les ultraportables puissants pour le travail.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
