<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:25:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What James Cameron Changed in &#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; After Audiences Saw &#8216;Way of Water&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/what-james-cameron-changed-in-avatar-fire-and-ash-after-audiences-saw-way-of-water-2000702090</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702090</guid>
      <description>In a new interview, Cameron gave details about the parts of 'Avatar 2' that inspired changes in 'Avatar 3.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Patagonia CEO Rose Marcario resigns from Rivian&#8217;s board</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/former-patagonia-ceo-rose-marcario-resigns-from-rivians-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3078011</guid>
      <description>Marcario joined the board in 2021, and will maintain her position as chair overseeing the Rivian Foundation, which made its first grants last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude's Chrome plugin is now available to all paid users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/claudes-chrome-plugin-is-now-available-to-all-paid-users-221024295.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7f62c98-4492-463a-9bc4-386e94c54b23</guid>
      <description>Anthropic is finally letting more people use Claude in Google Chrome. The company's AI browser plugin is expanding beyond $200-per-month Max subscribers and is now available to anyone who pays for a Claude subscription.&#160;The Claude Chrome plugin allows for easy access to Anthropic's AI regardless of where you are on the web, but its real draw is how it lets Claude navigate and use websites on your behalf. Anthropic says that Claude can fill out forms, manage your calendar and email and complete multi-step workflows based on a prompt. The latest version of the plugin also features integration wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runaway Black Hole Escapes Its Galaxy&#8212;and It&#8217;s Leaving Baby Stars in Its Wake</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/runaway-black-hole-escapes-its-galaxy-and-its-leaving-baby-stars-in-its-wake-2000701981</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701981</guid>
      <description>The Webb telescope confirmed one of the fastest moving celestial objects ever detected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-generation nuclear reactors could get a boost from the National Defense Authorization Act</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/848445/nuclear-energy-ndaa-defense-bill</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T17:04:48-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848445</guid>
      <description>President Trump signed the National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA) for Fiscal Year 2026 Thursday with measures that further the bipartisan push for next-generation nuclear power plants. The Trump administration has embraced the technology as a new energy source for data centers demanding greater amounts of electricity for AI. Many Democrats, meanwhile, have championed smaller and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are investors placing their bets next year? AI, AI, AI.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/where-are-investors-placing-their-bets-next-year-ai-ai-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077878</guid>
      <description>Investors at TechCrunch Disrupt explained their focus on artificial intelligence and offered advice to founders on how to stand out in a crowded AI field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world&#8217;s first &#8216;concentric&#8217; turntable and CD player combo is the turducken of hi-fi</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/turntables/the-worlds-first-concentric-turntable-and-cd-player-combo-is-the-turducken-of-hi-fi</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">x2YZK4uYW9uitFvxdhqWPc</guid>
      <description>The Mixx Analog+ is a turntable with a top-loading CD player in the center of it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursor continues acquisition Spree with Graphite deal</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/cursor-continues-acquisition-spree-with-graphite-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077998</guid>
      <description>Graphite is an AI code review assistant that was last valued at $290 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s $56B Tesla pay package restored by Delaware Supreme Court</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/elon-musks-56b-tesla-pay-package-restored-by-delaware-supreme-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077995</guid>
      <description>The decision brings to a close a years-long court battle that irked Musk so much he moved Tesla's incorporation from Delaware to Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We found 80 stocking stuffers under $100 that are actually useful</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/843079/best-stocking-stuffers-christmas-ideas-2025</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T16:48:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=843079</guid>
      <description>Let&#8217;s face it, it&#8217;s easy to fixate on the big gifts that crowd around the Christmas tree. However, we&#8217;d argue that the true treasures are the small, useful, and thoughtful gifts tucked within stockings. That&#8217;s why, for this guide, we&#8217;ve pooled together a bunch of tried-and-tested gadgets and goods to help bolster someone&#8217;s everyday carry [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing a New Chapter for &#8216;Uncanny Valley&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-new-chapter-for-uncanny-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69408756a6e438d1fa335015</guid>
      <description>In this episode, we look back at 2025 and look ahead to what's happening in 2026&#8212;including what&#8217;s in store for Uncanny Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk about coal in your stocking - SantaStealer malware steals data from browsers and crypto wallets</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/talk-about-coal-in-your-stocking-santastealer-malware-steals-data-from-browsers-and-crypto-wallets</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8wxqqP9rNe8K7DgwWALZe8</guid>
      <description>SantaStealer is a rebranded infostealer using modular data theft, modest pricing, and limited stealth, with no confirmed large-scale deployment yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out - hackers are coming after your Christmas bonus, as paychecks come under threat</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/watch-out-hackers-are-coming-after-your-christmas-bonus-as-paychecks-come-under-threat</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BXjVqn5m8x5Y5Pu5Ab8eWU</guid>
      <description>Payroll-focused social engineering attacks target help desk staff, redirect employee salaries, and show how human factors can bypass traditional technical protections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT will now let you pick how nice it is</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/848435/openai-chatgpt-characteristics-update-warmth-enthusiasm</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T16:28:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848435</guid>
      <description>OpenAI will now give you the ability to dial up - or down - ChatGPT's warmth and enthusiasm. An update rolling out on Friday gives you the option to choose whether you want "more" or "less" of these personality traits, or stick with the default. There are also options to tweak how often ChatGPT uses [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Laser Beams Could Power Military Drones 5,000 Feet in the Air</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/these-laser-beams-could-power-military-drones-5000-feet-in-the-air-2000702020</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702020</guid>
      <description>The U.S. military-backed project is now on the way to integrated system testing, the company said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DOJ&#8217;s Jeffrey Epstein Files Are Here</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-dojs-jeffrey-epstein-files-are-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6940406023b0c5e0ff2515d1</guid>
      <description>Forced by an act of Congress, the Justice Department has released &#8220;hundreds of thousands&#8221; of pages of documents related to Epstein&#8212;but not everything, as is required by law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg's nonprofit cuts ties with the immigration advocacy group he co-founded</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/mark-zuckerbergs-nonprofit-cuts-ties-with-the-immigration-advocacy-group-he-co-founded-183447900.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6527912-d56a-43d8-ab07-30a9ebbe2f23</guid>
      <description>Behold Mark Zuckerberg: man of principle. Witness the Meta CEO's dedication to the most high-minded of causes: "currying favor with whoever's in charge." In 2013, when Barack Obama was president, Zuckerberg co-founded FWD.us, a pro-immigration advocacy group. For years, he vocally supported providing paths to citizenship for "the most talented and hardest-working people, no matter where they were born." Now, in 2025, with Donald Trump back in power and pushing draconian immigration policies, Zuckerberg's philanthropy organization has officially cut ties with the group. Who says Big Tech execut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Spidey to Snoopy, Hollywood&#8217;s Acquisition Mania Has Come for &#8216;Peanuts&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-peanuts-snoopy-charlie-brown-2000701919</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000701919</guid>
      <description>Sony just purchased a controlling stake in the iconic brand featuring Snoopy, Charlie Brown, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; could break box office records. Do critics like it?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463560/avatar-3-fire-and-ash-box-office-predictions-critical-reviews</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T21:11:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463560/avatar-3-fire-and-ash-box-office-predictions-critical-reviews</guid>
      <description>Opening this weekend, the latest in James Cameron&#8217;s franchise is expected to be a boon for Twentieth Century Studios and parent company Disney.
Much like how the character Jack Dawson proudly proclaims to be king of the world after boarding the Titanic, film director James Cameron could claim to be king of the box office. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotspots Capable of Driving Catastrophic Mega-Hurricanes Are Spreading Across the Oceans</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hotspots-capable-of-driving-catastrophic-mega-hurricanes-are-spreading-across-the-oceans-2000702025</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000702025</guid>
      <description>This process, driven by climate change, is increasing the risk of &#8220;Category 6&#8221; tropical cyclones making landfall in densely populated areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split View Tabs in Chrome are a game-changer &#8212; I can&#8217;t believe I wasn&#8217;t using this before</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/chrome/split-view-tabs-in-chrome-are-a-game-changer-i-cant-believe-i-wasnt-using-this-before</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MufQGHztUZHN3n3jobXj3j</guid>
      <description>Chrome's new Split View Tabs feature, introduced in the November update, is a game-changer that allows users to view two browser tabs simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React2Shell exploitation continues to escalate, posing 'significant risk'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/react2shell-exploitation-continues-to-escalate-posing-significant-risk</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">wjHawdoUaRvYKfJ5RbMs5L</guid>
      <description>Several hundred machines across a diverse set of organizations already compromised, Microsoft says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sues web scraper for sucking up search results &#8216;at an astonishing scale&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/848365/google-scraper-lawsuit-serpapi</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-19T15:48:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=848365</guid>
      <description>Google has filed a lawsuit against SerpApi, a company that offers tools to scrape content on the web, including Google's search results. SerpApi is accused of violating the Copyright Act by using "deceptive means" to automatically access and take Google's search results "at an astonishing scale" before selling the data to customers. Reddit also sued [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok | L&#8217;accord am&#233;ricain n&#8217;aura aucune incidence sur le Canada</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2025-12-19/tiktok/l-accord-americain-n-aura-aucune-incidence-sur-le-canada.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:48:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa8cc2bbd51a31f69e560b9f9a5c65a2</guid>
      <description>Les utilisateurs canadiens de TikTok ne devraient pas remarquer de changements sur l&#8217;application &#224; la suite de la signature d&#8217;un accord entre d&#8217;importants investisseurs am&#233;ricains pour la cr&#233;ation d&#8217;une nouvelle coentreprise TikTok, selon un expert en cybers&#233;curit&#233;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix is acquiring game avatar maker Ready Player Me</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/netflix-is-acquiring-game-avatar-maker-ready-player-me-204443001.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7822683-862a-4270-b2d5-2957d63862c2</guid>
      <description>Netflix is acquiring Estonian startup Ready Player Me, a company creating "cross-game avatar tech" that allows players to bring their digital personas with them to different games, the company's CEO Timmu T&#245;ke shared in a LinkedIn post. The acquisition is part of Netflix's new games strategy, which puts an emphasis on approachable multiplayer titles and adaptations of the streaming service's IP.Ready Player Me's team of around 20 employees will be incorporated into Netflix's staff, TechCrunch writes, though T&#245;ke is the only one of the startup's four founders who will continue on after the acqu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous messaging app NGL was acquired by &#8216;EarnPhone&#8217; startup Mode Mobile</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/19/anonymous-messaging-app-ngl-was-acquired-by-earnphone-startup-mode-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3077874</guid>
      <description>Given NGL's track record of dubious growth hacking, this partnership with Mode Mobile seems like a good match.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
