<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:29:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#8217;s Animated &#8216;Ghostbusters&#8217; Movie Shows Signs of Life</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/netflixs-animated-ghostbusters-movie-shows-signs-of-life-2000719265</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719265</guid>
      <description>A new writer has joined the 'Ghostbusters' franchise's first animated movie, which got announced nearly a whole decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analogue unearths N64 prototype colors for its limited edition 3D console</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/nintendo/analogue-unearths-n64-prototype-colors-for-its-limited-edition-3d-console-171923894.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c67b52d8-06fd-44d2-b7b1-607e80aa9e03</guid>
      <description>Analogue is back with another hit of N64 nostalgia, but with colorways that are deep cuts for even the biggest Nintendo nerds. Analogue announced its latest run of limited edition versions of its 3D console, this time drawing inspiration from a batch of prototype colorways for the original N64 that were manufactured but never hit the market. Now, the Analogue 3D will come in Ghost, Glacier, Extreme Green, Ocean and yes, even Atomic Purple.
It may just be a cosmetic upgrade, but it's worth noting that each of the colorways has matching cables, power adapters and 16GB SD cards that come preinsta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test de la LG S20A : et si la vraie barre de son &#171;&#160;petit budget&#160;&#187; ne venait pas d&#8217;un kit 5.1 ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2966537_test-de-la-lg-s20a-et-si-la-vraie-barre-de-son-petit-budget-ne-venait-pas-dun-kit-5-1</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/lg/2966537_test-de-la-lg-s20a-et-si-la-vraie-barre-de-son-petit-budget-ne-venait-pas-dun-kit-5-1</guid>
      <description>
Avec son format ultra compact, son architecture 2.0 canaux et l&#8217;absence totale de caisson, la barre de son LG S20A promet de donner un second souffle aux petits t&#233;l&#233;viseurs sans transformer le salon en salle de cin&#233;ma pour un budget tr&#232;s raisonnable. Nous l&#8217;avons test&#233;e et en voici nos impressions.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested the Viltrox 35mm f/1.2 LAB for two months &#8211; photo assignments will never be the same again</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/camera-lenses/i-tested-the-viltrox-35mm-f-1-2-lab-for-two-months-photo-assignments-will-never-be-the-same-again</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74mU6xd8qHwG5ZTiqAXaPG</guid>
      <description>Viltrox's priciest prime lens is optically incredible, versatile for documentary work, and costs a fraction of proprietary equivalents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon casse le prix de ce chargeur Belkin 2-en-1 (50W) avec plus de 40% de remise</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2965069_amazon-casse-le-prix-de-ce-chargeur-belkin-2-en-1-50w-avec-plus-de-40-de-remise</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2965069_amazon-casse-le-prix-de-ce-chargeur-belkin-2-en-1-50w-avec-plus-de-40-de-remise</guid>
      <description>
Voil&#224; un accessoire indispensable &#224; prix mini avec le Belkin BoostCharge&#8239;50 W int&#233;grant un double port USB-C, qui est actuellement &#224; -43 % sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG&#8217;s C5 TV and Anker&#8217;s powerful power bank are this week&#8217;s best deals</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/874585/lg-c5-tv-anker-power-bank-deal-sale-super-bowl</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T11:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=874585</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s the first weekend of February, which can only mean one thing: The Super Bowl (or &#8220;Benito Bowl,&#8221; if you&#8217;re mainly tuning in for the Bad Bunny-led halftime show) is upon us. The game is Sunday, February 8th, at 6:30PM ET on Peacock, NFL Plus, and on live services that include NBC. With that out [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve used the DXRacer Martian Pro for three months and don&#8217;t want to sit in another gaming chair ever again</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/dxracer-martian-pro-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">h6GbFmPKkxVAmXo9aZJH4J</guid>
      <description>The DXRacer Martian Pro is a tech-filled gaming chair that offers worthwhile comfort upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the 2026 Super Bowl on NBC: Patriots vs. Seahawks channel, where to stream, start time, and more</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/how-to-watch-the-2026-super-bowl-on-nbc-patriots-vs-seahawks-channel-where-to-stream-start-time-and-more-175759402.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d4e4b2-2273-433c-87e7-fbfb4424f573</guid>
      <description>


  The New England Patriots are headed to the 2026 Super Bowl. (Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images)
 

  Lauren Leigh Bacho via Getty Images
 

The countdown is on, and Super Bowl LX, between the New England Patriots and Seattle Seahawks, is nearly here. This weekend, the Big Game will be held at Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, CA. The NFL Championship Game kicks off at 6:30PM ET this Sunday, Feb. 8. Pre-game coverage starts at 12PM ET. Like all other Sunday Night Football games this season, the Super Bowl will be broadcast on NBC, and will stream live on Peacock. Here's everything you need ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros. Magically Morphs &#8216;Clayface&#8217; and &#8216;Practical Magic 2&#8217; Dates</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/warner-bros-magically-morphs-clayface-and-practical-magic-2-dates-2000719236</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719236</guid>
      <description>September ain't big enough for two big movies, so WB's decided to leave 'Practical Magic 2' while 'Clayface' gets Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The second-gen AirTags are a scatterbrain&#8217;s best friend</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/875314/airtags-second-gen-review-item-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T10:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=875314</guid>
      <description>In a somewhat controversial Vergecast episode, I declared that AirTags are a superior product to iPads. The iPad lovers roasted me across social media. I have heard and respect their opinions. But, I'm sorry - the second-gen AirTag has only deepened my conviction that the humble, $29 item tracker is one of Apple's most helpful [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple could soon allow AI chatbots like ChatGPT and Gemini to appear on CarPlay</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/apple-could-soon-allow-ai-chatbots-like-chatgpt-and-gemini-to-appear-on-carplay</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">W4gXbdeuroXyXPZeGihgb3</guid>
      <description>A new report suggests Apple is thinking about opening up CarPlay to more AI bots, though Siri won't be replaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA is sending Crew-12 astronauts to the ISS on February 11</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-is-sending-crew-12-astronauts-to-the-iss-on-february-11-153000139.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6db2ecfb-75c7-455e-b319-8bd87f3ba4e6</guid>
      <description>The Crew-12 astronauts will soon make their way to the ISS, joining the three remaining spacefarers on board after the previous mission was cut short due to a medical concern. NASA was originally planning a February 15 launch date for the mission, but it has moved it up to February 11. It&#8217;s now targeting a liftoff of no earlier than 6:01 AM Eastern that day from Cape Canaveral in Florida. The crew members are already in quarantine, and if everything goes well on launch day, the Dragon capsule they&#8217;re on will dock with the orbiting lab at approximately 10:30 AM on February 12. If you&#8217;ll recall,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
