<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:27:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DRAM prices set to almost double by March 2026, and yes, we all have our AI overlords to thank for that wonderful news</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/dram-prices-set-to-almost-double-by-march-2026-and-yes-we-all-have-to-thank-our-ai-overlords-for-that-wonderful-news</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2RQDZLMHMVDHKvbkKrVJPM</guid>
      <description>AI-driven data center demand has intensified DDR5 DRAM prices, while server memory prioritization reduces availability for PC-focused products globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon's live-action God of War adaptation adds Teresa Palmer</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/amazons-live-action-god-of-war-adaptation-adds-teresa-palmer-201604602.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76fdff53-0df1-4043-8838-3bbed883b094</guid>
      <description>Amazon is reportedly adding Teresa Palmer (The Fall Guy, Warm Bodies, Hacksaw Ridge) to its pantheon of Norse gods for its God of War TV show adaptation. As first reported by Deadline, Palmer will play Sif, Thor's wife and eventual leader of the Aesir, in the live-action adaptation. It may not carry as much weight as the casting of the video game's protagonist that was revealed earlier this week to be Ryan Hurst, but it could hint at the direction the TV show may take.
        View this post on Instagram            

While Sif plays a minor role in the God of War Ragnarok game, the early casti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying Photo from the Minneapolis ICE Protests Will Have You Shopping for Leicas</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/terrifying-photo-from-the-minneapolis-ice-protests-will-have-you-shopping-for-leicas-2000711428</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711428</guid>
      <description>A very cool new way to stress test your $4600 camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers vs Seahawks Free Streams: How to watch NFL 2026 Divisional Round game online from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/san-francisco-49ers-vs-seattle-seahawks-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tQrkeaUZ78noZKEZYnspQU</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch 49ers vs Seahawks live in all parts of the world, including free streams and international TV channels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony and Netflix Will Keep Being Streaming Buddies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sony-and-netflix-will-keep-being-streaming-buddies-2000711367</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000711367</guid>
      <description>Numbers speak louder than words, and in this case, Netflix will still get dibs on Sony's movie slate for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nouveau Tesla Model Y, un crash-tests 2025 100 % &#233;lectrique et un moteur qui d&#233;fie Bosch et DJI &#8211; R&#233;cap&#8217; Survolt&#233;s</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2945497_recap-survoltes-202603</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/2945497_recap-survoltes-202603</guid>
      <description>
Cette semaine sur Survolt&#233;s, les actualit&#233;s ont &#233;t&#233; nombreuses et vari&#233;es : le FSD de Tesla passe en mode abonnement, Ananda a d&#233;gain&#233; un nouveau moteur pour v&#233;lo &#233;lectrique, les crash-tests automobiles de 2025 sont tomb&#233;s, et Canyon d&#233;voile de grandes ambitions financi&#232;res.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok's latest spinoff app feels a lot like Quibi, but with shorter and cornier content</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/tiktoks-latest-spinoff-app-feels-a-lot-like-quibi-but-with-shorter-and-cornier-content-185702010.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b30f46c8-bad5-4968-adb7-2253f252284e</guid>
      <description>In another attempt to reduce our attention spans to mush, TikTok has released the PineDrama app, which offers serialized drama series that are roughly a minute per episode. As first spotted by Business Insider, the app is designed exactly like TikTok, but instead of trendy dance videos, you can scroll through and watch "micro dramas."
For those new to the category, micro dramas are bite-sized TV shows shot in vertical video and available in minute-long episodes. Don't expect any nominations for Best Original Screenplay with series like The Officer Fell For Me or Married to my past life's nemes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney deleted a Thread because people kept putting anti-fascist quotes from its movies in the replies</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/863980/disney-deleted-anti-fascist-thread</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-17T13:38:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=863980</guid>
      <description>"Share a Disney quote that sums up how you're feeling right now!" That's what Disney posted on Threads the other day, and people immediately replied with lines from Star Wars, The Hunchback of Notre Dame, and even Mary Poppins. The throughline between all the quotes: they were pretty pointedly anti-fascist and clearly aimed at the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills vs Broncos Free Streams: TV Channels &amp; Preview for NFL 2026 Divisional Round Game</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/buffalo-bills-vs-denver-broncos-nfl-2026-divisional-round-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ijVzkEdbVBJw53UoSxqq8h</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Bills vs Broncos live streams for FREE, in the Divisional Round of the 2025/26 NFL playoffs at Empower Field at Mile High in Denver.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
