<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:26:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>People Are Big Mad About He-Man Having Pronouns</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/people-are-big-mad-about-he-man-having-pronouns-2000713094</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713094</guid>
      <description>A joke in the new 'Masters of the Universe' trailer plays into a familiar online grift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Switch 2&#8217;s GameCube library is failing to show the classic console at its best</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/the-switch-2s-gamecube-library-is-failing-to-show-the-classic-console-at-its-best</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yBAH2MQMzwYmHtEyq29xcc</guid>
      <description>Nintendo&#8217;s selection of GameCube Classics on Switch 2 is solid, but largely uninspired. What can be done to improve the collection?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve been an Apple user for 15 years &#8211; here&#8217;s why I&#8217;m actually excited about the Siri chatbot U-turn</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/ive-been-an-apple-user-for-15-years-heres-why-im-actually-excited-about-the-siri-chatbot-u-turn</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">knR4WmiZmXk7NdpqrhV8nL</guid>
      <description>Apple is apparently working on a Siri chatbot powered by AI, and I can&#8217;t wait to see it in action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This isn't your typical mini PC - Beelink reveals new SER10 Pro and SER10 Max powerhouses boasting DDR5, 10Gbps Ethernet, and Ryzen Gorgon Point</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/this-isnt-your-typical-mini-pc-beelink-reveals-new-ser10-pro-and-ser10-max-powerhouses-boasting-ddr5-10-gbps-ethernet-and-ryzen-gorgon-point</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZUkBDSBvMU6Fb3odzpKNGK</guid>
      <description>Beelink launches SER10 Pro and Max mini-PCs with Ryzen AI 9 HX 470, DDR5 memory, and 10 Gbps Ethernet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice AI engine and OpenAI partner LiveKit hits $1B valuation</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/voice-ai-engine-and-openai-partner-livekit-hits-1b-valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085271</guid>
      <description>The five-year-old-startup powers OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT voice mode and raised a $100 million round led by Index Ventures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference startup Inferact lands $150M to commercialize vLLM</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/inference-startup-inferact-lands-150m-to-commercialize-vllm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085302</guid>
      <description>The seed round values the newly formed startup at $800 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darth Maul's standalone series premieres on Disney+ on April 6</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/streaming/darth-mauls-standalone-series-premieres-on-disney-on-april-6-224036720.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8342ded-cef1-4851-b54d-9d826235029b</guid>
      <description>Darth Maul, the beloved, sometimes spider-legged former Sith Lord first introduced in Star Wars: Episode 1 &#8212; The Phantom Menace, is officially getting his own animated spin-off on April 6, 2026, based on a new teaser trailer published by Disney. Star Wars: Maul &#8212; Shadow Lord was originally announced at Star Wars Celebration in 2025, and is set after Maul's arc in Star Wars: The Clone Wars but before his appearance in Star Wars: Rebels.The 10-episode series covers Maul's plot to rebuild his criminal syndicate "on a planet untouched by the Empire," according to Lucasfilm. "There, he crosses path...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This top-tier robovac is back to its Black Friday price &#8211; get the Ecovacs Deebot X8 Pro Omni for a massive 45% off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/robot-vacuums/this-top-tier-robovac-is-back-to-its-black-friday-price-get-the-ecovacs-deebot-x8-pro-omni-for-a-massive-45-percent-off</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YqjRsQhc34QpVi9tmDsxKE</guid>
      <description>The AU$2,499 RRP was the Ecovacs Deebot X8 Pro Omni&#8217;s main drawback, so this huge discount brings it down to its lowest AU price yet and is now much easier to recommend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panne informatique | Plusieurs fonctionnalit&#233;s de Microsoft en panne</title>
      <link>https://www.lapresse.ca/affaires/techno/2026-01-22/panne-informatique/plusieurs-fonctionnalites-de-microsoft-en-panne.php?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=fil&amp;utm_campaign=affaires&amp;utm_content=techno</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:33:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a4134d5c84435ce9ccc4d203f188607</guid>
      <description>Plusieurs services de Microsoft, dont la messagerie Outlook, sont inutilisables pour des milliers d&#8217;utilisateurs depuis jeudi apr&#232;s-midi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yeah, This Guy&#8217;s Looking Like the Frontrunner for New CEO of Apple</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/yeah-this-guys-looking-like-the-frontrunner-for-new-ceo-of-apple-2000713135</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713135</guid>
      <description>Get ready to hear a lot about John Ternus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve tested tons of Bluetooth speakers, and this little-known JBL feature is a major reason I recommend its products so strongly</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/speakers/ive-tested-tons-of-bluetooth-speakers-and-this-little-known-jbl-feature-is-a-major-reason-i-recommend-its-products-so-strongly</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DEA3L4m2DAGar4X5qEtwZB</guid>
      <description>If you're looking to buy a new Bluetooth speaker, this one trick may tempt you to pick one up from JBL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 Outlook down: Microsoft breaks silence on outage</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/microsoft-365-outlook-down-microsoft-breaks-silence-on-outage</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06uolgee8UWCc3VdQBnynHd</guid>
      <description>Microsoft is sharing updates on the Microsoft 365 outage that took down Outlook and other services on Thursday, Jan. 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 outage: Outlook is down. What we know.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/microsoft-365-outage-outlook-teams-exchange-down-what-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03Wq98HWKCFueXRSp553tDX</guid>
      <description>Microsoft 365 appeared to have an outage on Thursday, Jan. 22, with Outlook, Teams, and Defender reportedly affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo is following up Alarmo with a weird Talking Flower in March</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/865618/nintendo-talking-flower-preorder-super-mario-wonder</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:17:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865618</guid>
      <description>After sharing a brief look at its new Talking Flower during a Nintendo Direct showcase last September that generated more questions than answers, Nintendo has finally revealed more details about what the interactive toy actually does and how much it costs. It shares some functionality with Nintendo's Alarmo alarm clock, but the Talking Flower seems [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL made a pair of AI-powered practice amps</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/jbl-made-a-pair-of-ai-powered-practice-amps-221000631.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2a5cbfe-8d8c-4131-b0b7-d3db14c557cc</guid>
      <description>JBL is trying its hand at something new, with a pair of AI-powered practice amps. The BandBox Solo and BandBox Trio include an onboard Stem AI that purportedly lets you separate or remove vocals and instruments from any music streamed over Bluetooth. So, say you're a young guitarist learning &#8220;Stairway to Heaven&#8221; (as one does). At least in theory, you could use the speaker to remove Jimmy Page's part and hone your chops with the rest of the band.The $250 BandBox Solo, designed for individual musicians, has a single guitar / mic input. And the $600 BandBox Trio, better for bands, supports up to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legislators Push to Make Companies Tell Customers When Their Products Will Die</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/legislators-push-to-make-companies-tell-customers-when-their-products-will-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69712224cad1b20bf41c64d0</guid>
      <description>A pair of bills in Massachusetts would require manufacturers to tell consumers when their connected gadgets are going dark. It should be a boon for cybersecurity as connected devices grow obsolete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vimeo lays off &#8216;large portion&#8217; of staff after Bending Spoons buyout</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/866238/vimeo-layoffs-bending-spoons-acquisition</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T17:02:50-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866238</guid>
      <description>Vimeo is laying off employees around the globe just months after the Italian software company Bending Spoons acquired the platform for $1.38 billion, as reported earlier by Business Insider. Even though it's not clear how many people were laid off, Dave Brown, Vimeo's former brand VP, says in a post on LinkedIn that "a large [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Coogler on &#8216;Sinners&#8217; Making Oscar History&#8212;Especially for Horror Movies</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ryan-coogler-on-sinners-making-oscar-history-especially-for-horror-movies-2000713063</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713063</guid>
      <description>The period vampire thriller scored a record-breaking 16 nominations, including Best Picture and Best Director.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best new floral Lego sets to brighten up your home</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/best-floral-lego-sets-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04fWavFhWMoZdKnDsSnUXba</guid>
      <description>Lego's new floral sets are great for brightening up your home during the winter months. Here's what's available as of January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give your kids stress-free screen time with this award-winning app</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/jan-22-pok-pok-lifetime-subscription</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01fICasStvjIGgshO9zQcwC</guid>
      <description>This lifetime subscription to Pok Pok is a great introduction to screen time for kids, offering a non-addictive, educational app, and it's on sale now for just $59.99 (reg. $250).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telly has only delivered 35,000 of its free televisions with always-on ads</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/telly-has-only-delivered-35000-of-its-free-televisions-with-always-on-ads-215033698.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c48e4be-853c-4c3a-9a66-c18965764ade</guid>
      <description>Telly appeared on the home theater scene in 2023 with an unusual proposition. Its business model revolves around giving customers free dual-screen televisions where the lower screen shows non-stop advertisements. At the time, the start-up&#8217;s execs projected that Telly would ship its first 500,000 screens that summer. However, Janko Roettgers of Lowpass reported that Telly only had 35,000 sets in people's homes at the end of the third quarter of 2025. The figure appears to come from a quarterly investor update, but Telly didn't provide Roettgers with any comment on the report.Personally, I don't...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic and Google have a secret $800 million Unreal Engine and services deal</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/866140/epic-google-fortnite-android-unreal-deal-antitrust-settlement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T16:47:07-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=866140</guid>
      <description>A judge is questioning whether Epic Games and Google are settling their long-running antitrust fight partly because of a previously unannounced partnership involving the Unreal Engine, Fortnite, and Android. In a hearing in San Francisco today, the court revealed that Epic and Google have struck a new deal that apparently includes "joint product development, joint [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are AI agents ready for the workplace? A new benchmark raises doubts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/are-ai-agents-ready-for-the-workplace-a-new-benchmark-raises-doubts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085277</guid>
      <description>New research looks at how leading AI models hold up doing actual white-collar work tasks, drawn from consulting, investment banking, and law. Most models failed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA&#8217;s Artemis 2 Is Sending Some Legendary Artifacts Around the Moon</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/artemis-2-is-sending-some-legendary-artifacts-around-the-moon-2000713150</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000713150</guid>
      <description>The Artemis 2 astronauts&#8212;and the historical keepsakes they&#8217;re bringing with them&#8212;will travel farther from Earth than any have gone before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Exactly the opposite of what AI and mission-critical workloads require": Dell VP says recycling enterprise SSDs to save costs could result in catastrophic data loss</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/exactly-the-opposite-of-what-ai-and-mission-critical-workloads-require-dell-vp-says-recycling-enterprise-ssds-to-save-costs-could-result-in-catastrophic-data-loss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UALxaPj5tAxySw9vKUcwb3</guid>
      <description>Dell warns reusing worn enterprise SSDs because of flash shortages increases failure risks for AI and mission-critical storage environments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ChatGPT ends up in childrens toys</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/chatgpt-ai-toys</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01zxekSq8hzseXOtl6G4tNt</guid>
      <description>A ChatGPT-enabled teddy bear got spicy. Then U.S. senators started paying attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 hit by outage, preventing access to emails and files</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/22/microsoft-365-hit-by-outage-preventing-access-to-emails-and-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085280</guid>
      <description>An hours-long outage is preventing Microsoft's enterprise customers from accessing their inboxes, files, and video meetings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Markey questions OpenAI about &#8216;deceptive advertising&#8217; in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/865854/senator-ed-markey-ai-companies-chatbots-advertising</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-22T16:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=865854</guid>
      <description>Sen. Ed Markey (D-MA) is pressing OpenAI about its move to bring ads to ChatGPT, and is asking several other companies whether they have similar plans. In letters to the CEOs of OpenAI, Anthropic, Google, Meta, Microsoft, Snap, and xAI, Markey writes that embedding ads into AI chatbots "raises significant concerns for consumer protection, privacy, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
