<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:29:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo's robot concept can help you digitally sign documents (and maybe annoy coworkers)</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/lenovo-concept-robot-ai-workmate-mwc-2026-230159746.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4adbef2-b5a4-426a-8c3b-bca3f32718c8</guid>
      <description>Lenovo can make a robot, too. Alongside proof-of-concept foldable gaming PCs and modular laptops, it introduced the AI Workmate Concept at MWC 2026. With its own Intel Core Ultra processor, 64GB of memory and its own Pico projector, it&#8217;s an AI-laced &#8220;workmate&#8221; meant to streamline office tasks and collaboration. And it has an LCD face.
For now, it&#8217;s a proof of concept, musing on how to integrate voice commands and LLMs (large language models) into workplace settings. It's meant to sit on your desk, but preferably also near a wall &#8211; more on that later.
Voice commands aside, the concept bot suppo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s Latest Wacky Concepts Include a Laptop With a Built-in Portable Monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/lenovo-mwc-concepts-thinkbook-modular-ai-pc-legion-go-fold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a1af7a1f9585923007b045</guid>
      <description>At MWC 2026, the company also showed off a dual-screen Yoga Book with 3D capabilities, and the Legion Go Fold&#8212;a gaming handheld with a folding screen that converts into a mini laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A robot arm with puppy dog eyes is just one of Lenovo&amp;#8217;s new desktop AI concepts</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885228/lenovo-ai-workmate-companion-work-concept-robot-arm-desktop-clock-hub</link>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T18:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885228</guid>
      <description>Alongside a handful of new laptop concepts (and a range of real products too), Lenovo used MWC to announce a pair of AI-based productivity companion concepts. Both are standalone desk devices designed to boost productivity while providing office workers with a bit of artificial dystopic companionship. Lenovo describes its AI Workmate Concept as an "always-on [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new Yoga 9i 2-in-1 from Lenovo has an angled &#8216;canvas mode&#8217; for easier note-taking</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/885724/lenovo-yoga-9i-2-in-1-angled-canvas-mode</link>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T18:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=885724</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has a few new Yoga laptops it's announcing at MWC 2026: the 14-inch Yoga Slim 7i Aura Edition, 15-inch Yoga Pro 7a, and 14-inch Yoga 9i 2-in-1 Aura Edition. The most interesting of the pack is that 9i 2-in-1, outfitted with a 2880 x 1800, 120Hz OLED touchscreen. It includes a Yoga Pen Gen [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s redesigned ThinkPad Detachable tablet has a bigger screen and legit keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/886134/lenovo-thinkpad-x13-detachable-tablet-t14-t14s-t16-laptops-price-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T18:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=886134</guid>
      <description>Lenovo is announcing five new ThinkPads and a new ThinkBook laptop for MWC 2026. There are various new chip offerings and updates for this swathe of ThinkPads, but the device I find the most interesting is the X13 Detachable. We haven't seen a major update to Lenovo's tablet-style ThinkPad in years, when it was the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo made a Framework-like laptop with modular ports &#8212; and a second screen</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/886814/lenovo-thinkbook-modular-ai-pc-concept-mwc-2026-specs</link>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T18:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=886814</guid>
      <description>One of Lenovo's big laptop concepts for MWC 2026 is a modular ThinkBook with two screens. Officially called the ThinkBook Modular AI PC Concept, the proof-of-concept is a 14-inch productivity machine with two plug-and-play interchangeable ports and a second 14-inch display magnetically attached to the rear of its lid. The second display is removable, and [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Windows gaming handheld has a screen that folds in half</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/886848/lenovo-legion-go-fold-concept-windows-foldable-pc-gaming-handheld</link>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T18:01:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=886848</guid>
      <description>Lenovo put a foldable display on a gaming handheld. The Legion Go Fold Concept is a Windows-based handheld with a flexible POLED display, detachable Joy-Con-like controllers, and a folio case to turn the whole thing into a mini laptop. You can use it as a standard Steam Deck-esque handheld with the display folded down to [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo unveils the 2026 refresh of its Yoga 9i 2-in-1 convertible laptop at MWC</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lenovo-unveils-the-2026-refresh-of-its-yoga-9i-2-in-1-convertible-laptop-at-mwc-230100644.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b282c091-8891-4768-9954-cc1abbe99b29</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has given the Yoga 9i 2-in-1 Aura Edition a refresh for 2026 and launched the new device at this year&#8217;s Mobile World Congress. The convertible laptop comes with a new Canvas Mode when the Yoga Pen Gen 2 case it&#8217;s bundled with is attached to the A-cover. When you lay the device down on a flat surface with the case attached, you&#8217;ll get a slight elevation on the display, which may make it easier to sketch or draw.The Copilot+ laptop is powered by Intel Core Ultra Series 3 processors with integrated graphics, has up to 32GB in memory and runs Windows 11. Its 14-inch screen has a resolution ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo's ThinkPads get a spec bump at MWC 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lenovos-thinkpads-get-a-spec-bump-at-mwc-2026-230100419.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1120c77-d3c3-4188-81c0-ecc1e8bcbc7a</guid>
      <description>Lenovo is updating its business-focused laptop lineup at MWC 2026. The best-selling ThinkPad T-series is getting a full refresh, and there's an updated ThinkBook 2-in-1 and an all-new Android tablet.The ThinkPad T-Series, the backbone of Lenovo's business PC lineup, now (optionally) ships with a 5MP camera that supports computer vision and vHDR. The 2026 versions of the laptops have larger speakers and a new color (&#8220;cosmic blue&#8221;) on some models.The ThinkPad T14 Gen 7 and ThinkPad T16 Gen 5 (each starting at $1,799) are the all-around workhorses of the ThinkPad lineup. Lenovo touts the 2026 mod...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next Generation of Modular, Repairable Laptops May Have More Than One Screen</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-next-generation-of-modular-repairable-laptops-may-have-more-than-one-screen-2000727371</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727371</guid>
      <description>And, apparently, Lenovo is still dreaming of a laptop with a glasses-less 3D screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s latest gaming tablet goes big on battery</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/lenovos-latest-gaming-tablet-goes-big-on-battery-230017436.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9d48ae7-c542-493b-94b4-387b29476601</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s buzziest gaming-related MWC announcement is undoubtedly its foldable Legion Go handheld-cum-laptop hybrid, which you can read all about here. But that wasn&#8217;t all the company showed off. We&#8217;re also getting an updated Legion Tab, Lenovo&#8217;s powerful gaming tablet.
Like the Gen 4 and 3 models before it, the latest Legion Tab features an 8.8-inch LCD display with an 165Hz refresh rate. The 3K panel can get up to 600 nits of brightness. The notable spec boosts come in the form of a jump up to a Snapdragon 8 Gen 5 chipset and a larger 9,000mAh battery, which should help you power through thos...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Screen on Lenovo&#8217;s Foldable Handheld Is Not Even Its Most Interesting Part</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-screen-on-lenovos-foldable-handheld-is-not-even-its-most-interesting-part-2000727349</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000727349</guid>
      <description>Lenovo is betting more on mobile PC gaming without the need for a discrete GPU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GameSir G7 Pro is one of the brand&#8217;s most customizable models yet, and it&#8217;s fantastic</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gamesir-g7-pro-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FLsnJA8N4qTzeGpobRoNQL</guid>
      <description>The GameSir G7 Pro is a highly customizable controller for Xbox and PC, and it&#8217;s one of the brand&#8217;s best to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lenovo Legion Go Fold gaming handheld concept looks awkward but its versatility is endless</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/the-lenovo-legion-go-fold-gaming-handheld-concept-looks-awkward-but-its-versatility-is-endless-230000816.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b42a61ea-ed99-49d3-b29d-da07b5531b46</guid>
      <description>Lenovo already has a large roster of gaming handhelds. However, it seems there's always room for another because at MWC the company showed off an ambitious concept device based around a flexible OLED display. And while the whole setup looks ungainly, after getting my hands on it, I'm very intrigued by its adaptability.&#160;Now I'll be the first to admit that an 11.6-inch display feels oversized on a handheld that, in theory, is meant to be somewhat portable. That said, the beauty of the Legion Go Fold's screen is that it can be bent in half to create a more appropriately-sized 7.7-inch panel. In t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lenovo Modular AI PC concept is a remixed dual-screen laptop with hot swappable ports</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/the-lenovo-modular-ai-pc-concept-is-a-remixed-dual-screen-laptop-with-hot-swappable-ports-230000158.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c9b526d-e530-410b-8b78-b62fe4959fb5</guid>
      <description>The potential of modular laptops has never fully translated to the real world. While companies like Framework have made major strides in recent years, there's still quite a bit of room for improvement. At MWC, Lenovo is looking to address that with its Modular AI PC concept. It features not one but two displays and a detachable keyboard to create something that strains the definition of a laptop, thanks to an innovative and very adaptable design.Compared to Framework's gadgets, which primarily use modularity to make upgrading the system and extending its lifespan easier, Lenovo's concept is ba...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mettre un robot dans un smartphone, Honor l&#8217;a fait et le r&#233;sultat est bluffant</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/mwc/2995439_mettre-un-robot-dans-un-smartphone-honor-la-fait-et-le-resultat-est-bluffant</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 22:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/mwc/2995439_mettre-un-robot-dans-un-smartphone-honor-la-fait-et-le-resultat-est-bluffant</guid>
      <description>
On a enfin vu le Robot Phone de Honor, cet appareil hybride qui m&#234;le t&#233;l&#233;phonie mobile et robotique. &#201;quip&#233; d'une intelligence artificielle multimodale capable de comprendre son environnement, ce terminal n'est plus un concept, il arrive dans le commerce.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu le robot de Honor faire un salto arri&#232;re au MWC, et c&#8217;est aussi impressionnant qu&#8217;effrayant</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/honor/2995359_on-a-vu-le-robot-de-honor-faire-un-salto-arriere-au-mwc-et-cest-aussi-impressionnant-queffrayant</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/honor/2995359_on-a-vu-le-robot-de-honor-faire-un-salto-arriere-au-mwc-et-cest-aussi-impressionnant-queffrayant</guid>
      <description>
Honor a fait son show aujourd'hui &#224; Barcelone. On s'y &#233;tait pr&#233;par&#233;, mais le constructeur chinois a tout de m&#234;me d&#233;ploy&#233; les grands moyens au MWC 2026. Il a d&#233;laiss&#233; quelques instants ses smartphones pour faire monter sur sc&#232;ne son premier robot humano&#239;de.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy Canada seemingly just leaked Sonos' next portable speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/best-buy-canada-seemingly-just-leaked-sonos-next-portable-speaker-215601978.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4a30194-9c4e-4e62-961a-342cc89c687c</guid>
      <description>A product briefly posted on the Canadian Best Buy website this weekend suggests Sonos may soon announce a new portable speaker called the Sonos Play. The speaker offers Wi-Fi and Bluetooth connectivity, AirPlay 2 support, Trueplay to tune the sound based on wherever you've placed it and voice controls, according to a page that's since been removed. Best Buy Canada had it listed for $399.99 CAD (or a little under 300 US dollars), and put the release date at March 31.The listing may have been taken down, but not before it was spotted and reposted on Reddit. The product page for the Sonos Play al...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
