<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:24:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Here are 15 TV deals for watching the Super Bowl that I recommend &#8212; $1,000 off 4K, QLED and OLED TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/seasonal-sales/here-are-15-tv-deals-for-watching-the-super-bowl-that-i-recommend-usd1-000-off-4k-qled-and-oled-tvs</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9JgLNA67qP43Hj9Efb63W8</guid>
      <description>If you're looking for a new TV for the Super Bowl, I've listed my top 15 recommendations, which include deals on best-rated 4K, QLED, and OLED TVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu cette bo&#238;te de rangement qui charge votre Nintendo Switch 2  et j&#8217;aime beaucoup</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/belkin/2936081_jai-vu-cette-boite-de-rangement-qui-charge-votre-nintendo-switch-2-et-jaime-beaucoup</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/belkin/2936081_jai-vu-cette-boite-de-rangement-qui-charge-votre-nintendo-switch-2-et-jaime-beaucoup</guid>
      <description>
J'ai pu essayer bri&#232;vement la tr&#232;s pratique housse de rangement de Belkin, capable de recharger votre Nintendo Switch 2 par l'int&#233;gration d'une batterie de 10 000 mAh.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I replaced Windows with Linux and everything&#8217;s going great</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/858910/linux-diary-gaming-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=858910</guid>
      <description>Greetings from the year of Linux on my desktop. In November, I got fed up and said screw it, I'm installing Linux. Since that article was published, I have dealt with one minor catastrophe after another. None of that has anything to do with Linux, mind you. It just meant I didn't install it on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We tried to get humanoid robots to do the laundry</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/featured-video/860104/we-tried-to-get-humanoid-robots-to-do-the-laundry</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T10:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=860104</guid>
      <description>At CES this year, humanoid robots appeared to be closer than ever to moving into our homes. LG introduced CLOiD, a household robot it says can handle chores like preparing food and loading the washing machine. SwitchBot showed off the Onero H1, another home helper built to tackle everyday tasks, and Boston Dynamics, WIRobotics, Zeroth, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From &#8216;Vibe Coding&#8217; to &#8216;Vibe Selling&#8217;: how AI is reshaping the art of selling</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/from-vibe-coding-to-vibe-selling-how-ai-is-reshaping-the-art-of-selling</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">V6CjpZCHN5JiibrEPxBxFb</guid>
      <description>'Vibe selling' is a crucial tool in sellers&#8217; kits, but isn&#8217;t ready to be put directly in front of buyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Connections hints and answers for Sunday, January 11 (game #945)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/nyt-connections-today-answers-hints-11-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hhugs7E8ydB2AXvRKwbz9o</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Connections answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, plus my commentary on the puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quordle hints and answers for Sunday, January 11 (game #1448)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/quordle-today-answers-clues-11-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4MRMCWBSjf99ZWz8gZi8w9</guid>
      <description>Looking for Quordle clues? We can help. Plus get the answers to Quordle today and past solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Strands hints and answers for Sunday, January 11 (game #679)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/websites-apps/nyt-strands-today-answers-hints-11-january-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UZFeQAmgLMVv4HVGgunsB4</guid>
      <description>Looking for NYT Strands answers and hints? Here's all you need to know to solve today's game, including the spangram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA makes final preparations for its first crewed moon mission in over 50 years</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/science/space/nasa-makes-final-preparations-for-its-first-crewed-moon-mission-in-over-50-years-150000825.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">840cd11a-ecb0-45c7-8989-1ccf53d63d86</guid>
      <description>Back in 2024, NASA announced that the Artemis 2 mission was going to be pushed back to April 2026. Now, the agency says it could launch as early as February, with the first flight opportunity being on February 6. NASA is currently making the final preparations for the mission and will soon roll out the Space Launch System (SLS) rocket and the Orion spacecraft to their launch pad at the Kennedy Space Center in Florida. The spacecraft system&#8217;s four-mile journey from the assembly building to Launch Pad 39B will take up to 12 hours. NASA is targeting a date no earlier than January 17, with the exa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tottenham vs Aston Villa Free Streams: How to watch FA Cup 2025/26 from anywhere in the world</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/football/tottenham-vs-aston-villa-fa-cup-2025-26</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sKD6Yx7LuvSj9JvRpPUtk9</guid>
      <description>All the ways to watch Tottenham vs Aston Villa online from anywhere for FREE, as football's oldest cup competition returns with giant-killings guaranteed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I can't stop playing Assassins Creed Shadows on Nintendo Switch 2 now it no longer crashes all the time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/assassins-creed-shadows-nintendo-switch-2-review</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FsoH8QBcF4ev57HnJuqS9Q</guid>
      <description>After a rocky start, I&#8217;m pleasantly surprised by how well Assassins Creed Shadows runs on Switch 2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Odyssey OLED G9 : ce mastodonte de 49&#8243; rafra&#238;chi &#224; 144 Hz perd 200 &#8364; pendant les soldes d&#8217;hiver</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936527_samsung-odyssey-oled-g9-ce-mastodonte-de-49-rafraichi-a-144-hz-perd-200-e-pendant-les-soldes-dhiver</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2936527_samsung-odyssey-oled-g9-ce-mastodonte-de-49-rafraichi-a-144-hz-perd-200-e-pendant-les-soldes-dhiver</guid>
      <description>
Le Samsung Odyssey OLED G9 est l'un des &#233;crans ultra wide les plus d&#233;sirables de ces soldes d'hiver 2026. Format 32:9, courbure 1800R, taux de rafra&#238;chissement de 144 Hz... L'immersion et la r&#233;activit&#233; sont clairement promises ici. Actuellement, la Fnac et Darty le proposent &#224; 799,99 euros au lieu de 999 euros. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My business travel essential goes everywhere with me - and it probably isn't what you'd expect</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/my-business-travel-essential-goes-everywhere-with-me-and-it-probably-isnt-what-youd-expect</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Gx5H2L8GoG5FqR8ijQHoki</guid>
      <description>The Skysper foldable backpack may not be the peak of human ingenuity, but I've found it to be an absolute essential for business travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus vies for fastest mini PC ever with Panther Lake NUC 16 Pro &#8212; B390 GPU inside the Core Ultra X9 388H impresses but won't beat the 8060S</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/asus-vies-for-fastest-mini-pc-ever-with-panther-lake-nuc-16-pro-b390-gpu-inside-the-core-ultra-x9-388h-impresses-but-wont-beat-the-8060s</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3gEyYpKjn6b7FYBKhx5s4n</guid>
      <description>The Panther Lake based Asus NUC 16 Pro blends strong integrated graphics with leading AI performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s on your desk, Stevie Bonifield?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/850479/desk-pc-keyboard-razer-kobo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850479</guid>
      <description>Stevie Bonifield is a news writer here at The Verge and, they say, &#8220;I cover a little bit of just about everything, from the FCC to AI shopping tools to Linux.&#8221; Before joining our news team, they wrote weekend news for PC Gamer and did reviews, news, features, and guides for Laptop Mag, along with [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Playdate gets its Monument Valley</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/859675/diora-review-playdate-monument-valley</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-10T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=859675</guid>
      <description>Diora might be the most ambitious game I've played on the Playdate. It's all about perspective: You turn the handheld's crank to rotate your viewpoint of the bite-size 3D landscapes, which lets you peek around corners to find solutions to various puzzles. On a device with a 1-bit, black-and-white display, the miniature worlds feel miraculous, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Wildcard Round 2026 Free Streams: How to Watch Rams vs Panthers, Packers vs Bears From Anywhere in the World</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/american-football/nfl-wildcard-round-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iciH8RXCMG6HNbmWnZNqJL</guid>
      <description>Saturday sees the first of six Wildcard games this postseason and here's how you can watch NFL Wildcard Round 2026 games for free and from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From rollable screens to a new AI tabletop companion - 5 of the best new Lenovo releases we saw at CES to boost your office...and one coming soon</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/from-rollable-screens-to-a-new-ai-tabletop-companion-5-of-the-best-new-lenovo-releases-we-saw-at-ces-to-boost-your-office-and-one-coming-soon</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXwsQ7PrarPSStds2q2kNS</guid>
      <description>Rollable screens, sensor hubs, and the most powerful ThinkPads ever - we go hands-on with Lenovo's top CES 2026 products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to change location with a VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/vpn/how-to-change-location-with-a-vpn-140000339.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b143258-aaec-4e80-aceb-3402b72d930e</guid>
      <description>Chances are that you're here because you've heard a virtual private network (VPN) can change your virtual location, and want to know what that means. If you know already, head over to my best VPN list to learn which services I recommend for changing your location. But if you're clueless, read on.Whenever any device connects to the internet &#8212; whether it's a laptop, a phone or a smart Lego brick &#8212; it's assigned a unique IP address that other devices can use to identify it. Think of the name you give the barista at a coffee shop, except instead of a hot beverage, you&#8217;re being served websites and ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
