<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:07:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MacBook 12,9 pouces : tout savoir sur le prochain Mac d&#8217;entr&#233;e de gamme</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/macos/2972963_macbook-129-pouces-tout-savoir-sur-le-prochain-mac-dentree-de-gamme</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/macos/2972963_macbook-129-pouces-tout-savoir-sur-le-prochain-mac-dentree-de-gamme</guid>
      <description>
Apple s'appr&#234;terait &#224; ressusciter le MacBook "tout court" avec une recette surprenante : une puce d'iPhone A18 Pro et un prix sous les 800 euros.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shokz OpenFit Air earbuds are matching their all-time low price</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876392/shokz-openfit-air-earbuds-kobo-clara-colour-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T12:05:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876392</guid>
      <description>If you like to take your workouts outside, open-ear earbuds are helpful for staying aware of surroundings, but that extra peace of mind often comes at the expense of bass. The Shokz OpenFit Air Earbuds actually try to address that problem, though, and they&#8217;re currently $79.95 ($40 off) at Amazon, Target, and directly from Shokz [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate WhatsApp on Android? Try my picks for 5 great alternatives</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/android/hate-whatsapp-on-android-try-my-picks-for-5-great-alternatives</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">o9t8BrghMaKLHo758DmWWb</guid>
      <description>Whether your priority is privacy, customization, or other features, there'll be a WhatsApp alternative that suits you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La fiche technique compl&#232;te des Galaxy S26 a fuit&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/la-fiche-technique-complete-des-galaxy-s26-a-fuite.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325228</guid>
      <description>Au point o&#249; on en est, Samsung n'a plus besoin de s'emb&#234;ter &#224; organiser un &#233;v&#233;nement Unpacked : un simple communiqu&#233; de presse suffira ! Car gr&#226;ce aux innombrables fuites, on sait d&#233;sormais &#224; peu pr&#232;s tout de la gamme Galaxy S26, que le constructeur doit pr&#233;senter le 25 f&#233;vrier. Dernier exemple en date, voici la fiche technique compl&#232;te.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is keeping Secure Boot alive with Windows updates</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876336/microsoft-windows-secure-boot-certificate-renewal</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T12:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876336</guid>
      <description>Microsoft is automatically replacing boot-level security certificates on Windows devices before they start expiring later this year. The new Secure Boot certificates will be rolled out as part of the regular Windows platform updates, according to Microsoft's announcement blog, marking a "generational refresh" of the security standard. Secure Boot was introduced in 2011 to protect [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft will start refreshing Secure Boot certificates in March for Windows 11 and Windows 10 ESU users</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/microsoft-will-start-refreshing-secure-boot-certificates-in-march-for-windows-11-and-windows-10-esu-users-170000777.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d63d7d73-4cd0-4275-8c77-4e6cf91a045b</guid>
      <description>Get ye to Windows Update, because there's a good chance you've got new Secure Boot certificates to install. Microsoft just announced that it will be refreshing those certificates, which were originally introduced when Secure Boot debuted in 2011, as a security precaution. Secure Boot was a way for Microsoft to protect systems from running unsigned and potentially malicious code before Windows launched. It went on to be an installation requirement for Windows 11, as well as anti-cheat software used in Valorant, Call of Duty: Black Ops 6/7 and Battlefield 6.  Without the new Secure Boot certific...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the &#8216;Spider-Noir&#8217; Show Stars Ben Reilly and Not Peter Parker</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-the-spider-noir-show-stars-ben-reilly-and-not-peter-parker-2000720149</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720149</guid>
      <description>Ben Reilly is a complicated character, and making him the lead of 'Spider-Noir' only adds to that&#8212;but there's a reason for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayaneo's massive Next 2 handheld has a similarly massive price tag</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/the-ayaneo-next-2-is-a-massive-pc-handheld-with-a-price-tag-to-match-165326534.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cc918ba-3ddb-4213-ab81-338076c85004</guid>
      <description>There appears to be no limit to how chonky and eye-wateringly expensive PC gaming handhelds can get, with the latest behemoth being the Ayaneo Next 2. First announced back in November, the latest Windows handheld in Ayaneo&#8217;s Next lineup is now up for pre-order, with a spec sheet that makes some of its rivals look modest.
If you missed the announcement at the end of last year, the Next 2 is packing a 9-inch OLED display with a 2,400 x 1,504 resolution and a maximum refresh rate of 165Hz (adjustable down to 60Hz). The Next 2 is powered by an AMD Ryzen AI Max+ 395 chip and has a massive 115Mh bat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 17 Pro : le nouveau coloris qui a permis &#224; Apple de battre des records en Chine</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/ios/2972895_iphone-17-pro-le-nouveau-coloris-qui-a-permis-a-apple-de-battre-des-records-en-chine</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/ios/2972895_iphone-17-pro-le-nouveau-coloris-qui-a-permis-a-apple-de-battre-des-records-en-chine</guid>
      <description>
En misant sur un coloris "Orange &#201;toil&#233;" aux faux airs de luxe, Apple a vu ses ventes exploser de 38 % en un trimestre.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung 990 Evo Plus : ce SSD interne 1 To pour PS5 ou PC est en promo en pleine flamb&#233;e des prix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2972569_samsung-990-evo-plus-ce-ssd-interne-1-to-pour-ps5-ou-pc-est-en-promo-en-pleine-flambee-des-prix</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2972569_samsung-990-evo-plus-ce-ssd-interne-1-to-pour-ps5-ou-pc-est-en-promo-en-pleine-flambee-des-prix</guid>
      <description>
Ce n'est plus une surprise : les SSD internes sont bien plus on&#233;reux qu'auparavant. Alors quand des offres int&#233;ressantes se pr&#233;sentent, mieux vaut en profiter sans trop tarder. Par exemple, le Samsung 990 Evo Plus de 1 To est propos&#233; &#224; 127,99 euros au lieu de 170 euros sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've been covering gaming laptops for years &#8212; these are the 9 I'd buy this week</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/ive-been-covering-gaming-laptops-for-years-these-are-the-9-id-buy-this-week</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">UyRXYHdTzdpwo74w9BRFYd</guid>
      <description>I've looked through hundreds of discounted gaming laptops today &#8212; these 9 are the obvious picks if you're looking to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US judicial body removes climate research paper after complaints from Republicans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/us-judicial-body-removes-climate-research-paper-after-complaints-from-republicans-164829295.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40247a38-063f-416b-9506-027b9f0e240c</guid>
      <description>A US judicial body has revised an internal document to remove climate research. The Reference Manual on Scientific Evidence is a document used by judges when they have to oversee cases involving complex scientific matters. The climate science chapter has now been deleted, so they'll be on their own with climate-related cases.
This move came after a group of Republican state attorneys wrote a letter to complain about the chapter on climate change. The language in the document, which was authored by researchers from Columbia University, suggests that climate change is driven by the actions of hu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman and Jony Ive&#8217;s AI Gadget Just Hit Another Eyebrow-Raising Roadblock</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altman-and-jony-ives-ai-gadget-just-hit-another-eyebrow-raising-roadblock-2000720067</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720067</guid>
      <description>Problems seem to be piling up for the duo's AI gadgets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a new super-cheap Dolby Atmos surround soundbar in town &#8212; the Bowfell Halo promises heavenly home theater for small spaces</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/soundbars/theres-a-new-super-cheap-dolby-atmos-surround-soundbar-in-town-the-bowfell-halo-promises-heavenly-home-theater-for-small-spaces</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39SfXJHjGVSKwVPmZw8roi</guid>
      <description>Majority's new soundbars are extremely affordable, extremely small, and pretty well-equipped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google can now help you find and remove your ID from search results</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876352/google-search-remove-sensitive-information-nonconsensual-images</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T11:45:56-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876352</guid>
      <description>Google is expanding its tools for removing your sensitive information and nonconsensual images from its search results. The company announced on Tuesday that you can now use its "results about you" tool to remove your driver's license, passport, and Social Security number from search, in addition to your phone number and address. Once you add [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#8217;s xAI Can&#8217;t Stop Bleeding Cofounders</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musks-xai-cant-stop-bleeding-cofounders-2000720117</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720117</guid>
      <description>Tony Wu is leaving at a time when SpaceX is expected to launch an IPO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psy-ops built car culture</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480898/psy-ops-built-car-culture</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:45:36</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480898/psy-ops-built-car-culture</guid>
      <description>To change our built environment, we&#8217;ve got to understand the forces that fuel our choices.
I don&#8217;t care if you own a car, SUV, minivan, pickup truck, private jet, or one of each. This essay isn&#8217;t a judgment on consumerism. It&#8217;s about how the forces shaping our automotive obsession ripple into land use policy, infrastructure funding, government subsidies, and every facet of urbanism....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got a KitchenAid stand mixer? Turn it into a food processor, spiralizer, or ice cream maker with these attachments, going cheap at Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/got-a-kitchenaid-stand-mixer-turn-it-into-a-food-processor-spiralizer-or-ice-cream-maker-with-these-attachments-going-cheap-at-best-buy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bF9qVXb8XDthGmYBzPiMjm</guid>
      <description>Mix things up in the kitchen with these great savings on KitchenAid add-ons in the Presidents' Day sale at Best Buy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razer&#8217;s resurrected 25-year-old gaming mouse will cost you $1,337</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/876333/razer-boomslang-20th-anniversary-edition-wireless-mouse-preorder-price</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T11:41:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876333</guid>
      <description>Nostalgia's getting expensive. When Razer announced last December it would be relaunching the world's first gaming mouse with a few modern upgrades, it didn't reveal how much the Razer Boomslang 20th Anniversary Edition would cost or when it would be released. The company will officially open preorders for the mouse on February 10th at 8AM [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram is reportedly being slowed down and restricted in Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876351/telegram-russia-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T11:39:16-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876351</guid>
      <description>Telegram users in Russia may begin noticing service disruptions on Tuesday after Russia's communications regulator, Roskomnadzor, reportedly moved to slow down and restrict access to the app, as reported by Russian news outlet RBC. Roskomnadzor said in a statement to RBC, translated using machine translation, that it "will continue to introduce successive restrictions" on Telegram, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;It&#8217;s absurd&#8217;: YouTube TV subscribers slam its new sports subscription plan, despite its tempting price tag</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/its-absurd-youtube-tv-subscribers-slam-its-new-sports-subscription-plan-despite-its-tempting-price-tag</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">gt4M94yNJsmCAX4RzyzTHC</guid>
      <description>New YouTube TV subscription tiers are on the way, but ESPN Unlimited is missing from the pack, and sports fans aren't happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget-friendly OLED TVs don't get much better than the LG B5 &#8211; this entry-level OLED 'offers impressive pictures for the price'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/budget-friendly-oled-tvs-dont-get-much-better-than-the-lg-b5-this-entry-level-oled-offers-impressive-pictures-for-the-price</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GDFJqgt2E8ADbgcPtqEYHU</guid>
      <description>If you're shopping for a new mid-sized OLED TV and you have a tight budget, then it's easy to recommend this excellent LG B5 while it's massively reduced in the Presidents' Day sales at Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Spot First Known Lava Tube on Venus</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-spot-first-known-lava-tube-on-venus-2000720125</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720125</guid>
      <description>Until now, lava tubes on the second planet were purely theoretical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This case is about two of the richest corporations who have engineered addiction in children&#8217;s brains' &#8212; lawsuit against Meta and YouTube could decide the fate of social media</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/social-media/this-case-is-about-two-of-the-richest-corporations-who-have-engineered-addiction-in-childrens-brains-lawsuit-against-meta-and-youtube-could-decide-the-fate-of-social-media</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">LZyw9SdPkhjUfbaytREZtn</guid>
      <description>As one lawyer labels social media platforms &#8220;digital casinos&#8221; that create dopamine addiction in children, Meta and YouTube dispute the claim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directive 8020 brings sci-fi survival horror to PS5, Xbox Series X/S and PC on May 12</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/directive-8020-brings-sci-fi-survival-horror-to-ps5-xbox-series-xs-and-pc-on-may-12-163358560.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c4b65bc-976e-4e29-9a75-eb24f4869b26</guid>
      <description>Supermassive Games has announced a new release date for the next entry in the Dark Pictures Anthology series. Directive 8020 is coming to PS5, Xbox Series X/S and Steam on May 12. The studio behind Until Dawn and The Quarry revealed the news with the help of a fresh trailer for the sci-fi survival horror game.The story focuses on the crew of a spaceship that has crash landed onto another world. The survivors have to contend with an alien lifeform that's hunting them and can mimic its prey (no prizes for guessing that Supermassive took inspiration from The Thing here). If these astronauts want ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un serveur de ce VPN connu saisi par les autorit&#233;s n&#233;erlandaises : les donn&#233;es des utilisateurs en danger ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/services/vpn/2972555_un-serveur-de-ce-vpn-connu-saisi-par-les-autorites-neerlandaises-les-donnees-des-utilisateurs-en-danger</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/services/vpn/2972555_un-serveur-de-ce-vpn-connu-saisi-par-les-autorites-neerlandaises-les-donnees-des-utilisateurs-en-danger</guid>
      <description>
Un service de VPN raconte que la police des Pays-Bas est venue saisir l'un des serveurs de l'infrastructure. Peut-elle y trouver quelque chose ?
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why corporate America is hedging as immigration agents show up at its doors</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91487795/why-corporate-america-is-hedging-as-immigration-agents-show-up-at-its-doors</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:30:54</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91487795/why-corporate-america-is-hedging-as-immigration-agents-show-up-at-its-doors</guid>
      <description>Companies tend to hedge on issues that are contested and polarizing.
When U.S. Border Patrol agents entered a Target store in Richfield, Minnesota, in early January, detaining two employees, it marked a new chapter in the relationship between corporate America and the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Tesla product manager wants to make luxury goods impossible to fake, starting with a chip</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/former-tesla-product-manager-wants-to-make-luxury-goods-impossible-to-fake-starting-with-a-chip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3090948</guid>
      <description>The fake goods crisis cuts two ways. Luxury brands lose more than $30 billion a year to counterfeits, while buyers in the booming $210 billion second-hand market have no reliable way to verify that what they&#8217;re purchasing is genuine. Veritas wants to solve both problems with a solution that combines custom hardware and software. The [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta, TikTok and Snap are participating in an online safety ratings system</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/meta-tiktok-and-snap-are-participating-in-an-online-safety-ratings-system-162921333.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">feee4d98-8e61-4375-aa82-0c4425a634fd</guid>
      <description>Numerous major social platforms including Meta, YouTube, TikTok and Snap say they will submit to a new external grading process that scores social platforms on how well they protect adolescent mental health. The program comes from the Mental Health Coalition&#8217;s Safe Online Standards (SOS) initiative, which comprises about two dozen standards covering areas like platform policy, functionality, governance and transparency, content oversight and more. The SOS initiative is led by Dr. Dan Reidenberg, Managing Director of the National Council for Suicide Prevention.
In announcing these companies' pa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At the Meta and YouTube trial, plaintiff&#8217;s lawyer says social media is &#8216;addicting the brains of children&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490111/at-meta-youtube-trial-plaintiffs-lawyer-says-social-media-addicting-brains-children</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:28:48</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490111/at-meta-youtube-trial-plaintiffs-lawyer-says-social-media-addicting-brains-children</guid>
      <description>On day one of the trial, Meta attorney Paul Schmidt spoke of the disagreement within the scientific community over social media addiction.
Comparing social media platforms to casinos and addictive drugs, lawyer Mark Lanier delivered opening statements Monday in a landmark trial in Los Angeles that seeks to hold Instagram owner Meta and Google&#8217;s YouTube responsible for harms to children who use their products.Instagram&#8217;s parent company Meta and Google&#8217;s YouTube face claims that their platforms addict children through deliberate design choices that keep kids glued to their screens. TikTok and Sn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify executives just revealed why you couldn&#8217;t stop talking about Wrapped: &#8216;We turned up the dial&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490249/spotify-executives-just-revealed-why-you-couldnt-stop-talking-about-wrapped-we-turned-up-the-dial</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:21:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490249/spotify-executives-just-revealed-why-you-couldnt-stop-talking-about-wrapped-we-turned-up-the-dial</guid>
      <description>In a blockbuster earnings report, the Swedish streamer said more than 300 million users engaged with the viral feature after it listened to user feedback.
Shares in Spotify Technology SA (NYSE: SPOT), the world&#8217;s largest music streamer, are surging this morning. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachat de Warner : le coup de th&#233;&#226;tre de Paramount qui pourrait tout faire basculer face &#224; Netflix</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/services/svod/2972725_rachat-de-warner-le-coup-de-theatre-de-paramount-qui-pourrait-tout-faire-basculer-face-a-netflix</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/services/svod/2972725_rachat-de-warner-le-coup-de-theatre-de-paramount-qui-pourrait-tout-faire-basculer-face-a-netflix</guid>
      <description>
Alors que Warner a d&#233;j&#224; donn&#233; son accord pour un rachat par Netflix, Paramount a avanc&#233; plusieurs arguments visant &#224; s&#233;duire les actionnaires et les inciter &#224; lui revendre ses parts. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore says China-backed hackers targeted its four largest phone companies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/singapore-china-backed-hackers-targeted-largest-phone-companies-salt-typhoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091493</guid>
      <description>The Singaporean government said the China-backed hackers gained "limited access to critical systems" run by the country's top four telecommunication giants, but said they did not disrupt services or steal customers' data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've spent hundreds of hours with Nintendo Switch 2 already, and I couldn't imagine doing it without these must-have accessories</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-accessories/ive-spent-hundreds-of-hours-with-nintendo-switch-2-already-and-i-couldnt-imagine-doing-it-without-these-must-have-accessories</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yPvGZRSS2MFh23xzv4tokG</guid>
      <description>These are the Nintendo Switch 2 accessories I use with my personal console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Bitcoin Miner Sells $305 Million Worth of Crypto to Fund Pivot to AI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/major-bitcoin-miner-sells-305-million-worth-of-crypto-to-fund-pivot-to-ai-2000720078</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720078</guid>
      <description>For the dubious tech of the last decade, one door closes and another one opens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walmart's Presidents' Day sale is live &#8212; here's everything I'm buying as a shopping expert, including kitchen appliances, AirPods, furniture and more</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech/walmarts-presidents-day-sale-is-live-heres-everything-im-buying-as-a-shopping-expert-including-kitchen-appliances-airpods-furniture-and-more</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6HwVVxmQvWxaFpX6MADC4S</guid>
      <description>Walmart's Presidents' Day sale is live, and I'm rounding up my top deal picks that I'd buy, including TVs, kitchen appliances, AirPods, furniture, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Is Expanding Across the US at Breakneck Speed. Here&#8217;s Where It&#8217;s Going Next</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-expansion-across-us-at-heres-where-its-going-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">696f8c3348b30cdab4cde947</guid>
      <description>ICE plans to lease offices throughout the US as part of a secret, monthslong expansion campaign. WIRED is publishing dozens of these locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla&#8217;s new AI strategy marks a return to its &#8216;rebel alliance&#8217; roots</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490055/mozillas-new-ai-strategy-marks-a-return-to-its-rebel-alliance-roots</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:02:38</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490055/mozillas-new-ai-strategy-marks-a-return-to-its-rebel-alliance-roots</guid>
      <description>New browser controls that let users disable AI features point to a broader push against default-on artificial intelligence.
As Big Tech races to weave AI into nearly every product, Mozilla is betting some users want the opposite: the ability to turn it off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft wants to rewire data centers to save space</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/876083/microsoft-ai-data-center-superconductor</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T11:01:40-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876083</guid>
      <description>Microsoft wants to design more efficient data centers using materials that allow electricity to flow with zero resistance. If these new materials, called high-temperature superconductors, can make it to market, Microsoft thinks it could be a game changer for how data centers and the energy infrastructure they connect to are built. Tech companies are facing [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le premier appareil d&#8217;OpenAI perd son nom et glisse vers 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-premier-appareil-dopenai-perd-son-nom-et-glisse-vers-2027.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325210</guid>
      <description>Le futur appareil IA concoct&#233; par OpenAI et Jony Ive ne s'appellera pas &#171; io &#187;. Et une pr&#233;sentation, voire un lancement, dans le courant du second semestre a pris du plomb dans l'aile, selon des documents judiciaires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Startup Hacks Pigeon Brains, Turns Them Into Living Drones</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/russian-startup-hacks-pigeon-brains-turns-them-into-living-drones-2000720086</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000720086</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the future nobody asked for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything to Remember About the Post-Apocalypse of &#8216;Paradise&#8217; Before Season 2</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/paradise-everything-to-remember-season-2-sterling-k-brown-james-marsden-2000718048</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000718048</guid>
      <description>Sterling K. Brown stars in Hulu&#8217;s dystopian mystery set in a world that&#8217;s barely survived a global disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are currently at work on a large scale expansion' &#8212; Monster Hunter Wilds producer teases major update that will be revealed this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/we-are-currently-at-work-on-a-large-scale-expansion-monster-hunter-wilds-producer-teases-major-update-that-will-be-revealed-this-summer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9eNjuH6GxKeJW2bHLUEyje</guid>
      <description>Monster Hunter Wilds producer Ryozo Tsujimoto has confirmed that a "large-scale" expansion is in development for the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vega raises $120M Series B to rethink how enterprises detect cyber threats</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/vega-raises-120m-series-b-to-rethink-how-enterprises-detect-cyber-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091004</guid>
      <description>Vega Security raised $120 million, bringing its valuation to $700 million, in a round led by Accel. The company aims to rethink how enterprises detect cybersecurity threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondTrust RCE flaw lets hackers run code without logging in</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/beyondtrust-rce-flaw-lets-hackers-run-code-without-logging-in</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BJJiWiVKkpt9RDJsyxwxb5</guid>
      <description>A 9.9/10 bug was found in multiple BeyondTrust products, but a patch is already available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jennette McCurdy on female rage and reclaiming authority</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91489648/jennette-mccurdy-on-female-rage-and-reclaiming-authority</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T16:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91489648/jennette-mccurdy-on-female-rage-and-reclaiming-authority</guid>
      <description>McCurdy is following up her 2022 bestselling memoir with Half His Age, a novel that viscerally explores a teen&#8217;s relationship with her teacher. 
In 2022, Jennette McCurdy released her memoir I&#8217;m Glad My Mom Died, a brutally honest portrait of her life as a former child star, her battle with eating disorders, and, as the title would suggest, her rather complicated relationship with her mother....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awol Vision Aetherion Pro et Max : vid&#233;oprojecteurs UST 4K triple laser et Dolby Vision en financement sur Kickstarter</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/tv-connectee-produits/projecteur/2972681_awol-vision-aetherion-pro-et-max-videoprojecteurs-ust-4k-triple-laser-et-dolby-vision-en-financement-sur-kickstarter</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/tv-connectee-produits/projecteur/2972681_awol-vision-aetherion-pro-et-max-videoprojecteurs-ust-4k-triple-laser-et-dolby-vision-en-financement-sur-kickstarter</guid>
      <description>
Awol Vision ouvre les pr&#233;commandes Kickstarter des vid&#233;oprojecteurs UST 4K triple laser Aetherion Pro et Aetherion Max &#224; des prix extr&#234;mement attractifs avant une r&#233;elle disponibilit&#233;. On vous explique tout.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about Netflix&#8217;s landmark acquisition of Warner Bros.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/what-to-know-about-netflixs-landmark-acquisition-of-warner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085519</guid>
      <description>Learn more about Netflix's acquisition of Warner Bros., considered the most historic megadeal in Hollywood, as it continues to develop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google expands tools to let users remove sensitive data about themselves from Search</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/google-remove-sensitive-personal-data-from-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091466</guid>
      <description>Users will be able to more easily request the removal of results that include private information or non-consensual explicit imagery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google's new tool helps you remove non-consensual explicit images from Search</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/cybersecurity/googles-new-tool-helps-you-remove-non-consensual-explicit-images-from-search-155352248.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72b154f6-cb65-4d71-88f1-57a785582c2f</guid>
      <description>The internet is ripe with horrible violations of people's privacy, including non-consensual explicit images. A new tool from Google won't do much in the way of prevention, but can help you remove this media from Search.&#160;
Now, you can choose an image and quickly request its deletion. Just click on the three dots that appear on the image. From there, choose "remove result" and then "It shows a sexual image of me." Other choices include the picture shows a person under 18 and that it has your personal information. If you choose the initial option then you will also be asked whether it contains a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon retire plus de 1 000 &#8364; sur ce TV LG OLED 120 Hz g&#233;ant de 77 pouces, c&#8217;est le super deal du jour</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2972235_amazon-retire-plus-de-1-000-e-sur-ce-tv-lg-oled-120-hz-geant-de-77-pouces-cest-le-super-deal-du-jour</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2972235_amazon-retire-plus-de-1-000-e-sur-ce-tv-lg-oled-120-hz-geant-de-77-pouces-cest-le-super-deal-du-jour</guid>
      <description>
Ne vous fiez pas &#224; son positionnement entr&#233;e de gamme : le LG OLED77B5 est un TV g&#233;ant polyvalent taill&#233; pour le gaming (4K 120 Hz, HDMI 2.1, VRR) et le home cin&#233;ma. Il voit son prix chuter &#224; seulement&#160;1 529 euros&#160;contre 2 799 euros au lancement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump EPA reportedly seeks to revoke landmark air pollution rule</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/trump-epa-reportedly-seeks-to-revoke-landmark-air-pollution-rule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091472</guid>
      <description>EPA administrator Lee Zeldin is reportedly expected to repeal the 2009 "endangerment finding" that underpins U.S. climate regulatory efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The M5 Pro and M5 Max MacBook Pro could be here in weeks &#8211; and a new leak suggests they&#8217;ll have a big change in store</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/macbooks/the-m5-pro-and-m5-max-macbook-pro-could-be-here-in-weeks-and-a-new-leak-suggests-theyll-have-a-big-change-in-store</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">p568TiLDwPWkgSaEJGZage</guid>
      <description>Apple's long-awaited MacBook M5 Pro and M5 Max could be here 'as early as March', but with a surprising change not many may have seen coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein&#8217;s digital cleanup crew</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/report/876081/jeffrey-epstein-files-seo-google-digital-footprint-emails</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T10:45:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876081</guid>
      <description>In between hobnobbing with royalty and world leaders and abusing children and young women, Jeffrey Epstein appears to have been googling himself regularly. Across several batches of documents related to the convicted sex offender made public, we see Epstein shoot off emails to associates, complaining that his digital footprint includes factual information about his crimes. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's been more than two years since I reviewed the PlayStation Portal, and it's still my absolute favorite PS5 accessory &#8212; here's how some of you can get 5% off</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/ps5/its-been-more-than-two-years-since-i-reviewed-the-playstation-portal-and-its-still-my-absolute-favorite-ps5-accessory-heres-how-some-of-you-can-get-5-percent-off</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afeZtoxv34diMRcdTo3kAM</guid>
      <description>I gave the PlayStation Portal five stars when I first reviewed it more than two years ago, and I'd give it the same score now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidy up your home with $500 off the Roborock Saros 10R robot vacuum</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-10-roborock-saros-10r-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07fU0HR8jrz6X7cx9vk6pRD</guid>
      <description>As of Feb. 10, get $500 off the Roborock Saros 10R robot vacuum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication in 2026 - moving beyond foundational MFA to tackle the new era of attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/authentication-in-2026-moving-beyond-foundational-mfa-to-tackle-the-new-era-of-attacks</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dRMfSf3jdjpahQUUbGVZeU</guid>
      <description>Organizations must build on existing security practices and embrace phishing-resistant authentication to deliver robust protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safer Internet Day &#8211; How the VPN industry is reacting to the rising risks of AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/safer-internet-day-how-the-vpn-industry-is-reacting-to-the-rising-risks-of-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7Lw4hZZ3sJjita8M58VNP8</guid>
      <description>From privacy-first chatbots to advanced security tools designed to mitigate danger: here's what Proton, ExpressVPN, and NordVPN are shaping their offering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a simple way to watch the Winter Olympics 2026 for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/sport/simple-way-watch-winter-olympics-2026-free</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">F29j8CUBriFM4f2k6JuAx4</guid>
      <description>Here's our guide on a super simple way to stream every moment of the Winter Olympics for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;envers du d&#233;cor de Crew-12 : comment Sophie Adenot et ses coll&#232;gues astronautes se pr&#233;parent &#224; partir dans l&#8217;espace</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/crew-12-envers-decor-crew-12-sophie-adenot-collegues-astronautes-preparent-partir-espace-131096/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:28:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/crew-12-envers-decor-crew-12-sophie-adenot-collegues-astronautes-preparent-partir-espace-131096/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Alors que Jessica Meir, Jack Hathaway, Sophie Adenot et Andrey Fedyaev prendront bient&#244;t place &#224; bord de la capsule Crew Dragon de SpaceX, plongez au c&#339;ur de la pr&#233;paration intense de l&#8217;&#233;quipage de la mission Crew-12 &#224; destination de l&#8217;ISS. Entre s&#233;ances d&#8217;entra&#238;nements physiques, tests en...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Shark AI Ultra robot vacuum clean up the crumbs while its on sale for $250 off</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/feb-10-shark-ai-ultra-robot-vacuum-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">010Ybf9a7ChFXeJcShA5bVr</guid>
      <description>The Shark AI Ultra robot vacuum is on sale at Amazon for $299.99, down from the list price of $549.99. That's a 45% discount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How sports leagues are vying for Gen Z and Gen Alpha&#8217;s attention to build the next generation of fans</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91490096/how-sports-leagues-are-vying-gen-z-gen-alphas-attention-build-next-generation-fans</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T15:25:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91490096/how-sports-leagues-are-vying-gen-z-gen-alphas-attention-build-next-generation-fans</guid>
      <description>Mark Beal, a communication professor at Rutgers, says media consumption for Gen Z and Gen Alpha is &#8216;uprecedented&#8217;.
Trevor McOmber and his 14-year-old son, Tye, share a love for the Chicago Blackhawks. When Trevor was his son&#8217;s age, he watched the Blackhawks on TV, caught highlights on ESPN and read about the team in the newspaper.It&#8217;s a much different experience for Tye.&#8220;I go to YouTube with Snapchat, or Google something if I just have an idea that I want to know,&#8221; Tye McOmber said while sitting next to his father at a recent Blackhawks game.Tye McOmber is on the border of Generation Z, born r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This vintage-looking camera has been updated for shooting the stars</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876264/om-system-om-3-astro-digital-camera-stars-astrophotography</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-10T10:22:53-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=876264</guid>
      <description>Just over a year after OM System launched its vintage-styled OM-3 Micro Four Thirds mirrorless camera, the company has announced a new version with a handful of upgrades catering to astrophotography. The new OM-3 Astro will be available starting in March 2026 for $2,499.99, which is $500 more expensive than the standard model. Both can [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony met fin &#224; ses enregistreurs Blu-ray</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2972593_sony-met-fin-a-ses-enregistreurs-blu-ray</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2972593_sony-met-fin-a-ses-enregistreurs-blu-ray</guid>
      <description>
Le g&#233;ant japonais Sony a officialis&#233; en f&#233;vrier 2026 l'arr&#234;t de l'exp&#233;dition de l'ensemble de ses enregistreurs Blu-ray. Cette d&#233;cision, qui intervient sans qu'aucune nouvelle g&#233;n&#233;ration ne soit pr&#233;vue, montre le recul continu du support optique grand public face &#224; la domination du streaming.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin is giving away free iced coffee &#8212; use this promo code to qualify</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dunkin-free-coffee-promo-code</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01AjsKIsywfBtQ5zKIEGJJp</guid>
      <description>How to get free coffee from Dunkin' &#8212; get a free iced coffee with this promo code on Feb. 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zettlab D6 Ultra NAS review: Ironically, AI might not be the best feature of this network-attached storage device</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/zettlab-d6-ultra-nas-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nCzn9atBprWAkohWEyFN78</guid>
      <description>The Zettlab D6 Ultra is a high-performance NAS with aspirations to become a full-blown AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twingo &#233;lectrique &#224; 16&#160;000 euros&#160;: une tr&#232;s mauvaise surprise pour la version la moins ch&#232;re</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/twingo-electrique-a-16-000-euros-une-tres-mauvaise-surprise-pour-la-version-la-moins-chere.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1325193</guid>
      <description>Disponible &#224; la commande, la Twingo E-Tech Electric dans sa version Evolution donne &#224; voir tout l'&#233;quipement de cette version &#224; moins de 16 000 euros. La fiche technique est rassurante mais il y a un gros b&#233;mol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton VPN deal: Get up to 70 percent off two-year plans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/proton-vpn-deal-get-up-to-70-percent-off-two-year-plans-123000585.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dac4d6ed-e475-4c0c-80c0-7c390227395c</guid>
      <description>Proton VPN is running a solid deal right now, dropping its two-year Proton VPN Plus plan to $2.99 per month. That works out to $72 billed upfront for the first 24 months, which represents a 70 percent discount compared to its regular pricing.&#160;We&#8217;ve rated Proton VPN highly thanks to its strong privacy credentials, transparent nonprofit backing and consistently fast performance. It&#8217;s one of the services we recommend in our guide to the best VPNs, and this deal also shows up alongside other standout offers in our ongoing roundup of the best VPN deals. It&#8217;s a good option if you&#8217;re looking to lock ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce bug &#233;trange permet de discuter avec Google Traduction</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2972459_ce-bug-etrange-permet-de-discuter-avec-google-traduction</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/google/2972459_ce-bug-etrange-permet-de-discuter-avec-google-traduction</guid>
      <description>
Des internautes ont d&#233;couvert que dans certaines conditions, l'application Google Traduction se transforme en chatbot avec qui vous pouvez &#233;changer.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevation Lab's 10-year extended battery case for AirTag is back on sale for $16</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/elevation-labs-10-year-extended-battery-case-for-airtag-is-back-on-sale-for-16-151215952.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61f14f8b-e71c-4724-a1bf-0d7992632921</guid>
      <description>If you're an iPhone user who likes to keep tabs on where your stuff is, you can't go far wrong with an AirTag. The second-gen model that Apple just released outpaces the original in every way (aside from the galling lack of a keyring hole, that is). While it's easy enough to replace the battery in both versions of the AirTag, you might not want to have to worry about the device's battery life for a very long time. Enter Elevation Lab's extended battery case for the AirTag, which is currently on sale at Amazon for $16.
The case usually sells for $23, so that's a 30 percent discount. It's not th...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
