<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:37:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The best earbuds we&#8217;ve tested for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T16:33:23-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</guid>
      <description>It&#8217;s hard to buy a bad pair of wireless earbuds these days, and with constant discounts and deals wherever you look, now is as good a time as any to splurge on the pair you&#8217;ve been eyeing. The market has come a long way since the early era of true wireless earbuds, when we had [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aphelion seems like a solid space adventure, but I need to see more before it really excites</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/aphelion-hands-on-preview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cxpWDqqWiFXhibnjXFo5Yh</guid>
      <description>Aphelion has decent platforming and a creepy alien foe, but I want to see more of its story before getting fully on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google says its AI systems helped deter Play Store malware in 2025</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/google-says-its-ai-systems-helped-deter-play-store-malware-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094561</guid>
      <description>Google said it prevented 1.75 million bad apps from going live on Google Play during 2025, a figure that's down from previous years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Price Crash Hasn&#8217;t Stopped One Company From Adding to Its $47 Billion Crypto Stash</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/bitcoins-price-crash-hasnt-stopped-one-company-from-adding-to-its-47-billion-crypto-stash-2000724252</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724252</guid>
      <description>How low can it go until it's too late? Well...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The chip shortage is now hitting employee bonuses &#8212; MediaTek worker rewards sliced as costs begin to bite hard</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/chip-shortage-is-now-hitting-employee-bonuses-mediatek-worker-rewards-sliced-as-costs-begin-to-bite-hard</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xnfMcqenDiCSzYoSZgMuC8</guid>
      <description>MediaTek reduced employee bonuses for H2 2025 amid RAM and storage shortages affecting smartphone chipset shipments and overall revenue performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI data center boom is fueling Redwood&#8217;s energy storage business</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/an-ai-data-center-boom-is-fueling-redwoods-energy-storage-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094559</guid>
      <description>Redwood Materials says its new energy storage business is the fastest growing unit within the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slay the Spire 2 will enter early access on March 5</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/slay-the-spire-2-will-enter-early-access-on-march-5-210338514.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">333a4dbb-1204-4e0a-a389-641eea962db8</guid>
      <description>Slay the Spire 2 will launch in early access next month. This sequel to the hugely popular 2019 roguelike deckbuilder hits early access on Steam beginning March 5, 2026. Along with releasing the teaser trailer above, developer Mega Crit shared some details about its goals for this phase ahead of the game's official release."Slay the Spire requires a lot of player feedback so we can balance content, add quality of life features, and make sure the game runs without issues," the developers explained. "Early Access is also a chance for us to test experimental features, try exotic designs, identify...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Time (Travel) to See &#8216;Nirvanna The Band The Show The Movie&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/make-time-travel-to-see-nirvanna-the-band-the-show-the-movie-2000722952</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722952</guid>
      <description>The new pop culture comedy starring Matt Johnson and Jay McCarrol is now in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tested Sony's WF-1000XM6 against WF-1000XM5 to see whether the new flagship earbuds are worth it &#8212; and yes, I did find a winner</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/wireless-headphones/sony-wf-1000xm6-vs-wf-1000xm5-are-sonys-newest-flagship-earbuds-worth-it</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KsBFLMqMG6DWdwdG4py9jn</guid>
      <description>A deep dive suggests that the older model remains an excellent choice for the budget-conscious</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s VR metaverse is ditching VR</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/881647/meta-vr-mobile-metaverse-horizon-worlds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T15:47:54-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881647</guid>
      <description>Meta, after laying off about 10 percent of its Reality Labs division, closing three VR studios, stopping new content for VR fitness app Supernatural, and discontinuing its metaverse for work, is announcing a major change for its Horizon Worlds metaverse platform. Instead of attempting to make the 3D social platform work for both VR and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why these startup CEOs don&#8217;t think AI will replace human roles</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/web-summit-qatar-read-ai-lucidya-notetakers-customer-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3091415</guid>
      <description>The CEOs of Read AI and Lucidya told TechCrunch at Web Summit Qatar that they see AI tools replacing tasks, rather than workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump Jr.&#8217;s Private DC Club Has Mysterious Ties to an Ex-Cop With a Controversial Past</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/magas-secretive-members-only-club-is-partly-owned-by-an-ex-cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6996005c292f53dc4837a1fa</guid>
      <description>The Executive Branch has a reported membership list that includes&#160;Trumpworld elites like David Sacks. A WIRED review of corporate filings reveals an under-the-radar player: a notorious former DC police officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Staples Baddie&#8217; went viral. Here&#8217;s what the retailer is doing about its Gen Z employee&#8217;s internet fame</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495470/staples-baddie-gen-z-employee-what-the-retailer-is-doing-about-internet-fame</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T20:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495470/staples-baddie-gen-z-employee-what-the-retailer-is-doing-about-internet-fame</guid>
      <description>The company&#8217;s chief marketing officer weighs in on the breakout in-house influencer.
By now, the so-called &#8220;Staples Baddie&#8221; may have crossed your feed with her tutorials and informational videos exploring her workplace. TikTok creator @blivxx, known online as Oblivion, started getting attention in January for highlighting niche services and products offered at Staples....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube&#8217;s latest experiment brings its conversational AI tool to TVs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/youtubes-latest-experiment-brings-its-conversational-ai-tool-to-tvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094582</guid>
      <description>YouTube is testing conversational AI on smart TVs, allowing viewers to ask the assistant questions related to the video they're watching on the big screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toyota hires seven Agility humanoid robots for Canadian factory</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/toyota-hires-seven-agility-humanoid-robots-for-canadian-factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094580</guid>
      <description>The robots will be unloading totes full of auto parts from an automated warehouse tugger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the best problem-solvers think like jazz musicians</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91480883/why-the-best-problem-solvers-think-like-jazz-musicians</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T20:24:59</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91480883/why-the-best-problem-solvers-think-like-jazz-musicians</guid>
      <description>The secret is to balance wonder and rigor
Picture a jazz quartet mid-performance. The bassist anchors the rhythm with meticulous precision&#8212;years of practice evident in every note. The saxophonist, meanwhile, closes her eyes and ventures into uncharted melodic territory, responding to something she heard in the drummer&#8217;s improvised fill three bars ago. What you&#8217;re witnessing isn&#8217;t chaos, nor is it rigid execution. It&#8217;s something far more valuable: the dynamic interplay between discipline and imagination that produces work no one has ever heard before....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#8217;s the Difference Between Tesla&#8217;s Cybercab and Robotaxi?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/whats-the-difference-between-teslas-cybercab-and-robotaxi-2000724073</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724073</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk kicked off the confusion back in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch USA vs. Slovakia in mens ice hockey online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/usa-slovakia-winter-ice-hockey-2026-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00vDL8uHOkwcQqtSAHThpK2</guid>
      <description>How to watch ice hockey for free. Live stream USA vs. Slovakia in men's ice hockey for free from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Is Celebrating 10 Years of &#8216;Rogue One&#8217; With Some New Prequel Adventures (Exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/marvel-rogue-one-10th-anniversary-comics-andor-star-wars-2000724123</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724123</guid>
      <description>Cassian, Jyn, Saw, Chirrut, Baze, and even Darth Vader himself will star in a series of new one-shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Best Shows to Stream Right Now (February 2026)</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-best-shows-to-stream-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6994fce99d85208c5f768223</guid>
      <description>Fallout, Neighbors, and Monarch: Legacy of Monsters are just a few of the TV shows we&#8217;re swooning over for February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Pew Pew&#8217;: The Chinese Companies Marketing Anti-Drone Weapons on TikTok</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/pew-pew-the-chinese-sellers-marketing-military-drones-on-tiktok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6995e7f39b922c10e5b4ded5</guid>
      <description>On TikTok, Chinese manufacturers are advertising signal-blocking weapons with the breezy cadence of consumer lifestyle advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White men file workplace discrimination claims but are less likely to face inequity</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91493825/white-men-file-workplace-discrimination-claims-but-are-less-likely-to-face-inequity</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T19:58:43</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91493825/white-men-file-workplace-discrimination-claims-but-are-less-likely-to-face-inequity</guid>
      <description>About 10% of sex discrimination complaints are filed by white males. 
In December 2025, Andrea Lucas, the chair of the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, invited white men to file more sex- and race-based discrimination complaints against their employers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The boys&#8217; club no one was supposed to write about</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/the-boys-club-no-one-was-supposed-to-write-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094546</guid>
      <description>Reporter Zo&#235; Bernard spent months talking to 51 people (31 of them gay men) to map out a subculture that's been an open secret in Silicon Valley for years: gay men, at the upper echelons of tech, quietly raising up their own networks the way powerful people have always done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX&#8217;s Starbase city is getting its own court</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/19/spacexs-starbase-city-is-getting-its-own-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094535</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk's company town already has a volunteer fire department, and is forming a Starbase Police Department. Now it wants its own court, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Rolling Layoffs at Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-rolling-layoffs-jack-dorsey-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698b82178953d9ba40ac4835</guid>
      <description>Workers describe a deteriorating culture at Block, the company behind Square and Cash App, where layoffs continue and employees are expected to use AI tools daily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony is shutting down the studio behind the Demon's Souls remake</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/playstation/sony-is-shutting-down-the-studio-behind-the-demons-souls-remake-195234213.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32c81258-ab2c-4036-a054-beba1ce26861</guid>
      <description>Sony is closing Bluepoint Games, the studio behind the Shadow of the Colossus and Demon's Souls remakes, Bloomberg reports. Bluepoint's last major project was God of War: Ragnarok from 2022, which it co-developed with Sony Santa Monica.&#160;According to Bloomberg, Sony decided to shut down the studio following "a recent business review." Around 70 employees will lose their jobs as part of the studio closure, which will officially happen in March. "Bluepoint Games is an incredibly talented team and their technical expertise has delivered exceptional experiences for the PlayStation community," Sony ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Your Computer Speakers With These Discounted Edifier M60s</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/edifier-m60-deal-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69974a086f079a455ff23998</guid>
      <description>These compact Edifier speakers may not be the fanciest, but they&#8217;ll blow your monitor&#8217;s built-in speakers out of the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#8217;ve Caught the Gaming Industry at a Very Chinese Moment in Its Life</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/youve-caught-the-gaming-industry-at-a-very-chinese-moment-in-its-life-2000724153</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000724153</guid>
      <description>A new State of Gaming analysis reveals Chinese success in an otherwise suffering industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation sacrifie les rois du remake : Sony ferme d&#233;finitivement le studio Bluepoint Games</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2983791_playstation-sacrifie-les-rois-du-remake-sony-ferme-definitivement-le-studio-bluepoint-games</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/sony/2983791_playstation-sacrifie-les-rois-du-remake-sony-ferme-definitivement-le-studio-bluepoint-games</guid>
      <description>
Coup de tonnerre dans la sph&#232;re PlayStation. Sony vient d&#8217;annoncer la fermeture pure et simple de Bluepoint Games, le studio texan &#224; qui l'on doit les superbes remakes de Demon's Souls ou Shadow of the Colossus. Le studio n'aura jamais l'occasion de lancer son premier jeu original.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Search Party backlash, Ring is still avoiding the bigger questions</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/881339/after-search-party-backlash-ring-is-still-avoiding-the-bigger-questions</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-19T14:40:42-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=881339</guid>
      <description>Ring founder Jamie Siminoff has been on an "explanation tour," as The New York Times puts it, following the fallout from its Super Bowl ad and the introduction of its Search Party feature. In an interview with The Times this week, Siminoff explained that he understands people's concerns and that "maybe people were 'triggered' by [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
