<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:50:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Loses Her Limbs After Innocent Dog Lick</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/woman-loses-her-limbs-after-innocent-dog-lick-2000725425</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725425</guid>
      <description>Manjit Sangha developed an aggressive case of sepsis, one that led her hospitalized for 32 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Coogler&#8217;s &#8216;X-Files&#8217; Reboot Has Found Its Star</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ryan-coogler-x-files-reboot-pilot-cast-hulu-2000725583</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725583</guid>
      <description>Danielle Deadwyler will star in the Hulu pilot, which will be written and directed by Coogler and showrun by Jennifer Yale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s So-Called &#8216;Board of Peace&#8217; Wants to Put Gaza on the Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trumps-so-called-board-of-peace-wants-to-put-gaza-on-the-blockchain-2000725437</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725437</guid>
      <description>Gazans have been restricted to 2G networks. Now planners are talking about a stablecoin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Trump&#8217;s DOJ actually take on Ticketmaster?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/883155/doj-antitrust-division-gail-slater-live-nation-ticketmaster-trial</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T15:37:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883155</guid>
      <description>In mid-February, the Department of Justice lost its head antitrust enforcer - just weeks before it was scheduled to argue one of the year's biggest anti-monopoly cases in court. Antitrust Division chief Gail Slater announced her departure suddenly, via a post on her personal X account. But to those who follow the agency closely, it [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Apple team launches Acme Weather, a new take on weather forecasting</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/23/ex-apple-team-launches-acme-weather-a-new-take-on-weather-forecasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095686</guid>
      <description>The team that sold their last app Dark Sky to Apple are back with Acme Weather, which offers alternative forecasts, rainbow and sunset alerts, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions of dollars later and still nobody knows what an Xbox is</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/883159/phil-spencer-xbox-game-pass</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T15:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883159</guid>
      <description>The last few years of Xbox have been expensive. Under Phil Spencer's leadership, Microsoft has spent billions of dollars in an attempt to build an ambitious future for gaming that looks a lot like Netflix. And while its subscription service Game Pass started out as a good deal for gamers (although now not so much), [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk about an unwelcome tax cut - DOGE restructuring saw IRS lose 40% of its IT workforce in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/talk-about-an-unwelcome-tax-cut-doge-investigations-saw-irs-lose-40-of-workforce-in-2025</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Y5BVDJhh2d5M9EfYo6s2zk</guid>
      <description>The IRS lost massive IT and executive staff in 2025, forcing AI and cross-functional teams to manage critical filing processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic accuses DeepSeek and other Chinese firms of using Claude to train their AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/883243/anthropic-claude-deepseek-china-ai-distillation</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T15:22:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883243</guid>
      <description>Anthropic claims DeepSeek and two other Chinese AI companies misused its Claude AI model in an attempt to improve their own products. In an announcement on Monday, Anthropic says the "industrial-scale campaigns" involved the creation of around 24,000 fraudulent accounts and more than 16 million exchanges with Claude, as reported earlier by The Wall Street [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flat Molecules Aren&#8217;t Actually Flat. Blame Quantum Physics</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/flat-molecules-arent-actually-flat-blame-quantum-physics-2000725513</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725513</guid>
      <description>In chemistry, molecules with a "flat" geometry are often stable enough to support a wide range of reactions. But in the quantum world, that's not technically true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ph&#233;nom&#232;ne rare &#224; ne pas manquer : 6 plan&#232;tes vont &#234;tre visibles en m&#234;me temps dans quelques jours !</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-phenomene-rare-ne-pas-manquer-6-planetes-vont-etre-visibles-meme-temps-quelques-jours-131331/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:03:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronomie-phenomene-rare-ne-pas-manquer-6-planetes-vont-etre-visibles-meme-temps-quelques-jours-131331/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Les plan&#232;tes seront align&#233;es, litt&#233;ralement, dans le ciel de cette fin du mois de f&#233;vrier. Elles seront six &#224; &#234;tre visibles dans le ciel nocturne, et tout particuli&#232;rement durant ces prochaines semaines, ce qui a le m&#233;rite d'&#234;tre rare, mais aussi et surtout facile &#224; observer, m&#234;me sans mat&#233;riel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Goodbye, All of Evangelion&#8217; Actually Means &#8216;Hello, to More Evangelion&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/evangelion-new-anime-yoko-taro-endings-2000725310</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725310</guid>
      <description>The legendary mecha series will carve itself another ending once more, with a new animated series helmed by 'Nier' writer Yoko Taro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo is the latest victim of the RAM crisis, and states, 'there's no way around' upcoming March price hikes</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/lenovo-is-the-latest-victim-of-the-ram-crisis-and-states-theres-no-way-around-upcoming-march-price-hikes</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Zn4dGPm9KJtHWkkutNjpi</guid>
      <description>Lenovo is the latest to be affected by the RAM crisis, and it has warned its partners to place orders before inevitable price hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic accuses Chinese AI labs of mining Claude as US debates AI chip exports</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/23/anthropic-accuses-chinese-ai-labs-of-mining-claude-as-us-debates-ai-chip-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095772</guid>
      <description>Anthropic accuses DeepSeek, Moonshot, and MiniMax of using 24,000 fake accounts to distill Claude&#8217;s AI capabilities, as U.S. officials debate export controls aimed at slowing China&#8217;s AI progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber&#8217;s new autonomous vehicle division is about survival and opportunity</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/23/uber-autonomous-solutions-av-robotaxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3095547</guid>
      <description>Uber Autonomous Solutions will see the company taking on all the tasks associated with operating a robotaxi, self-driving truck, or sidewalk delivery robot business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Exec Learns the Hard Way That AI Can Just Delete Your Stuff</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/meta-exec-learns-the-hard-way-that-ai-can-just-delete-your-stuff-2000725450</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725450</guid>
      <description>One small trick to get you to inbox zero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The AI model and prompt are predefined in the code and cannot be changed': Experts say PromptSpy is the first known Android malware to use Gemini to ensure infection</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-ai-model-and-prompt-are-predefined-in-the-code-and-cannot-be-changed-experts-say-promptspy-is-the-first-known-android-malware-to-use-gemini-to-ensure-infection</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kzHLPYboHNgRbF54HdKV2G</guid>
      <description>PromptSpy Android malware uses Gemini AI and Accessibility Services to maintain persistence, record activity, and evade normal malware removal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Game Fest runs from June 5-8</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/summer-game-fest-runs-from-june-5-8-193054418.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19213846-71d8-4a0c-9850-fb913d6300b6</guid>
      <description>It's getting to be that time of year again. Summer Game Fest officially kicks off on June 5 and will go until June 8. The Live Kickoff show will once again be hosted by Geoff Keighley and takes place on June 5 at 5PM ET. This is where we'll see all of those juicy reveals and trailers.
The opening event will be streamed globally on just about every digital platform, including YouTube, Twitch, X and even Steam. Those in the Los Angeles area will be able to pick up tickets for the live show sometime in the Spring.
The kickoff event is just the beginning. There's something called Play Days, which ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 major housing markets with falling home prices</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496910/housing-markets-home-prices-100-major-markets-with-falling-price</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496910/housing-markets-home-prices-100-major-markets-with-falling-price</guid>
      <description>After a burst of softening, the count of major metros seeing year-over-year home price declines has stabilized over the past seven months.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncanny Valley: AI Researchers&#8217; Resignations, Bots Hiring Humans, Evie Magazine&#8217;s Party</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/uncanny-valley-podcast-ai-researcher-resignations-bots-hiring-humans-evie-magazines-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699758603887d82b1d67ef47</guid>
      <description>This episode of Uncanny Valley covers the people resigning from AI companies and the humans getting hired by AI agents. Plus, we attend a soiree thrown by a conservative women's magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's a sneaky way to watch Love Island All Stars final for free</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/how-to-watch/theres-a-sneaky-way-to-watch-love-island-all-stars-final-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">x26DodD6TTJkrMEUkprVvL</guid>
      <description>Here's how to watch Love Island All Stars finale for free &#8211; live on 23rd February as season 3 favorites Belle and Harrison compete for a shot at love and the &#163;50,000 prize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s Cloud AI lead on the three frontiers of model capability</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/23/googles-cloud-ai-lead-on-the-three-frontiers-of-model-capability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3094627</guid>
      <description>AI models are pushing against three frontiers at once: raw intelligence, response time, and a third quality you might call "extensibility."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie says 'no second chances' if you're caught cheating in Marathon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/bungie-says-no-second-chances-if-youre-caught-cheating-in-marathon-191633998.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">080bb32e-0c4d-4de1-a25a-f7b418949cff</guid>
      <description>Bungie isn't taking any prisoners when it comes to cheating on its upcoming extraction shooter, Marathon. In a detailed blog post explaining its anti-cheat measures, Bungie took a very declarative position against those caught trying to gain an unfair advantage.
"We are taking a strong stance against cheating and anyone found to be cheating or developing cheats will be permanently banned from playing Marathon forever, no second chances," the blog post read, adding that there will be an appeals system in place.
However, Bungie's anti-cheat standards go beyond punishment. In the blog post, Bungi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micron&#8217;s $100 billion New York semiconductor manufacturing project is facing local pushback</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91495639/microns-100-billion-new-york-semiconductor-manufacturing-project-is-facing-local-pushback</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T19:13:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91495639/microns-100-billion-new-york-semiconductor-manufacturing-project-is-facing-local-pushback</guid>
      <description>Lawsuit over Micron&#8217;s massive Syracuse project raises concerns about toxic risks and alleges a rushed environmental review.
On a snowy Friday&#160;in January, dignitaries from both political parties braved the chill of a central New York winter for the groundbreaking ceremony of Micron Technology&#8217;s planned $100 billion manufacturing complex in Clay, a town not far from Syracuse. Over the next 20 years, Micron is promising the region thousands of jobs and the revitalization of a community hard hit by&#160;the decline of manufacturing....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faire tourner Cyberpunk 2077 sur Android : voici ce que &#231;a donne</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2987075_faire-tourner-cyberpunk-2077-sur-android-voici-ce-que-ca-donne</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/console/2987075_faire-tourner-cyberpunk-2077-sur-android-voici-ce-que-ca-donne</guid>
      <description>
&#201;quip&#233; d'une puce Snapdragon 8 Gen 5, un terminal Android a r&#233;ussi l'impossible : faire tourner Cyberpunk 2077. C'est spectaculaire, c'est instable et &#231;a transforme votre appareil en brique br&#251;lante en quelques minutes. Regardez comment c'est possible.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Legislators Want Device-Level Age Restrictions for Minors. Here&#8217;s What That Means</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/colorado-legislators-want-device-level-age-restrictions-for-minors-heres-what-that-means-2000725313</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725313</guid>
      <description>Lawmakers are following in California's foot steps. Could this spark a nationwide trend?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Altered Ending of &#8216;A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms&#8217; Hints at Changes for Season 2</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-episode-6-ending-explained-egg-maekar-2000725396</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000725396</guid>
      <description>The finale of HBO's 'Game of Thrones' spin-off made a small but significant change to George R.R. Martin's 'Tales of Dunk and Egg' novella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon wants fewer AI limits. Anthropic doesn&#8217;t. Here&#8217;s why it matters</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91496847/the-pentagon-wants-fewer-ai-limits-anthropic-doesnt-heres-why-it-matters</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T19:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91496847/the-pentagon-wants-fewer-ai-limits-anthropic-doesnt-heres-why-it-matters</guid>
      <description>Anthropic CEO Dario Amodei will meet with Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth as talks stall over how the military can use AI.
Dario Amodei, CEO of Anthropic, will head to the Pentagon on Tuesday to meet with Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth about how the military uses the company&#8217;s artificial intelligence models. And it&#8217;s likely to be a tense meeting, as sources first told Axios....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Northwest FragBox review: A compact gaming rig that does everything right</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/falcon-northwest-fragbox-review-a-compact-gaming-rig-that-does-everything-right-130000837.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cb0f4af-9ec0-4d0e-af7b-c41403f6e8f4</guid>
      <description>Mafia: The Old Country demands to be played on an enormous screen. As much as I love my 32-inch Alienware OLED gaming monitor, it doesn't do justice to Mafia's cinematic vistas of Sicily. But, I also wanted to play that game in its full 4K glory, with none of the compromises of today's game consoles. So why not just shove a tiny gaming desktop under my home theater? Enter the Fragbox, Falcon Northwest's revamped small form factor gaming PC. While it's very expensive, starting at $3,997, it's incredibly powerful and gives you the freedom to easily upgrade the hardware down the line.&#160;
I know wha...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
