<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:34:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy S26 could have the most AI camera ever</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-samsung-galaxy-s26-could-have-the-most-ai-camera-ever</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">QBYqwJjGMk2QGmVavoJdQD</guid>
      <description>Samsung just teased a huge camera system upgrade that could be an AI game-changer for the Galaxy S26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung teases mobile AI photography tools ahead of Unpacked</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/samsung-teases-mobile-ai-photography-tools-ahead-of-unpacked-233000358.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd33fa69-16e6-4e60-9022-6163119ef8ac</guid>
      <description>Anyone who's been paying even a little bit of attention to tech news lately could have made a reasonable guess that AI will be a big topic at Samsung's Unpacked next week. Ahead of the event, Samsung teased some of what's to come for AI in terms of the Galaxy S26 smartphone lineup's photography tools.&#160;The S26 phones will feature a new camera system using Galaxy AI that combines capturing, editing and sharing of photos and videos. "Users will be able to turn a photo from day to night in seconds, restore missing parts of objects in images, capture detailed photos in low light, and seamlessly mer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&#8217;s a New Term for Workers Freaking Out Over Being Replaced by AI</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/theres-a-new-term-for-workers-freaking-out-over-being-replaced-by-ai-2000723019</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723019</guid>
      <description>No one's mental health improves when they are told constantly that they are about to lose their job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Duvall&#8217;s &#8216;Twilight Zone&#8217; Episode Is Equal Parts Sweet and Strange</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/robert-duvalls-twilight-zone-episode-is-equal-parts-sweet-and-strange-2000723015</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723015</guid>
      <description>The late acting legend&#8217;s spotlight on Rod Serling&#8217;s sci-fi series came soon after his breakout role in &#8216;To Kill a Mockingbird.&#8217;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Colbert says CBS banned him from airing this James Talarico interview</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/880009/stephen-colbert-cbs-fcc-brendan-carr-talarico-interview</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-17T18:13:08-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880009</guid>
      <description>The Late Show host Stephen Colbert says CBS blocked him from broadcasting an interview with James Talarico, a Democratic representative from Texas. During his opening monologue on Monday night, Colbert says the network's lawyers told him in "no uncertain terms" that he couldn't have Talarico on the show, forcing him to post the interview on [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#8217;s AI Pendant Sounds Like a Watered-Down Humane Ai Pin</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/apples-ai-pendant-sounds-like-a-watered-down-humane-ai-pin-2000723004</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000723004</guid>
      <description>And its smart glasses sound exactly like Ray-Ban Meta AI glasses clones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best deals on MacBooks right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-17T18:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals</guid>
      <description>Apple currently sells MacBooks equipped with its own M-series processors in a wide range of sizes and price points, all of which run the company&#8217;s newest operating system, macOS 26. Purchasing a new MacBook can be complicated if you&#8217;re trying to figure out what specs you need, but finding a deal on a relatively speedy [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 of the best free movies to stream on Tubi, Pluto TV and more this week (February 17)</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/5-of-the-best-free-movies-to-stream-on-tubi-pluto-tv-and-more-this-week-february-17</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">G6xY2fq2eNnoY3L456kfaU</guid>
      <description>There's horror, comedy and a western available on the best free streaming services this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I don&#8217;t want any new features in watchOS 27 &#8211; I just want better battery life</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/smartwatches/i-dont-want-any-new-features-in-watchos-27-i-just-want-better-battery-life</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9pVMVeuqGGdFdDfZBGJ5Xd</guid>
      <description>Apple should forget about adding new features to watchOS 27 and just focus on improving the Apple Watch&#8217;s battery life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#8217;s AI search results will make links more obvious</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/880475/google-ai-overviews-ai-mode-links-update</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-17T17:38:24-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880475</guid>
      <description>Google says it will now display links more prominently inside its AI-powered features in Search. Robby Stein, the vice president of Google Search, announced on Tuesday that a list of links will now appear inside a pop-up when you hover over the sources in AI Overviews and AI Mode on desktop, alongside a description of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony&#8217;s WH-1000XM6 are nearly $100 off for just a few more hours</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/880476/sony-wh-1000-xm6-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-17T17:32:39-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=880476</guid>
      <description>If you&#8217;re looking for a great pair of noise-canceling headphones, Sony&#8217;s WH-1000XM6 are amongst the best available and are now down to $368 ($92 off) at Amazon in black or gray.&#160; While their high price usually makes them harder for us to suggest over the last-gen model, which is often on sale for around $278.99, [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How &#8216;Magic: The Gathering&#8217; Uses the TMNT to Show Off a New Side to Its Hottest New Plane: New York City</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/magic-the-gathering-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-spoilers-new-york-spider-man-2000722990</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000722990</guid>
      <description>After the 'Spider-Man' set made the Big Apple a key part of the Magic multiverse, the upcoming 'Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles' set wants to present the city in a warmer light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are officially the most reliable HDDs around &#8212; latest Backblaze report praises Seagate and Western Digital, others aren't so lucky</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/these-are-officially-the-most-reliable-hdds-around-latest-backblaze-report-praises-seagate-and-western-digital-others-arent-so-lucky</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">NDyPx5HcFjqLjVGP2cHimc</guid>
      <description>Backblaze analyzes 344,196 drives that collectively operated for over 115 million days, reporting improved reliability overall while exposing aging hardware risks and price volatility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&#8217;s Holy Grail AR Smart Glasses Have One Big Puck-Shaped Problem</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/heres-what-the-puck-on-metas-xr-glasses-will-probably-look-like-2000719635</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000719635</guid>
      <description>Do you really want to cart around a puck with your groundbreaking smart glasses?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't buy an iPad Air right now &#8211;Apple&#8217;s rumored budget MacBook could be a better buy, here's why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/dont-buy-an-ipad-air-right-now-apples-rumored-budget-macbook-could-be-a-better-buy-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eTP96ZuzuRVhhfbRzEUTyK</guid>
      <description>Apple is rumored to be launching a budget MacBook next month, and it could be a good iPad alternative.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
