<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:29:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The best tech announced at CES 2026 so far</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854159/ces-2026-best-tech-gadgets-smartphones-appliances-robots-tvs-ai-smart-home</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:29:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854159</guid>
      <description>Ahead of the CES show floor officially opening on Tuesday, January 6th, many companies have already announced new tech, gadgets, concepts, and AI-powered upgrades that will be released over this year. Yesterday's CES Unveiled event delivered even more announcements and reveals. If you're already struggling to keep on top of all the news coming out [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk goes all-in on SMBs with new Grok Enterprise and Business offerings</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/elon-musk-goes-all-in-on-smbs-with-new-grok-enterprise-and-business-offerings</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CDuL6qVRRV34xpKmkagc6U</guid>
      <description>xAI has launched Business and Enterprise tiers for Grok with like-for-like pricing, but ChatGPT is still cheaper for casual users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple's latest MagSafe charger is on sale for only $30</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/apples-latest-magsafe-charger-is-on-sale-for-only-30-141707602.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ce1496f-1e48-428a-bb64-aefda025bc79</guid>
      <description>If you want a wireless charger for your iPhone and prefer to stick with Apple, Amazon has a sale that may pique your interest. The retailer is selling the one meter Apple Magsafe charger for $30, saving you $10 off the regular price, while also selling the two meter model for $40 ($10 off).&#160;


If you have an iPhone 16, iPhone 17 or iPhone Air, this cable can charge your device at 25W as long as it's connected to a 30W power adapter on the other end. While you'll need a more recent iPhone to get the fastest MagSafe charging speeds, the charger can wirelessly top up the battery of any iPhone fro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJI's tiny action cam will soon get a big 8K rival from a mysterious Chinese company</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/action-cameras/djis-tiny-action-cam-will-soon-get-a-big-8k-rival-from-a-mysterious-chinese-company</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sn84x6AAp5CZXZgjNjQvTn</guid>
      <description>A new Chinese company is set to unveil a tiny modular action camera at CES 2026, and it could rival the DJI Osmo Nano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve South&#8217;s Valet is a handsome place to put your stuff</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854124/twelve-south-valet-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:14:45-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854124</guid>
      <description>For years, the accessory maker Twelve South has sold clever accessories for charging gadgets. Its new device, the Valet, is maybe its simplest idea ever: it's a nice-looking tray designed to be the place you drop your keys, sunglasses, and other pocket detritus, and offers a couple of ways to charge whatever needs to be [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#160;Edge is getting a Copilot-inspired redesign</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/854832/microsoft-edge-copilot-redesign-ui-features</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:14:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854832</guid>
      <description>Microsoft is preparing to launch a major UI refresh of its Edge browser soon. The software maker has started bringing the design language from Copilot to early Canary and Dev test versions of its Microsoft Edge browser. Design changes include a settings section that looks identical to the Copilot app, updated context menus, and an [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syst&#232;me anti-martres, pack s&#233;curit&#233;, cire haute performance : la loi est formelle, vous n&#8217;avez pas &#224; payer ces frais impos&#233;s par les vendeurs auto</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2928195_systeme-anti-martres-pack-securite-cire-haute-performance-la-loi-est-formelle-vous-navez-pas-a-payer-ces-frais-imposes-par-les-vendeurs-auto</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/survoltes/voitures-electriques/2928195_systeme-anti-martres-pack-securite-cire-haute-performance-la-loi-est-formelle-vous-navez-pas-a-payer-ces-frais-imposes-par-les-vendeurs-auto</guid>
      <description>
Sur le bon de commande d'une voiture neuve ou d'occasion achet&#233;e chez un concessionnaire, il y a r&#233;guli&#232;rement (pour le pas dire tout le temps), des "frais annexes". Mais &#224; quoi correspondent-ils vraiment ? Sont-ils obligatoires ? On fait le point. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Au risque d&#8217;un nouveau clash avec Washington, Bruxelles remet la pression sur les g&#233;ants am&#233;ricains de la tech</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/au-risque-dun-nouveau-clash-avec-washington-bruxelles-remet-la-pression-sur-les-geants-americains-de-la-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318156</guid>
      <description>L'Europe n'a pas fini de jouer le r&#244;le de poil &#224; gratter dans la tech mondialis&#233;e et surtout am&#233;ricaine. Malgr&#233; les protestations des premiers int&#233;ress&#233;s et les gesticulations de la Maison Blanche, la Commission europ&#233;enne a bien l'intention de poursuivre, voire d'amplifier, les enqu&#234;tes contre les mastodontes US. Au risque de provoquer l'ire de Donald Trump....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your guide to the 2026 Winter Olympics, launching soon in Italy</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468997/your-guide-2026-winter-olympics-launching-soon-italy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:06:26</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468997/your-guide-2026-winter-olympics-launching-soon-italy</guid>
      <description>The Games run from February 4&#8211;22. 
The countdown is on for the 2026 Winter Olympics in Italy.The torch relay is already underway and some of the top athletes are already making headlines. There are 16 sports in all, including some never seen before, and 116 gold medals are waiting to be awarded when competition begins in less than a month.This will be the most spread-out Winter Games in history: The two primary competition sites are the city of Milan and Cortina d&#8217;Ampezzo, the winter resort in the Dolomites that is more than 400 kilometers (250 miles) away by road. Athletes also will compete i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oubliez le Galaxy S26 Ultra, Samsung miserait tout sur son successeur en photo</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2928761_oubliez-le-galaxy-s26-ultra-samsung-miserait-tout-sur-son-successeur-en-photo</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2928761_oubliez-le-galaxy-s26-ultra-samsung-miserait-tout-sur-son-successeur-en-photo</guid>
      <description>
Apr&#232;s plusieurs ann&#233;es de l&#233;ger copier&#8209;coller technique, Samsung pourrait enfin se d&#233;cider &#224; d&#233;poussi&#233;rer l&#8217;appareil photo de ses mod&#232;les Ultra. Et si le Galaxy&#8239;S26 Ultra s&#8217;annonce peu inspir&#233;, son successeur, lui, pourrait bien marquer un tournant.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow the Lego CES 2026 press conference live right here</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/follow-the-lego-ces-2026-press-conference-live-right-here-130005940.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02a28a6-f21c-46c9-a5e0-dcff1b13d26a</guid>
      <description>picture alliance via Getty Images
The Lego Group is set to host its very first press conference at CES 2026 later today &#8212; but exactly what it plans to unveil is still under wraps. The iconic toy brick maker has offered no clues about what's on the agenda, leaving speculation wide open, from new video games to Formula 1 race cars.
Unlike nearly every other press event at CES today, however, Lego's event is not being livestreamed. Thankfully, Engadget is here to bridge the gap: Our own Nate Ingraham will be in the room at the Mandalay Bay in Las Vegas, liveblogging the event in real-time.&#160;
Follo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuite de donn&#233;es chez Ledger&#160;: le g&#233;ant fran&#231;ais des cryptos annonce un incident chez un prestataire</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/fuite-donnees-chez-ledger-geant-francais-cryptos-annonce-incident-chez-prestataire.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318142</guid>
      <description>Ledger, le champion fran&#231;ais de la s&#233;curit&#233; des cryptos, est &#224; nouveau victime d'une fuite de donn&#233;es. Les informations personnelles de clients ayant pass&#233; commande sur Ledger.com ont &#233;t&#233; compromises. On peut redouter une nouvelle d'arnaques... ou de tentatives d'extorsion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette nouvelle tablette veut se faire passer pour du papier : voici la TCL Note A1 NXTPAPER</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tcl/2927077_cette-nouvelle-tablette-veut-se-faire-passer-pour-du-papier-voici-la-tcl-note-a1-nxtpaper</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tcl/2927077_cette-nouvelle-tablette-veut-se-faire-passer-pour-du-papier-voici-la-tcl-note-a1-nxtpaper</guid>
      <description>
Voici la nouvelle tablette de TCL, la Note A1 NXTPAPER. Elle mise sur divers modes d'&#233;cran permettant de se rapprocher plus que jamais d'une liseuse. Notez aussi un lancement commercial sur Kickstarter.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Making-of Doc Hits Netflix Next Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-stranger-things-making-of-doc-hits-netflix-next-week-2000705046</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705046</guid>
      <description>'One Last Adventure: The Making of Stranger Things 5' may not answer all your burning questions, but it looks like an affectionate, emotional ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Makes Dashcams a Dealership Add-On</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mitsubishi-makes-dashcams-a-dealership-add-on-2000705268</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705268</guid>
      <description>The common aftermarket purchase becomes part of the carbuying process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockly&#8217;s new smart locks will support Matter and NFC</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851157/lockly-smart-lock-matter-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851157</guid>
      <description>Lockly has introduced a series of smart locks that have native Matter compatibility, meaning that they will be able to be used across different smart home systems. The Affirm Series of smart locks will come in both deadbolt and latch editions. What's more, the locks will support several ways to allow access, including not only [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These wireless headphones roll up to become a Bluetooth speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851496/tdm-neo-wireless-headphones-bluetooth-speaker-kickstarter</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851496</guid>
      <description>A new company called TDM, or "Tomorrow Doesn't Matter," has announced its first pair of wireless headphones at CES 2026 with a unique multifunctional design. The Neo look like a traditional pair of over-ear wireless headphones but feature an extra flexible headband that can be twisted and rolled up around the ear cups to turn [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShiftCam has a trackable 8TB SSD that sticks to your phone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853511/shiftcam-planck-studio-ssd-price-availability</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853511</guid>
      <description>Content creation gadget maker ShiftCam is launching a superfast mobile SSD that sticks to the back of your phone for safekeeping. The Planck Studio was made with production teams and creators in mind, according to ShiftCam, providing devices like phones, laptops, and cameras with up to 8TB of additional storage and transfer speeds of up [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE Lighting&#8217;s new Matter-compatible smart shades start at just $300</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853562/ge-lightings-matter-screw-free-smart-shades</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853562</guid>
      <description>GE Lighting is launching smart shades at CES that come in at a pretty reasonable (for motorized shades, at least) $299.99. They're not the cheapest smart shades out there. SwitchBots start at just $199, but they're still quite a bit more affordable than Lutron's, which start at $399. They should look pretty sleek, too, since [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL challenges RGB LED at CES with its X11L SQD-Mini LED TV</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853589/tcl-x11l-sqd-mini-led-tv-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853589</guid>
      <description>CES is poised to be the story of RGB LED, with almost every major TV manufacturer set to show off their latest models using the technology. But TCL is hoping to change that narrative, or even overtake it, with its own story - that of the X11L SQD-Mini LED TV. The X11L uses blue LEDs [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cozyla&#8217;s TV-sized smart calendar makes your home look like a classroom</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854003/cozyla-smart-calendar-plus-max-concept-display-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854003</guid>
      <description>Smart calendars can be a boon for busy families that have room for them, but Cozyla's latest concept is pushing that to the limit if you're short on space. The 55-inch Cozyla Calendar Plus Max announced at CES is a Wi-Fi-enabled 4K touchscreen display on a wheeled stand, which Cozyla says is the "largest smart [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini on Google TV is getting Nano Banana and voice-controlled settings</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854112/gemini-google-tv-nano-banana-veo-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854112</guid>
      <description>Gemini on Google TV is getting a major update that makes the AI assistant more helpful and more visually engaging. The big highlights are obviously the addition of Nano Banana and Veo support for creating AI videos and images directly on your TV. This can be anything from modifying your family photos for a laugh [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google previews new Gemini features for TV at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/google-previews-new-gemini-features-for-tv-at-ces-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079326</guid>
      <description>Google TV will let you ask Gemini to find and edit your photos, adjust your TV settings and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCL launches next-gen SQD mini-LED TV at CES &#8211; the &#8216;best TV in the market&#8217; for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/tcl-launches-next-gen-sqd-mini-led-tv-at-ces-the-best-tv-in-the-market-for-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fywi9UH3Z6N8vHa8gVXeaT</guid>
      <description>TCL launched the X11L SQD mini-LED, its flagship TV for 2026, at CES, along with a new RGB mini-LED TV and a budget mini-LED TV series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for Fallout season 2 episode 4 on Prime Video?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/amazon-prime-video/what-is-the-release-date-for-fallout-season-2-episode-4-on-prime-video</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">VpGNX6NTvkoNBazDWjHnSd</guid>
      <description>Fallout season 2's next episode will be with us shortly &#8211; here are all of the release details you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google TV is getting Gemini-powered photo editing at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/google-tv-is-getting-gemini-powered-photo-editing-at-ces-140000172.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7d74536-4d4c-4056-aa67-2bdef7eeddcc</guid>
      <description>Google is working even more Gemini features into Google TV at CES 2026. The company demoed how the AI assistant would work on its TV platform at last year's show, and this time, it's expanding the AI's features to make it easier to do things like adjust your TV's settings or edit photos.The ability to view photos stored in Google Photos has long been a feature of Google TV, but as part of this new update, Gemini will be able to do a lot more with them, too. Google says Gemini will be able to search your Google Photos library for specific people and moments, and remix those photos into differen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Saratoga Spring Water is suddenly everywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468528/why-saratoga-spring-water-is-suddenly-everywhere</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468528/why-saratoga-spring-water-is-suddenly-everywhere</guid>
      <description>Backed by Primo Brands, the iconic blue bottle is being repositioned as both aspirational and accessible.
If you&#8217;ve been noticing that cobalt-hued water bottles have started to pop up everywhere you&#8217;re not alone. The water has recently made an appearance on shelves at major retailers including Whole Foods and 7-Eleven, starred in viral social media videos created by fitness influencer Ashton Hall, adorned on tables at the Golden Globes, and beginning this week, will star in a fresh new advertising campaign featuring WNBA point guard Skylar Diggins....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone ou liseuse ? Le TCL NXTPAPER 70 Pro mise tout sur le confort de vos yeux</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tcl/2926915_smartphone-ou-liseuse-le-tcl-nxtpaper-70-pro-mise-tout-sur-le-confort-de-vos-yeux</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tcl/2926915_smartphone-ou-liseuse-le-tcl-nxtpaper-70-pro-mise-tout-sur-le-confort-de-vos-yeux</guid>
      <description>
Voici le tout nouveau TCL NXTPAPER 70 Pro. Il profite d'un niveau de r&#233;flectance super bas pour un confort des yeux aux petits oignons. Un nouveau bouton permet m&#234;me de le transformer en liseuse.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Watch : Samsung franchit une &#233;tape majeure vers le suivi du glucose et la sant&#233; c&#233;r&#233;brale des personnes &#226;g&#233;es</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2928267_galaxy-watch-samsung-franchit-une-etape-majeure-vers-le-suivi-du-glucose-et-la-sante-cerebrale-des-personnes-agees</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2928267_galaxy-watch-samsung-franchit-une-etape-majeure-vers-le-suivi-du-glucose-et-la-sante-cerebrale-des-personnes-agees</guid>
      <description>
Samsung a profit&#233; du CES de Las Vegas pour pr&#233;senter ses nouveaut&#233;s &#224; venir dans le domaine de la nutrition ou de la sant&#233; cognitive des personnes &#226;g&#233;es. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un &#233;cran g&#233;ant de 171 pouces dans la poche, Asus et XREAL s&#8217;associent et pr&#233;sentent les ROG XREAL R1</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2928681_un-ecran-geant-de-171-pouces-dans-la-poche-asus-et-xreal-sassocient-et-presentent-les-rog-xreal-r1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2928681_un-ecran-geant-de-171-pouces-dans-la-poche-asus-et-xreal-sassocient-et-presentent-les-rog-xreal-r1</guid>
      <description>
On vous parlait ce matin des nouvelles Xreal 1S, mais ASUS vient de mettre la barre un cran plus haut. En partenariat avec... Xreal (tiens donc), la marque gaming lance les ROG R1. La promesse ? Un &#233;cran Micro-OLED 240 Hz viss&#233; sur le nez.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8BitDo is unveiling a new mobile gaming pad at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/8bitdo-is-unveiling-a-new-mobile-gaming-pad-at-ces-134555603.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86c3be84-9f19-4df9-9e16-905e423e4c5b</guid>
      <description>Gaming peripheral company 8BitDo is teasing a new smartphone gaming pad that seems aimed exclusively at portrait-mode gamers. In a post on X, the company says the 8BitDo FlipPad will debut in the summer of 2026 and will be compatible with iOS and Android devices. It also mentions the peripheral is "officially supported by Apple."
The post doesn't give too much away, as the company will be premiering the FlipPad at CES this week. A short, rendered video shows that the mobile gaming peripheral connects via USB-C, and then flips upward on a hinge to lay flat against the bottom portion of a user's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce laptop gaming 16&#8243; QHD 165 Hz avec RTX 5070 perd 300 &#8364; : l&#8217;affaire &#224; ne pas rater en ce d&#233;but 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2927537_ce-laptop-gaming-16-qhd-165-hz-avec-rtx-5070-perd-300-e-laffaire-a-ne-pas-rater-en-ce-debut-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2927537_ce-laptop-gaming-16-qhd-165-hz-avec-rtx-5070-perd-300-e-laffaire-a-ne-pas-rater-en-ce-debut-2026</guid>
      <description>
Bonne nouvelle pour les gamers&#8239;! Le Gigabyte AERO X16, arm&#233; d&#8217;un Ryzen AI 9, d&#8217;une RTX 5070 et d&#8217;un &#233;cran QHD 165&#8239;Hz, passe &#224; 1&#8239;539&#8239;euros au lieu de 1&#8239;819&#8239; euros. Une affaire en or pour d&#233;buter 2025 avec une machine surpuissante sans exploser son budget.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#8217;s plan to take over Venezuela&#8217;s oil industry faces major hurdles. Here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469000/trumps-plan-take-over-venezuelas-oil-industry-faces-major-hurdles-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T13:39:56</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469000/trumps-plan-take-over-venezuelas-oil-industry-faces-major-hurdles-heres-why</guid>
      <description>Massive investment will be required to overcome an infrastructure in disrepair.
President Donald Trump&#8217;s plan to take control of Venezuela&#8217;s oil industry and ask American companies to revitalize it after capturing President Nicol&#225;s Maduro in a raid isn&#8217;t likely to have a significant immediate impact on oil prices.Venezuela&#8217;s oil industry is in disrepair after years of neglect and international sanctions, so it could take years and major investments before production can increase dramatically. But some analysts are optimistic that Venezuela could double or triple its current output of about 1.1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just don't immerse it: Jackery reveals world's lightest kWh-capacity IP65-rated portable power station &#8212; and it can even withstand a 1m fall</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/just-dont-immerse-it-jackery-reveals-worlds-lightest-kwh-capacity-ip65-rated-portable-power-station-and-it-can-even-withstand-a-1m-fall</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Zak5Tc5G4hP5gRUweaZwF7</guid>
      <description>The Jackery Explorer 1500 Ultra is a professional-grade portable power station offering high-capacity energy, rapid recharge, IP65 durability, and extreme environmental resilience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirTag deal: Get a four-pack of the Bluetooth trackers for only $65</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/airtag-deal-get-a-four-pack-of-the-bluetooth-trackers-for-only-65-202333050.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b60c33-f851-4bee-9d8b-9c00c8cc034a</guid>
      <description>Apple keeps most of its product pricing on a tight leash, but we do see the company's AirTags go on sale pretty frequently. Another cost cut has come around for this item just in time for the holidays. Amazon is currently selling a four-pack of AirTags for $65. At a third off the regular cost, that price is pretty close to the record low discount of $63 we've seen for these Bluetooth trackers.


AirTags can be useful for people who travel frequently, helping you to keep track of essentials like your passport as well as a way to keep tabs on luggage while you're on the go. If you do purchase so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clap de fin pour l&#8217;Apple Vision Pro ? Pourquoi Apple aurait d&#233;j&#224; stopp&#233; la production de son casque</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2928071_clap-de-fin-pour-lapple-vision-pro-pourquoi-apple-aurait-deja-stoppe-la-production-de-son-casque</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/2928071_clap-de-fin-pour-lapple-vision-pro-pourquoi-apple-aurait-deja-stoppe-la-production-de-son-casque</guid>
      <description>
Le casque de r&#233;alit&#233; mixte d&#8217;Apple ne se vend pas aussi bien que l&#8217;aurait esp&#233;r&#233; la firme. Selon des experts du secteur, Apple aurait m&#234;me cess&#233; la production de l&#8217;Apple Vision Pro au d&#233;but de l&#8217;ann&#233;e 2025.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La nouvelle balance connect&#233;e de Withings ne se contente plus de mesurer le poids</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/la-nouvelle-balance-connectee-de-withings-ne-se-contente-plus-de-mesurer-le-poids.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318145</guid>
      <description>Withings revient &#224; ses premi&#232;res amours avec une nouvelle balance connect&#233;e, la Body Scan 2. Le constructeur fran&#231;ais promet une photographie en 90 secondes de l&#8217;&#233;tat cardiovasculaire, m&#233;tabolique et cellulaire, gr&#226;ce &#224; une soixantaine d&#8217;indicateurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu le prix des nouveaux chargeurs USB-C d&#8217;IKEA, et c&#8217;est un probl&#232;me pour la concurrence</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ikea/2928513_jai-vu-le-prix-des-nouveaux-chargeurs-usb-c-dikea-et-cest-un-probleme-pour-la-concurrence</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/ikea/2928513_jai-vu-le-prix-des-nouveaux-chargeurs-usb-c-dikea-et-cest-un-probleme-pour-la-concurrence</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez l'habitude de payer vos chargeurs 20 ou 30 euros ? Arr&#234;tez tout de suite. IKEA vient de dynamiter le march&#233; avec une violence rare. Avec sa nouvelle gamme Sj&#246;ss, l'enseigne propose des blocs de charge fiables &#224; partir de 2,99 euros. &#192; ce tarif-l&#224;, on couvre &#224; peine les frais de transport.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blu-ray just turned 20 years old and it&#8217;s still my go-to optical disc for movies &#8212; here&#8217;s why</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/blu-ray/blu-ray-just-turned-20-years-old-and-its-still-my-go-to-optical-disc-for-movies-heres-why</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">o6GLWqmKcywEvWbatoGnkQ</guid>
      <description>If thinking back to CES 2006 makes you feel old, don&#8217;t &#8211; just keep on collecting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;ANFR fait le m&#233;nage : ces 8 smartphones n&#8217;auraient jamais d&#251; atterrir dans votre poche</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2928461_lanfr-fait-le-menage-ces-8-smartphones-nauraient-jamais-du-atterrir-dans-votre-poche</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/smartphone/2928461_lanfr-fait-le-menage-ces-8-smartphones-nauraient-jamais-du-atterrir-dans-votre-poche</guid>
      <description>
L'ANFR vient de taper du poing sur la table. L'agence ordonne le retrait imm&#233;diat de huit smartphones du march&#233; fran&#231;ais. Entre des niveaux d'ondes qui d&#233;passent les bornes et des appareils vendus sans aucune certification europ&#233;enne.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des parieurs crypto ont gagn&#233; une fortune gr&#226;ce &#224; la capture de Nicol&#225;s Maduro</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/investisseurs-crypto-gagne-fortune-grace-capture-nicolas-maduro.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318088</guid>
      <description>La capture de Nicol&#225;s Maduro par l&#8217;arm&#233;e am&#233;ricaine a aussi fait exploser les compteurs sur PolyMarket. En misant sur son arrestation avant m&#234;me le d&#233;but des frappes, quelques parieurs anonymes ont empoch&#233; des centaines de milliers de dollars en cryptomonnaies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL just announced a bunch of new earbuds at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/jbl-just-announced-a-bunch-of-new-earbuds-at-ces-130044239.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6ff7736-63ca-4e16-8302-2fdf7b38f9ad</guid>
      <description>JBL just revealed a bunch of new earbuds at CES 2026, suiting just about every ear canal out there. First up, there are several new additions to the Endurance line of sports-adjacent earbuds.
The baddest of the bunch is likely the Endurance Zone, which offers 32 hours of battery life and fast charging. They include the company's proprietary OpenSound technology, which directs audio signals to the ears without blocking the ear canal. This means that wearers should be able to detect ambient noise during a workout. This is extremely helpful when someone is asking to use the machine because you've...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL is going all-in on open earbuds at CES 2026: meet the firm&#8217;s 3 new open-fit options</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/jbls-going-all-in-on-open-earbuds-at-ces-2026-meet-every-new-open-fit-option-in-las-vegas</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4tQjYnoRaBQywc4eWVxzPS</guid>
      <description>JBL really wants to keep your ear canals free of intrusion in 2026 &#8211;and the Soundgear Clips, Sense Pro and Sense Lite prove it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JBL launches a trio of gaming headsets for CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/jbl-launches-a-trio-of-gaming-headsets-for-ces-130000929.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f97c1e6-de94-4899-b3be-fef5b59038e2</guid>
      <description>For CES this year, JBL has added three new gaming headsets to its JBL Quantum product lineup. JBL Quantum 950X is the latest set of flagship headphones from the brand, with 50mm carbon dynamic drivers and features such as spatial audio, 3D head tracking and active noise cancelation. The set is compatible with PC, consoles and mobile platforms through 2.4GHz, Bluetooth 5.3 or wired connection. The 950X has a pair of hot-swappable and rechargeable batteries that give 50 hours of playtime. It comes with a 6mm cardioid boom microphone that uses AI noise reduction to keep background sounds out of i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to tell if it&#8217;s time for a career pivot</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91462109/how-tell-time-career-pivot</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91462109/how-tell-time-career-pivot</guid>
      <description>Science-based lessons for a successful professional reinvention.
Most people never change careers, which is remarkable when you consider how little evidence most of us had when we chose our first one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC gamers face a miserable new year as Nvidia RTX 5000 GPUs are reportedly hit by shortages due to RAM crisis</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gpu/pc-gamers-face-a-miserable-new-year-as-nvidia-rtx-5000-gpus-are-reportedly-hit-by-shortages-due-to-ram-crisis</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">EPFFxVRFKSoQALSXisSxFb</guid>
      <description>PC gaming could be in disarray in 2026, if reports of Nvidia RTX 5000 GPU shortages continue to surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus ne sortira aucun smartphone en 2026 : la production est suspendue</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2928449_asus-ne-sortira-aucun-smartphone-en-2026-la-production-est-suspendue</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2928449_asus-ne-sortira-aucun-smartphone-en-2026-la-production-est-suspendue</guid>
      <description>
L'histoire se r&#233;p&#232;te-t-elle ? Apr&#232;s Acer en 2016 et LG en 2021, c'est au tour d'Asus de vaciller. Le fabricant a confirm&#233; l'arr&#234;t des lancements pour toute l'ann&#233;e 2026. Officiellement, ce n'est pas un retrait d&#233;finitif. Officieusement, &#231;a y ressemble terriblement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil and defense stocks react to Venezuela news: Chevron, Exxon&#8239;Mobil, Palantir, Lockheed, Halliburton, more</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468985/oil-defense-stock-prices-today-venezuela-news-chevron-palantir-halliburton</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T12:53:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468985/oil-defense-stock-prices-today-venezuela-news-chevron-palantir-halliburton</guid>
      <description>Publicly traded energy giants are seeing a significant boost in premarket trading as investors digest this weekend&#8217;s stunning capture of Nicol&#225;s Maduro. 
The geopolitical implications of President Trump&#8217;s controversial weekend attack on Venezuela and the capture and extradition of its president, Nicol&#225;s Maduro, are still being digested by legal and security experts in the two days following the shocking announcement....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live Q&amp;A &#8211; ask our experts anything about the wildest new tech at the Vegas show</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/ces-2026-live-q-and-a</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uVYhLsSzyEDQbSjFeD3KvL</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 has started, and we're here to answer your burning questions about everything on show in Vegas. Hit us up below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govee unveils 3 new smart lights, plus a host of new features to help you create the perfect mood</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/smart-lights/govee-unveils-3-new-smart-lights-plus-a-host-of-new-features-to-help-you-create-the-perfect-mood</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">r6DTs8njVWrst98b7NskUb</guid>
      <description>There are three new smart lights joining the Govee family, and they're looking to be serious Philips Hue competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Samsung Galaxy Buds 4 have leaked again &#8211; here are 3 upgrades to expect from the wireless earbuds</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/the-samsung-galaxy-buds-4-have-leaked-again-here-are-3-upgrades-to-expect-from-the-wireless-earbuds</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iYDmjKDFbXQvusTRkYXEXE</guid>
      <description>Samsung is slowly getting around to releasing another two pairs of its flagship wireless earbuds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin has a new plan to improve your fitness using your food intake &#8212; if you pay for Connect+</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/health-fitness/garmin-has-a-new-plan-to-improve-your-fitness-using-your-food-intake-if-you-pay-for-connect</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Awtxi55amcteKGmjJHf574</guid>
      <description>The Garmin Connect app will add the ability to enter food intake using a quick photo (for Connect+ users).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 finishes an embarrassing last in speed test of six Windows generations &#8212; but there's a big catch</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/windows-11-finishes-an-embarrassing-last-in-speed-test-of-six-windows-generations-but-theres-a-big-catch</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4Tvo6HKFGTvSm6cMdoNBwA</guid>
      <description>There are obvious sticking points with the methodology of the suite of tests, but the results are still worth discussing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
