<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:30:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia launches Alpamayo, open AI models that allow autonomous vehicles to &#8216;think like a human&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/nvidia-launches-alpamayo-open-ai-models-that-allow-autonomous-vehicles-to-think-like-a-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079883</guid>
      <description>Nvidia unveiled Alpamayo at CES 2026, which includes a reasoning vision language action model that allows an autonomous vehicle to think more like a human and provide chain-of-thought reasoning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TII&#8217;s Falcon H1R 7B can out-reason models up to 7x its size &#8212; and it&#8217;s (mostly) open</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/tiis-falcon-h1r-7b-can-out-reason-models-up-to-7x-its-size-and-its-mostly</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Xtm5q8aKZPRVAXyxTnV8L</guid>
      <description>For the last two years, the prevailing logic in generative AI has been one of brute force: if you want better reasoning, you need a bigger model. While "small" models (under 10 billion parameters) have become capable conversationalists, they have historically crumbled when asked to perform multi-step logical deduction or complex mathematical proofs.Today, the Technology Innovation Institute (TII) in Abu Dhabi is challenging that scaling law with the release of Falcon H1R 7B. By abandoning the pure Transformer orthodoxy in favor of a hybrid architecture, TII claims to have built a 7-billion par...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the AMD CES 2026 keynote with CEO Lisa Su live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-the-amd-ces-2026-keynote-with-ceo-lisa-su-live-190012438.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c864a817-a6e7-423f-ab33-fb69dbcbdab4</guid>
      <description>AMD is kicking off CES 2026 on Monday, where it'll cover its latest AI developments and perhaps show off its newest Ryzen chips. The company will outline the full scope of its vision for AI implementations across the full spectrum of consumer and enterprise applications. The presentation &#8212; which is the lead keynote for CES 2026 &#8212; will be led by CEO Dr. Lisa Su.
We'll tell you how to tune in to the livestream and what else you can expect to see.
How to watch AMD's keynote live
Dr. Su will deliver a keynote speech from the Palazzo Ballroom at the Venetian on Monday, January 5 at 9:30PM ET (6:30P...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel at CES 2026: Live updates from the Core Ultra Series 3 Panther Lake launch event</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/intel-at-ces-2026-live-updates-from-the-core-ultra-series-3-panther-lake-launch-event-130040881.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f580535b-fd7f-4472-8749-2372604b977f</guid>
      <description>SOPA Images via Getty Images
CES 2026 is off and running, and chipmakers enabling the AI moment are one of the big starts of the show. In addition to NVIDIA and AMD taking the stage today, we'll also be getting Intel's 2026 launch event. The chip giant is expected to provide more details on its AI PC initiative and the new processors powering it: The Core Ultra Series 3 CPUs (aka Panther Lake) are made using an 18A process &#8212; that's 18 angstroms, or just under 2nm &#8212; and designed for high-end laptops and gaming devices.
For Intel, the stakes at CES are higher than ever. In the past 12 months, bo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers claim breach of engineering firm, offer sale of info on three major US utilities</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/security/hackers-claim-breach-of-engineering-firm-offer-sale-of-info-on-three-major-us-utilities</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f29S4NVLd6KmkgvkXdSMxT</guid>
      <description>Investigations are underway but the data seems to be quite valuable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a vu la nouvelle batterie solaire d&#8217;Ecoflow capable d&#8217;alimenter toute une maison (et bien plus)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929783_on-a-vu-la-nouvelle-batterie-solaire-decoflow-capable-dalimenter-toute-une-maison-et-bien-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929783_on-a-vu-la-nouvelle-batterie-solaire-decoflow-capable-dalimenter-toute-une-maison-et-bien-plus</guid>
      <description>
La nouvelle batterie solaire d'Ecoflow est un monstre de puissance, qui prend tout son sens en France avec les nouvelles r&#233;glementations sur les installations solaires. On a pu approcher la b&#234;te au CES.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurry, you only have a few days to back the world's fastest mini PC &#8212; and it even comes with a translucent touchscreen</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/hurry-you-have-a-few-days-to-back-the-worlds-fastest-mini-pc-and-it-even-comes-with-a-translucent-touchscreen</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rn85nF8RarHLjCZN7JpWMY</guid>
      <description>The AquaTouch mini PC integrates high-performance Ryzen components, a translucent touchscreen, user-upgradeable hardware, and modern connectivity in a compact 9-liter case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon d&#233;voile l&#8217;Ember Artline : le rival du Samsung The Frame &#224; prix cass&#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazon/2929785_amazon-devoile-lember-artline-le-rival-du-samsung-the-frame-a-prix-casse</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazon/2929785_amazon-devoile-lember-artline-le-rival-du-samsung-the-frame-a-prix-casse</guid>
      <description>
Un &#233;cran brillant dans un salon lumineux, c'est l'enfer. Amazon l'a compris et lance sa nouvelle gamme Ember Artline. Au programme : une dalle QLED mate trait&#233;e antireflet qui se fond dans le d&#233;cor. L'objectif n'est pas de battre l'OLED sur les noirs, mais de faire dispara&#238;tre la tech de votre mur.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Ahead in TV</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/tv-2026-preview-knight-of-the-seven-kingdoms-starfleet-academy-2000704994</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704994</guid>
      <description>Brand-new shows that take place on familiar turf are a big theme for 2026&#8212;a year that's also stuffed full of highly anticipated returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 2026 tax changes could leave more money in your paycheck</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469276/how-2026-tax-changes-could-leave-more-money-in-your-paycheck</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T20:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469276/how-2026-tax-changes-could-leave-more-money-in-your-paycheck</guid>
      <description>Inflation-adjusted tax brackets and new withholding rules under Trump&#8217;s tax law may boost take-home pay for some workers.
Your paycheck could be a little bigger in 2026, even if you didn&#8217;t get a New Year&#8217;s raise. That&#8217;s because, in order to adjust for inflation, the IRS made some major changes to the tax code last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Hyundai CES 2026 press conference live</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/how-to-watch-the-hyundai-ces-2026-press-conference-live-190051823.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37edf748-4f98-43d1-8ee2-27a98b6a0143</guid>
      <description>Hyundai
CES has long felt like a full-on auto show, but the car-centric energy seems somewhat muted at CES 2026. Sure, the Afeela electric vehicle from the Sony-Honda joint venture is returning to the show floor, but with the Trump administration yanking most EV incentives from the market, the industry isn't offering a full-court press of new vehicles in Las Vegas this year.
That includes Hyundai. While the company's Mobis subsidiary will present "more than 30 mobility convergence technologies" during CES week &#8212; including its Holographic Windshield Display &#8212; we're hearing the Korean auto giant...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#171;&#160;30 % plus rapide&#160;&#187;, Amazon repense totalement l&#8217;interface Fire TV : voici ce qui va changer</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazon/2929767_30-plus-rapide-amazon-repense-totalement-linterface-fire-tv-voici-ce-qui-va-changer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/amazon/2929767_30-plus-rapide-amazon-repense-totalement-linterface-fire-tv-voici-ce-qui-va-changer</guid>
      <description>
Si vous avez une Fire TV, vous connaissez ce petit moment de frustration : le lag au d&#233;marrage, les menus charg&#233;s, la lenteur. Amazon semble avoir (enfin) compris le message. L'interface fait peau neuve en ce d&#233;but 2026 avec une promesse forte : 30 % de rapidit&#233; en plus.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris court finds 10 people guilty of cyberbullying Brigitte Macron</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/paris-court-finds-10-people-guilty-of-cyberbullying-brigitte-macron-195500994.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f9f3597-08dc-42a1-8337-e67318bbf482</guid>
      <description>A Paris court has found 10 people guilty of cyberbullying Brigitte Macron, wife of President of France Emmanuel Macron, the BBC reports. The judge found that the defendants made false claims about Macron's gender and sexuality, and "malicious remarks" about the 24-year age gap between Macron and her spouse.The defendants, eight men and two women, received a range of sentences, including jail time up to eight months and mandatory online harassment awareness training. Five of the defendants will also lose access to their X accounts for six months, according to The New York Times.Key to the lawsu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fini les gadgets : j&#8217;ai vu ces deux bagues connect&#233;es Pebble et Vocci qui rendent l&#8217;IA (enfin) utile au quotidien</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2929711_fini-les-gadgets-jai-vu-ces-deux-bagues-connectees-pebble-et-vocci-qui-rendent-lia-enfin-utile-au-quotidien</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/bagues-connectees/2929711_fini-les-gadgets-jai-vu-ces-deux-bagues-connectees-pebble-et-vocci-qui-rendent-lia-enfin-utile-au-quotidien</guid>
      <description>
Les bagues connect&#233;es entrent dans une nouvelle &#232;re, gr&#226;ce &#224; l'intelligence artificielle. Elles deviennent plus pratique. La preuve avec le Pebble 01 Index et Vocci que nous avons pu voir au CES 2026 de Las Vegas.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA is reportedly bringing back 2021's RTX 3060 GPU because AI is eating all of the newer cards</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/nvidia-is-reportedly-bringing-back-2021s-rtx-3060-gpu-because-ai-is-eating-all-of-the-newer-cards-194241706.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa3c866-6052-4a61-a7e0-69223c334b85</guid>
      <description>A reputable leaker has indicated that NVIDIA plans on bringing the RTX 3060 back to market, according to reports by Kotaku and WFCCTech. It first released the GPU at the beginning of 2021. The leaker Hongxing2020 indicates that NVIDIA will resume production of the 3060 sometime in the next few months.
Why is the world's most valuable company reportedly bringing back such an antiquated graphics card? You know the answer. It's the endless gaping maw known as AI. Tech companies have been hoovering up PC parts for AI applications with reckless abandon. It has become a legitimate challenge for a re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything announced at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/everything-announced-at-ces-2026-130124802.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3b4bbf-1b78-4e34-9914-70a2e6f85389</guid>
      <description>It's the first week of a new year and there's no time for the tech world to slowly ease back into things following the holidays. That's because CES 2026 is in full swing, with all manner of companies descending on Las Vegas to reveal their latest innovations and what they're planning to bring your way in the near future.&#160;Many of the Engadget crew are on the ground to check out as much of the new tech as possible. Of course, we're keeping tabs on all of the major CES press conferences too. Samsung has already held its First Look presentation, which focuses on home products, while LG has shown o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin unveils a new rugged cam designed to cover blind spots &#8212; and it's the safety device truck drivers need</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/dash-cams/garmin-unveils-a-new-rugged-cam-designed-to-cover-blind-spots-and-its-the-safety-device-truck-drivers-need</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fJEk8QhFUCRxsQGE5brj7</guid>
      <description>The Garmin d&#275;zl DualView system comprises two rugged exterior cameras and a transmitter, delivering surrounding vehicle alerts and coverage of a truck's remaining blind spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Office, c&#8217;est fini : la d&#233;cision folle et incons&#233;quente de Satya Nadella</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2929667_microsoft-office-cest-fini-la-decision-folle-et-inconsequente-de-satya-nadella</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/microsoft/2929667_microsoft-office-cest-fini-la-decision-folle-et-inconsequente-de-satya-nadella</guid>
      <description>
Microsoft met fin &#224; l'une des marques les plus reconnues de l'informatique de ces 35 derni&#232;res ann&#233;es. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia's CES 2026 keynote live - all the latest news from the GPU and AI superpower</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/nvidia-ces-2026-live</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Xe8Be67Yu5wUraMbCmjysP</guid>
      <description>What will the GPU giant unveil at CES 2026? We have all the breaking news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 live updates: See the latest news, surprises, and strange tech from LG, Samsung, Lego, and new startups</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/live/ces-2026-news-live-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00HdPGMgSorg1E6HI6usOJ2</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 is finally here, and Mashable reporters are on the ground looking for the best in show. Get live updates from the showroom floor and behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does self-improvement in 2026 start on TikTok?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469165/tiktok-2026-365-buttons-self-improvement</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469165/tiktok-2026-365-buttons-self-improvement</guid>
      <description>The 365 buttons trend, explained.
How seriously are you taking your 2026 rebrand? Do you have your 365 buttons ready?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UK just banned junk food ads before 9pm and across the internet</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469198/the-uk-just-banned-junk-food-ads-before-9pm-and-across-the-internet</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T19:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469198/the-uk-just-banned-junk-food-ads-before-9pm-and-across-the-internet</guid>
      <description>Even foods perceived as healthy, including some cereals and sandwiches, fall under the new restrictions.
For Americans, the idea of watching live television without the constant barrage of commercials for prescription medications and junk food might seem foreign. That&#8217;s now the norm in the United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG Sound Suite hands-on at CES 2026: Home theater powered by Dolby Atmos FlexConnect</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/lg-sound-suite-hands-on-at-ces-2026-home-theater-powered-by-dolby-atmos-flexconnect-192709499.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd3ed876-1529-45da-a2de-070181bb53a8</guid>
      <description>Dolby introduced its FlexConnect technology a few years ago, vowing that it would allow customers to position soundbars and speakers anywhere in a room. The company said the platform would then reconfigure the sound automatically, taking into account any locations that may be further away from the center sweet spot. At CES 2026, LG is the first to put Dolby Atmos FlexConnect in a soundbar, offering the so-called Sound Suite that also includes satellite speaker options and a subwoofer. You don&#8217;t need every member of the lineup to use Dolby&#8217;s tech, so you can pick and choose which items work bes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nouveaux LEGO Star Wars avec briques &#171;&#160;Smart Play&#160;&#187; : voici &#171;&#160;la plus grosse &#233;volution depuis 50 ans&#160;&#187;</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929691_nouveaux-lego-star-wars-la-plus-grosse-evolution-depuis-50-ans-ils-integrent-une-technologie-revolutionnaire-de-smart-play</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/events/ces/2929691_nouveaux-lego-star-wars-la-plus-grosse-evolution-depuis-50-ans-ils-integrent-une-technologie-revolutionnaire-de-smart-play</guid>
      <description>
C'est probablement l'annonce la plus excitante du CES 2026 pour les grands enfants que nous sommes (ou que je suis). LEGO lance le Smart Play. L'id&#233;e ? Une brique intelligente capable de d&#233;tecter les mouvements et de communiquer avec les autres, sans l'horrible design des sets Mario. La marque promet la plus grosse &#233;volution depuis 50 ans. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working on the go? You can no longer activate Windows with your phone</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/working-on-the-go-you-can-no-longer-activate-windows-with-your-phone</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HUwweXTiRhD3dsFi52iVwd</guid>
      <description>By all accounts, Microsoft isn't letting you activate Windows from your phone anymore, so make sure you have an internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than 40 Million People Use ChatGPT Daily for Healthcare Advice, OpenAI Claims</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/more-than-40-million-people-use-chatgpt-daily-for-healthcare-advice-openai-claims-2000705509</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705509</guid>
      <description>OpenAI wants ChatGPT to be a bigger player in healthcare. First, they need regulators to play ball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi le nouveau chargeur Anker Nano risque de devenir votre indispensable</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/anker/2929669_pourquoi-le-nouveau-chargeur-anker-nano-risque-de-devenir-votre-indispensable</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/anker/2929669_pourquoi-le-nouveau-chargeur-anker-nano-risque-de-devenir-votre-indispensable</guid>
      <description>
Anker ne s'est pas calm&#233; pour ce CES 2026. La marque vient de l&#226;cher une avalanche d'accessoires, du chargeur minuscule capable d'alimenter un MacBook Air &#224; la station d'accueil qui se transforme en hub nomade.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transporter de l&#8217;&#233;lectricit&#233; gr&#226;ce &#224; la lumi&#232;re : c&#8217;est possible avec cette technologie int&#233;gr&#233;e &#224; une serrure connect&#233;e</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/securite-connectee/serrures-connectees/2929619_transporter-de-lelectricite-grace-a-la-lumiere-cest-possible-avec-cette-technologie-integree-a-une-serrure-connectee</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/maison-connectee/securite-connectee/serrures-connectees/2929619_transporter-de-lelectricite-grace-a-la-lumiere-cest-possible-avec-cette-technologie-integree-a-une-serrure-connectee</guid>
      <description>
La recharge sans fil, par voie optique, sans aucun c&#226;ble, devient une r&#233;alit&#233; avec cette serrure connect&#233;e qu'on a pu voir dans les all&#233;es du CES. L'id&#233;e : pouvoir recharger une batterie &#224; 4 m&#232;tres de distance, uniquement avec de la lumi&#232;re. &#199;a fonctionne vraiment, et c'est bient&#244;t disponible.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026 day 1: the 11 best gadgets we've seen so far, from smart lights to LG's new OLEDs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/tech-events/the-best-of-ces-2026-day-one</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Ed54sk2YV2TJ6i4yBgpqbb</guid>
      <description>CES 2026 has kicked off in style, and we've been busy finding the highlights from the show floor in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung CEO Says What We Already Know About the Memory Shortage</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/samsung-ceo-says-what-we-already-know-about-the-memory-shortage-2000705543</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705543</guid>
      <description>It's a new year. Start pinching those pennies!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These On-Ear Beats Headphones Are Marked Down by $70</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/beats-solo-4-deal-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695bf1ae363a90f378f47670</guid>
      <description>What these headphones lack in active noise canceling, they make up for with big, bold sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest TV announcements at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/home-theater/the-biggest-tv-announcements-at-ces-2026-190929976.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecf435a5-d2a0-4321-9064-dcce9611c48e</guid>
      <description>CES is once again where TV manufacturers lay out their plans for the year ahead, and CES 2026 is shaping up to be a showcase of both familiar rivalries and genuinely new display tech. While OLED and Mini LED remain central to most lineups, Micro RGB has emerged as one of the most talked-about developments at the show so far, especially at the higher end of the market.
Below are the TV announcements that stood out most from the pre-show events and early press conferences, with more expected as CES continues.
Samsung Micro RGB TVs



  Samsung's flagship Micro RGB TV
 

  Engadget
 

Samsung&#8217;s M...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cette vieille carte graphique fait son retour en 2026 : Nvidia change ses plans</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2929603_cette-vieille-carte-graphique-fait-son-retour-en-2026-nvidia-change-ses-plans</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/nvidia/2929603_cette-vieille-carte-graphique-fait-son-retour-en-2026-nvidia-change-ses-plans</guid>
      <description>
On pensait l'avoir enterr&#233;e fin 2024. C'&#233;tait mal conna&#238;tre Nvidia. Face &#224; une crise de la m&#233;moire vive qui fait exploser les co&#251;ts, le g&#233;ant vert s'appr&#234;te &#224; ressortir sa GeForce RTX 3060 du placard. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Health Band Is Like if Whoop Went Wild With Voice Assistants</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/this-health-band-is-like-if-whoop-went-wild-with-voice-assistants-2000705329</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705329</guid>
      <description>The Luna Band is all about yelling at your wrist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Duffer Brothers Have No Idea Why They Tried to Answer So Many &#8216;Stranger Things&#8217; Questions Last Week</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/stranger-things-finale-duffer-brothers-backlash-2000705567</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705567</guid>
      <description>'I'm, like, fried,' Matt Duffer explained in the wake of the Netflix hit's big finale, which we can certainly understand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego debuts Smart Play system that reacts as you play. Heres how it works.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-lego-smart-play-system-announced</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06J99aExnJ9iu6rfG9nqEuE</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Lego announced the imminent launch of the Lego Smart Play system, one of the biggest evolutions in brick-building technology in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego&#8217;s Smart Brick Gives the Iconic Analog Toy a New Digital Brain</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/lego-smart-brick-new-digital-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6958076061289fcb0d09c3c1</guid>
      <description>The new sensor-packed Smart Play Brick will land this spring as part of a special Star Wars collection. The update adds interactive lights and sound to the Lego experience&#8212;including the minifigs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego announces Smart Brick, the &amp;#8216;most significant evolution&amp;#8217; in 50 years</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/854556/lego-announces-smart-brick-the-most-significant-evolution-in-50-years</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T14:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=854556</guid>
      <description>On March 1st, 2026, The Lego Group will begin selling the most ambitious brick it's ever made: a tiny computer that fits entirely inside a classic 2&#215;4 Lego brick. When it detects NFC-equipped smart tags nearby, embedded inside new Lego tiles and new Lego minifigures, or when it sees other Smart Bricks, the company claims [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego unveils a technology-packed Smart Brick at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/lego-unveils-a-technology-packed-smart-brick-at-ces-2026-190000511.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6354879d-871a-4410-855d-b4db770893fe</guid>
      <description>Lego bricks come in a ridiculously vast array of sizes and shapes, but the company is unveiling an entirely new take on its classic shape at CES 2026. Meet the Lego Smart Brick, a standard-sized 2 x 4 brick that&#8217;s packed with modern technology to enable sets that can respond to how they&#8217;re played with or the sets you build. It&#8217;s part of a new initiative called Smart Play, which encompasses the Smart Brick as well as Smart Minifigures and Smart Tags. While we obviously don&#8217;t know yet how Lego fans will take to this new system, it&#8217;s still fair to say it&#8217;s the biggest move Lego has every made to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grindr for lesbians? Here are the best dating apps for LGBTQ women.</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/roundup/best-dating-apps-for-lesbians</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05OeYFtDK5qi44fkvKr0KKO</guid>
      <description>Looking for love, friends, or casual fun? We've curated a list of the best dating apps for lesbians, from HER to Hinge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk promet un voyage vers Mars en 2026&#8230; mais son Starship est-il vraiment pr&#234;t ?</title>
      <link>https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-elon-musk-promet-voyage-vers-mars-2026-mais-son-starship-il-vraiment-pret-129787/#xtor%3DRSS-8</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:59:40 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.futura-sciences.com/sciences/actualites/astronautique-elon-musk-promet-voyage-vers-mars-2026-mais-son-starship-il-vraiment-pret-129787/#xtor%3DRSS-8</guid>
      <description>Apr&#232;s une ann&#233;e 2025 marqu&#233;e par plusieurs d&#233;convenues pour SpaceX, l'entreprise d'Elon Musk attend beaucoup de son Starship pour 2026. Mais peut-elle r&#233;aliser l'impossible et faire face aux nombreux d&#233;fis techniques qui attendent son lanceur lourd ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktivist deletes white supremacist websites live onstage during hacker conference</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/05/hacktivist-deletes-white-supremacist-websites-live-on-stage-during-hacker-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079707</guid>
      <description>A hacker known as Martha Root broke in and deleted three white supremacist websites at the end of a talk during the annual hacker conference Chaos Communication Congress in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lego brick just got its biggest upgrade yet with Smart Play &#8212; and it's coming to Star Wars sets first</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/the-lego-brick-just-got-its-biggest-upgrade-yet-with-smart-play-and-its-coming-to-star-wars-sets-first</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Tkg3VrTHxx6kVi7DxVjfLF</guid>
      <description>Similar looks, but supercharged internals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verge announces world-first motorcycle with solid-state batteries &#8211;and it promises a 370-mile range with 10-minute charge times</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/verge-announces-world-first-motorcycle-with-solid-state-batteries-for-a-370-mile-range-and-10-minute-charge-times</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Lh8XgM9JuNSwyLBA53end5</guid>
      <description>Verge Motorcycles unlocks ten-minute charge times with world-first all solid-sate battery in a bike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Nigeria vs. Mozambique online for free</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/nigeria-mozambique-africa-cup-of-nations-2025-live-stream-for-free</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01curlm1QxIGywxphCwADD3</guid>
      <description>How to watch AFCON for free. Live stream Nigeria vs. Mozambique in the 2025 Africa Cup of Nations for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce mini PC modulaire r&#233;alise un vieux fantasme et c&#8217;est malin</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2929569_ce-mini-pc-modulaire-realise-un-vieux-fantasme-et-cest-malin</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/ordinateurs/2929569_ce-mini-pc-modulaire-realise-un-vieux-fantasme-et-cest-malin</guid>
      <description>
La qu&#234;te de l'anneau unique est un vieux fantasme de la tech. Au CES 2026, la marque Khadas en propose un aboutissement gr&#226;ce &#224; Intel Panther Lake.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That viral Reddit post about food delivery apps was an AI scam</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/855328/viral-reddit-delivery-app-ai-scam</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T13:43:02-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855328</guid>
      <description>A viral Reddit confessional about a "major food delivery app" posted January 2nd is most likely AI-generated. The original post by user Trowaway_whistleblow alleged that an unnamed food delivery company regularly delays customer orders, calls couriers "human assets," and exploits their "desperation" for cash, among other indefensible actions. Nearly 90,000 upvotes and four days later, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&#8217;ai vu le Honor Robot Phone avec sa cam&#233;ra articul&#233;e et j&#8217;en suis ressorti avec plus de questions que de r&#233;ponses</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/jai-vu-le-honor-robot-phone-avec-sa-camera-articulee-et-jen-suis-ressorti-avec-plus-de-questions-que-de-reponses.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1318246</guid>
      <description>Au CES 2026, Honor d&#233;voile le Robot Phone, un &#233;tonnant smartphone &#224; cam&#233;ra articul&#233;e. Simple concept ou v&#233;ritable r&#233;volution mobile&#8239;? Cette premi&#232;re prise en main soul&#232;ve de nombreuses questions sur les ambitions de la marque chinoise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu virus tracker: Latest update shows high influenza activity across most states. Watch out for these symptoms</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469196/flu-virus-tracker-2026-high-influenza-activity-states-symptoms</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:39:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469196/flu-virus-tracker-2026-high-influenza-activity-states-symptoms</guid>
      <description>After reporting was delayed due to the holidays, new CDC data shows the flu is spreading, with 33,000 people hospitalized during the last week of the year.
As today is the first Monday of 2026, Americans across the country are settling back into their everyday routines after the busy holiday season. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Play Chess in Hyperbolic Space Now, and It Sucks</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/you-can-play-chess-in-hyperbolic-space-now-and-it-sucks-2000705568</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705568</guid>
      <description>It may not be particularly fun yet, but it's weird!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. quietly expands list of countries whose citizens must pay up to $15,000 bonds for visas</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91469257/us-quietly-expands-countries-list-visa-bonds</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-05T18:35:20</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91469257/us-quietly-expands-countries-list-visa-bonds</guid>
      <description>Bhutan, Botswana, the Central African Republic, Guinea, Guinea-Bissau, Namibia, and Turkmenistan are now on the list. 
The Trump administration has added seven countries, including five in Africa, to the list of nations whose passport holders are required to post&#160;bonds of up to $15,000&#160;to apply to enter the United States.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
