<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:40:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims he&#8217;ll make data centers pay for their own power supply</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/science/884191/ai-data-center-energy-state-of-the-union-trump</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T15:37:25-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884191</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump tried to quell Americans' concerns about rising electricity costs during his State of the Union speech by claiming that he's negotiated a "rate payer protection pledge" with major tech companies, which would see them build out or pay for new electricity generation for their data centers. Leaders from Amazon, Google, Meta, Microsoft, [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Messed-Up-Looking &#8216;Absolute Batman&#8217; Villains, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-most-messed-up-looking-absolute-batman-villains-ranked-2000726415</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726415</guid>
      <description>A hero is only as good as his villains&#8212;and so far DC's blockbuster new take on the Dark Knight is knocking it out of the park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US cybersecurity agency CISA reportedly in dire shape amid Trump cuts and layoffs</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/us-cybersecurity-agency-cisa-reportedly-in-dire-shape-amid-trump-cuts-and-layoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096990</guid>
      <description>Under the first year of the Trump administration, the U.S. cyber agency CISA has faced cuts, layoffs, and furloughs, as bipartisan lawmakers and cybersecurity industry sources say the agency is unprepared to handle a crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalshi Bans MrBeast Video Editor and Political Candidate Over Insider Trading</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/kalshi-bans-mrbeast-video-editor-and-political-candidate-over-insider-trading-2000726520</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726520</guid>
      <description>This is the first known action that the prediction market has taken against users for alleged insider trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the post-hype crypto market</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/video/welcome-to-the-post-hype-crypto-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?post_type=tc_video&amp;p=3096986</guid>
      <description>Crypto is creeping back into the startup conversation, but at&#160;ETHDenver&#160;last week, the buzz was as much about Washington as it was about tokens. Policy shifts are rippling through the market as&#160;Tether&#160;and stablecoins face scrutiny,&#160;players like Stripe&#160;re-enter the&#160;conversation, and startups either find traction or flame out. The hype cycle is&#160;over, or&#160;at least taking a&#160;break.&#160;So&#160;what&#160;comes next?&#160; On [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why This Part of Antarctica Bleeds Blood Red</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/why-this-part-of-antarctica-bleeds-blood-red-2000726530</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726530</guid>
      <description>Perhaps surprisingly, the answer isn't climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here&#8217;s how the new Samsung Galaxy S26 compares with last year&#8217;s S25</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/884281/samsung-galaxy-s26-plus-ultra-vs-s25-specs-features</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T15:09:14-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884281</guid>
      <description>Samsung unveiled its Galaxy S26 lineup at its recent Unpacked event in San Francisco. As expected, the new series consists of the baseline S26, which starts at $899.99, and the bigger S26 Plus, which starts at $1,099.99. At the high end, there's also the $1,299.99 S26 Ultra, which is the largest in the lineup and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet-owned robotics software company Intrinsic joins Google</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/alphabet-owned-robotics-software-company-intrinsic-joins-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096871</guid>
      <description>Nearly five years after graduating into an independent Alphabet company, Intrinsic is moving under Google's domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ce qui cloche avec les Samsung Galaxy S26</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2987095_ce-qui-cloche-avec-les-samsung-galaxy-s26</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2987095_ce-qui-cloche-avec-les-samsung-galaxy-s26</guid>
      <description>
Samsung vient d'annoncer les Galaxy S26, S26 Plus et S26 Ultra. Au milieu de plusieurs qualit&#233;s, certains d&#233;fauts retiennent aussi notre attention sur ces smartphones.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riley Walz, the Jester of Silicon Valley, Is Joining OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-hires-riley-walz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699e08ff458686361c3c0d20</guid>
      <description>The software engineer is famous for his online stunts. Now he&#8217;s joining the company behind ChatGPT to work on new ways for humans to use AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google and Samsung just launched the AI features Apple couldn&#8217;t with Siri</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/884703/google-samsung-galaxy-s26-gemini-apple-siri</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T14:56:55-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=884703</guid>
      <description>Google just announced that Gemini will soon be able to take care of some multi-step tasks on your phone, like ordering food or hailing a car, starting first with the Pixel 10, Pixel 10 Pro, and the just-announced Samsung Galaxy S26 phones. It all sounds a bit like features Apple announced for Siri way back [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat announces &#8216;The Snappys,&#8217; its first-ever creator awards show</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/snapchat-announces-the-snappys-its-first-ever-creator-awards-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096864</guid>
      <description>Snapchat is the latest social media platform to launch awards for creators, joining TikTok and Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tecno just unveiled a ridiculously thin modular smartphone concept design</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/tecno-just-unveiled-a-ridiculously-thin-modular-smartphone-concept-design-194741776.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3f8f8ca-6771-42a1-a5f0-26e1ee8704e5</guid>
      <description>Tecno just unveiled a rather intriguing modular smartphone concept design at MWC 2026. The standout feature here is likely the size. Most modular smartphone concepts start bulky and only get bulkier once attaching accessories. Tecno's base smartphone is just 4.9mm thin, which is significantly thinner than a pencil and the iPhone Air.
Of course, the size increases with each attached module. However, snapping on the power bank module makes the thickness comparable to a standard modern smartphone. Another key feature here is how these various modular components stick together. Tecno has developed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel ditches human customer support for 'one of the first of its kind in the semiconductor industry' system made up of Copilot-powered AI agents</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/intel-ditches-human-customer-support-for-one-of-the-first-of-its-kind-in-the-semiconductor-industry-system-made-of-copilot-powered-ai-agents</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xmBtpT933EEoFPpkQo9tVE</guid>
      <description>Ask Intel is an AI-powered assistant replacing phone-based support and centralizing warranty, troubleshooting, and case management online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An accountant won a big jackpot on Kalshi by betting against DOGE</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/an-accountant-won-a-big-jackpot-on-kalshi-by-betting-against-doge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096863</guid>
      <description>A tax accountant saw Elon Musk fans bidding up a Kalshi prediction market and saw a sure bet to make easy money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the story of the US defense contractor who leaked hacking tools to Russia</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/inside-the-story-of-the-us-defense-contractor-who-leaked-hacking-tools-to-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096822</guid>
      <description>The former boss of a U.S. hacking tools maker was jailed for selling highly sensitive software exploits to a Russian broker. This is how we first learned of his arrest, reported the story, and some of the unanswered questions we still have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;The brightness does not change&#8217; &#8212; Samsung answers our 5 biggest Galaxy S26 Ultra Privacy Display questions</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/the-brightness-does-not-change-samsung-answers-our-5-biggest-galaxy-s26-ultra-privacy-display-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YV5iaDNnp2zxWFLKwGJ5Pm</guid>
      <description>Samsung just unveiled the Galaxy S26 Ultra, and its new Privacy Display feature is one of its most valuable upgrades in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra : comment activer l&#8217;affichage confidentiel ? Voici toutes les options &#224; conna&#238;tre</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2985541_samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-comment-activer-laffichage-confidentiel-voici-toutes-les-options-a-connaitre</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2985541_samsung-galaxy-s26-ultra-comment-activer-laffichage-confidentiel-voici-toutes-les-options-a-connaitre</guid>
      <description>
Voici comment activer l'option d'affichage confidentiel du Samsung Galaxy S26 Ultra ainsi que toutes les fonctions pratiques de cette technologie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP says RAM now accounts for more than a third of its PC costs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/hp-says-ram-now-accounts-for-more-than-a-third-of-its-pc-costs-192914150.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88a6a211-afc4-4d0b-b1bc-76a26a7aa121</guid>
      <description>The cost of PC components has been skyrocketing as AI infrastructure buildout creates extraordinary demand amid limited supply. HP says that squeeze is now hitting PC memory especially hard, with RAM now accounting for 35 percent of a system&#8217;s overall cost.
"We did share last quarter that memory and storage costs made up roughly 15 percent to 18 percent of our PC bill of materials, and we now currently estimate this to be roughly 35 percent for the year," said CFO Karen Parkhill on the company's latest earnings call. She also confirmed that part of the company's response will be price increase...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Galaxy S26 Ultra a un mode Oc&#233;an pour photographier et filmer les profondeurs comme un Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2990858_le-galaxy-s26-ultra-a-un-mode-ocean-pour-photographier-et-filmer-les-profondeurs-comme-un-pro</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2990858_le-galaxy-s26-ultra-a-un-mode-ocean-pour-photographier-et-filmer-les-profondeurs-comme-un-pro</guid>
      <description>
&#192; la toute fin de son Galaxy Unpacked, Samsung a jet&#233; en p&#226;ture un tout nouveau mode photo/vid&#233;o pour son Galaxy S26 Ultra : le mode oc&#233;an.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung shows off new display tech that adds a privacy screen to apps and notifications</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/samsung-shows-off-new-display-tech-that-adds-a-privacy-screen-to-apps-and-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096892</guid>
      <description>The new privacy tech uses different types of pixels to let you block certain apps and notifications from being viewed by others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic Rolls Back Safety Protocols as It Waits to Find Out If It&#8217;s Being Drafted by the Army</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anthropic-rolls-back-safety-protocols-as-it-waits-to-find-out-if-its-being-drafted-by-the-army-2000726567</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726567</guid>
      <description>Launching missiles for defense is fine, apparently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S26, S26 Plus et S26 Ultra : tout ce qu&#8217;il faut savoir pour pr&#233;commander au meilleur prix les nouveaux fleurons de Samsung</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2987675_galaxy-s26-s26-plus-et-s26-ultra-tout-ce-quil-faut-savoir-pour-precommander-au-meilleur-prix-les-nouveaux-fleurons-de-samsung</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2987675_galaxy-s26-s26-plus-et-s26-ultra-tout-ce-quil-faut-savoir-pour-precommander-au-meilleur-prix-les-nouveaux-fleurons-de-samsung</guid>
      <description>
Ce mercredi 25 f&#233;vrier 2026 l&#232;ve enfin le voile sur les nouveaux fleurons de Samsung : les Galaxy S26, Galaxy S26 Plus et Galaxy S26 Ultra. Les pr&#233;commandes sont d&#233;j&#224; ouvertes et il y a m&#234;me des r&#233;ductions. 
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalshi fined a MrBeast editor for insider trading</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/big-tech/kalshi-fined-a-mrbeast-editor-for-insider-trading-191027814.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa2f8551-4e8b-47ae-9488-f85f6f280629</guid>
      <description>Kalshi, one of several online prediction markets that have exploded in popularity in the last few years, has suspended one of YouTube MrBeast's video editors for insider trading, NPR reports. Besides being suspended from the platform for two years, Kalshi says the editor will also be required to pay a financial penalty that's five times his initial trade size.The editor, Artem Kaptur, traded in markets related to YouTube and specifically, MrBeast. Kalshi says his transactions were initially flagged because of his "near-perfect trading success on markets with low odds, which were statistically ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable startup CUDIS launches a new health ring line with an AI-fueled &#8216;coach&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/wearable-startup-cudis-launches-a-new-health-ring-line-with-an-ai-fueled-coach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096560</guid>
      <description>The wearable incentivizes healthy behavior with points that can be redeemed for health products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preorders for Samsung&#8217;s S26 phones come with up to $200 in gift cards</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/883829/samsung-galaxy-s26-plus-ultra-how-to-buy-preorder-price-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-25T14:09:29-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=883829</guid>
      <description>As expected, Samsung has taken the wraps off its flagship lineup for 2026. Introduced during the company's recent Unpacked event, the new Galaxy devices - which include the standard S26, the larger S26 Plus, and the high-end S26 Ultra - will be available on March 11th. Preorders are now open ahead of launch, with pricing [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalshi fined a MrBeast editor for insider trading on markets related to the YouTube star</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/kalshi-fined-a-mrbeast-editor-for-insider-trading-on-markets-related-to-the-youtube-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3096827</guid>
      <description>Kalshi fined the MrBeast editor, Artem Kaptur, for over $20,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The public opposition to AI infrastructure is heating up</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/25/the-public-opposition-to-ai-infrastructure-is-heating-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3085804</guid>
      <description>Public backlash over the data center boom is leading to a variety of draconian policies &#8212; including bans on new construction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firing Melissa Barrera Was Very Costly &#8216;Scream&#8217; Decision</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/firing-melissa-barrera-was-very-costly-scream-decision-2000726534</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726534</guid>
      <description>A new report reveals how much it cost to rewrite the script and how much Neve Campbell was paid to return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenClaw Users Are Allegedly Bypassing Anti-Bot Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openclaw-users-bypass-anti-bot-systems-cloudflare-scrapling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">699ca7bc7af267bad382dacb</guid>
      <description>An open source project called Scrapling is gaining traction with AI agent users who want their bots to scrape sites without permission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This new Hitman crossover mission features a blockbuster star from the Resident Evil movies</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/this-new-hitman-crossover-mission-features-a-blockbuster-star-from-the-resident-evil-movies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eCVUajYnEonHNtfuhqyTxf</guid>
      <description>The latest celebrity Elusive Target mission has arrived in Hitman World of Assassination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S26, S26 Ultra et Buds 4 Pro : voici le r&#233;sum&#233; des annonces</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2989759_comment-suivre-le-samsung-unpacked-pour-decouvrir-en-direct-les-nouveaux-smartphones-galaxy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2989759_comment-suivre-le-samsung-unpacked-pour-decouvrir-en-direct-les-nouveaux-smartphones-galaxy</guid>
      <description>
On y est. C'est aujourd'hui, mercredi 25 f&#233;vrier, que Samsung abat ses cartes pour l'ann&#233;e 2026. Entre le Galaxy S26 Ultra qui a fait une cure d'amincissement et les promesses de l'IA agentique, il y a de quoi dire. Voici comment ne rien rater.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung has unveiled its newest earbuds, the Galaxy Buds Pro 4 &#8212; and Best Buy is already offering a free gift card with your purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/audio/earbuds-airpods/samsung-has-unveiled-its-newest-earbuds-the-galaxy-buds-pro-4-and-best-buy-is-already-offering-a-free-gift-card-with-your-purchase</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SU2it3UHsZZnSRw7FuQybY</guid>
      <description>Samsung's Galaxy Unpacked event unveiled the Galaxy Buds Pro 4, and I've found the best preorder deal: a free $30 gift card with your purchase at Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;We are getting it ready': Samsung explains why the Galaxy S26 didn't get a silicon carbon battery upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/we-are-getting-it-ready-samsung-explains-why-the-galaxy-s26-didnt-get-a-silicon-carbon-battery-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">o7XPiv2jLvuZbvTseX75s3</guid>
      <description>A Samsung exec claims the company is getting silicon carbon batteries ready, but that they're still not quite ready for prime-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une commande &#224; passer ? Laissez votre t&#233;l&#233;phone faire, Gemini s&#8217;occupe de tout</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2990676_une-commande-a-passer-laissez-votre-telephone-faire-gemini-soccupe-de-tout</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/samsung/2990676_une-commande-a-passer-laissez-votre-telephone-faire-gemini-soccupe-de-tout</guid>
      <description>
Google a pr&#233;sent&#233; le futur de son IA mobile lors du Galaxy Unpacked de Samsung.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Grills MAHA Influencer Pick for Surgeon General Over Vaccines, Autism, and Financial Ties</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/trumps-surgeon-general-pick-a-maha-influencer-dodges-autism-question-during-tense-senate-hearing-2000726443</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000726443</guid>
      <description>Casey Means refused to state her opinion on whether vaccines cause autism and suggested most women are not getting informed consent about the birth control pill.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
