<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:35:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Le patron de Microsoft admet que l&#8217;IA g&#233;n&#233;rative doit encore prouver son utilit&#233; r&#233;elle</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/le-patron-de-microsoft-admet-que-lia-generative-doit-encore-prouver-son-utilite-reelle.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317849</guid>
      <description>Les grands acteurs de l'IA g&#233;n&#233;rative semblent vivre dans un monde o&#249; leur technologie est accept&#233;e &#224; bras ouverts par des centaines de millions d'utilisateurs b&#233;ats, mais la r&#233;alit&#233; est bien plus nuanc&#233;e &#8212; dans les faits, il existe une vraie opposition et cela pourrait ne pas aller en s'arrangeant. Satya Nadella, le patron de Microsoft, en a conscience et s'interroge sur la l&#233;gitimit&#233; sociale de l'IA....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One UI 8.5 leaks show off Samsung's new Privacy Display feature for phones, and Bixby powered by Perplexity AI</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/samsung-galaxy-phones/one-ui-8-5-leaks-show-off-samsungs-new-privacy-display-feature-for-phones-and-bixby-powered-by-perplexity-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oaRMosUsaqioyvTJZgXZLU</guid>
      <description>A major software update for Samsung phones is on the way, and we just got a preview of two of its new features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un vol spatial tous les deux jours en 2025&#160;: SpaceX bat son propre record de lancements</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/un-vol-spatial-tous-les-deux-jours-en-2025-spacex-bat-son-propre-record-de-lancements.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317836</guid>
      <description>Avec 165 vols spatiaux SpaceX a &#233;tabli un nouveau record en 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG announces the &amp;#8216;world&#8217;s lightest 17-inch RTX laptop&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852628/lg-gram-pro-17-16-laptop-2026-ces</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T08:03:59-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852628</guid>
      <description>LG is teasing the 2026 Gram Pro laptops that will be fully unveiled at CES, including what the company claims is the "world's lightest 17-inch RTX laptop." The LG Gram Pro 17 (17Z90UR) and Gram Pro 16 (16Z90U) will introduce a new ultralight "Aerominum material" developed by LG that aims to reduce a laptop's weight [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fender Audio will introduce a new line of Bluetooth speakers and headphones at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/audio/speakers/fender-audio-will-introduce-a-new-line-of-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-at-ces-130041696.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82c34f82-fb42-4d5f-9eda-38ffa0ada5c0</guid>
      <description>Fender Audio, the consumer electronics arm of the instrument maker, will introduce two flagship audio products at this year's CES in Las Vegas. These products were made under a licensing agreement with Singapore-based company RiffSound.
First up is a line of Bluetooth speakers dubbed the ELIE (Extremely Loud Infinitely Expressive). The lineup includes two models, the E6 and E12. The speakers leverage a combination of DSP and system-on-a-chip processing, which Fender says can deliver more volume while maintaining greater power efficiency.
Each speaker can handle up to four audio channels at onc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to watch Lenovo's Tech World event at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/how-to-watch-lenovos-tech-world-event-at-ces-2026-130004053.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fedcbad-9aca-41b8-93db-45c9330ce965</guid>
      <description>It's been known for months now that technology giant Lenovo is hosting its Tech World event at Sphere in Las Vegas during CES week. Like many other tech conglomerates, the world's largest PC manufacturer by units shipped will put its main focus on AI. Lenovo says it's a "Tech World experience unlike anything CES has seen before." We'll tell you where to livestream the event and what to expect so far.
How to watch the Lenovo CES 2026 event live
Lenovo CEO Yuanqing Yang will host the event on Tuesday, January 6 at 8PM ET. You can follow along to the livestream on YouTube once the event starts. (...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fender&#8217;s first wireless headphones have a long-lasting, replaceable battery</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/850879/fender-mix-wireless-headphones-bluetooth-modular-replaceable-battery</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850879</guid>
      <description>Fender Audio, the consumer electronics brand owned by the famous guitar maker, has announced its first pair of wireless headphones at CES 2026. What sets the Mix headphones apart from the competition are impressive battery life, a modular design that allows the ear cups and headband to be swapped to alternate colors, and a focus [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fender&#8217;s new Bluetooth speakers can play audio from four sources simultaneously</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/850912/fender-audio-elie-bluetooth-portable-wireless-speakers-four-inputs-simultaneous</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=850912</guid>
      <description>Fender, the guitar maker also known for its amps and speakers, has a new consumer electronics brand called Fender Audio making its debut at CES 2026. In addition to a new pair of wireless headphones, Fender Audio has announced a pair of portable Bluetooth speakers called ELIE, which is short for "Extremely Loud Infinitely Expressive." [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to expect at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851165/ces-2026-what-to-expect</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851165</guid>
      <description>The biggest tech show of the year kicks off next week, as some of the industry's top players show up to Las Vegas for CES 2026. We'll be there to see all the new product demos we can and to bring you the most exciting news from the show. Follow our coverage for a preview [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clicks Communicator is a Blackberry for your phone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851298/clicks-communicator-phone-blackberry-keyboard</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851298</guid>
      <description>You ever find yourself thinking, "I wish my phone had a phone?" Good news, friend. Clicks - the company behind the QWERTY keyboard case for your iPhone - has just the thing: the Clicks Communicator. It's intended as a kind of complement to your smartphone for when you just want to stay in touch without [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clicks Power Keyboard is also a backup battery for your phone</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/851368/clicks-power-keyboard-phone-battery</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T08:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851368</guid>
      <description>Clicks is expanding beyond keyboard cases and bringing its QWERTY keys for phones to another format: a magnetic power bank accessory with a slide-out keyboard. The Power Keyboard offers a 2150mAh battery that can top off a phone battery via MagSafe or Qi2 wireless charging, but its real superpower is its full keyboard that can [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clicks debuts its own take on the BlackBerry smartphone, plus a $79 snap-on mobile keyboard</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/01/02/clicks-debuts-its-own-take-on-the-blackberry-smartphone-plus-a-79-snap-on-mobile-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3079405</guid>
      <description>The company behind the add-on mobile keyboards with physical buttons is now doing its own phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single people are more apt to work on Sundays</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91463951/single-people-are-more-often-to-work-on-sundays</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91463951/single-people-are-more-often-to-work-on-sundays</guid>
      <description>Experts say it&#8217;s a maladaptive way to stave off loneliness, which is a broader concern in the workplace.
Singles are drowning their Sunday blues with work, which experts warn isn&#8217;t necessarily the healthiest coping strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla stock price is on the rise today despite gloomy expectations for vehicle deliveries: This could be why</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91468201/tesla-stock-price-today-shares-up-gloomy-deliveries-news-why</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T12:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91468201/tesla-stock-price-today-shares-up-gloomy-deliveries-news-why</guid>
      <description>Tech and AI stocks are generally getting a bump on Friday as we head into the first trading day of 2026. Here&#8217;s the latest.
Shares of Tesla Inc are enjoying a premarket upswing on Friday as they head into their first trading day of 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;Asus Vivobook 14 se d&#233;charge de 150 euros chez Boulanger, mais conserve son autonomie de 29 heures</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925395_lasus-vivobook-14-se-decharge-de-150-euros-chez-boulanger-mais-conserve-son-autonomie-de-29-heures</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2925395_lasus-vivobook-14-se-decharge-de-150-euros-chez-boulanger-mais-conserve-son-autonomie-de-29-heures</guid>
      <description>
L'Asus Vivobook 14 se d&#233;marque gr&#226;ce &#224; une impressionnante batterie capable de tenir 29 heures et chez Boulanger, ce laptop chute &#224; 649,99 euros au lieu de 799,99 euros habituellement.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts warn AI advances could lead to 200,000 banking jobs being cut this year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/experts-warn-ai-advances-could-lead-to-200-000-banking-jobs-being-cut-this-year</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">xgQEVgDSxcYyXbLBZ6M26N</guid>
      <description>European banking workers could be at risk of redundancy due to AI after years of job cuts from store closures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung's new Freestyle+ portable projector nearly doubles the brightness, and makes the image look better on any surface</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/televisions/projectors/samsungs-new-freestyle-portable-projector-nearly-doubles-the-brightness-and-makes-the-image-look-better-on-any-surface</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZStGwUdtSX6qc9ZMj7PQnC</guid>
      <description>Smarter features and bolder images are exactly what Samsung's projector needed needed &#8212; but what about audio and battery power?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Morning After: Instagram boss says &#8216;more practical to fingerprint real media than fake media&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/general/the-morning-after-engadget-newsletter-121544371.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33e144da-1089-44b3-af73-3e7985ba2e1d</guid>
      <description>Instagram&#8217;s top exec Adam Mosseri expects AI content to overtake non-AI imagery and discussed the implications for the platform and users.
Mosseri shared his thoughts on broader trends he expects to shape Instagram in 2026. &#8220;Everything that made creators matter &#8212; the ability to be real, to connect, to have a voice that couldn&#8217;t be faked &#8212; is now suddenly accessible to anyone with the right tools,&#8221; he wrote. &#8220;The feeds are starting to fill up with synthetic everything.&#8221; He added: &#8220;There is already a growing number of people who believe, as I do, that it will be more practical to fingerprint rea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 million fewer vehicles: One year of congestion pricing in New York City</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460609/23-million-fewer-vehicles-one-year-of-congestion-pricing-in-new-york-city</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T12:01:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460609/23-million-fewer-vehicles-one-year-of-congestion-pricing-in-new-york-city</guid>
      <description>Traffic is down, commutes are faster, and air quality has improved in America&#8217;s largest city in the 12 months since the program took effect. 
It&#8217;s been one full year of congestion pricing in New York City, and downtown Manhattan looks markedly different: 23.7 million fewer vehicles, traffic delays down 25%, and a 22% drop in air pollution, to start....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Future of Noise Canceling</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/welcome-to-the-future-of-noise-canceling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6943fb432db3b01570a00563</guid>
      <description>The next generation of noise reduction is currently being developed in R&amp;D labs around the world. Take a look at what's to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Running Shoes, Tested and Reviewed (2026): Saucony, Nike, Hoka</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-running-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">673df4b1904f03a5e578397f</guid>
      <description>We clocked thousands of test miles to bring you the best running shoes for every pace, ability, and running goal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the release date for When Calls the Heart season 13 episode 1 on Hallmark+?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/when-calls-the-heart-season-13-episode-1-release-date-time-hallmark</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SiniEqUeJrXyLKNrLRCst4</guid>
      <description>After a year-long wait, we're finally returning to Hope Valley. When does When Calls the Heart season 13 episode 1 hit Hallmark?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk affirme que la Tesla est num&#233;ro 1 mondiale : les chiffres de Toyota prouvent le contraire (pour le moment)</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2925297_elon-musk-affirme-que-la-tesla-est-numero-1-mondiale-les-chiffres-de-toyota-prouvent-le-contraire-pour-le-moment</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2925297_elon-musk-affirme-que-la-tesla-est-numero-1-mondiale-les-chiffres-de-toyota-prouvent-le-contraire-pour-le-moment</guid>
      <description>
Selon Elon Musk, la Tesla Model Y serait la voiture la plus vendue dans le monde. Mais est-ce r&#233;ellement le cas&#160;? Pas si s&#251;r si on regarde les chiffres de Toyota...
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 2026, corporate purpose will come to a fork in the road</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91458834/in-2026-corporate-purpose-faces-a-fork-in-the-road-corporate-purpose</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-02T11:36:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91458834/in-2026-corporate-purpose-faces-a-fork-in-the-road-corporate-purpose</guid>
      <description>Companies that can connect purpose to the bottom line will gain a competitive advantage. For the rest, the idea will fade into the background.
If 2025 was the year purpose went quiet, 2026 is when the fork in the road will become impossible to ignore. Insights from the Purpose Collaborative, a 40-member network of impact-driven companies, predict what the year ahead will mean for responsible businesses....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
