<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:03:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Planning to see Acer at CES 2026? Here are the three things you don&#8217;t want to miss</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/planning-to-see-acer-at-ces-2026-heres-the-three-things-you-dont-want-to-miss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bSMJdrGUStmeU7QkwDgNFo</guid>
      <description>Acer's updated lineup was on display at CES 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands on at CES 2026: Lenovo debuts two new rollable concept laptops, including one that grows wider</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-lenovo-concept-laptops-thinkpad-rollable-xd-legion-pro-rollable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00l2osI2LhO2rr7qVUJnRya</guid>
      <description>Mashable went hands-on with Lenovo's two new rollable concept laptops at CES 2026: The ThinkPad Rollable XD Concept and the Legion Pro Rollable Concept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ikea Will Soon Sell an Adorable, Tiny, Surprisingly Nice-Sounding Bluetooth Speaker for $10</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/ikea-will-soon-sell-an-adorable-tiny-surprisingly-nice-sounding-bluetooth-speaker-for-10-2000706402</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706402</guid>
      <description>It's called the Kallsup, and up to 100 can be paired for multispeaker audio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame's latest robot vacuum concept has slightly terrifying legs that can climb full-size stairs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/dreames-latest-robot-vacuum-concept-has-slightly-terrifying-legs-that-can-climb-full-size-stairs-210000399.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efe72a0d-8e7e-44a0-8cf7-e8910908c28b</guid>
      <description>Robot vacuum companies are once again out in full force at CES 2026, giving their devices a new set of intriguing &#8212; and sometimes unsettling &#8212; capabilities. This year, Chinese appliance maker Dreame is showing off a vacuum prototype with giant legs that can climb up and down an entire flight of stairs.The concept, called the Cyber X, was previewed last year at IFA in Berlin. The vacuum sports a somewhat terrifying set of legs with rubber treads that allow it to autonomously navigate multi-story environments. While Dreame has previously shown off vacuums that can move up smaller steps, it says ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung and Intel&amp;#8217;s OLED tech makes HDR easier on laptop battery life</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/857229/samsung-display-intel-oled-smartpower-hdr</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:06:12-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=857229</guid>
      <description>Samsung Display and Intel have teamed up on laptop technology called SmartPower HDR that they claim can minimize power usage while you're watching HDR content on an OLED screen. Intel showed off this technology last year, but Samsung Display is sharing details about how it works and the power savings you might expect. However, the [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo just revealed a concept for AI-powered smartglasses at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/lenovo-just-revealed-a-concept-for-ai-powered-smartglasses-at-ces-010057822.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f03c9b8-5cd8-44ab-bb18-bcde61bbda1d</guid>
      <description>Lenovo just revealed a new smartglasses concept design at CES 2026. The appropriately-named Lenovo AI Glasses Concept promises to transform "how users interact with their surroundings and unifies their workflow."
They look like a standard pair of specs and not all that different from something like Meta's Ray-Ban Display glasses. A pair weighs just 45 grams and the battery lasts eight hours, which is just enough time to get through a standard workday.
The glasses are wirelessly tethered to a smart device, which is what does most of the computational heavy lifting. They do include Lenovo and Mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola lance une toute nouvelle gamme encore plus premium&#160;: Motorola Signature</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/motorola-lance-une-toute-nouvelle-gamme-encore-plus-premium-motorola-signature.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317820</guid>
      <description>Motorola annonce la sortie d&#8217;un nouveau smartphone, le Moto G Edge. Premier mod&#232;le de la nouvelle gamme &#171; Signature &#187;, il promet des performances &#233;lev&#233;es tout en conservant finesse et &#233;l&#233;gance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Spins Its Latest ThinkBook Right Round (Like a Record, Baby)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lenovo-spins-its-latest-thinkbook-right-round-like-a-record-baby-2000704127</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704127</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has all new laptops that extend and spin, and one of them is available to actually buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Razr Fold&#160;: le premier smartphone pliant au format livre de la marque est l&#224;</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/motorola-razr-fold-le-premier-smartphone-pliant-au-format-livre-de-la-marque-est-la.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1317816</guid>
      <description>Apr&#232;s le succ&#232;s critique de sa gamme de smartphones &#224; clapet, Motorola franchit une nouvelle &#233;tape et annonce la sortie de son premier smartphone pliant au format livre, le Razr Fold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo updates its Legion and LOQ gaming laptops for CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/lenovo-updates-its-legion-and-loq-gaming-laptops-for-ces-010042509.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">016d9e17-e1aa-46c8-894a-56969bca3cd0</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has brought a slew of updates to its Legion and LOQ line of gaming laptops for CES 2026. The refreshed laptops are all built around Nvidia RTX 50-series GPUs.
The new Legion 7a is both thinner and lighter than the previous generation and is aimed at gamers, creators, and working professionals. Lenovo says the new 7a will be powered by AMD Ryzen AI 400 CPUs and RTX 50-series GPUs, delivering up to 125W of total system power.&#160;
Presumably this means buyers will choose from multiple CPU and GPU configurations, and Lenovo says the 7a will support up to a Ryzen AI 9 HX 470 and up to an RTX 50...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Thinks You Want an Ultrawide Gaming Laptop That Uses a Rollable Screen</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lenovo-thinks-you-want-an-ultrawide-gaming-laptop-that-uses-a-rollable-screen-2000706449</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706449</guid>
      <description>Lenovo's latest concept device takes rollable laptops to their extreme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s Legion Go 2 Now Comes With SteamOS</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lenovo-legion-go-2-now-comes-with-steamos-2000704396</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000704396</guid>
      <description>The biggest, costliest, and most enticing handheld now has a better OS and price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola just announced a foldable phone to rival Samsung and Google at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/motorola-just-announced-a-foldable-phone-to-rival-samsung-and-google-at-ces-010015323.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af6b29f2-bed1-430a-af06-e1562dfc2661</guid>
      <description>Motorola just announced its very first side-foldable smartphone, joining the ranks of the Pixel 10 Pro Fold and the Galaxy Z Fold 7. The Razr Fold boasts an impressive 6.6-inch external screen and an 8.1-inch flexible main display. The company hasn't provided dimensions, so we don't know how thick it is.
We do know, however, that it'll include support for the Moto Pen Ultra stylus. This is actually a fairly big deal, as Samsung dropped the feature for the Z Fold 7. Modern foldables basically double as tablets, so a stylus is always appreciated.
Motorola 
There's a robust camera system here, wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands on at CES 2026: Lenovos voice-controlled twisting laptop arrives</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-lenovo-thinkbook-plus-gen-7-auto-twist-twisting-laptop</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03XoTHRemMOnrTSZt7QNQJc</guid>
      <description>Mashable checked out the Lenovo ThinkBook Plus Gen 7 Auto Twist, a laptop with a twisting screen, at CES 2026. The former concept will hit the market in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s Legion Pro Rollable Gaming Laptop Goes Ultrawide at the Press of a Key</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/lenovo-legion-pro-gaming-laptop-ultrawide-rollable-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695b64ca5d4ddd2d415d9739</guid>
      <description>Lenovo brought a Legion gaming laptop to CES this year with a rollable OLED display that expands horizontally by six inches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Razr Fold Book-Style Foldable: Specs, Details, Release Date</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/motorola-razr-fold-ces-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695c39cbeb8b1b73790d16f6</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, the company also announced a new smartwatch, stylus, Bluetooth tracker, and even a weird AI pendant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola&#8217;s first smartwatch promises 13-day battery life and Polar-powered health tracking</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/851643/moto-watch-android-smarwatch-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=851643</guid>
      <description>At CES, Motorola announced its first smartwatch, the Moto Watch. According to Motorola, the Android watch offers up to 13 days of battery life, alongside Polar-powered health tracking, open-source software, and dual-frequency GPS - a combination that helps set it apart from Apple's and Google's flagship wearables. Battery life is easily its most notable feature. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s Auto Twist laptop is going from concept to real product</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852251/lenovos-auto-twist-laptop-is-going-from-concept-to-real-product</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852251</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Lenovo is announcing a new ThinkBook Plus Gen 7 Auto Twist laptop. Once a concept, the 14-inch thin-and-light sports a motorized pivoting hinge, allowing it to twist and angle its screen toward you. It can be manually controlled, but the real trick is tracking your head and automatically adjusting to your position [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new Lenovo Yoga Pro 9i laptop has a super-bright tandem OLED and magnetic stylus</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852276/the-new-lenovo-yoga-pro-9i-laptop-has-a-super-bright-tandem-oled-and-magnetic-stylus</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852276</guid>
      <description>Lenovo's new pair of Yoga laptops for CES 2026 are its most powerful and most lightweight models. The flagship Yoga Pro 9i is a creator-focused laptop with a 16-inch 4K tandem OLED reaching 1,600 peak nits of brightness, Intel Panther Lake processor options, and up to an RTX 5070 for a discrete GPU. It also [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&amp;#8217;s new concept rollable could be the ideal gaming laptop</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/852352/lenovo-legion-pro-rollable-gaming-laptop-concept-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852352</guid>
      <description>Lenovo is at it again with wild laptop concepts for CES 2026, and the biggest one is the Legion Pro Rollable gaming laptop. It has a flexible OLED display that expands horizontally - as opposed to Lenovo's ThinkBook Plus Gen 6, which rolls up and down. The Legion Pro Rollable's screen goes from a conventional [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This ThinkPad laptop concept has a rollable display that wraps around its lid</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852482/lenovo-thinkpad-rollable-xd-concept-laptop-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852482</guid>
      <description>At CES 2026, Lenovo is announcing yet another new concept laptop with a transforming screen: the ThinkPad Rollable XD Concept. It's a ThinkPad, complete with its iconic red TrackPoint nub, but it features a flexible OLED display that wraps around to the outer part of its lid. Slide your finger along the folded spin of [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s new All-in-One PC can sync its lighting to your notifications</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/852860/lenovo-yoga-aio-i-aura-edition-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=852860</guid>
      <description>If you prefer to have your notifications on silent but don't want to miss anything, Lenovo's new All-in-One (AIO) PC might have a solution. The Yoga AIO i Aura Edition unveiled today at CES features a major design overhaul with a transparent light bar at the bottom of the display. The customizable ambient lighting can [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s joining the bandwagon with concept AI glasses</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853434/ces-2026-lenovo-concept-ai-glasses-wearables</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853434</guid>
      <description>Lenovo is the latest tech company to get bit by the smart glasses bug. The company just showed off a pair of concept AI glasses at CES 2026. While these weren't a working prototype, we have some idea of where Lenovo's head is at. The lightweight frames weigh about 45g and have a 2MP camera [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo&#8217;s second SteamOS handheld is the Legion Go 2</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/853587/lenovo-legion-go-2-steam-os-annoucement-price-release-date</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=853587</guid>
      <description>One year ago, Lenovo became the first company besides Valve to announce a handheld with SteamOS instead of Windows. The result was the Legion Go S with SteamOS; no Steam Deck killer due to price and battery life, but a big step forward in performance and pick-up-and-play portability. Now, Lenovo's doing it again - it's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moto&#8217;s new tracking tag comes with a healthy battery boost</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/855049/moto-tag-2-tracker</link>
      <pubDate>2026-01-06T20:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=855049</guid>
      <description>It's always refreshing when the new version of a product gets significantly better battery life than the last. And that's the case with the Moto Tag 2: Motorola's second-gen tracker tag can go more than 500 days before it needs a new battery. That's almost a year and a half that you can forget about [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Razr Fold is mostly a mystery, but it already outdoes the Samsung Galaxy Fold 7 in one key way</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/phones/motorola-phones/motorola-razr-fold-is-mostly-a-mystery-but-it-already-outdoes-the-galaxy-fold-7-in-one-key-way</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">g5AsBSztahNp8TbJGNbEPC</guid>
      <description>Motorola is unveiling a new, larger flexible phone, the Razr Fold, but questions about specs, pricing, and availability remain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo unveils the AI tools it hopes will supercharge your productivity at work</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/lenovo-unveils-the-ai-tools-it-hopes-will-supercharge-your-productivity-at-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kAKGNByJNsBUnR4M5RFwMG</guid>
      <description>Lenovo's releases for includes an all-new, combined "Qira" AI platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of the SLI: Lenovo's new workstation PC supports up to two RTX 5060 Ti GPUs for AI inference - but I'm more interested in the secretive 1TB AI Fusion Card</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/return-of-the-sli-lenovos-new-workstation-pc-supports-up-to-2-rtx-5060-ti-gpus-for-ai-inference-but-im-more-interested-in-the-secretive-1tb-ai-fusion-card</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">hPn9rRBCVkR2DDGTRMWfUn</guid>
      <description>Lenovo ThinkCentre X Tower supports dual RTX 5060 Ti GPUs, 256GB RAM, and a 1TB AI Fusion Card for inference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first PC with a square screen announced at CES 2026 &#8212; extraordinary ThinkCentre X AIO Aura Edition has 16MP webcam, 28-inch display, and can even be used as a monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/worlds-first-pc-with-a-square-screen-announced-at-ces-2026-extraordinary-thinkcentre-x-aio-aura-edition-has-16mp-webcam-28-inch-display-and-can-even-be-used-as-a-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">iExt3RQcFrUiagRecWzt6X</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s ThinkCentre X AIO Aura Edition combines a square 16:18 display with desktop hardware, prioritizing vertical productivity over traditional widescreen norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo debuts $1,499 convertible laptop that comes with a tongue-twisting name &#8212; ThinkBook Plus Gen 7 Auto Twist rotates and pivots as you move around the room</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/lenovo-debuts-usd1-499-convertible-laptop-that-comes-with-a-tongue-twisting-name-thinkbook-plus-gen-7-auto-twist-rotates-and-pivots-on-two-axes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">vRDtGr8LitkMJ3f2WCoXwY</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s ThinkBook Plus Gen 7 Auto Twist combines a rotating OLED display, Intel Core Ultra hardware, and business-friendly features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo launches the most powerful sub-1kg laptop ever &#8212; ThinkPad X1 Carbon Gen 14 sports a Core Ultra X7 Series 3 CPU and weighs just 996g</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/lenovo-just-launched-the-most-powerful-sub-1kg-laptop-ever-thinkpad-x1-carbon-gen-14-sports-a-core-ultra-x7-series-3-cpu-and-weighs-996g</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">As2ySH22eDnWRgukGRGWHR</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s latest Carbon series laptop features an ultralight design, enhanced thermal efficiency, extensive connectivity, and sustainable materials for modern business professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo releases its most grandiose and powerful ThinkPad laptop ever &#8212; 2TB PCIe 5.0 SSD, six speakers, 10MP webcam, but weighing in at just 1.5Kg!</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/lenovo-releases-its-most-grandiose-and-powerful-thinkpad-laptop-ever-2tb-pcie-5-0-ssd-six-speakers-10mp-webcam-and-just-1-5kg</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">H4eja8dzFSuYkz5a5ZZCJa</guid>
      <description>Lenovo unveils the ThinkPad X9 15p Aura Edition at CES 2026, combining an OLED display, Intel Arc graphics, and advanced features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo adds Copilot Mac Mini rival to Yoga product line &#8212; but I am so disappointed that it didn't revive the Nano M75n, the smallest PC ever</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/lenovo-adds-copilot-mac-mini-rival-to-yoga-product-line-but-i-am-so-disappointed-that-it-didnt-revive-the-nano-m75n-the-smallest-pc-ever</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uzS7BBRjbeT5BAGGkanRcg</guid>
      <description>Lenovo&#8217;s Yoga Mini i is a 600-gram ultra-compact PC with AI Copilot, four display support, 32GB memory, and extensive connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo officially unveils the rumored Legion Pro Rollable gaming laptop with expanding screen</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/gaming-laptops/i-was-one-of-the-first-to-test-lenovos-new-legion-pro-rollable-laptop-im-as-impressed-as-i-am-skeptical</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mtxv5ciVefC7hLxy3nWfaT</guid>
      <description>Lenovo brings a new expandable gaming laptop to the scene, but will it ever see production?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo's 14th-gen ThinkPad X1 Carbon comes with a new Space Frame design</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lenovos-14th-gen-thinkpad-x1-carbon-comes-with-a-new-space-frame-design-010000262.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63dd4a68-3380-48c9-ab18-fb6cd134d29c</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has unveiled a bunch of new laptops and concepts at CES 2026, including its latest ThinkPad X1 models. The ThinkPad X1 Carbon Gen 14 Aura Edition and ThinkPad X1 2-in-1 Gen 11 Aura Edition come with a new design the company has dubbed &#8220;Space Frame.&#8221; Lenovo calls Space Frame an &#8220;engineering breakthrough&#8221; and describes it as a design that restructures the interior of a laptop, so that components are placed on both sides of the motherboard. This structure improves the computer&#8217;s cooling and, hence, enables higher sustained performance. It comes with replaceable USB ports, battery, keyboard...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo reveals a SteamOS variant of the Legion Go 2 at CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/pc/lenovo-reveals-a-steamos-variant-of-the-legion-go-2-at-ces-010000852.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95a8626f-1070-4dec-8605-b9b4660aea54</guid>
      <description>If you saw Lenovo's Legion Go 2 launch last year and thought, "I'll wait for the SteamOS version," well, you'll have to wait a little longer. But at least now it's official. At CES 2026, the company revealed the Legion Go 2, Powered by SteamOS. The Valve-friendly variant of the gaming handheld arrives in June, starting at a pricey $1,199.There aren't any surprises here. It's the same Lenovo Legion Go 2 hardware, with SteamOS replacing the sometimes-awkward Windows. In many ways, you could view the SteamOS Legion Go 2 as a more powerful and versatile (and expensive!) Steam Deck. One notable exc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: The Lenovo ThinkBook Plus Gen 7 Auto Twist won't let you out of it sight</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/ces-2026-the-lenovo-thinkbook-plus-gen-7-auto-twist-wont-let-you-out-of-it-sight-010000913.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69534102-2569-4e3e-84b0-164c87efbd97</guid>
      <description>A couple years ago Lenovo showed off a concept laptop stand that used cameras and AI to follow you around. But now at CES 2026, the company has taken that idea and turned it into a full-fledged system that it&#8217;s actually going to sell.&#160;Dubbed the ThinkBook Plus Gen 7 Auto Twist, instead of a laptop stand, Lenovo created a standalone notebook with the same functionality, plus a little more. The impressive thing is that despite having a built-in motor that lets its display follow you around, the laptop&#8217;s design doesn't look all that outlandish. And after playing around with it a bit, I discovered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola expands its Moto Things lineup with a new Bluetooth tracker, stylus and smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/smartphones/motorola-expands-its-moto-things-lineup-with-a-new-bluetooth-tracker-stylus-and-smartwatch-010000669.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebd83f19-6706-460e-9c60-e13d8a1eb3b3</guid>
      <description>After kicking off its Moto Things accessory line with wireless earbuds, a Bluetooth tracker and a cheap smartwatch in 2024, Motorola is doubling down. At CES 2026, the company is announcing a sequel to its tracker, the Moto Tag 2, a stylus for its new folding phone, the Moto Pen Ultra and a more premium smartwatch called the Moto Watch.The Moto Watch has a 47mm round face with a stainless steel crown and an aluminum frame. The smartwatch comes with a PANTONE "Volcanic Ash" silicone band, but is designed to support third-party 22mm bands, too, which greatly expands its customization options. Mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo and Motorola are releasing their own on-device AI assistant</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/lenovo-and-motorola-are-releasing-their-own-on-device-ai-assistant-010000696.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18960e9d-8982-4aef-82bb-83aeba452a12</guid>
      <description>If the world didn't already have one too many digital assistants, Lenovo is adding another one to the pile. On Tuesday evening, the company announced Qira, a cross-device AI for both its own computers and Motorola smartphones. Set to arrive later this quarter, it will live at the system level of Lenovo devices. Users won't need to open or switch to the assistant. Instead, "it's always present," says Lenovo.&#160;&#160;&#160;Of course, you can ignore Qira, and it will stay quiet if you don't need the software to do anything for you. Occasionally, Lenovo says Qira will surface proactive suggestions, and for fr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo goes sci-fi with its wild XD Rollable Concept at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/lenovo-goes-sci-fi-with-its-wild-xd-rollable-concept-at-ces-2026-010000817.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11ebd211-6af0-4f43-9e46-6f10a571ddd0</guid>
      <description>Lenovo has experimented more with laptops featuring rollable displays than pretty much any other PC maker and at CES 2026 it&#8217;s keeping that trend going with the XD Rollable Concept.Equipped with a 180-degree Gorilla Glass Victus 2 cover, the XD Rollable concept features a very futuristic design. However, underneath, it has the same basic engineering as last year&#8217;s ThinkBook Plus Gen 6. That means with the touch of a button, its 13.3-inch flexible OLED display can expand to 16 inches, which gives you around 50 percent extra screen space in just a few seconds. The main difference with Lenovo&#8217;s l...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: The Lenovo Legion Pro Rollable concept goes big wide at the touch of a button</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/computing/laptops/ces-2026-the-lenovo-legion-pro-rollable-concept-goes-big-wide-at-the-touch-of-a-button-010000333.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">236ea539-52b7-4f06-8924-01ecd14d4b19</guid>
      <description>Lenovo might have the most concept devices of any company at CES 2026, but the wildest and most interesting one is almost certainly the Legion Pro Rollable which features a 16-inch flexible display that can expand to not one but two different sizes.&#160;To make the Legion Pro Rollable, Lenovo started out with a standard Legion Pro 7i and kept the bottom half including all of its ports and support for an RTX 5090 GPU. But then the company went a bit crazy: Instead of replacing the notebook&#8217;s original 16-inch OLED screen with a rollable variant that extends upwards like the Thinkbook Plus Gen 6 from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola is entering the wearable AI game</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-motorola-entering-wearable-ai</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05mdFHIO1G358LC0aImVgSl</guid>
      <description>Motorola unveiled a proof of concept wearable AI as part of its AI living ecosystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo debuts a concept no-charging keyboard and mouse combo at CES 2026</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/lenovo-solar-charging-keyboard-mouse-ces-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02fUe4gkraefssPHYfORsnk</guid>
      <description>For CES 2026, Lenovo is showing off a new solar-charging keyboard and mouse combo that offers a "no-charging" experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorola s&#8217;allie &#224; Polar pour sa nouvelle montre connect&#233;e : une r&#233;volution pour votre suivi sportif ?</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2931945_motorola-sallie-a-polar-pour-sa-nouvelle-montre-connectee-une-revolution-pour-votre-suivi-sportif</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2931945_motorola-sallie-a-polar-pour-sa-nouvelle-montre-connectee-une-revolution-pour-votre-suivi-sportif</guid>
      <description>
Motorola profite du CES 2026 pour d&#233;voiler sa nouvelle &#171; Moto Watch &#187;, un mod&#232;le qui marque un tournant gr&#226;ce &#224; un partenariat avec Polar.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus fort que l&#8217;iPhone Air ? Motorola d&#233;voile le Signature, le smartphone ultra-fin qui ne sacrifie rien</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2932003_plus-fort-que-liphone-air-motorola-devoile-le-signature-le-smartphone-ultra-fin-qui-ne-sacrifie-rien</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2932003_plus-fort-que-liphone-air-motorola-devoile-le-signature-le-smartphone-ultra-fin-qui-ne-sacrifie-rien</guid>
      <description>
&#192; l'occasion du CES 2026, Motorola d&#233;voile son mod&#232;le Signature. Ce smartphone inaugure une nouvelle gamme ultra-premium qui mise sur une finesse extr&#234;me de 6,99 mm sans pour autant sacrifier l'&#233;quipement photographique ni l'autonomie.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adieu Samsung ? Motorola d&#233;voile son Razr Fold, un g&#233;ant qui veut d&#233;tr&#244;ner le Galaxy Z Fold</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2931981_motorola-razr-fold-le-premier-pliant-format-livre-de-la-marque-arrive-pour-bousculer-samsung-et-google</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/motorola/2931981_motorola-razr-fold-le-premier-pliant-format-livre-de-la-marque-arrive-pour-bousculer-samsung-et-google</guid>
      <description>
Motorola a profit&#233; du CES 2026 pour officialiser son tout premier smartphone pliable au format livre : le Motorola Razr Fold, un appareil qui entend bien s'imposer face aux r&#233;f&#233;rences de chez Samsung et Google.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crazy Geniuses at Shokz Gave Open Earbuds Noise Cancellation</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-crazy-geniuses-at-shokz-gave-open-earbuds-noise-cancellation-2000706427</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706427</guid>
      <description>The OpenFit Pro have what Shokz is calling "noise reduction," and the effect is similar to ANC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lego Smart Brick Hands-On: The Unknown Play Experience Is a Feature, Not a Flaw</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lego-smart-brick-hands-on-the-unknown-play-experience-is-the-whole-point-2000705996</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000705996</guid>
      <description>I think Lego might be really onto something with its tech-equipped Smart Play Smart Brick sets, but is it the future of Lego sets?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame's robot vacuum with an arm is back at CES 2026 and it can do more than pick up shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/home/smart-home/dreames-robot-vacuum-with-an-arm-is-back-at-ces-2026-and-it-can-do-more-than-pick-up-shoes-210000020.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48f39b83-a16b-4998-91b7-41d31eb4145a</guid>
      <description>Last year at CES, Dreame showed off a robot vacuum prototype with a mechanical arm. But while we were able to see the arm extend and retract, we didn&#8217;t see the device, which was described as a prototype at the time, actually grab anything, which was a bit disappointing.This year, though, the company has made its arm-enabled vacuum a reality with the Cyber 10 Ultra. Dreame previewed it recently at IFA in Berlin, but has now confirmed it will be on sale later this year.&#160;The vacuum has an extendable arm that looks pretty similar to the prototype version we saw last year. It extends from the top o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPolish brings color-changing press-on smart nails to CES</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wearables/ipolish-brings-color-changing-press-on-smart-nails-to-ces-001345407.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">780c33de-5d8a-4bd7-aca5-dbd5f5358db5</guid>
      <description>In the original, and best Total Recall, there&#8217;s a scene where Rekall&#8217;s receptionist uses a digital pen to change the color of her nail polish. It&#8217;s only taken 35 years, but now a company has turned up to CES 2026 with a version that actually works outside a pricey sci-fi movie. iPolish is a company which makes press-on acrylic nails that, when you apply an electric charge, changes color.In order to enjoy kaleidoscopic nails, you&#8217;ll need to charge the wand, which then connects to your phone. Once you&#8217;ve selected your color of choice, you just put the tip of the nail into the wand, and it&#8217;ll pas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Could Get a 4-Year Ban on Toys With AI Chatbots</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/california-could-get-a-4-year-ban-on-toys-with-ai-chatbots-2000706416</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000706416</guid>
      <description>"Our children cannot be used as lab rats for Big Tech to experiment on," said the state senator who introduced new legislation around AI toys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2026: TCLs RayNeo Air 4 Pro smart glasses have a killer HDR display &#8212; and a killer low price</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/ces-2026-tcl-rayneo-air-4-pro-smart-glasses</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06DiqOAzUHL9W0U4OTQmMGj</guid>
      <description>Smart glasses have been one of the top categories at CES 2026, and Mashable's Tech Editor tried the yet-to-be-released TCL RayNeo Air 4 Pro AR glasses.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
