<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:29:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark scraps controversial VPN ban proposal after public backlash</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/denmark-scraps-controversial-vpn-ban-proposal-after-public-backlash</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PMpKF5rdndc2peWHnND6BM</guid>
      <description>Just days after proposing a bill that would have made it illegal to use a VPN to bypass geoblocking, the Danish government has reversed its position following a wave of criticism from digital rights groups and the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House wants to poach tech giants' best workers -  new "Tech Force" looks to up the US government's tech skills</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/the-white-house-wants-to-poach-tech-giants-best-workers-new-tech-force-looks-to-up-the-us-governments-tech-skills</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ceWGn23Jvhz9EUNfpCNgD</guid>
      <description>A number of private sector companies have already signed up to  "Tech Force" US government tech talent acquisition scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Avatar: Fire and Ash&#8217; Is Completely Insane in the Best Possible Way</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/avatar-fire-and-ash-movie-review-james-cameron-2000694265</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000694265</guid>
      <description>James Cameron's new film, starring Sam Worthington, Zoe Salda&#241;a, Sigourney Weaver, and Stephen Lang, is in theaters December 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ d&#233;barque dans le casque Meta Quest, mais pas (encore) pour vous</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/disney-debarque-dans-le-casque-meta-quest-mais-pas-encore-pour-vous.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315604</guid>
      <description>La plateforme de streaming Disney+ et le g&#233;ant Meta s&#8217;associent pour rendre disponible le contenu Disney+ sur le casque de r&#233;alit&#233; virtuelle Meta Quest. Cette application est uniquement disponible aux &#201;tats-Unis pour le moment. Un d&#233;ploiement &#224; l&#8217;international est attendu d&#233;but 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Fallout&#8217; Season 2 Is a Slower, Smarter Follow-Up</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/fallout-season-2-review-amazon-prime-video-2000699991</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000699991</guid>
      <description>The sophomore season of Prime Video's smash-hit gaming adaptation doesn't fix what isn't broken, for better and occasionally worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Giant Redesigns Its Iconic Classic Full Zip Hoodie</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/american-giant-redesign-classic-full-zip-hoodie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693cbdedf505766918f42248</guid>
      <description>The refreshed Classic Full Zip hoodie uses a softer cotton fleece, but it&#8217;s still US-made. It&#8217;s the first major overhaul of American Giant&#8217;s most well-loved sweatshirt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avatar: Fire and Ash is a gorgeous spectacle of titanic proportions</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/844731/avatar-fire-and-ash-review</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844731</guid>
      <description>In the almost 20 years since James Cameron first introduced us to the alien world of Pandora, 20th Century Studios has repeatedly tried to parlay the Avatar films' financial success into a sprawling multimedia franchise. Almost immediately after the first movie hit theaters, there was a video game, plans for a book series that never [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout&#8217;s goofy apocalypse gets serious in season 2</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/844926/fallout-season-2-review-amazon-prime-video</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844926</guid>
      <description>The most impressive thing about Fallout's first season was how well it nailed the tone. The games are a mix of grim and goofy, a postapocalyptic story in a bleak world that's also full of crude jokes and ridiculous characters. It's a tough balance to get right - too serious and it's a miserable place [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#8217;ve been waiting years for Animal Crossing&#8217;s best new features</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/games/845242/animal-crossing-new-horizons-3-0-update-switch-2-edition-features</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T09:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845242</guid>
      <description>I never felt done with my Animal Crossing: New Horizons island. Despite playing every day for two years, and racking up 1,700 hours of playtime, I somehow never finished decorating. I had plenty of ideas for my island, sure, but actually implementing them was another story: The decorating and terraforming systems that helped make New [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Firefly now supports prompt-based video editing, adds more third-party models</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/adobe-firefly-now-supports-prompt-based-video-editing-adds-more-third-party-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076352</guid>
      <description>Adobe is updating its AI video-generation app, Firefly, with a new video editor that supports precise prompt-based edits, as well as adding new third-party models for image and video generation, including Black Forest Labs' FLUX.2 and Topaz Astra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avatar: Fire and Ash is just a flame-filled version of The Way of Water &#8212; are we ready to admit that the franchise is getting boring?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/entertainment/avatar-fire-and-ash-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HFeHz6fQ3tnQhMh5hE6geK</guid>
      <description>I'm tired of pretending films like Avatar: Fire and Ash are interesting just because their visual craft is impeccable... and we've seen this particular film before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is fixing a huge problem with a nifty Windows 11 security feature that polices app installations</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/windows/microsoft-is-fixing-a-huge-problem-with-a-nifty-windows-11-security-feature-that-polices-app-installations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8AvZxQNPjkGX3329osox3G</guid>
      <description>Windows 11 has a powerful security feature you may not have heard of &#8211; and I'm glad to see Microsoft is fixing its most baffling drawback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avatar Fire and Ash review: Maybe it's time to sunset Pandora</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/avatar-fire-and-ash-review-maybe-its-time-to-sunset-pandora-140000997.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8baa1046-8280-4340-b4d2-00912f1b5ab1</guid>
      <description>No matter what you think of James Cameron's Avatar movies,&#160;their technical ambitions are undeniable. Cameron developed his own camera system to shoot the first Avatar in 3D, but since most of the actors were digitally captured, he also had the freedom to construct scenes with a virtual camera after they were physically shot. For Avatar: The Way of Water, which arrived a whopping 13 years after the first film, Cameron also leaned into high frame rate footage and new ways of modeling natural fluid dynamics.&#160;Even though the third entry, Avatar: Fire and Ash, is coming just a few years after the l...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz CLA first drive: Head of the EV class</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/evs/mercedes-benz-cla-first-drive-head-of-the-ev-class-140000562.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23ce3709-a8ec-4bef-b82f-2be57c151008</guid>
      <description>This one's been a long time coming. Mercedes-Benz has been researching, refining and even reshaping the car that would ultimately be the CLA for years now, teasing us with technical briefings and even showing off a sultry crimson concept car a full two years ago.That was the Concept CLA, and while the production CLA you see here doesn't look quite that good, it is a fine-looking little electric sedan. More importantly, it goes as far as you'd think its slippery, 0.21-coefficient-of-drag body would carry it: up to 374 miles on a charge.With a $47,250 starting price, is this electric CLA the com...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout Season 2 review: Viva New Vegas</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/entertainment/tv-movies/fallout-season-2-review-viva-new-vegas-140000678.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd50a255-8599-4120-8bb3-15cc63ea84bb</guid>
      <description>The follow-up to a successful debut is often harder to make than the first, and that goes double when the inspiration for a show comes from the most beloved installment of the underlying franchise. That's precisely the challenge Fallout season 2 is facing as the TV series shifts its stage to the irradiated lights of New Vegas when the series returns on December 16 at 9PM ET/6PM PT on Prime Video. However, while other video game adaptations like The Last of Us suffered from a bit of a sophomore slump, Fallout continues to get more crass, vulgar and abrasive in the most entertaining ways.&#160;Editor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo raises $35M to secure the enterprise cloud's base layer &#8212; container images &#8212; with autonomous AI agents</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/security/echo-raises-usd35m-to-secure-the-enterprise-clouds-base-layer-container</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7Mn0wjQxu6Ra9wmNSjQKEJ</guid>
      <description>As enterprises accelerate the deployment of LLMs and agentic workflows, they are hitting a critical infrastructure bottleneck: the container base images powering these applications are riddled with inherited security debt. Echo, an Israeli startup, is announcing a $35 million in Series A funding today (bringing its to-date total to $50 million in funding) to fix this by fundamentally reimagining how cloud infrastructure is built.The round was led by N47, with participation from Notable Capital, Hyperwise Ventures, and SentinelOne. But the real story isn't the capital&#8212;it's the company&#8217;s ambitio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zencoder drops Zenflow, a free AI orchestration tool that pits Claude against OpenAI&#8217;s models to catch coding errors</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-drops-zenflow-a-free-ai-orchestration-tool-that-pits-claude-against</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20DWZsg3jqHAtKkRUEddUc</guid>
      <description>Zencoder, the Silicon Valley startup that builds AI-powered coding agents, released a free desktop application on Monday that it says will fundamentally change how software engineers interact with artificial intelligence &#8212; moving the industry beyond the freewheeling era of "vibe coding" toward a more disciplined, verifiable approach to AI-assisted development.The product, called Zenflow, introduces what the company describes as an "AI orchestration layer" that coordinates multiple AI agents to plan, implement, test, and review code in structured workflows. The launch is Zencoder's most ambitio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom says it aced AI&#8217;s hardest exam. Critics say it copied off its neighbors.</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/ai/zoom-says-it-aced-ais-hardest-exam-critics-say-it-copied-off-its-neighbors</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4JJiDuZiE9q73MnqOznPlZ</guid>
      <description>Zoom Video Communications, the company best known for keeping remote workers connected during the pandemic, announced last week that it had achieved the highest score ever recorded on one of artificial intelligence's most demanding tests &#8212; a claim that sent ripples of surprise, skepticism, and genuine curiosity through the technology industry.The San Jose-based company said its AI system scored 48.1 percent on the Humanity's Last Exam, a benchmark designed by subject-matter experts worldwide to stump even the most advanced AI models. That result edges out Google's Gemini 3 Pro, which held the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 91% accuracy, open source Hindsight agentic memory provides 20/20 vision for AI agents stuck on failing RAG</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/data/with-91-accuracy-open-source-hindsight-agentic-memory-provides-20-20-vision</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1nEV8IRNDg4gFeYC7HeoF7</guid>
      <description>It has become increasingly clear in 2025 that retrieval augmented generation (RAG) isn't enough to meet the growing data requirements for agentic AI.RAG emerged in the last couple of years to become the default approach for connecting LLMs to external knowledge. The pattern is straightforward: chunk documents, embed them into vectors, store them in a database, and retrieve the most similar passages when queries arrive. This works adequately for one-off questions over static documents. But the architecture breaks down when AI agents need to operate across multiple sessions, maintain context ove...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon brade &#224; moiti&#233; prix son r&#233;veil connect&#233; et assure m&#234;me la livraison avant No&#235;l</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2816345_amazon-brade-a-moitie-prix-son-reveil-connecte-et-assure-meme-la-livraison-avant-noel</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2816345_amazon-brade-a-moitie-prix-son-reveil-connecte-et-assure-meme-la-livraison-avant-noel</guid>
      <description>
L'Echo Spot d'Amazon est plus qu'une enceinte Bluetooth, c'est un assistant du quotidien avec Alexa que vous retrouvez pour 49,99 euros au lieu de 94,99 euros sur Amazon.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How too much collaboration destroys creativity&#8212;and how to fix that</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91450306/how-too-much-collaboration-destroys-creativity-and-how-to-fix-that-creativity-collaboration-advice</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T13:46:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91450306/how-too-much-collaboration-destroys-creativity-and-how-to-fix-that-creativity-collaboration-advice</guid>
      <description>What&#8217;s needed is a balance of individual thinking, group critique, and rest.
I have a confession to make.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China approves two level-3 autonomous EVs</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/transportation/china-approves-two-level-3-autonomous-evs-134548316.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f0bb11f-c532-4017-922c-30a4fb69edb7</guid>
      <description>China has taken another step forward in the self-driving car market. The country's Ministry of Industry and Information Technology (MIIT) has made its first approval for cars with level-3 autonomous driving capabilities. The two electric sedans come from state-owned automakers Changan Auto and BAIC Motor.
The US National Highway Transportation Safety Administration (NHTSA) defines level-3 driving as "the system handles all aspects of the driving task while you, as the driver, are available to take over driving if requested. If the system can no longer operate and prompts the driver, the driver...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: Fate of the Old Republic director Casey Hudson says not to worry, the game will be out before 2030 &#8212; 'Game will be out before then. I&#8217;m not getting any younger!'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/star-wars-fate-of-the-old-republic-director-casey-hudson-says-not-to-worry-the-game-will-be-out-before-2030-game-will-be-out-before-then-im-not-getting-any-younger</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jQUi9KmKzMqFkb8uHuWPjH</guid>
      <description>Following speculation online, Star Wars: Fate of the Old Republic director Casey Hudson has assured fans that the game will be released before 2030.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus d&#233;voile un &#233;cran gaming d&#8217;un nouveau genre, mais vous ne pourrez peut &#234;tre pas en profiter</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2911327_asus-devoile-le-premier-ecran-5k-dual-mode-au-monde-mais-vous-ne-pourrez-peut-etre-pas-en-profiter</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/asus/2911327_asus-devoile-le-premier-ecran-5k-dual-mode-au-monde-mais-vous-ne-pourrez-peut-etre-pas-en-profiter</guid>
      <description>
Asus vient d'annoncer un &#233;cran Dual Mode &#224; la fiche technique encore jamais vue pour convenir &#224; toutes les cat&#233;gories de jeux sur PC.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Best White Elephant Gifts (2025): Coffee Pot Mug, Legos, Sushi Magnets, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-white-elephant-gifts-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">671f0007dc407fd8b5892976</guid>
      <description>Bring the gift everyone will want to win from this year's holiday party, from a cute jacket for a beer can to magnets they'll wish they could eat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Tesla Cybertruck sacr&#233; champion de la s&#233;curit&#233; : un tour de force qui surprend autant qu&#8217;il interroge</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2911575_le-tesla-cybertruck-sacre-champion-de-la-securite-un-tour-de-force-qui-surprend-autant-quil-interroge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/marques/tesla/2911575_le-tesla-cybertruck-sacre-champion-de-la-securite-un-tour-de-force-qui-surprend-autant-quil-interroge</guid>
      <description>
Contre toute attente, le Tesla Cybertruck vient de d&#233;crocher la distinction Top Safety Pick+ de l'IIHS, une premi&#232;re pour un v&#233;hicule 100 % &#233;lectrique dans cette cat&#233;gorie. Une cons&#233;cration qui repositionne le pick-up futuriste dans le d&#233;bat, mais qui ne fait pas tout oublier pour autant.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racks of AI chips are too damn heavy</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/844966/heavy-ai-data-center-buildout</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T08:30:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=844966</guid>
      <description>In the span of a decade and a half, from 2010 to the end of 2024, the number of data centers in the US quadrupled. The trend is similar worldwide: more data centers, bigger, now or soon. The number of the construction projects of centers over 100 megawatts announced over the last four years total [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming U.S. jobs report, delayed by government shutdown, will likely show sluggish hiring</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461216/upcoming-u-s-jobs-report-delayed-government-shutdown-likely-show-sluggish-hiring</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T13:28:49</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461216/upcoming-u-s-jobs-report-delayed-government-shutdown-likely-show-sluggish-hiring</guid>
      <description>According to data firm FactSet, the report for November is expected to show that employers added an unimpressive 40,000 jobs to the U.S. economy. 
The U.S. job market is sluggish and confusing this fall.American companies are mostly holding onto the employees they have. But they&#8217;re reluctant to hire new ones as they struggle to assess how to use artificial intelligence and how to adjust to President Donald Trump&#8217;s unpredictable policies, especially his double-digit taxes on imports from around the world.The uncertainty leaves jobseekers struggling to find work or even land interviews. Federal ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetris takes to the skies &#8211; watch 2,800 drones create a playable version of the world&#8217;s favorite puzzle game over Dubai</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/cameras/drones/tetris-takes-to-the-skies-watch-2-800-drones-create-a-playable-version-of-the-worlds-favorite-puzzle-game-over-dubai</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5T3mRkgk5nzbZb9kMzadaL</guid>
      <description>Red Bull hosted a Tetris tournament brought to life by 2,800 illuminated drones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce says it's OK with losing money on AI agents - for now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/salesforce-says-its-ok-with-losing-money-on-ai-agents-for-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cq3rnRuX7KYCDVpN2fBYaF</guid>
      <description>Customers love flat, seat-based AI agent pricing, so Salesforce sees great monetization opportunities ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 prompts to really get the most out of the new ChatGPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/5-prompts-to-really-get-the-most-out-of-the-new-chatgpt-5-2</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">io6BHD2ryKB3hxsgxK7R3i</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT-5.2&#8217;s improved reasoning, memory, and conversational control make it feel more like a helpful collaborator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejoignez-nous pour l&#8217;avant-premi&#232;re des Frandroid Awards 2025 et d&#233;couvrez notre court-m&#233;trage in&#233;dit</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2911267_rejoingnez-nous-pour-lavant-premiere-des-frandroid-awards-2025-et-decouvrez-notre-court-metrage-inedit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/humanoid/emissions/2911267_rejoingnez-nous-pour-lavant-premiere-des-frandroid-awards-2025-et-decouvrez-notre-court-metrage-inedit</guid>
      <description>
Une fois n&#8217;est pas coutume, l&#8217;&#233;quipe de Frandroid vous donne rendez-vous non pas le mercredi &#224; 17h, mais ce mardi 16 d&#233;cembre, &#224; la m&#234;me heure, pour d&#233;couvrir en avant-premi&#232;re notre court-m&#233;trage YouTube des Frandroid Awards 2025. Tout simplement in&#233;dit.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla&#8217;s new CEO is doubling down on an AI future for Firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/845216/mozilla-ceo-anthony-enzor-demeo</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T08:15:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=845216</guid>
      <description>Mozilla is in a tricky position. It contains both a nonprofit organization dedicated to making the internet a better place for everyone, and a for-profit arm dedicated to, you know, making money. In the best of times, these things feed each other: The company makes great products that advance its goals for the web, and [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox maker Mozilla appoints new CEO to navigate it through its AI era</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91461183/firefox-maker-mozilla-appoints-new-ceo-to-navigate-it-through-its-ai-era</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T13:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91461183/firefox-maker-mozilla-appoints-new-ceo-to-navigate-it-through-its-ai-era</guid>
      <description>&#8220;The browser is AI&#8217;s next battleground,&#8221; says Anthony Enzor-DeMeo, who will aim to turn Mozilla into the &#8220;world&#8217;s most trusted software company.&#8221;
The Mozilla Corporation, maker of the popular Firefox web browser, has announced the appointment of a new CEO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mise en avant par Google, cette extension Chrome espionne vos conversations avec ChatGPT, Gemini et 8 autres IA</title>
      <link>https://www.01net.com/actualites/mise-avant-google-extension-chrome-espionne-conversations-chatgpt-gemini-8-autres-ia.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.01net.com/?p=1315595</guid>
      <description>Une extension Chrome malveillante a &#233;t&#233; d&#233;busqu&#233;e. Recommand&#233;e par Google, elle siphonne en douce les conversations d&#8217;IA de millions d'internautes. L'extension est taill&#233;e pour les &#233;changes sur des chatbots comme ChatGPT, Gemini ou Perplexity. Elle enfreint les r&#232;gles &#233;dict&#233;es par Google pour prot&#233;ger les donn&#233;es de ses utilisateurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AirPods Pro 3 are $40 off right now on Amazon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/deals/the-airpods-pro-3-are-40-off-right-now-on-amazon-222806233.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42f7f263-d7c8-4a21-ad07-9121207a6244</guid>
      <description>If you haven't yet upgraded to Apple's AirPods Pro 3, you can pick up the company's latest model at a discount through a deal on Amazon right now. The AirPods Pro 3, which came out in September, are currently down to $210. That's $40 off and only $10 more than the record-low price we saw last week. The Pro 3s have been fluctuating in price since Black Friday, with the lowest they've been being $199 for a brief period. With the new AirPods Pro, Apple made some big improvements, including better battery life and sound quality, and introduced useful new features, such as Live Translation.


The A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone's new smart home router can even tell you when your family gets home</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/vodafones-new-smart-home-router-can-even-tell-you-when-your-family-gets-home</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KzWNxBVrNpUd69sRmBU6v6</guid>
      <description>'Who's Home' turns Vodafone's Ultra Hub 7 into a home security tool to check who's connected to the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has &#8216;Godzilla X Kong: Supernova&#8217; Found Its Big New Villain?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/godzilla-x-kong-supernova-villain-spacegodzilla-2000700058</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000700058</guid>
      <description>Plus, Nia DaCosta teases Dr. Kelson's 'quite weird' turn in '28 Years Later: The Bone Temple'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Best Office Chairs of 2025&#8212; I&#8217;ve Tested Nearly 60 to Pick Them</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-office-chairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">607895413c4558580f4abffa</guid>
      <description>Sitting at a desk for hours? Upgrade your WFH setup and work in style with these comfy WIRED-tested seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear startup Last Energy raises $100M for its steel-encased micro reactor</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/16/nuclear-startup-last-energy-raises-100m-for-its-steel-encased-micro-reactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3076244</guid>
      <description>Last Energy will use the funds to build its 5 megawatt pilot reactor in Texas, which it hopes to turn on next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 6 best Christmas movies I&#8217;m streaming on Disney Plus, Prime Video and more this December</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/streaming/the-6-best-christmas-movies-im-streaming-on-disney-plus-prime-video-and-more-this-december</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cxDcZkHyAJHRzFMwfEc8uN</guid>
      <description>These are the best 6 Christmas movies ever made. Disagree? Have your say in our poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divinity: Original Sin 2 for modern consoles is free for old fans</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/divinity-original-sin-2-for-modern-consoles-is-free-for-old-fans-130000192.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e8ce152-8060-4872-92d2-fafb2169e38b</guid>
      <description>The definitive version of Divinity: Original Sin 2, the sequel to Original Sin first released back in 2017, is now available for the PS5, Nintendo Switch 2 and Xbox X|S. The role-playing game was developed by Larian Studios, the same company that developed Baldur&#8217;s Gate 3. To be clear, the game&#8217;s new release isn&#8217;t a remake or even a remaster &#8212; it&#8217;s just a port for new consoles so that old and new fans alike can enjoy the game without having to bust out their previous-gen devices. Fans who already own a copy of the game can even get it for free. Original Sin 2 is the fifth main entry in the Div...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: Weight Watchers&#8217;s big rebrand is a bid to win the Ozempic era</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91460343/inside-weight-watchers-rebrand-for-ozempic-era</link>
      <pubDate>2025-12-16T13:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91460343/inside-weight-watchers-rebrand-for-ozempic-era</guid>
      <description>We sat down with new Weight Watchers CEO Tara Comonte, chief experience officer (and SoulCycle cofounder) Julie Rice, and the team behind the new brand to hear about how they&#8217;re rebuilding the company into a digital powerhouse that&#8217;s focused on holistic health (and yes, GLP-1s).
Weight-loss giant Weight Watchers is relaunching itself for the Ozempic era. Six months after completing a Chapter 11 restructuring, the company is rolling out a revamped app and digital platform, a reimagined digital coaching experience, and a new brand identity....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a cheap coffee maker? I'm a trained barista and these are my three top recommendations</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/coffee-machines/looking-for-a-cheap-coffee-maker-im-a-trained-barista-and-these-are-my-three-top-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K7Vph8Q5UaeRBZR48eqdTh</guid>
      <description>The cost of takeout coffee has rocketed, so pick up one of these excellent budget brewers and save cash by making your own at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Maps just got a big upgrade for your skiing trip &#8211; and it&#8217;s all thanks to a backlash from snowsports lovers</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/software/google-maps-just-got-a-big-upgrade-for-your-skiing-trip-and-its-all-thanks-to-a-backlash-from-snowsports-lovers</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">zn6Hn2bQ84LmNHyaNMAkih</guid>
      <description>Ski trails, lodge markers, and lifts have returned to Google Maps &#8211; and these are the resorts that are currently available to view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockstar says that the IWGB union 'have no idea who was in this Discord' as the GTA 6 developer continues to claim that the firings of former devs were over leaks of 'specific game features'</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/gaming-industry/rockstar-says-that-the-iwgb-union-have-no-idea-who-was-in-this-discord-as-the-gta-6-developer-continues-to-claim-that-the-firings-of-former-devs-were-over-leaks-of-specific-game-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MuvjQgnMgc9S74sBSPvMXh</guid>
      <description>Rockstar Games has once again addressed accusations of union-busting from the Independent Workers Union of Great Britain (IWGB), claiming that it fired over 30 Grand Theft Auto 6 developers for sharing company secrets in a Discord channel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pok&#233;mon TCG Mega Venusaur ex Premium Collection is over $30 cheaper at TCGplayer vs. Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-16-pokemon-tcg-mega-venusaur-ex-premium-collection-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">015Rr4cNk1d7fwQeqvvZuDr</guid>
      <description>TCGplayer is selling the Mega Venusaur ex Premium Collection for $46.39, $31.60 less than Amazon at $77.99. I don't need to tell you which one is the better deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple d&#233;ploie la b&#234;ta d&#8217;iOS 26.3 : voici les deux nouveaut&#233;s importantes</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/os/ios/2911739_apple-deploie-la-beta-dios-26-3-voici-les-deux-nouveautes-importantes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/os/ios/2911739_apple-deploie-la-beta-dios-26-3-voici-les-deux-nouveautes-importantes</guid>
      <description>
D'habitude, une mise &#224; jour d'iOS sert &#224; vous garder dans l'&#233;cosyst&#232;me. Avec la b&#234;ta d'iOS 26.3 sortie ce lundi, Apple fait exactement l'inverse : elle vous offre une porte de sortie native vers Android.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash sale &#8212; get $35 off a refurbished PS5 at Back Market for a limited time</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/ps5/flash-sale-get-usd35-off-a-refurbished-ps5-at-back-market-for-a-limited-time</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">sPHdQQBsXDJxtXqpont6zB</guid>
      <description>Refurbished retailer Back Market is offering an additional $35 off PlayStation 5 consoles for a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L&#8217;enceinte Devialet Phantom Ultimate 108 dB, ic&#244;ne de l&#8217;audio haut de gamme, profite d&#8217;une offre rare pour les amateurs de son d&#8217;exception</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2911569_lenceinte-devialet-phantom-ultimate-108-db-icone-de-laudio-haut-de-gamme-profite-dune-offre-rare-pour-les-amateurs-de-son-dexception</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/2911569_lenceinte-devialet-phantom-ultimate-108-db-icone-de-laudio-haut-de-gamme-profite-dune-offre-rare-pour-les-amateurs-de-son-dexception</guid>
      <description>
Devialet est une marque connue pour le raffinement de ses enceintes Bluetooth. Raffinement que vous retrouvez sur la Phantom Ultimate 108 dB disponible &#224; 2 720 euros au lieu de 3 200 euros sur Boulanger.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pok&#233;mon TCG Lugia ex &amp; Latios ex Premium Collection is $36.33 cheaper at TCGplayer vs. Amazon</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/dec-16-pokemon-tcg-lugia-ex-latios-ex-premium-collection-deal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02MQXbnQOghqSqn4NNUCzR9</guid>
      <description>As of Dec. 16, the Amazon-exclusive Lugia ex &amp; Latios ex Premium Collection is $36.33 at TCGplayer, which is insane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enfin une app Disney+ pour le Meta Quest, mais Apple garde le meilleur morceau</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/android/2911727_enfin-une-app-disney-pour-le-meta-quest-mais-apple-garde-le-meilleur-morceau</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/android/2911727_enfin-une-app-disney-pour-le-meta-quest-mais-apple-garde-le-meilleur-morceau</guid>
      <description>
Vous avez un Meta Quest 3 ? Vous pouvez enfin arr&#234;ter de passer par le navigateur web bugg&#233; pour regarder Andor. Disney+ d&#233;ploie son application officielle.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollow Knight: Silksong's upcoming DLC pack will be free for all players</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gaming/hollow-knight-silksongs-upcoming-dlc-pack-will-be-free-for-all-players-123055729.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af500132-8ecb-479b-9114-5562238c726a</guid>
      <description>One of 2025's splashiest games, Hollow Knight: Silksong, is getting its first major DLC expansion, developer Team Cherry announced in a blog post. The nautically-themed Sea of Sorrow update will come to the moody Metroidvania some time in 2026, and better still, it will be free for all players.&#160;
The DLC will include "new areas, bosses, tools and more," the developer wrote. There aren't a lot of clues to the gameplay in the short trailer below, but the four shots definitely relay the vibe. The first shows what looks like fishing tackle, then we see something (or someone) on a tomb-like wooden p...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Best Electric Scooters (2025), Tested and Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-electric-scooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">618220fe4910d7835a6d64ea</guid>
      <description>These WIRED-tested two-wheelers will help you scoot scoot scoot around town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Anker Laptop Power Bank soothed my (self-inflicted) battery anxiety</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/mobile/the-anker-laptop-power-bank-soothed-my-self-inflicted-battery-anxiety-123000024.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f60d172b-bdff-4823-ba90-d510d97102f6</guid>
      <description>For the longest time, I refused to upgrade my work-issued MacBook. I was leery of the hassle, and would much rather hang on to an aging Intel-powered laptop than have to transfer files, set up apps and sign in to accounts all over again. What did it matter if my notebook barely lasted long enough to cover an iPhone launch? My petty brain blamed it all on external factors (like being forced to use a MacBook instead of a PC), and left me dripping in stress as I watched the power levels dip down to zero at many of the live events I attend every year. So when I saw the Anker Laptop Power Bank was ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We've got to stop the panic' &#8211; Sapphire pushes for calm on RAM crisis fears and predicts price stability next year</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/computing/memory/weve-got-to-stop-the-panic-sapphire-pushes-for-calm-on-ram-crisis-fears-and-predicts-price-stability-next-year</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">s7rp7ou8nBRguxfQtro98F</guid>
      <description>RAM prices are skyrocketing due to the current AI boom, but Sapphire's PR manager encourages consumers to stay calm and avoid panic buying.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
