<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:40:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Gadgets for Throwing a Kick-Ass Super Bowl LX Party</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/best-gadgets-for-throwing-kick-ass-super-bowl-lx-party-2000716968</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000716968</guid>
      <description>Sure, TVs and sound systems are the crux of any good Super Bowl party, but there's so much more you could do to upgrade the NFL's Big Game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is down for many, as OpenAI confirms an active issue &#8212; here's everything we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/news/live/chatgpt-open-ai-down-outage-february-3-2026</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2LtYjRs7ZgiUnmCUmPqwc3</guid>
      <description>If you can't log in or get a conversation with ChatGPT going, you're not alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The four best Super Bowl TV deals we found</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/gadgets/873160/super-bowl-4k-oled-big-tv-deal-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T16:23:36-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873160</guid>
      <description>The Super Bowl is not only one of the biggest sporting events in the world, it&#8217;s also one of the best times of year to find a deal on a big TV. For major events in particular, a large TV makes sense because it provides a more immersive experience and allows for groups of friends [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is down for many, as OpenAI confirms an active issue &#8212; here's everything we know</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/live/chatgpt-is-down-for-many-as-openai-confirms-an-active-issue-heres-everything-we-know</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5k7pgXLxMPQH27t4zMUBTZ</guid>
      <description>If you can't log in or get a conversation with ChatGPT going, you're not alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Successfully Bullied Into Letting Olympian Use &#8216;Minions&#8217; Music</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/winter-olympics-minions-skater-music-universal-2000717421</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717421</guid>
      <description>A Spanish figure skater thought he wasn't going to be able to use the music, until the fans stepped in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X's Paris HQ raided by French prosecutors</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/social-media/xs-paris-hq-raided-by-french-prosecutors-110411170.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06a0419b-a1f3-4338-aaa7-b5442b1f07a4</guid>
      <description>Paris prosecutors announced that a search was underway at offices belong to Elon Musk&#8217;s X platform as part of an ongoing investigation first launched in January 2025. The raid is being conducted by Paris and national cybercrime units, with support from Interpol, according to post from Paris prosecutors on X. Officials from X have yet to comment on the matter.  At the same time, Paris prosecutors issued summonses to Elon Musk and Linda Yaccarino for &#8220;voluntary interviews&#8221; on April 20, 2026 in Paris. The prosecutors also announced they would no longer use X and would only communicate on LinkedIn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is down for many users this afternoon</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/chatgpt-is-down-for-many-users-this-afternoon-210238573.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d88f72-a1b8-4f16-b13d-8dfe2dc59834</guid>
      <description>If you've had trouble using ChatGPT today, you aren't alone. The AI chatbot is experiencing a partial outage for many users this afternoon. Down Detector reports of issues with the service leapt from almost nothing to more than 12,000 around 3PM ET.&#160;Down DetectorOpenAI issued a status update noting that "elevated error rates" are occurring for ChatGPT and Platform users. All 13 components of ChatGPT are marked as having &#8220;degraded performance&#8221; on the OpenAI status page. "We are working on implementing a mitigation," the company said, although it didn't provide an anticipated timeline for when t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel will start making GPUs, a market dominated by Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/intel-will-start-making-gpus-a-market-dominated-by-nvidia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089319</guid>
      <description>Intel has been bulking up a team to focus on this effort and will develop its GPU strategy around customer needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk is merging SpaceX and xAI to build data centers in space &#8212; or so he says</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/transportation/873203/elon-musk-spacex-xai-merge-data-centers-space-tesla-ipo</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T16:01:03-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873203</guid>
      <description>On Monday, Elon Musk announced that he was merging two of his companies, SpaceX and xAI, in a deal said to be worth $1.25 trillion. The reason, Musk said in an announcement, was that in order for AI to grow, it needed to go to space. AI relies on "large terrestrial data centers" that run [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman Expects to Get What He Wants</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/sam-altman-expects-to-get-what-he-wants-2000717277</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717277</guid>
      <description>He wants you to have AI whether you want it or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capcom's new Resident Evil Requiem trailer might have two massive hints you missed</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/gaming/capcoms-new-resident-evil-requiem-trailer-might-have-two-massive-hints-you-missed</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f76PugEAFpXzg5QMCBFqZF</guid>
      <description>It's still speculative at this stage, but the new Resident Evil live-action trailer may have just given us new hints for Requiem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China has banned concealed car door handles &#8211; as Tesla&#8217;s trend-setting design turns into a safety nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vehicle-tech/hybrid-electric-vehicles/china-bans-concealed-car-door-handles-as-teslas-trend-setting-design-turns-into-a-safety-nightmare</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">yXzSjfDHH8KtRMAGgLVt8R</guid>
      <description>Tesla's one-innovative door handle design comes under scrutiny by safety experts, as China bans the technology altogether.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyson's new launches are proof that branching out isn't always a good thing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/home/vacuums/dysons-new-launches-are-proof-that-branching-out-isnt-always-a-good-thing</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KUsc3fTmX6ZV6ZhbPps23c</guid>
      <description>After reviewing Dyson's three new launches, I'm even more convinced that it should stick to what it's good at.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This one statistic clearly shows the housing market&#8217;s post-boom recalibration</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486218/housing-market-this-one-statistic-clearly-shows-post-boom-recalibration</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T21:00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486218/housing-market-this-one-statistic-clearly-shows-post-boom-recalibration</guid>
      <description>At the height of the Pandemic Housing Boom, only 38% of U.S. homes in 2021 sold for less than their original list price. By 2025, that figure had risen to 62%&#8212;roughly on par with its 2019 level of 64%.
Want more housing market stories from Lance Lambert&#8217;s ResiClub&#160;in your inbox?&#160;Subscribe&#160;to the&#160;ResiClub&#160;newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple integrates Anthropic&#8217;s Claude and OpenAI&#8217;s Codex into Xcode 26.3 in push for &#8216;agentic coding&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/technology/apple-integrates-anthropics-claude-and-openais-codex-into-xcode-26-3-in-push</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29Q1quXmYBvP8wkUbz8x2T</guid>
      <description>Apple on Tuesday announced a major update to its flagship developer tool that gives artificial intelligence agents unprecedented control over the app-building process, a move that signals the iPhone maker's aggressive push into an emerging and controversial practice known as "agentic coding."Xcode 26.3, available immediately as a release candidate, integrates Anthropic's Claude Agent and OpenAI's Codex directly into Apple's development environment, allowing the AI systems to autonomously write code, build projects, run tests, and visually verify their own work &#8212; all with minimal human oversigh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani is set to kill off New York's 'functionally unusable' business chatbot, which often gave out illegal advice</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/zohran-mamdani-is-set-to-kill-off-new-yorks-functionally-unusable-business-chatbot-which-often-gave-out-illegal-advice</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">YfGDPUjeJ8zTEp5uxLjVS9</guid>
      <description>Mayor Zohran Mamdani plans to remove NYC business chatbot after repeated illegal advice, high costs, and inefficiencies exposed by testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big ChromeOS and Android Merger May Be Google&#8217;s Last Walled Garden</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-big-chromeos-and-android-merger-may-be-googles-last-walled-garden-2000717336</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717336</guid>
      <description>The Google-pilled ChromeOS may die so that &#8216;Aluminum&#8217; will live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracker Barrel&#8217;s new dining rule is not actually new, it says</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486119/cracker-barrel-new-dining-rule-is-not-actually-new-restaurant-employee-policy</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T20:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486119/cracker-barrel-new-dining-rule-is-not-actually-new-restaurant-employee-policy</guid>
      <description>The restaurant&#8217;s policy asking employees to eat at Cracker Barrel when traveling for business is going viral. Here&#8217;s what the company has to say about it.
These are tough times for many businesses across corporate America, many of whom are cutting down on business travel and perks on the road. And in these times, one company&#8217;s policy on business travel is going viral: According to a recent Wall Street Journal article, Cracker Barrel employees reportedly must follow a new policy that they must eat at Cracker Barrel restaurants while traveling for work....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#8216;Starfleet Academy&#8217; Sneakily Brought Some More &#8216;Star Trek Online&#8217; Ships to TV</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/starfleet-academy-star-trek-online-klingon-ships-2000717306</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717306</guid>
      <description>After 'Picard' bolstered the Starfleet of the 25th century's fleets with some video game canonization, 'Starfleet Academy' lends a helping hand to the Klingons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything we know about Anya Taylor-Joys heist series, Lucky</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/lucky-anya-taylor-joy-apple-tv</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04D9N86Tilgw1gmTsbUw2Hm</guid>
      <description>Anya Taylor-Joy stars in Apple TV's "Lucky," about a con artist on the run after a multi-million heist goes wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get more screen space for less with this 16.1-inch Arzopa portable monitor &#8212; boasting a sharp 2.5K QHD display for only $140 right now</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/get-more-screen-space-for-less-with-this-16-1-inch-arzopa-portable-monitor-boasting-a-sharp-2-5k-qhd-display-for-only-usd140-right-now</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">i6DDpCicUi5ytVnVLDkAsW</guid>
      <description>The Arzopa 16.1-inch portable monitor with a 2.5K QHD display is $60 off at Amazon, now just $139.99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft says it&#8217;s building an app store for AI content licensing</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/873296/microsoft-publisher-content-marketplace-ai-licensing</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T15:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=873296</guid>
      <description>Microsoft says it is working on the Publisher Content Marketplace (PCM), an AI licensing hub that shows usage terms set by publishers. That way, AI companies can easily shop the terms and set up deals to use online content for "grounding" their AI models, while the content owners get usage-based reporting to help set prices. [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucky teaser: Anya Taylor-Joy is a con artist, and Im already in</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/lucky-teaser-anya-taylor-joy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05zy0wUfEsrwtqqW2JEmCYV</guid>
      <description>Anya Taylor-Joy leads Apple TV's heist drama "Lucky," out July 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grindr is testing a new AI plan that could cost $220 a week</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/grindr-testing-ai-subscription-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05Lnvk3WhliNYGt2gBwKw2b</guid>
      <description>Grindr is piloting EDGE, a new AI-powered subscription that carries a hefty price tag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple just made Xcode better for vibe coding</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/ai/apple-just-made-xcode-better-for-vibe-coding-195653049.html?src=rss</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">477d4d1b-ab12-4ec8-ac1f-ec11c985c0ae</guid>
      <description>Apple has just released Xcode 26.3, and it's a big step forward in terms of the company's support of coding agents. The new release expands on the AI features the company introduced with Xcode 26 at WWDC 2025 to give systems like Claude and ChatGPT more robust access to its in-house IDE.&#160;With the update, Apple says Claude and OpenAI's Codex "can search documentation, explore file structures, update project settings, and verify their work visually by capturing Xcode Previews and iterating through builds and fixes." This is in contrast to earlier releases of Xcode 26 where those same agents were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Infiltrated Moltbook, the AI-Only Social Network Where Humans Aren&#8217;t Allowed</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/i-infiltrated-moltbook-ai-only-social-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69822a3b7c553e1f8e36ee8d</guid>
      <description>I went undercover on Moltbook and loved role-playing as a conscious bot. But rather than a novel breakthrough, the AI-only site is a crude rehashing of sci-fi fantasies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YC startups can now receive investment in stablecoin</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/03/yc-startups-can-now-recieve-investment-in-stablecoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3089218</guid>
      <description>All startups accepted into YC will soon have the option to receive their seed checks via stablecoins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paramilitary ICE and CBP Units at the Center of Minnesota's Killings</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ice-cbp-srt-bortac-units-immigration-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697bda99eeb4ef697c02db68</guid>
      <description>Two agents involved in the shooting deaths of US citizens in Minneapolis are reportedly part of highly militarized DHS units whose extreme tactics are generally reserved for war zones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check Out 10 Weird and Wonderful Finalists for the &#8216;Pulitzer of the New Instrument World&#8217;</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/check-out-10-weird-and-wonderful-finalists-for-the-pulitzer-of-the-new-instrument-world-2000717314</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000717314</guid>
      <description>The finalists for Georgia Tech&#8217;s annual Guthman Musical Instrument Competition just dropped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road markers are a new target for hackers - experts find self-driving cars and autonomous drones can be misled by malicious instructions written on road signs</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/not-even-road-markers-are-safe-from-hackers-experts-find-that-self-driving-cars-and-autonomous-drones-can-be-hacked-by-reading-malicious-instructions-written-on-road-signs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">rXZx9Ufv3YyPTfrFm8ByMh</guid>
      <description>Manipulated text in physical spaces can hijack autonomous systems, while existing cybersecurity tools offer no protection against this risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal replaces CEO Alex Chriss with HP&#8217;s Enrique Lores</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91486201/paypal-hp-lores-chriss-venmo-dorman-ai</link>
      <pubDate>2026-02-03T19:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91486201/paypal-hp-lores-chriss-venmo-dorman-ai</guid>
      <description>Lores will take over as PayPal CEO on March 1. 
PayPal is replacing CEO Alex Chriss with Enrique Lores, saying that the pace of change and execution at the company has not met board expectations over the past two years.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
