<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://abdoullah-code.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Technology-related news</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:40:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Podcasts is generating automatic links and chapters</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813817/apple-podcasts-automatic-links-and-chapters</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T17:34:28-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813817</guid>
      <description>Apple Podcasts will soon include automatically-generated chapters for shows in English and allow creators to add links at specific timestamps in their episodes. Timed links may also be added to episodes automatically whenever creators mention another podcast.&#160; Creators can opt-out of both features, and chapters will only be generated when creators don&#8217;t add their own. [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Inc forges AI licensing deal with Microsoft as Google traffic drops</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/04/people-inc-forges-ai-licensing-deal-with-microsoft-as-google-traffic-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3065066</guid>
      <description>People Inc. signs an AI licensing deal with Microsoft, which will use its media content in Copilot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ever Lego &#8216;Ideas&#8217; Project That Is Currently in the Works</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/every-lego-ideas-project-in-development-2025-2000681461</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681461</guid>
      <description>After a streak of high-profile crossover announcements, from 'X-Files' to 'Power Rangers', here's everything that's currently in development for Lego's crowd-supported line of sets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beta Technologies ends first day on NYSE in the green and $1B raised</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/04/beta-technologies-ends-first-day-on-nyse-in-the-green-and-1b-raised/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3065077</guid>
      <description>The electric aviation company Beta Technologies made an impressive showing in its debut on the New York Stock Exchange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Stream Deck&#8217;s &#8216;device not supported&#8217; error should fix itself if you log in</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/813814/your-stream-decks-device-not-supported-error-should-fix-itself-if-you-log-in</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T17:17:35-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813814</guid>
      <description>Did your Stream Deck sprout a red &#8220;Device Not Supported&#8221; badge where a button used to be? If so, you were probably using BarRaider&#8217;s popular plug-ins, which apparently check to see if StreamDeck.exe is digitally signed &#8212; and it just so happens that Elgato&#8217;s digital signature expired yesterday (see image below). But as of 5PM [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer reveals its fanciest Chromebook yet - but will it be enough to convince your IT team to upgrade you?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/acer-reveals-its-fanciest-chromebook-yet-but-will-it-be-enough-to-convince-your-it-team-to-upgrade-you</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98snqP4CQgm9mmiVSjPfSm</guid>
      <description>Acer Chromebook Plus Enterprise 714 and 514 blend AI tools, long battery life, and rugged builds for serious business use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's no better PC under $350 than this Ryzen 7 powerhouse with a CPU that's faster than a 10-core Apple M5 CPU, and that's no mistake</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/theres-no-better-pc-under-usd350-than-this-ryzen-7-powerhouse-with-a-cpu-thats-faster-than-a-10-core-apple-m5-cpu-and-thats-no-mistake</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dNWSCqgq9BcnNFKSxgD4B</guid>
      <description>$349 Machenike AI Mini PC is one of the best sub-$400 desktops available, powered by an AMD Ryzen 7 8745HS and delivering performance that rivals more expensive systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best deals on 4K TVs</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22371561/best-4k-tv-deals-sale-lg-samsung-sony-tcl</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T17:05:05-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22371561/best-4k-tv-deals-sale-lg-samsung-sony-tcl</guid>
      <description>Things are looking bright for those who want to nab a great TV in 2025 at a substantial discount. There&#8217;s usually a great deal happening on a mid- or high-end TV from LG, Sony, Roku, Hisense, or Samsung &#8212; even if the biggest discounts remain reserved for Black Friday, Amazon Prime Day, and the lead-up [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian blames ChatGPT for low law class test scores &#8211; even as OpenAI dismisses a rumored ban of legal and medical advice from ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/ai-platforms-assistants/chatgpt/kim-kardashian-blames-chatgpt-for-low-law-class-test-scores-even-as-openai-dismisses-a-rumored-ban-of-legal-and-medical-advice-from-chatgpt</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">akBY22JWWnmHLeRB9soob7</guid>
      <description>Kim Kardashian&#8217;s confession that ChatGPT led to flunking law tests arrives amid confusion over AI&#8217;s legal and medical advice policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Immigration Enforcement Apparently Provides Facial Scanning Tech to Local Cops</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/u-s-immigration-enforcement-apparently-provides-facial-scanning-tech-to-local-cops-2000681475</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681475</guid>
      <description>It's part of a program that essentially deputizes police into the federal mass deportation effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDA email warns stores: discounts for SNAP users could violate federal law</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435252/usda-email-warns-stores-discounts-for-snap-users-could-violate-federal-law</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:48:32</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435252/usda-email-warns-stores-discounts-for-snap-users-could-violate-federal-law</guid>
      <description>The agency says offering discounts exclusively to food-aid recipients violates program rules, sparking backlash during the shutdown.
Restaurants, food banks, nonprofits, and other organizations have stepped up to offer assistance to the 41 million Americans who have been thrust into limbo this month regarding SNAP benefits that have been halved. But retailers are prohibited from offering discounts on groceries....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AI&amp;#8217;s first in-house image generator MAI-Image-1 is now available</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813789/microsoft-in-house-ai-image-generator-mai-image-1</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:48:09-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813789</guid>
      <description>Microsoft&#8217;s first in-house AI image generator, MAI-Image-1, is now available in two products, Bing Image Creator and Copilot Audio Expressions. The company announced the model in October. Microsoft AI chief Mustafa Suleyman wrote in a post on X that the text-to-image model will be &#8220;coming soon&#8221; to the EU.&#160; Suleyman added that the model &#8220;really [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrysler recalls 320,000 Jeep plug-in hybrids over battery fire risk</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435238/chrysler-recalls-jeep-plug-in-hybrids-battery-fire</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:45:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435238/chrysler-recalls-jeep-plug-in-hybrids-battery-fire</guid>
      <description>Chrysler is aware of 19 reports and 1 injury potentially related to the issue.
Chrysler is recalling more than 320,000 Jeep plug-in hybrid vehicles due to a faulty battery that can fail and lead to a fire, U.S. traffic safety regulators said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nomad&#8217;s magnetic charging stands now support faster 25W rates</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813769/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max-wireless-charging-25w-magsafe-pixelsnap</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:42:13-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813769</guid>
      <description>Nomad has announced updated versions of its Stand One and Stand One Max hubs that now support the Qi2.2 standard for faster wireless charging rates of up to 25W when used with compatible smartphones like the Pixel 10 Pro XL and the iPhone 16 and 17 series. As with previous versions, the new Stand One [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon and Perplexity have kicked off the great AI web browser fight</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/news/813755/amazon-perplexity-ai-shopping-agent-block</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:36:41-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813755</guid>
      <description>Amazon doesn&#8217;t want to be a part of Perplexity&#8217;s AI-powered shopping experience. In a post on Tuesday, the ecommerce giant says it has &#8220;repeatedly requested&#8221; that Perplexity stop allowing its Comet AI browser to buy products for customers, which Perplexity has responded to by accusing Amazon of &#8220;bullying.&#8221; Perplexity&#8217;s AI browser, Comet, currently offers an [&#8230;]...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Trump hijacked the .gov domain</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/column/813499/viral-politics-trump-mamdani-cuomo</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:33:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/813499/what-the-trump-family-stands-to-gain-from-changpeng-zhaos-pardon</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Regulator. Happy New York City mayoral election day to everyone who's voting, watching from afar, or just here for the memes. And happy 35th day of the federal government shutdown, which, as of today, is tied for the longest shutdown in history. But let's step back for a second, because there's [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI and AWS team up in potentially one of the biggest tech partnerships ever seen - so what will it mean for you?</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/pro/openai-and-aws-team-up-in-potentially-one-of-the-biggest-tech-partnerships-ever-seen-so-what-will-it-mean-for-you</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RFoTvXxyUu9KMFFEqxDSXe</guid>
      <description>OpenAI&#8217;s $38 billion partnership with AWS will expand massive AI workloads, deepening cloud hosting dependence and raising sustainability concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transportation Secretary warns of &#8216;mass chaos&#8217; in the skies if the shutdown continues</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435235/duffy-shutdown-mass-chaos-skies</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435235/duffy-shutdown-mass-chaos-skies</guid>
      <description>Duffy and the head of the air traffic controllers union have&#160;both warned&#160;that the situation will only get worse the longer the shutdown continues.
Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy predicted Tuesday that there could be&#160;chaos in the skies&#160;next week if the government shutdown drags on and air traffic controllers miss a second paycheck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit and Art the Clown Are Refusing to Let Halloween Go</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/spirit-and-art-the-clown-are-refusing-to-let-halloween-go-2000681476</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681476</guid>
      <description>Spooky season might be over, but the retailer wants to keep its meme-y reputation enduring with new holiday offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber Wants To Be an AI Company Too</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/uber-wants-to-be-an-ai-company-too-2000681388</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681388</guid>
      <description>Uber CEO wants physics PhDs using the app for AI gigs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tesla investor will reject Elon Musk&#8217;s $1 trillion pay package</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435231/musk-tesla-pay-package-norway-sovereign-wealth-fund</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:15:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435231/musk-tesla-pay-package-norway-sovereign-wealth-fund</guid>
      <description>Norway&#8217;s sovereign wealth fund has a 1.16% stake in Tesla, the sixth largest holding among institutional investors.
Norway&#8217;s sovereign wealth fund, one of Tesla&#8217;s biggest investors, said Tuesday that it will vote against a proposed compensation package that could pay CEO Elon Musk as much as&#160;$1 trillion&#160;over a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Popular Gourmet Mushroom Is Escaping Gardens and Invading US Forests</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-popular-gourmet-mushroom-is-escaping-gardens-and-invading-us-forests-2000681430</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681430</guid>
      <description>&#8220;It is slowly marching south, which is really terrifying.&#8221;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivian creates another spinoff company called Mind Robotics</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/11/04/rivian-creates-another-spinoff-company-called-mind-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3065038</guid>
      <description>It's the second time this year Rivian has spun out a new company, after it created micromobility startup Also in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Hut&#8217;s parent company weighs selling the chain</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/91435227/pizza-huts-yum-brands-sale</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T21:03:13</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fastcompany.com/91435227/pizza-huts-yum-brands-sale</guid>
      <description>Yum Brands is conducting a formal review of options for Pizza Hut, which has struggled to compete in a crowded pizza market.
Pizza Hut could soon be up for sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I let Gemini watch my family for the weekend &#8212; it got weird</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/813523/gemini-for-home-google-nest-camera-hands-on</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:01:37-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813523</guid>
      <description>This weekend, I turned my home into a test lab for Google's new Gemini for Home AI and subjected my family to 72 hours of surveillance as it watched, interpreted, and narrated our every move. My purpose? To find out if an AI that sees everything is actually helpful or just plain creepy. "R unpacking [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencers have fractured reality in Portland</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/policy/813408/portland-influencers-national-guard-oregon-ninth-circuit</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T16:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/?p=813408</guid>
      <description>The legal fight over whether the president can send troops into Portland, Oregon, depends on whether judges believe their own eyes or their smartphones. Even before inception, the lawsuit has been dogged by a war on reality fueled by social media influencers, some of whom have direct lines to federal officials. At every turn, influencers [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple d&#233;sactive une fonction iPhone/Watch en Europe : le DMA pousse trop loin, Apple casse tout</title>
      <link>https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2855387_apple-desactive-une-fonction-iphone-watch-en-europe-le-dma-pousse-trop-loin-apple-casse-tout</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.frandroid.com/produits-android/accessoires-objets-connectes/montres-connectees-2/2855387_apple-desactive-une-fonction-iphone-watch-en-europe-le-dma-pousse-trop-loin-apple-casse-tout</guid>
      <description>
Apple d&#233;sactive une fonction plut&#244;t que de se conformer au DMA.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Towns Are Betting That the Data Center Boom Will Never End</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/small-towns-are-betting-that-the-data-center-boom-will-never-end-2000681426</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gizmodo.com/?p=2000681426</guid>
      <description>What do data centers bring? Short-term growth, and long-term questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best deals on MacBooks right now</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals</link>
      <pubDate>2025-11-04T15:51:49-05:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals</guid>
      <description>Apple currently sells MacBooks equipped with its own M-series processors in a wide range of sizes and price points, all of which run the company&#8217;s new operating system, macOS 26. The latest 14-inch MacBook Pro that debuted in October 2025 features the M5 processor, its fastest and most efficient yet, and it&#8217;s already over $50 [&#8230;]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
